Chapter 650: Return to Hu Immortal Blessed Land

Book 4: The Demon Lord Rampages Unhindered

Slowly opening his eyes, Fang Yuan woke up.

Seeing crystal walls sparkling with a bright pink colored light, Fang Yuan was dazed, before reacting — he had used the stargate to return to Hu Immortal blessed land from northern plains.

Except that in this trip to northern plains, he had exhausted his mind and spirit, it was such a dangerous trip, it was a near fatal experience. Even though Fang Yuan's body was that of six arm heavenly zombie king, his mind was still filled with fatigue.

After returning to Hu Immortal blessed land, he made some arrangements and fell into deep sleep.

He slowly woke up now, after sleeping for an unknown amount of time.

He was very exhausted, even now, Fang Yuan only wanted to lie down and not get up.

"My body is filled with death energy, I have completely turned into a zombie, my body knows no fatigue, but my soul is still my original soul, it has its limits and will suffer injuries too."

A thought flashed in his mind, as Fang Yuan gradually got up.

His mind was in tranquility, it was a comfortable feeling.

Sleeping had the effect of soothing one's soul.

Fang Yuan breathed out some turbid air, stretching his limbs, but he only felt like his body was rusty, he felt very inflexible and heavy.

He was not surprised, he knew that this was the backlash of using his killer move, myriad self — his soul was greatly depleted. Thus, when he tried to move this extremely strong zombie body, he felt difficulty and resistance.

"Where is the land spirit?" Fang Yuan spoke. His voice was coarse and irritating, like the sound of sand grinding on ice shards, it would give a dry and icy feeling to people.

"Master!" At the next moment, the land spirit Little Hu Immortal's voice resounded in Fang Yuan's ears.

The voice was still cute and sweet, but there was a hint of worry and sadness in it.

Fang Yuan turned around, only to see Little Hu Immortal appearing before his left hand with reddened eyes.

"How long have I been asleep?" Fang Yuan nodded, asking.

"Master, you have been asleep for two days and three nights." Little Hu Immortal replied.

Fang Yuan recalled, two days and three nights was in terms of Hu Immortal blessed land time. Five days in Hu Immortal blessed land was one day in the outside world of the five regions. That means that since Fang Yuan left the wind veil of assimilation, less than a day had passed in northern plains.

Fang Yuan's inner thoughts settled.

Before he slept, he had made an agreement with Hei Lou Lan, they were temporarily cooperating, thus, he would have to return to northern plains soon.

Little Hu Immortal saw that Fang Yuan was silent, and thought he was upset. She opened her tiny mouth and consoled; "Master, master, don't be too upset. Your current appearance, although it is quite ugly, I'm sure there's a way to change it back. I believe that one day, master will go back to his original form. Master, you have to cheer up!"

Fang Yuan laughed speechlessly, stretching out one arm and touching Little Hu Immortal's tiny head.

Little Hu Immortal dodged for a bit, but eventually, Fang Yuan's terrifying giant zombie hand landed on her head.

She lowered her head, not making a sound.

Fang Yuan started stroking her hair and Little Hu Immortal could not take it anymore, she cried: "Master, although your palm is icy cold, I still like it!"

Saying this, she hugged Fang Yuan's huge legs and began sobbing.

Little Hu Immortal was still so cute, she was like a five to six year old child, pure and innocent, cute and tiny. She wore a rainbow dress and her snow-white fox tail was drooping towards the ground, showing her current sad mood.

The land spirit was formed from the fusion of obsession and heavenly power, it was different from wills and would never lie.

Little Hu Immortal spoke the honest truth.

Fang Yuan's expression was calm, he did not speak. But the fangs that were outside his mouth retracted a little, and the movement of his hand stroking Little Hu Immortal's head became more gentle.

He split a portion of his consciousness and looked inside his body.

In the first aperture, there was dead silence. There was not a bit of primeval essence inside, only Fang Yuan's first vital Gu.

The originally clear crystal purple walls had turned into a rock-like material. The rock wall was filled with small cracks, the culprit behind this wound was the Spring Autumn Cicada in the middle of his aperture.

Spring Autumn Cicada's body was glowing with green and yellow light, the aura of a rank six Immortal Gu was permeating the entire aperture.

If it was his rank five peak stage aperture, it might have burst already. But now that the aperture was dead, it could handle more of the Immortal Gu's pressure. Even though there was a limit, he was far from reaching it yet.

At the same time, Fang Yuan also noticed that the aperture was completely dry and could not produce any more primeval essence.

"This is the price for turning into a zombie, the aperture is dead and cannot produce any primeval essence." Fang Yuan assessed in his mind.

He could not help but think of First Gen Gu Yue, he had turned into a blood wight and his aperture could not produce primeval essence, thus he had great desire for Gu worms like Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus.

"My current situation is way better than First Gen Gu Yue. I have already ascended into an immortal, I have nineteen green grape immortal essence and limitless primeval essence!"

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan moved his consciousness from the first aperture to the second aperture.

The newly born strength path immortal aperture had also turned grey, the blessed land was now a dead land. The sky was grey and the white stone mountains had collapsed, the ground was rotten and dark, emitting a foul odor. The ground was full of cracks, like the aftermath of an earthquake. This was the result of forcefully containing wisdom Gu.

Inside this immortal aperture were almost all of Fang Yuan's Gu worms.

The most attention grabbing ones were naturally the Immortal Gu.

There were seven Immortal Gu in here!

This amount was bound to shock others if revealed publicly. Immortal Gu were unique, they were extremely hard to get. Most ordinary Gu Immortals would not even have one Immortal Gu.

If he included Fixed Immortal Travel that he had lent to Hei Lou Lan, as well as Spring Autumn Cicada, Fang Yuan had a total of nine Immortal Gu.

This number could put most rank seven Gu Immortals to shame.

There were three Immortal Gu that were related to Water Pavilion, they were: worldly wave trace Gu, delight in mountain and water Gu and calamity beckoning Gu. The other four Immortal Gu were obtained when Fang Yuan painstakingly smashed the formless fists.

Other than the Immortal Gu, there were mortal Gu.

The most valuable mortal Gu were also obtained when Fang Yuan smashed the formless fists. All these Gu worms originated from the true inheritance secluded domain's many inheritances, each of them were high quality Gu worms and had profound differences from common Gu.

But of greater importance was the second aperture's vital Gu — rank four all-out effort Gu, as well as bitter strength Gu, borrow strength Gu, self-reliance Gu, refine essence spirit Gu, earth strength Gu, water strength Gu, wind strength Gu, lightning strength Gu, fire strength Gu, lurking beast coat Gu, aura concealment Gu and so on.

It was these Gu worms that formed the foundation of the killer move myriad self, allowing Fang Yuan to ultimately clinch victory within the wind veil of assimilation.

Other than these, there were the other random Gu worms, like the eagle rise Gu which Fang Yuan had used and expended the most in this journey within northern plains. The wind flower Gu which could allow changes in direction easily, the sole blade Gu obtained from Sole Blade General Pan Ping. There was also the battle bone wheel Gu, Stargate Gu, and the Gu that made up the foundation of a Gu Immortal, hole earth Gu, connecting heaven Gu, divine sense Gu and others.

The highest quantity that he had among them were of beggar moths, almost a thousand of them, they had the effect of storing primeval essence. They were a huge help to Fang Yuan during the final moments of his northern plains trip.

After inspecting his mortal and immortal aperture, Fang Yuan directed his attention to his body.

Without using a mirror, he knew that he had turned into a monster completely. Six meters tall, a green face and sharp fangs, blood red eyes, bulging muscles that were tough as rocks. Most importantly, he had eight arms, other than his two human arms, his other six arms were terrifying in appearance, they originated from the other rank five flying zombie Gu — asura zombie Gu, heavenly demon zombie Gu, blood wight Gu, nightmare zombie Gu, plague zombie Gu, and earth chief zombie Gu.

Fang Yuan did not care whether his appearance was handsome or ugly. Little Hu Immortal was concerned about it because she was formed from the obsession of the female Gu Immortal, Fairy Bai Hu.

What Fang Yuan cared about was that the zombie body caused his cultivation to stagnate, he was unable to advance his cultivation in the slightest. This was a huge obstacle in his pursuit of the demonic path and his dream.

He had grand ambitions, he wanted to obtain eternal life. Eternal life was in reference to being the strongest, an indestructible being that cannot be taken down by tribulations or disasters, a person that cannot be harmed by anyone, as well as having infinite lifespan.

Although a zombie body had no lifespan, his soul could still suffer damage, and his body could still be destroyed if he was attacked by someone stronger than him, there were still many flaws and weaknesses. Thus, many Gu Masters and Gu Immortals would turn into zombies only after they were left with no other choice. This method was truly a last resort for survival, it was like longing towards heaven while being in hell.

"How can I get rid of the zombie body, returning to life from death, and obtain a live human body again?" Fang Yuan asked in his heart, evidently, this was a problem that needed to be solved.

Although he had no answers, he had some rough ideas.

Interrogating Mo Yao's will who was in his immortal aperture was one method. Using wisdom Gu was the second.

Little Hu Immortal's crying slowly stopped, as Fang Yuan retracted his hand, his emotions calmed down as he asked: "During the days when I was asleep, did anything happen?"

Little Hu Immortal heard her master's inquiry and immediately stood up straight, she wiped her tears and answered him maturely: "Reporting to master, there were two things. First, your senior brother, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, had already woken up, he has been wanting to meet you over these last few days, he was so anxious he even cried several times. But master had given me the orders, thus I refused to let him in. The second matter is regarding Immortal Crane Sect, they have stopped engaging in our rockmen transactions."

Fang Yuan heard this and frowned lightly.

Fang Yuan was well aware of the reason why Immortal Crane Sect stopped the rockmen transactions. Hu Immortal blessed land had Dang Hun mountain, this was something known by everyone in central continent. Immortal Crane Sect's target was Dang Hun mountain, but they could not attack Hu Immortal blessed land directly, thus over a year ago, they had sent Fang Zheng to negotiate, eventually settling on the transactions of rockmen. But their primary objective was Dang Hun mountain and the guts Gu.

After that, Immortal Crane Sect had repeatedly urged and emphasized while requesting Fang Yuan to sell the guts Gu, but he refused them every time.

After a year, seeing that Hu Immortal blessed land was refusing to give in, Immortal Crane Sect had lost their patience, thus stopping the rockmen trade. As to whether they would express anger and want to force Fang Yuan to renegotiate, or whether they have other objectives, that would depend on how the situation progresses.

"Hu Immortal blessed land is not a utopia, it is located at Tian Ti mountain, and the outside situation is also perilous."

If Fang Yuan had a blessed land as an immortal aperture, his reliance towards Hu Immortal blessed land would greatly reduce. He could even swallow Hu Immortal blessed land directly, making his escape and leaving this place. Unfortunately, he was now a zombie, his immortal aperture was a dead aperture, there was no way to consider this.

Fang Yuan thought about it, but for now could not come up with any ideas.

"Damn it, after becoming a zombie, my cognitive abilities have weakened, my thoughts are moving slower and slower, it is too inefficient." Fang Yuan frowned deeply, he started to feel the drawback of the zombie body.

Chapter 651: Guilt-ridden Tai Bai Yun Sheng

The stagnation of his cultivation was only the main drawback, other than that, there were many other smaller drawbacks. One of them, was the fact that he had no sense of pain. His cognition slowing down was another problem.

In this world, wisdom path had already deciphered the mysteries behind how a person thinks.

When a person thinks, many thoughts would be created in their minds. Intelligent people would generate a large number of thoughts more quickly, while stupid people would generate fewer thoughts, and at a slower pace.

When these individual thoughts collide into one another, they would fuse or possibly be destroyed, eventually, one or more new thoughts would be created. These new thoughts would be the result of their thinking.

The brain is the place which gives birth to thoughts, it is an important domain for all life forms when they think. But this domain is decided on two aspects.

One was the body, while the other was the soul.

If a person's soul resided in a wild beast's body, then this 'wild beast' would become very intelligent. This level of intelligence would far surpass an ordinary wild beast, but would be lower than a normal human being.

Gu is the essence of heaven and earth, man is the spirit of all beings. Among all living beings, humans were the most intelligent. To achieve this, one needed a human's physical body and a human's soul.

Now that Fang Yuan's body was completely dead, only his soul was intact. Thus, in his mind, the number of thoughts generated would be much fewer, and the speed of his cognition would reduce greatly.

Intensive thinking would lead to a sharp fall in the number of thoughts. Because the zombie's mind produces fewer thoughts, and at a slower pace, the thoughts generated cannot keep up with the expenditure of thoughts.

If Fang Yuan was a brute, so be it. But he was very skilled at scheming, he was an ambitious person who was used to plotting in order to succeed in situations, after becoming a zombie, he felt very uncomfortable, he was not used to this new change at all.

"No wonder most zombies like First Gen Gu Yue choose to enter deep sleep. When one is sleeping, they would think less, and the consumption of their thoughts would fall sharply, thus they would be able to accumulate more thoughts in their mind. When they battle, they would think intensely and use up these thoughts." Fang Yuan had a new understanding in his mind.

This was the same reason as that of Giant Sun's will, who chose to enter deep sleep.

"The less I think, the more dull and slow I would become. To think that one day, I, Gu Yue Fang Yuan, would turn into an idiot. Hehe." Fang Yuan mocked himself in his mind, collecting his scattered thoughts.

Next, he turned to Little Hu Immortal: "Bring my senior brother, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, in here, I want to meet him."

Little Hu Immortal replied to him obediently, immediately vanishing from the spot.

She was the land spirit, she could freely teleport anywhere within Hu Immortal blessed land.

After ten breaths of time, Little Hu Immortal reappeared, this time bringing Tai Bai Yun Sheng with her.

"Junior brother, you... sigh!" What shall we do now?" Taking a look at Fang Yuan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was stunned, his eyes turned red as he spoke in a choking voice.

He already was aware of the fact regarding Fang Yuan turning into a six arm heavenly zombie king completely. This was something Fang Yuan had specified to Little Hu Immortal earlier, as something that could be exposed to Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Originally, I had advanced into a strength path Gu Immortal, what a pity that I have ended up in this state, there is no choice, I will have to continue calling you senior brother. Come! Senior brother, this is a crude place, please find a block of stone and take a seat."

The cave that Fang Yuan was in now was dug out from the center of Dang Hun mountain back in the day by Fairy Bai Hu, it was the place where she had built Dang Hun palace.

After Dang Hun mountain was destroyed by the gruel mud Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan had returned it to normal with Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

The restored Dang Hun mountain retained this mountain cave.

But the golden bricks, the silver tiles, the pink curtains, the large round bed, the golden silk blankets, and the fragrant wind chimes that were in Dang Hun palace were nowhere to be found.

Rank six Immortal Gu Landscape as Before, it could restore any mountain or body of water back to a state in the past. The furniture inside Dang Hun palace did not count as being part of a mountain or body of water.

Of course, Fang Yuan did not want to restore the former Dang Hun palace, either. After all, Fairy Bai Hu's bedroom was way too pink, it was filled with a feminine aura and did not suit Fang Yuan.

There was no furniture in the mountain cave, it was really crude and simple. Tai Bai Yun Sheng chose the boulder closest to Fang Yuan and sat down.

Right now, his inner thoughts were filled with concern, gratitude, and unconditional trust towards Fang Yuan.

After all, the two of them had braved dangers and near death experiences together, they had gone through a lot in northern plains, and had witnessed the sincerity and feelings in each other's hearts.

Not to mention the two times Fang Yuan had helped Tai Bai Yun Sheng in the true inheritance secluded domain, he did not hesitate at all, not even batting an eyelid. The first time, it was to retrieve landscape as before Immortal Gu, while the second time, he gave up on man as before Immortal Gu in order to save Tai Bai Yun Sheng's life.

During that moment, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was so touched his tears nearly flowed down his cheeks.

He had a Gu Immortal inheritance, he naturally knew the immense attraction an Immortal Gu had towards a Gu Immortal. Fang Yuan gave up on the Immortal Gu in order to save him, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, this completely displayed Fang Yuan's true feelings!

After that, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was captured by Hei Lou Lan. Fang Yuan immediately changed his direction, taking back man as before Gu first, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was in complete agreement with his actions and his heart settled, this was truly a rational decision.

When he woke up, he found that he was inside Hu Immortal blessed land, and was out of danger.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was jubilant, being able to luckily maintain his life was naturally a very joyous matter. But what made him even happier was that afterwards, seeing that he had woken up, Little Hu Immortal returned Landscape as Before and Man as Before, these two Immortal Gu back to him!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had a soft and kind nature, he had deep attachment towards these two Immortal Gu. Regaining his important treasures after losing them, he was truly overjoyed.

But when he heard about Fang Yuan's situation from Little Hu Immortal, his heart shuddered, all of his joy was swept away, his inner thoughts was filled with sadness, guilt, regret, and pity.

Thus, he had repeatedly tried to meet Fang Yuan, attempting to give it his all to save this junior brother.

At this moment, he sat on the stone boulder, he had an expression of grief as he sighed deeply: "I am ashamed, not only did junior brother save this life of mine, I even have to bear your consolation and kind words after meeting you."

Fang Yuan stretched out one arm, patting Tai Bai Yun Sheng's shoulders, using his hoarse voice as he laughed: "Destiny is unpredictable, most things in life do not go your way. As a person, we should be more open minded. Although I became a zombie, it is still halfway between life and death, compared to those dead people and Giant Sun's will, we are much better! Especially when at the final moment, I even obtained wisdom Gu! This is a huge profit, senior brother does not need to blame yourself, you should be happy."

When Fang Yuan was leaving, he opened the stargate.

Wisdom Gu knew that this was a tunnel to the outside world, its survival instincts urged it to fly towards Fang Yuan on its own initiative.

This was something Fang Yuan had expected.

Stargate Gu was a mortal Gu, it could not contain the aura of an Immortal Gu. Fang Yuan gritted his teeth as he forcefully placed wisdom Gu in his immortal aperture.

Even though wisdom Gu restrained its own aura and Fang Yuan's immortal aperture was a dead land, having much greater capability to support it, Fang Yuan was barely able to handle it during the short period of time needed to pass through the stargate.

The moment he returned to Hu Immortal blessed land, he quickly let wisdom Gu out.

Hu Immortal blessed land was a rank six immortal aperture, but it was situated on Tian Ti mountain, it took in the earth qi of central continent and was very stable. It was not comparable with an immortal aperture that was still in a Gu Immortal's body.

Regarding wisdom Gu, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was aware of the matter.

"An outstanding person will do outstanding things, junior brother's abilities have truly made me feel nothing but deep admiration. But even the legendary rank nine Immortal Gu would not be able to treat junior brother's zombie body. Why don't you let me try and use man as before Gu!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was very emotional, at this point, he had already stood up, ready to give it a try.

But Fang Yuan stopped him.

"Senior brother, you know clearly deep within your mind that this man as before Immortal Gu can only return a person to a prior state within one moment in the past. Although it can revive a person, such a long time has already gone by, I do not know what countless number of moments have passed since then. How can it possible heal me? It will be in vain even if you try, why should you waste your precious green grape immortal essence?"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression was ashen, his emotions were unstable. When Fang Yuan had finished his words, he suddenly stretched out his palms, slapping harshly on his own face!

Crack crack crack.

Five to six sharp sounds were heard, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was actually slapping himself.

"Senior brother, stop it! What are you doing this for?" Fang Yuan acted like he was caught off guard, he hurriedly stood up, stretching out two arms and grabbing Tai Bai Yun Sheng's hands.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng could not compete with Fang Yuan's strength at all, after being immobilized, he cried profusely: "Junior brother, I have let you down, I am really very sorry!"

As he cried, his knees bent as he actually attempted to kneel down.

Fang Yuan quickly grabbed him, asking in shock: " Senior brother, what are you doing?!"

"Junior brother, if back then, I had lent man as before Immortal Gu to you, you would have been able to use it at the crucial moment and would not have turned into this current form!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng said with a tear stricken face.

He was a very kind person, although he had indirectly caused the death of Gao Yang and Zhu Zai in the past, that was just a person's instincts to survive. To him, Fang Yuan was the savior of his life, a benefactor. He was also his junior brother, they had the same master, but this person who was his benefactor and junior brother, was harmed because of his own negligence.

If back then, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had taken the initiative to lend his Gu worm to Fang Yuan, Fang Yuan would not have ended up in such an awkward state.

After Tai Bai Yun Sheng woke up, this thought had been lurking in his mind, it caused him to feel great grief and regret, he was in deep agony.

At this moment, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was weakly falling towards the ground, he was in agony and regret, he was only supported by Fang Yuan's two arms.

Fang Yuan was six meters tall, he looked down at the crying Tai Bai Yun Sheng from above as a trace of eeriness flashed across his eyes.

"I am very glad that you have such thoughts..." He laughed in his mind, but with his mouth he sounded very sincere as he said: "Senior brother, you do not need to be like this. Although a zombie's body is very hard to revert, there exist many ways and methods that are available for me. And don't forget that we have wisdom Gu here."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng slowly shook his head, he spoke weakly: "Wisdom... wisdom Gu is as high as rank nine, it came here with you all because of its survival instincts. Junior brother, even if you are a rank six Gu Immortal, you are unable to refine it, and there is no way you can control... can control it!"

"Of course I understand this. But even like this, just a bit of the light of wisdom is able to give me great rewards. In fact, my current zombie body has no lifespan, it is even more suitable for getting close to wisdom Gu!" Fang Yuan stretched out his third arm, patting Tai Bai Yun Sheng's back lightly as he explained amicably.

"And what's more, I still have Mo Yao's will."

"Mo Yao?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was confused.

"This was an additional gain of mine in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, Mo Yao was once a refinement path grandmaster, a certain generation's fairy of central continent's Spirit Affinity House."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a born and bred man of northern plains, he had never heard of Mo Yao's name, but as Spirit Affinity House was one of the the famous top ten sects of central continent, he had heard of it before.

"A certain generation's fairy of Spirit Affinity House, as well as a refinement path grandmaster. It seems that this Mo Yao is not simple." Tai Bai Yun Sheng's gloomy expression eased.

Fang Yuan laughed again, saying: "And most importantly, senior brother, don't forget that we still have master. I am sure that master has a solution for this. I will not hide this from you, after master handed me the mission for Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, he only left me a single consumable Gu, with the specific use of reporting the details to him. I had already used this Gu two days ago, when I first returned to Hu Immortal blessed land."

Fang Yuan had searched Tai Bai Yun Sheng's soul earlier in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, and learnt about his life experiences as well as secrets.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had once met a mysterious beggar, and obtained a time path Gu Immortal inheritance from him.

Thus, Fang Yuan lied and swindled, using his eloquent tongue and world class acting skills to convince Tai Bai Yun Sheng in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, making him believe that both of them have the same master, which is that old beggar.

Fang Yuan even gave that old beggar a random title of Purple Mountain True Monarch.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng believed this lie from Fang Yuan completely.

Now that Fang Yuan mentioned this, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's eyes were shining: "So junior brother has a method to contact master! This is truly fantastic, others might not have a way, but master is such a knowledgeable person, I am sure he has a method!"

The fires of hope were burning in his heart.

From his tone, one could tell that the old beggar held a very important position within his inner thoughts, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was filled with confidence towards this old beggar.

If at this moment, he knew the truth, who knows what expression he would show.

Fang Yuan showed no flaws, replying calmly: "Senior brother, don't be hasty, I believe that master's letter is going to come in a few days, we should wait patiently."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng nodded, after Fang Yuan used the name of Purple Mountain True Monarch, his mood had finally calmed down.

He stood up straight, as Fang Yuan let go of his arms.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng took a step back, his gaze was locked with Fang Yuan's bright red eyes, he raised his palm and placed it by his chest, saying with a very solemn expression: "Junior brother, I will engrave your kindness deep into my heart, I will never forget it. I swear to Longevity Heaven, even if master has no way to cure you, I, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, will spend my entire life looking for a way to revive you, junior brother!"

"Hahaha! Longevity Heaven is Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's grotto-heaven, we have just wrecked this old fellow's True Yang Building, now you are swearing in its name, this is simply too ironic!" Fang Yuan raised his head and laughed: "Senior brother, I will be frank with you! We are all master's pupils, and I have saved your life before. A droplet received in need will be repaid with an entire spring, next, I will need you to repay me fully!"

"Tell me." Tai Bai Yun Sheng immediately responded without hesitation. He had long since decided to repay this debt, even if Fang Yuan wanted him to do the impossible, he would have no objections! During these days after he woke up, he had felt extremely guilty, his conscience was taking a beating and only by making a sacrifice for Fang Yuan would his heart feel slightly better.

Thus, Fang Yuan also became solemn: "This matter, I have been thinking about it for a long time. That is our seniority issue! I am master's legacy disciple, but because you became an immortal, you caught up to me. I am unsatisfied with this! I was originally a strength path Gu Immortal, even though I turned into a zombie, but sooner or later, there will be a day when I revert back. Thus, according to seniority, I am the senior brother, you are the junior brother."

"What?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng stared with his eyes wide open, he had never expected that the great debt Fang Yuan was requesting him to pay back was for such a tiny matter.

A touched feeling welled up in his heart.

Fang Yuan was someone who did not want to take advantage of his favor, but was he, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, someone who did not know how to repay favors?

Tai Bai Yun Sheng thought in his mind, he sighed and stretched out his palm, patting Fang Yuan's leg which was tough like a mountain rock. His sharp and rough leg hair even caused pain to Tai Bai Yun Sheng's palm.

Fang Yuan was like a giant, about six meters tall.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng could only pat his leg with that height.

He was solemn, before raising his head, looking at Fang Yuan's face, he laughed teasingly: "Oh junior brother, that is wishful thinking! How can a thing like seniority be so easily changed? Unless master personally rearranges our positions, I will definitely still be your senior brother, hahaha!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a man not lacking in pride, how could he repay this huge favor so easily?

"Hey!" Fang Yuan shouted, venting his unhappiness: "Old Bai, why are you such a petty person! Could it be that you forgot what I said earlier? I will definitely not call you senior brother!"

"Hahaha, junior brother, I can completely understand you, this senior brother does not mind." Tai Bai Yun Sheng laughed and laughed, he was so touched his tears were overflowing.

How many years had passed in which he had not laughed so joyfully?

He had finally found his organisation.

Although he had not known Fang Yuan for long, he felt very close to him, it was as if they were family...

His laughter was echoing in the mountain cave, with the pink crystal mountain walls also looking very heartwarming at this moment.

Chapter 652: Seeing Wisdom Gu Again

There was only Fang Yuan left in the cave, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had already left.

He sat on the stone bench, his eight monstrous arms were hanging down, some were behind his back, some were crossed, together with his huge body, just by sitting, he gave off a mountainous aura, it gave people fear.

As for the way to deal with Tai Bai Yun Sheng, Fang Yuan had considered it deeply.

Fang Yuan only trusted himself, he would never truly trust others.

If he killed Tai Bai Yun Sheng, he would obtain man as before Gu and landscape as before Gu, as well as his rank six time path immortal aperture. But this was not maximising his benefits.

He could not deny the fact that Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a very useful chess piece.

This 'useful' was in two aspects.

Firstly, he was worth using. Before he became an immortal, he was a famous healing Gu Master in northern plains. Now that he was a rank six time path Gu Immortal with a high grade blessed land, and don't forget, he was even a flying master, he had great value if exploited.

The second aspect was that he was easy to control. Fang Yuan had once searched his soul, thus he knew about Tai Bai Yun Sheng's life experience clearly. Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a kind-hearted man, he was conscientious and knew how to repay favors. He was indebted to Fang Yuan, because he had been helped several times in True Yang Building, especially during the final moment when he was rescued from the wind veil of assimilation, and even had his two Immortal Gu returned to him, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had placed his complete trust in Fang Yuan now.

This point could be seen when Tai Bai Yun Sheng chose his seat earlier.

There were many boulders in the cave. Fang Yuan had such an ugly appearance and was so huge, normal people who got close to Fang Yuan would feel great pressure and would subconsciously keep a distance from him. But Tai Bai Yun Sheng purposely chose a seat that was closest to Fang Yuan.

This meant that in his heart, Fang Yuan was one of the closest people to him, he was not afraid that Fang Yuan would cause any harm to him.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had once harmed Gao Yang and Zhu Zai, this was the most important point!

His survival instincts took over his reasoning, this was something very natural. After that incident, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was filled with guilt and could not forget it. His appearance was haggard and he was mentally tortured. After Fang Yuan's entrapment, he had almost gone crazy and rushed his immortal ascension, his original intention was to die.

Attempting suicide because of his guilt, one could see how powerful his conscience was.

By coincidence, Tai Bai Yun Sheng received the help of Giant Sun's will and successfully became a Gu Immortal, before falling unconscious.

Fang Yuan used the glass owner token, entering the round of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building he was placed in and woke him up. At this crucial moment, he told Tai Bai Yun Sheng about the 'secret' of their master. This precisely hit a weak point within Tai Bai Yun Sheng's mental state.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng denied his own self, thus he was in great agony and was very lost.

But at this moment, Fang Yuan appeared, giving him a group of apprentices and an organisation to provide him a sense of belonging, it gave him a feeling of protection and warmth. Next, Fang Yuan entered and exited his time path immortal aperture, casually asking him to take care of his Immortal Gu, this gave him the initial confidence.

In addition, during their encounters and difficulties in True Yang Building, all that had happened gave Tai Bai Yun Sheng a good reason to fully trust Fang Yuan. In a way, he had to thank Mo Yao for interfering with his own mind, otherwise, how could he have obtained Tai Bai Yun Sheng's unconditional trust?

"Tai Bai Yun Sheng caused the death of Gao Yang and Zhu Zai, this greatly violated his values and beliefs, he harboured extreme guilt. He felt that he was not such a person, yet he committed such an act. Now that I am his benefactor, he is indebted to me, he will definitely repay me a hundredfold or even a thousandfold. This is not only because he knows to repay favors, but also because this is a chance for him to prove that he is a good person!" Fang Yuan calmly analyzed.

Bad people would not repay favors, in fact, they would even return the favor with ill intentions. In the future, the more Tai Bai Yun Sheng sacrifices for Fang Yuan, the more it would prove that he is a good person. That way, this can cancel out the guilt he felt towards Gao Yang and Zhu Zai. This touched upon the psychological studies from Earth, including the balance theory and compensation mentality.

In a way, Fang Yuan gave Tai Bai Yun Sheng a chance to prove himself once more, and a reason for him to continue living.

Fang Yuan knew this clearly, thus when he saved Tai Bai Yun Sheng, he even returned Man as Before and Landscape as Before, these two Immortal Gu.

"I have way too many Immortal Gu, it is very costly to feed them. At this point, leaving Man as Before and Landscape as Before to Tai Bai Yun Sheng is undoubtedly better. At the same time, my immortal aperture is dead, it cannot produce immortal essence. I only have nineteen beads of green grape immortal essence, the more I use them, the fewer I have left. Although I can use some of Bai Hu's immortal essence, isn't it best if I can make use of Tai Bai Yun Sheng's green grape immortal essence instead?"

Thinking of the cost of feeding Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan felt a headache.

Raising a Gu worm was like supporting a mistress, Gu Masters are often unable to afford it or maintain their upkeep. Ever since Fang Yuan had Hu Immortal blessed land, he had no problems feeding mortal Gu. But now that he had so many Immortal Gu, not even Hu Immortal blessed land could afford such high costs.

This was a blissful worry!

Many Gu Immortals did not have a single Immortal Gu, they were still looking for one. In Fang Yuan's previous life, he also struggled to refine one, Spring Autumn Cicada, after he finally succeeded after numerous difficulties, he was forced to self-detonate.

Right now, Fang Yuan was racking his brain, trying to think of how to feed so many Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan sat silently, attempting to find some inspiration from his previous life's memories, after trying for a while, he gave up.

"Sigh, after becoming a zombie, my cognition has truly slowed down. Earlier when speaking to Tai Bai Yun Sheng, I could feel my thoughts moving slowly. Right now, my thinking speed cannot keep up with my original pace."

He summoned the land spirit, Little Hu Immortal: "How is wisdom Gu? Where is it now?"

Little Hu Immortal was the blessed land's land spirit, she could understand everything that was happening in the blessed land.

"Master, wisdom Gu had gone deep underground since it was brought here by you. It found a rockman cave and is currently slumbering inside." Little Hu Immortal closed her eyes, after sensing for a while, she opened her giant watery eyes and said this.

Fang Yuan nodded, ordering: "Bring me there."

The cave that wisdom Gu was in was rather big, after Fang Yuan was brought over by Little Hu Immortal, he could still move about freely.

Sensing that Fang Yuan had arrived, wisdom Gu shone with a five colored light.

Little Hu Immortal sat on Fang Yuan's shoulder, staring at wisdom Gu curiously.

This was the rank nine wisdom Gu!

Although Little Hu Immortal could sense everything in the blessed land, but such a close range encounter was still very rare.

"Oh wisdom Gu, I helped you to escape and saved your life. According to our earlier agreement, it is time for you to hold your end of the deal." In the dark and grey cave, Fang Yuan's voice echoed.

Wisdom Gu was silent, after a few breaths' time, it floated up into the air.

At the same time, it summoned the light of wisdom.

"So beautiful!" Little Hu Immortal stared with shining eyes, laughing joyfully.

The sphere shaped light of wisdom was shining in many colors, it engulfed Fang Yuan and Little Hu Immortal.

Fang Yuan could instantly feel many of his thoughts colliding, he could think at lightning speed, this was the result of an accelerated cognition speed.

"This feeling... this is so comforting." Little Hu Immortal slowly opened her eyes wide and stared dazedly, she was immersed in the wonderful feeling of being in the light of wisdom.

But after a few breaths' time, her body started fading.

"Little Hu Immortal, you were formed from obsession, although fused with the heavenly power, you are still restricted by the wisdom Gu. You cannot stay here for long, quickly go back." Fang Yuan stretched out a finger, pointing at Little Hu Immortal's head, waking her up.

Little Hu Immortal hugged her head, her white cheeks turned red with excitement.

"Master, master, I can't believe I could become so smart. Wisdom Gu is amazing!" She shouted, like a child who had found new toys, she was overjoyed.

"Master is most amazing, you could even get wisdom Gu! Just let me stay here a bit longer, is that okay?" She started bootlicking Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "It seems that wisdom Gu had made you think more, quickly get out." Saying so, his two fingers pressed on Little Hu Immortal's head.

Little Hu Immortal's cute, tiny head was squeezed by Fang Yuan's finger, as he pressed again and again.

Little Hu Immortal pouted slightly as she shook her head: "Master, I am going to leave."

She did not dare to disobey Fang Yuan's words, she vanished with a flash.

The cave was quiet again, Fang Yuan did not sit down, since the zombie's body was extremely hard and tough, there was no difference in feeling between sitting or standing.

He stood in the halo, the first thing he did was to inspect Mo Yao's will which was suppressed in his immortal aperture.

Mo Yao's will was unaffected by the light of wisdom.

Even though he had confirmed this earlier in the wind veil of assimilation, Fang Yuan's heart was finally at ease after confirming it once again.

"Once the immortal aperture is formed, it is a small world. The walls of the immortal aperture are the walls of heaven and earth. It isolates the inside and outside, there is almost no outside force that can influence the small world inside."

Fang Yuan shut his bright red eyes as he started to think and ponder.

He had become a zombie, the production of thoughts in his mind had become much slower, and his cognition had also slowed. But the light of wisdom could cause his thoughts to collide at an increased speed, as they collided, he would expend a lot of thoughts in a short period of time.

If he was another ordinary zombie basking in this light, although he would turn smarter for a moment, he would become an idiot immediately afterwards.

But there were wills in Fang Yuan's mind.

These wills were all formed from wisdom path Gu worms, they could think.

Earlier, in order to deal with Mo Yao, Fang Yuan had delved into wisdom path and bought many different Gu worms like special will Gu, deliberate will Gu, sharp intent Gu and so on. These wills all helped him at the last moments of his journey in northern plains.

Right now, Fang Yuan's brain could no longer keep up, he had to use these wills as replacements.

His primeval essence was limitless, thus his wills were also near infinite. Under the light of wisdom, the originally stable wills all melted like snow in sunlight, they were shrinking.

What followed after was the appearance of flashes of inspiration, and his old memories were becoming clearer. As long as Fang Yuan concentrated and recalled his memories, these huge amounts of memories would vividly play out again in his mind.

At this moment, the world seemed brighter.

Even before he had truly thought of the result, Fang Yuan already had many different ideas to resolve the problem. As long as he followed these methods, Fang Yuan was sure that he would be able to find the most suitable method to solve this problem!

Chapter 653: Bankruptcy and Zombie Alliance

In the underground cave, Fang Yuan bathed in the light of wisdom and pondered deeply.

"Although I am reborn and have five hundred years of experience from my past life, but in contrast to old monsters like Mo Yao and Giant Sun, I pale in comparison. My previous dominance in this aspect has already vanished."

Throughout the flow of history, there were as many grand heroes as there were stars in the sky!

In the history of humans, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was an unrivalled expert that could seldom be produced even in a million years.

Fairy Mo Yao was a refinement path grandmaster, and back then was the fairy of Spirit Affinity House; she was a famous and influential person with shocking talent. In those days, she would be listed among the top ten renowned Gu Immortals in the large Central Continent.

Fang Yuan had firm willpower and had gone through unique experiences, but he was also a single unremarkable star in this vast starry sky. With just his current strength and foundation, it was hard for him to be on par with the great experts that appeared in history.

"This trip to northern plains has far surpassed my original expectations. If not for the meddling of Mo Yao's will, I could have stayed in True Yang Building and explored gradually using a different identity every ten years. But at this point, the die is cast and northern plains is bound to be in a great uproar; countless experts and powerful forces will seek to find trouble with me!"

Fang Yuan summed up his experiences and sensed that the losses he suffered were due to his weakness in the aspect of wisdom path.

His strong points were in calculating and scheming. And building upon his experience preserved from rebirth, his advantages were further amplified.

However, Mo Yao's will was able to disturb his thoughts which caused him to not be able to think properly.

"Eighty-Eight True Yang Building is a spiritual symbol of northern plains and I am the main culprit in causing it to be toppled. If I am captured now, the consequences will be unimaginable. Although I am able to hide in Hu Immortal blessed land right now, it is not actually safe. Not speaking of Immortal Crane Sect which has been eyeing Dang Hun mountain since the beginning, perhaps northern plains' Gu Immortals could discover my origins and track me down through wisdom path deductions!"

Fang Yuan knew clearly that holing up within Hu Immortal blessed land seemed extremely safe but was actually akin to waiting for death. Only by going on the offensive before these enemies ascertain the truth could he remedy this perilous situation.

"Dark limit Immortal Gu, I have heard of it even in my previous life, it can indeed conceal aura and obstruct calculations. If I can get this Gu, I believe I can avert the dangerous situation."

Fang Yuan thought of Hei Lou Lan.

This woman was not of minor importance and was an outstanding, ruthless person. She was pragmatic and could flexibly take advantage of situations; she betrayed her ancestor for her own interests and wanted to kill her own father - these evidently displayed a demonic nature! She possessed Great Strength True Martial Physique and also obtained a strength path Immortal Gu, once she advanced into a Gu Immortal, her path would be one of rapid progress.

One could say that she was similar to Fang Yuan, but precisely because of this, in cooperating with her, it demanded exceptional caution.

Whether it was Immortal Gu Dark Limit or Fixed Immortal Travel, they were both things he desired.

Fang Yuan's thoughts started to slow down as he thought till this point.

The wills in his mind were nearly expended.

Fang Yuan was dazed for a moment, before retreating from the light of wisdom to activate Gu worms and create new wills.

His mind was soon filled with many types of wills.

"It is a pity that mortal Gu cannot create too many wills and they are easily consumed in the light of wisdom. If I can use an Immortal Gu to create wills, their number would be enormous and could also be sustained for a long period of time, allowing me to think as much as I like!"

Fang Yuan felt some regret.

He had a rank six wisdom path Immortal Gu, Delight in Water and Mountain which could create joyful will.

However, Fang Yuan did not use it after slight consideration.

Immortal Gu required immortal essence. He only had nineteen beads of green grape immortal essence left, and because his immortal aperture had become a dead land, using one immortal essence bead would mean one fewer bead left without replenishment.

He needed to save his immortal essence as much as possible to be prepared for the times when they are necessary.

Thus, he opted to use mortal Gu for now.

After accumulating a fixed amount of mortal wills, Fang Yuan stepped into the light of wisdom again.

This time, he did not think about external situations, instead concentrating on himself.

"I have transformed into a zombie, my cultivation cannot progress an inch, how to resurrect and restore my human body is the first issue. It would be great if I could use yin-yang rotation Gu, but I am an immortal zombie while yin-yang rotation Gu only is at rank four. The second issue is that I am already bankrupt!"

Fang Yuan had invested almost all of his savings in his trip to northern plains. His required expenses were now already greater than his earnings and he was now facing bankruptcy.

He did not even have one immortal essence stone in his possession now, even Hu Immortal blessed land had become extremely barren.

Before the decisive battle in northern plains, Fang Yuan had already used up the remaining immortal essence stones. At the final juncture, he even had to exchange his goods to make purchases. He had already sold almost all the fox groups and wolf groups in Hu Immortal blessed land; in the large grassland in the blessed land, foxes and wolves could only be seen occasionally.

Most of the nearly ten thousand hairy men Fang Yuan had bought in the past were also sold for emergency support. Now there were only around two thousand old hairy men that were experienced in refining Gu left which Fang Yuan was reluctant to sell off.

The rockmen slave transactions had been a strong economic pillar for Fang Yuan. But after Immortal Crane Sect stopped the transactions, this pillar crumbled down. The rockmen trading market in treasure yellow heaven had already been divided up completely and it would be hard for Fang Yuan to squeeze in. This caused the already bad situation to turn worse.

There was no use in merely having powerful battle strength. There must be enough resources to support one's cultivation.

The way of Gu involved nurturing, using and refining; Gu Masters could not just use Gu, they had to raise and also refine Gu.

Fang Yuan was now a zombie, his cultivation had stagnated which further increased the resources he required. Only by doing so could he have a higher chance of restoring his life.

Three days later.

Within Dang Hun Palace.

Fang Yuan made simple arrangements once again, building a rough hall where stone chairs were arranged in two rows. The main chair was as spacious as a bed with its back as high as a monument, however when Fang Yuan sat on it, it fit him just right.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was sitting on the first seat to Fang Yuan's left; his brows were furrowed as he held a small and exquisite white dove.

This white dove was flickering with faint radiance, it was the rank five messenger dove Gu.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's consciousness left the messenger dove Gu after few moments; he heaved a deep sigh and worriedly said: "Master does not plan on helping and is making this a test for junior brother."

Fang Yuan nodded: "Right. Master criticized me in the letter, saying I was greedy for small gains, not listening to his advice before I left and rashly opening Di Qiu inheritance, which caused me to encounter Mo Yao's will and created a series of ill consequences. So this time, he wants me to resolve this issue by myself. Sigh, master's style has always been like this, it seems I have no other option but to work hard!!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng nodded, approving of Fang Yuan's last sentence.

Back then, the old beggar disappeared right after giving him the Gu Immortal inheritance, not concerned with anything else. This style was the same as Fang Yuan's test, thus Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not sense anything weird.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng asked in a quiet voice: "Junior brother, you said master had already taken in six legacy disciples. You are ranked fifth, grasping strength and enslavement path, with two Gu Immortal inheritances. That means you have five other fellow disciples, how about we ask them for help?"

Fang Yuan shook his head.

What a joke, of course it was not possible!

This messenger dove Gu's contents were fabricated by Fang Yuan. Purple Mountain True Monarch's name was also casually made up by him. The six great legacy disciples were even more fictitious, how could one ask for help from those that did not exist?

"This is not possible." Fang Yuan gave a bitter smile, his gaze revealing extreme sincerity, "First of all, I only have heard master mentioning these fellow disciples once in a while. I have not personally seen them and also don't know what their identities are or where they are located. More importantly, this is a task assigned by master! He has already approved of your status in the letter and has ranked you as the fifth disciple, and has said you have to help me for this period of time to solve this issue. At the same time, he allowed me to retain and use all the spoils of battle from northern plains, this is the help master is giving me. If I still ask for help from the other disciples, it would not be what master wishes for. After all, this is his test for me."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng worriedly and anxiously said: "Even if master did not say it, I would still remain by junior brother's side and use all my strength to help you! What are your plans now?"

"Old Bai, you also read the contents in the letter. Master mentioned for me to join Zombie Alliance."

"What kind of organisation is this Zombie Alliance?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng asked. He had just recently advanced into a Gu Immortal, as such there were many things regarding Gu Immortals he did not know about.

"Zombie Alliance is just like what its name implies, it is an alliance of zombies. This alliance has existed since long ago, and reportedly it appeared in the Medieval Antiquity Era, three hundred thousand years ago. Now, it is a super force which is spread throughout the five regions; its main headquarters is in eastern sea, with a branch in each of the other four regions." Fang Yuan introduced.

"It actually extends throughout the five regions, could they be even more powerful than northern plains' Huang Jin family?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was moved.

Fang Yuan shook his head: "That isn't the case. Almost all of Zombie Alliance's members compose of zombies, and their higher ups are immortal zombies like me. For the most part, these immortal zombies are Gu Immortals who reached the end of their lifespan and had no choice but to turn into zombies to prolong their life. These Gu Immortals' immortal apertures are dead; they cannot produce immortal essence nor can they absorb heaven and earth qi, and after some time, their blessed land would start shrinking and parts of it would crumble. Thus, their battle strengths often can't compare to normal Gu Immortals. Naturally, certain immortal zombies are exceptions."

Zombie Alliance's branches were weaker than the respective region's super forces. But the headquarters at eastern sea was a level stronger than the native super forces.

"So it is like that." Tai Bai Yun Sheng had grown in knowledge, he then asked with some doubt, "Then why does master want junior brother to join Zombie Alliance?"

Fang Yuan thought for a moment before saying: "If a Gu Immortal reached the end of their lifespan and transformed into an immortal zombie with no other choice left, then later on, if they obtain lifespan Gu, they are sure to want to resurrect. Originally, one of the purposes for Zombie Alliance's establishment was to help each other to research the method to regain a live physical body. So much time has gone by, they definitely have obtained some results. I think master's purpose lies in this point."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was happy and also worried: "This suggestion is really good. But how will you join Zombie Alliance?"

Fang Yuan laughed: "Old Bai, you don't need to worry. Joining Zombie Alliance is extremely simple, I only need to show my status as an immortal zombie."

"It's that simple?"

"Of course. Zombie Alliance is suppressed by all the super forces, thus they operate with much difficulty, as such they are very eager to have more members in the alliance. At the same time, an immortal zombie's identity is not easy to disguise. Zombie Alliance has researched very deeply and has many methods to distinguish between immortal zombies. I intend to join northern plains' Zombie Alliance, but before this, we have to wait for someone."

"Hei Lou Lan." Tai Bai Yun Sheng blurted out.

Fang Yuan nodded.

He did not hide his plans to go to northern plains from Tai Bai Yun Sheng and had revealed almost everything, as he still needed to borrow the latter's strength in the future.

Chapter 654: Asking Mo Yao’s will

"Sigh, it has been so many years since I last saw a mirror willow." Mo Yao's will sighed, she touched the one and only mirror willow tree, speaking with deep emotions as she recalled the memories of her past.

Fang Yuan's will was by her side, he silently watched and did not say a word to disrupt her.

This world was rotting and dark, it was Fang Yuan's dead immortal aperture.

Fang Yuan had tricked Mo Yao's will into entering his immortal aperture, suppressing her afterwards.

Mo Yao was a refinement grandmaster, she was once a legendary Gu Immortal. In the history of central continent, she had left behind her markings.

Her will naturally had great value.

Although Fang Yuan was harmed by Mo Yao's will and had gone through a near death experience in northern plains, Fang Yuan did not hate Mo Yao's will. On the contrary, there was appreciation, even as much as admiration.

If he was the one scheming, he might not have done any better than Mo Yao's will.

He was prepared to interrogate Mo Yao's will, but it turned out that she was extremely cooperative. Towards the questions that Fang Yuan asked regarding refinement path, not only did she answer all of them, she even elaborated on the points and Fang Yuan gained huge insights from her words.

But when Fang Yuan asked about the information of Spirit Affinity House, Mo Yao's will suddenly had a request: "I have been away from central continent for so many years, over these years, I have been missing the people and things over there more and more. Please find for me a tree of the mirror willow, it will alleviate my longingness for my homeland."

Mirror willows were ordinary plants, they were about the size of ordinary willow trees, but their leaves were like pieces of mirrors. The leaves of these willows were the food of beggar moths.

In the past, during the rockmen transactions, Fang Yuan had purchased a batch of mirror willows from Immortal Crane Sect and had planted them in Hu Immortal blessed land.

Thus, he casually picked one of them and placed it into his immortal aperture.

"Back in the day, my main body and brother Bo Qing had first met each other under this mirror willow. The world moves on after a genius perishes..." Mo Yao's will sighed.

Immediately after, she turned around, looking at Fang Yuan's will: "Thank you for acceding to my request. Since you want to know about Spirit Affinity House's matters, I will tell you about them. However, my information is extremely dated, you need to take note of this."

Fang Yuan's will nodded.

Mo Yao's will stood below the mirror willow, telling him much of Spirit Affinity House's inside information.

Fang Yuan listened to her as he made comparisons to his five hundred years of experience, his understanding of Spirit Affinity House greatly increased.

"Your immortal aperture is already dead, the mirror willow will be corroded by the death energy and turn into a dead tree in less than three days. What a pity..." After giving him Spirit Affinity House's details, Mo Yao sighed again.

But it unclear whether her 'pity' was directed towards the mirror willow or Fang Yuan's immortal aperture.

"The next time you come here, can you bring a cup of qingpu tea? This is Spirit Affinity House's specialty tea, it is not rare. Although I cannot taste it, I would like to see it." Mo Yao said.

Fang Yuan's will snorted: "It seems you have no awareness of your captive status. You are asking for this and that, are you scheming something again?"

Mo Yao's will laughed charmingly: "Oh Fang Yuan, you are too vigilant. Ever since my plan was exposed by you and was lured into the immortal aperture to be suppressed, I was already meat on the chopping block, subjected to your supervision at all times, you can do anything you want to me. How can I create any schemes and how would I be able to execute them?"

"However, let's speak openly. Even though I failed completely and have no way of turning this around, if you try and be forceful, you will get a very incomplete result. After all, soul searching is easy, but will searching is tough. If you were a wisdom path grandmaster, that would be possible, but sadly you have nearly no foundation in wisdom path, all your Gu worms were bought randomly in the market. Wisdom path is different from other paths, it is mysterious and complex, you have not even reached the entry level yet."

Mo Yao's will started criticizing Fang Yuan, she was not holding back at all, after all, she knew that Fang Yuan was very broad-minded, he was a rare and extraordinary demon.

Indeed, at the next moment, Fang Yuan's will laughed: "You are right, my wisdom path attainment is low, but thanks for your cooperation, from now on, you can live in my immortal aperture. I will bring the qingpu tea next time."

Saying so, his will flew into the sky.

The immortal aperture opened a tiny slit, and this will flew all the way up into Fang Yuan's mind.

In an instant, Fang Yuan learnt of all the information that this will had gotten from Mo Yao.

Indeed, he lacked methods to proper search wills.

Soul searching was easy, will searching was hard, this was normal.

If that was not the case, when wisdom path Gu Masters fight their enemies using wills, these will would reveal their own secrets to their enemies when they are captured and taken.

Precisely because will searching was hard, wisdom path Gu Masters used them to fight enemies.

As for Mo Yao...

"She is indeed quite a formidable person, no wonder she could leave her name in history." Fang Yuan praised her and sighed secretly.

Mo Yao's will's plan was exposed, she had utterly failed. She could not even self-detonate, she was sealed in Fang Yuan's immortal aperture and was fully suppressed.

But even in such a desperate situation, she did not give up.

She cooperated with Fang Yuan, answering his questions for him, that was to display her value, and to fight for more time for herself.

If one day, Fang Yuan encounters any danger and his immortal aperture shatters, or if he was captured by anyone, or died in the battlefield, Mo Yao's will would have a chance to escape for freedom.

Mo Yao's will did not give up, her persistent and unyielding attitude made Fang Yuan inwardly feel admiration towards her.

Of course, if Fang Yuan had the proper methods and could search wills, he would strike at the first moment. But currently, Mo Yao's will was cooperating with him, this was better for his benefits.

"If I could really find a wisdom path inheritance, it would all be easier. Unfortunately, wisdom path is mysterious and deep, there are very few wisdom path Gu Masters and Gu Immortals in number. There are no wisdom path inheritances that I know of in my memories."

Back then, Fang Yuan had collected some scattered wisdom path Gu worms in treasure yellow heaven. He had mild progress in terms of wisdom path.

But now that he was bankrupt, he had almost no purchasing power, he could not even continue this mild progress.

As for the details of Red Lotus Demon Venerable's inheritance, he did not ask. Because Mo Yao's will knew: Fang Yuan did not have any methods to deal with her yet.

The two of them were smart people, they knew that asking forcefully was not possible.

"Master, Immortal Crane Sect's reply is here." At this time, Little Hu Immortal appeared beside him, holding a rank five letter Gu.

Immortal Crane Sect suddenly stopped the purchase of rockmen, not long ago, Fang Yuan had sent them a letter to probe about this.　　

Immortal Crane Sect's reply came very quickly.

Fang Yuan took the letter Gu and his consciousness went into it.

The content of the letter was written in a tough stance, they requested for Fang Yuan to initiate the trade of guts Gu, otherwise, Immortal Crane Sect would announce that Fang Yuan was a traitor of the sect, and would mobilize the Gu Immortals to attack Hu Immortal blessed land!

A year ago, Fang Yuan had used Fixed Immortal Travel and snatched Hu Immortal blessed land from under everyone's nose, it was like he was taking food from a tiger.

Immortal Crane Sect immediately reacted, using the similar appearance of Fang Yuan and Fang Zheng to announce that Fang Yuan was actually a disciple that Immortal Crane Sect had nurtured in secret. The other nine sects thus recognised Immortal Crane Sect's victory.

Immortal Crane Sect's plan was to remove the other nine competitors, then deal with Fang Yuan single handedly, attempting to take Hu Immortal blessed land for themselves.

Fang Yuan was happy to see this.

After all, the difficulty of dealing with solely Immortal Crane Sect was completely different from dealing with the ten great sects at the same time.

But this way, Fang Yuan silently agreed with Immortal Crane Sect's lie — he was Immortal Crane Sect's disciple.

"Hu Immortal blessed land is situated on Tian Ti mountain, even the ten great sects cannot attack it casually, as it would provoke public anger within central continent. But if they announced that I was a traitor of the sect, they would have the perfect reason to attack." Fang Yuan's expression was solemn, thinking about the situation.

He was not afraid, this was something that he had expected over a year ago.

He only did not expect that Immortal Crane Sect's patience had worn thin so quickly.

Fang Yuan laughed, saying to Little Hu Immortal: "Bring Tai Bai Yun Sheng here."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng heard this news and his face turned gloomy: "What shall we do now? Immortal Crane Sect is one of the ten great ancient sects of central continent, it is a powerful force that surpasses northern plains' super tribes. If they really attack, just the two of us cannot stop them!"

Fang Yuan laughed: "Old Bai, oh Old Bai, I asked you here to inquire about your opinion regarding this difficult question. But the moment you met me, you asked me a question instead."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng gasped, he showed some embarrassment and shame as he frowned, thinking about it. Eventually, he had an idea: "Didn't we ally with Hei Lou Lan? We can ask her to help us!"

Evidently, Hei Lou Lan's great battle strength was ingrained into Tai Bai Yun Sheng's heart.

"Although Hei Lou Lan has the Great Strength True Martial Physique, even if she advance into a Gu Immortal successfully, with just the three of us, we cannot stop Immortal Crane Sect." Fang Yuan sighed and shook his head.

"Then what shall we do? What shall we do?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng paced back and forth, thinking hard.

Fang Yuan looked at him, laughing but not saying a word.

Suddenly, Tai Bai Yun Sheng stopped in his tracks, he patted his head: "I've got it! Didn't master ask you to join Zombie Alliance? We can totally join Zombie Alliance, and use Zombie Alliance's force to threaten Immortal Crane Sect."

But Fang Yuan shook his head, saying: "Zombie Alliance's structure is loose with little binding force, and central continent's Zombie Alliance branch is far inferior to Immortal Crane Sect, it is not threatening in the least. Furthermore, if I try to make use of Zombie Alliance, I will have to give up some benefits. I'm afraid that instead of Immortal Crane Sect, Zombie Alliance would be the first to benefit from this."

"That won't work too, then what are we going to do?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng raised his head and looked at Fang Yuan with a bitter, frowning expression.

But when he saw Fang Yuan's smile at the corner of his lips, he was stunned, before reacting, pointing at Fang Yuan as he scolded laughingly: "What a junior brother you are, actually lying to this senior brother, watching my desperation! You look so confident, it is obvious you already have a plan."

"Hahaha, Old Bai, you have amazing vision, I could not lie to you." Fang Yuan laughed loudly, admitting it.

"What method do you have, aren't you going to tell me?"

Fang Yuan replied: "I had already told you the background of this matter. Immortal Crane Sect said I was their disciple because they were afraid of the other nine great sects' interference. This is their weakness, and is something I am going to use to make a breakthrough."

"What are you going to do?"

Fang Yuan did not keep it from him: "I already have a plan to send a letter to Spirit Affinity House, establishing our first contact."

Earlier, Fang Yuan had asked about Spirit Affinity House's information from Mo Yao for this purpose.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was worried again: "Establishing a relationship now and only sending a letter, isn't that too late? The ten great sects compete with each other, but they also cooperate. Is it possible that Spirit Affinity House would reject your letter and give it to Immortal Crane Sect to express goodwill?"

"Of course not, because this letter... is very special." Fang Yuan was extremely confident.

Chapter 655: Deducing a Gu recipe

Many flashes of inspiration appeared in his mind.

Countless ingredients and Gu worms formed into many different ideas.

The thoughts in his mind were also being consumed at a rapid rate. Such intense expenditure had far exceeded Fang Yuan's own limit in thinking speed.

"The power of a rank nine Gu is truly terrifying! In fact, I have not even refined wisdom Gu, I am only using a bit of its light of wisdom." Fang Yuan sighed in shock as he went out of the wisdom light halo.

He was deducing and perfecting the refinement recipe of gruel mud Immortal Gu.

Unlike beforehand when he reflected on the current situation or the changes in his body, perfecting an Immortal Gu recipe needed many more fields of consideration. A set of Gu refinement materials contained up to tens of hundreds of different materials. Not to mention the grouping and coordination of different Gu worms.

Precisely because of this, the wills in Fang Yuan's mind were depleting at a shocking rate.

After a few days of accumulating wills, they were all expended in a dozen breaths' time.

The result of this was an advancement of less than 0.1% in the deduction of gruel mud Gu's recipe.

"But to get such progress, if I did this alone without the help of the light of wisdom, I would need at least half a year." Fang Yuan estimated.

A dozen breaths' time in exchange for half a year's time, this showed the great power of wisdom Gu.

But Fang Yuan was not satisfied.

Deducing Gu recipes required too many areas of consideration, too many of his wills were being consumed, and too quickly. The wills that he accumulated in a few days were quickly used up in such a short time.

The result was, he could not deduce more than 0.1% of the Gu recipe.

Fang Yuan's original plan was to use wisdom Gu to deduce Immortal Gu recipes, before selling them in treasure yellow heaven for profit. But now he encountered a problem.

"Deducing Immortal Gu recipe requires a great amount of will. But mortal Gu produce too little will each time. Even though I have been using these mortal Gu to create wills at full capacity these days, I have almost pushed them to their limits, if I exceed this, the mortal Gu will be damaged, unless I use the rank six delight in water and mountain Gu..."

Fang Yuan thought about it for a while before deciding to give it a go.

He consumed one bead of green grape immortal essence, activating delight in water and mountain Gu.

Swoosh!

The Immortal Gu floated above his head, bursting out with a brilliant and dazzling light.

The light poured down, like a heavenly river, injecting into Fang Yuan's mind.

This joyful will was produced at such a grand scale. Compared to rank five mortal wisdom path Gu, the will they produced was like a puddle of water. Meanwhile, this joyful will was produced like a great river!

"As expected of an Immortal Gu!" Fang Yuan was overjoyed.

Joyful will continued to pour and inject into him, only after a long while did it stop.

In Fang Yuan's spacious mind, a third of it was filled with joyful will.

Special will was a golden color, appearing like sand. Joyful will was bright yellow.

"That is to say, as long as I activate delight in water and mountain Gu three times, my mind would be filled completely? No wonder the market in treasure yellow heaven would have those wisdom path Gu that can make the mind more spacious." Fang Yuan gained some enlightenment from his experiment.

Strength path Gu worms modified the Gu Master's body. In contrast, wisdom path Gu worms modified the person's mind.

Fang Yuan entered the wisdom light halo once again, falling into deep thoughts.

Euphoria!

This felt way too good!

Like there were no limits binding him, everything was clear. For any difficult problem, a breakthrough could be attained in a flash! The only difference was: The harder the problem, the more will would be expended.

A vast amount of refinement materials were chosen one by one, countless Gu worms were combined into groups and tested at lightning speed, before splitting them apart again.

Fang Yuan showed off his great skills, he felt that there was no problems in this world that could trouble him.

This feeling was splendid, only until all of the joyful will was expended, did Fang Yuan leave the light of wisdom reluctantly, he felt that only a dozen breaths' time had passed by since then.

But in reality, seven minutes had gone by already.

"Puff..." Fang Yuan let of a sigh of turbid air, he shook his head.

After leaving the light of wisdom, he immediately went back to his former self, he was still that zombie with slow cognitive abilities.

The great difference felt like falling from heaven into hell.

Fang Yuan breathed in deeply, adjusting his emotions as he inspected the fruits of his labor.

The progress of the deduction of gruel mud Immortal Gu's recipe advanced by one percent.

Compared to before, this was huge progress!

Fang Yuan nodded, but he soon shook his head again.

He silently left the underground cave, going to Dang Hun mountain's palace.

"Junior brother, how is the situation?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng had been waiting inside the palace for some time, he quickly asked Fang Yuan in concern.

He was covered in dust and sand, he had just returned after inspecting the western area of Hu Immortal blessed land.

"Take a seat." Fang Yuan waved to him, taking a few big steps to the main seat and sitting down.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng looked at Fang Yuan with a curious gaze after choosing the seat closest to him.

He knew that Fang Yuan was using wisdom Gu to deduce an Immortal Gu recipe. Not long ago, he had followed Fang Yuan into the underground cave, and had looked at wisdom Gu from far away — he had finally obtained a lifespan Gu from Fang Yuan some time ago, he had limited lifespan and did not dare to get close to this legendary Gu worm.

Fang Yuan leaned on the stone block like it was a chair, his legs were spread open and a pair of his arms were placed on his leg. One pair was crossed over his abdomen, while another pair was at the handle of the seat. The final pair was crossed over his chest, he sat with a grand posture, like an unmoving mountain, he was still and silent, like a giant statue.

He sighed, saying: "Mortal Gu were not efficient to use. I tried using the wisdom path Immortal Gu Delight in Water and Mountain. The river of joyful will that it produced, under the light of wisdom, allowed my Gu recipe deduction to progress by one percent."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng heard this and stood up from his seat in excitement, he showed evident joy on his face: "One percent? As expected of the rank nine wisdom Gu! That means, if we use it a hundred times, we will be able to deduce an Immortal Gu recipe? With these Immortal Gu recipes, we can sell them in treasure yellow heaven, this is a huge treasure chest that can yield us endless profits! By then, we will have an unceasing flow of immortal essence stones!! To think... that after becoming a zombie, junior brother can actually receive such benefits!"

These days, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had been worrying over cultivation resources.

He found out that after becoming a Gu Immortal, he needed much more cultivation resources.

When Gu Master cultivate, they nurture their apertures, when Gu Immortal cultivate, they nurture their immortal aperture.

There are many different ways one can nurture an immortal aperture. But the ultimate goal was the same, that is to make the immortal aperture's small world more vibrant and diverse.

Planting more varieties of plants in the immortal aperture, bringing in more animals, improving the cycle of life and establishing a proper food chain, nurturing and feeding more varieties of Gu worm groups...

The more prosperous the immortal aperture, the greater life force it would have, and the faster immortal essence would be produced in the immortal aperture.

This was the cultivation path of Gu Immortals, this was their way of improving.

Thus, in treasure yellow heaven, not only were Gu worms and Gu recipes sold, there were also the sale of beast groups, vegetation, mysterious stones, precious water, and so on.

Looking at Tai Bai Yun Sheng's excited look, Fang Yuan nodded in satisfaction: "It seems that my method of asking you to inspect Hu Immortal blessed land and becoming familiar with the cultivation path of Gu Immortals is very effective. You have finally realized the importance of cultivation resources. But unfortunately, although selling Immortal Gu recipes is a very profitable trade, we temporarily cannot engage in that."

"Ah, why is that?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was confused.

"Because the investment is too great." Fang Yuan sighed: "To get something from nothing, to deduce a rank six Immortal Gu recipe, the amount of green grape immortal essence we would need to expend is at least over a hundred."

"Junior brother, didn't you deduce one percent of this Immortal Gu recipe?"

"That is because what I was deducing was the gruel mud Immortal Gu remnant recipe. I told you before, earlier I had engaged in the trade of gruel mud, thus I obtained many gruel mud Immortal Gu remnant recipes. But after I collated these remnant recipes, I only obtained this sixty percent remnant recipe." Fang Yuan answered.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was not stupid, he immediately understood Fang Yuan's words.

With the light of wisdom, no problem could trouble Fang Yuan.

Under normal circumstances, if he encountered difficulty when deducing Gu recipes, they would be hard to resolve. If he was lucky and had a burst of inspiration, he would be able to think of a solution. But if he was unlucky and could not resolve this problem, he would be stuck there for years, or even decades without making any progress.

But with wisdom Gu, Fang Yuan faced no difficulty when deducing Gu recipes.

Even if Fang Yuan encountered a problem that he could not solve due to his foundations, he just needed to think more. Using the light of wisdom to think, he only needed to consume more wills in order to resolve this problem.

In this way, Immortal Gu recipes were easier to deduce towards the later parts.

A sixty percent remnant recipe means it already has a general direction, this could allow Fang Yuan to rule out a large number of Gu refinement elements. On this basis, he progressed by one percent of the deduction.

That is to say, if he started from zero, from scratch, and deduced the recipe from nothing, it would be extremely difficult, he would not even reach one percent.

Fang Yuan continued: "I only have eighteen green grape immortal essence beads, while you have twenty-six. Hu Immortal blessed land only has sixty-four beads of Bai Hu's immortal essence. But you and Hu Immortal land spirit cannot be under the wisdom light halo. Even if I lend delight in water and mountain Immortal Gu to you, the joyful will that you create cannot be used by me. At this point, the gruel mud remnant recipe is the most promising of them, but it also requires about forty beads of immortal essence from us. Don't forget that we are not safe now. Northern plains' Gu Immortals and Immortal Crane Sect are going to find trouble with us. Especially if wisdom Gu is exposed, I'm afraid every Gu Immortal in the five regions would charge towards us with killing intent!"

"Yes, the investment is too big, and we also need to preserve some green grape immortal essence as a preemptive measure to guard against enemies and accidents." Tai Bai Yun Sheng nodded, he sighed deeply and looked at the ground, he accepted this fact in disappointment.

But immediately after, he raised his head, his eyes shining with light: "Eh? I have an idea! Junior brother, I remember you told me about the matter with Lang Ya land spirit. Master told you about the secrets of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, thus when you requested help from Lang Ya land spirit, you said you deduced it yourself. That caused Lang Ya land spirit to assume you were a wisdom path Gu Master, and it wanted to work with you to perfect Gu recipes."

"Oh!" Fang Yuan pretended to jolt into realization, he showed an appropriately excited expression on his face: "There is such a thing, ahh, ahh, after becoming a zombie, my brain is so useless, I did not think of this! Old Bai, you are completely right, the best remnant recipe that I have right now is the sixty percent gruel mud Immortal Gu recipe. There must be many remnant recipes in Lang Ya land spirit's hands. He probably has remnant recipes with a much higher completion rate."

"Junior brother, you are familiar with Lang Ya land spirit, and you also know the method to enter Lang Ya blessed land, we can totally cooperate with Lang Ya land spirit!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng thought about this amazing plan and laughed loudly and heartily.

Chapter 656: I will take down my brother in the name of justice

"Old Bai, your reminder is very true, but I have no way to directly contact Lang Ya land spirit. I used two opportunities in the past to obtain two Immortal Gu from that old man, Lang Ya land spirit, and I was nearly chased out by him. Hehehe, I don't think I'll be able to contact him." Fang Yuan smiled bitterly.

"Is that so..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng's joy on his face froze.

Linking between two blessed lands could be done through hole earth Gu, directly connecting both of their territories. Earlier, when Fang Yuan traded with Immortal Crane Sect, he used this method.

But Fang Yuan and Lang Ya land spirit's relationship was naturally not close to that extent.

Most critically, Hu Immortal blessed land was in central continent, while Lang Ya blessed land was in northern plains, even the hole earth Gu was not easy to use. To directly connect to there, he needed to use stargate Gu.

Stargate Gu came in pairs, but Fang Yuan only had one stargate Gu left now. The other one was destroyed in the wind veil of assimilation.

"It seems we can only return to northern plains and meet Lang Ya land spirit personally, before asking for cooperation." Tai Bai Yun Sheng sighed.

"No, there is another method that relies on luck." Fang Yuan hummed: "That old land spirit loves refining Gu, but he cannot go out to search for Gu refinement materials. Lang Ya blessed land's terrain is very plain, it can produce very limited varieties of materials, he will have to go to treasure yellow heaven often. We can wait for him patiently, staring at treasure yellow heaven until his divine sense appears."

"Right, there is still this method!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's eyes shone.

"So from now on, I will be relying on you, Old Bai." Fang Yuan said as a matter of fact.

"No problem, count on me. I will go back now and open connecting heaven Gu, linking to treasure yellow heaven!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng patted his chest, he could not wait any longer, he was brought back to his residential area by the land spirit.

He chose to build a temporary house at the western area of the blessed land.

That was his temporary home.

The terrain of Hu Immortal blessed land was similar to northern plains, Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not feel any discomfort living here, he felt a serene feeling like being at home.

Having roamed northern plains for about half his life, he had finally found an organisation and had settled down, therefore he especially treasured this home.

After sending Tai Bai Yun Sheng away, Fang Yuan fell into deep thought.

He had already thought of cooperating with Lang Ya land spirit long ago. In truth, a few days ago, he had asked Little Hu Immortal to keep an eye on treasure yellow heaven, waiting for Old Immortal Lang Ya's divine sense.

But there was no progress at all.

What he was thinking about now was not the matter about Lang Ya land spirit, but about Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

His journey in northern plains was very chaotic, now during these days when he was in Hu Immortal blessed land, he observed Tai Bai Yun Sheng heavily and gained a lot of insight on this person.

"Tai Bai Yun Sheng is indeed a good person. He has ability but no ambition. His intelligence is only that of an average person, what he really has is the wisdom accumulated from his entire life's experiences. He does not have a grasp of the big picture, it is no wonder that even though he was a former young tribe leader, and having roamed for so many years, with sufficient reputation and strength, he did not manage to create a force of his own." Fang Yuan evaluated in his mind.

Such a person is best as a follower that closely sticks to him, he should not be left alone due to his lack of leadership capability. Because of his nature and beliefs, if he is far away, not only would he be unable to cooperate, he might even ruin plans.

Over these days, Fang Yuan had been in constant contact with Tai Bai Yun Sheng, their relationship had been improving.

During several of their late night talks, Fang Yuan talked of his experiences since rebirth, only with the addition of the non-existent "Purple Mountain True Monarch".

Meanwhile, Tai Bai Yun Sheng talked about basically all of his life's experiences.

Many times, even though Fang Yuan already had some plan in his heart, he still asked Tai Bai Yun Sheng to come over and discuss it.

It might seem like a waste of time, but this was Fang Yuan's elaborate plan.

Firstly, it was to test Tai Bai Yun Sheng's ability and true self, to see if his emotions really came from the bottom of his heart.

Secondly, telling him about the current situation without concealing anything increased his sense of belonging, and his feelings of responsibility.

Thirdly, it was a type of formless suppression towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng. The result of all their discussions usually ended up with Fang Yuan's method being used, and Tai Bai Yun Sheng's method being denied. As this happened more frequently, subconsciously, Tai Bai Yun Sheng would rely more and more on Fang Yuan, paying greater attention to his plans and denying his own ideas. At crucial moments, Fang Yuan would be able to make decisions without any opposition. They would not quarrel over their own ideas and lead to conflict which could botch a situation.

Fang Yuan was not Hei Lou Lan, Hei Lou Lan had the rank six slavery Gu and could enslave a Gu Immortal.

Fang Yuan did not have it, but Tai Bai Yun Sheng was neither Bai Ning Bing nor Hei Lou Lan.

Most importantly, Fang Yuan had his own methods, and he believed: Even without slavery Immortal Gu, he could still subdue Tai Bai Yun Sheng, to squeeze out his greatest potential and become his tool.

This was the confidence of a demonic path overlord!

Central Continent, Fei He mountain.

The clouds were abundant in the sky, thousands of cranes were flying.

Winds blew on the verdant green mountain, Fang Zheng sat on a cliff, focusing his gaze on thousands of iron beak flying cranes, as they created different formations according to his will. At times they charged, at times they split into two to pincer attack, and at times they formed a circular defensive formation.

The wind blew his long hair, his bright eyes were shining with determination.

Tough times make men grow, to Fang Zheng, the Hu Immortal blessed land's competition a year ago was a major setback for him.

After some consolation, he walked out of his despair, and put in even more effort, he had almost risked his life to cultivate daily!

At this time, a voice came from Fang Zheng's aperture: "Good, your command of the iron beak flying cranes have reached a stage where you can manipulate them with ease, they move with a thought from you. Now, you can already go back to the sect to take the flying crane manipulation test, and attempt to get B grade evaluation. You have a sixty percent chance of succeeding, if you do, you will get the test reward — a rank five, five hole jade flute Gu. Once you have this Gu, your manipulation of the crane group would reach quasi enslavement master level."

The voice originated from a spirit incubating flea in Fang Zheng's aperture.

Fang Zheng's master — Lord Sky Crane's soul was residing in this Gu worm.

"Rank five, five hole jade flute Gu?" His eyes shone, excitement was all over his face: "Yes, master, I will go now."

Fang Zheng stood up, he willed and a large iron beak flying crane king arrived before him.

He jumped and easily got on the crane king's back.

The crane king cried out in a proud tone. Fang Zheng sat on the crane king's back, the crane group flying around him, it was a scene of white as he flew towards Immortal Crane Sect amidst the wind and clouds.

Not long after, he arrived at white jade square D.

The iron beak flying crane landed in the square, Fang Zheng had just landed, when one of Immortal Crane Sect's disciples ran over quickly, greeting him: "Senior brother Fang Zheng."

Fang Zheng nodded: "Junior brother, I am here to take the flying crane manipulation test."

"Senior brother Fang Zheng, please follow me." Immortal Crane Sect's disciple led the way.　　

"Quickly look, guys, that is senior brother Fang Zheng. He is the number one elite disciple of our batch!"

"Did you hear, senior brother Fang Zheng is actually attending the flying crane manipulation test."

"Senior brother Fang Zheng is an enslavement path genius, to think that he has already reached the stage of quasi enslavement path master, he is truly amazing..."

Along the way, everyone's whispered discussions entered Fang Zheng's ears.

Fang Zheng heard them and smiled lightly.

He was now fully grown, his body was tall and he had long black hair that resembled a cape, his eyes were crystal clear. Although he looked ordinary, he had quite the disposition and was full of life. Wearing a green and white robe, he looked like a gentleman, it was very comfortable to look at him.

"Although senior brother Fang Zheng is strong, his brother is even more amazing, he is a superb character who managed to obtain Hu Immortal blessed land."

"That's right, according to a reliable source, his brother, Fang Yuan, is secretly a legacy disciple of a certain supreme elder. When Spirit Affinity House were on the verge of taking Hu Immortal blessed land, the supreme elder had no choice but to send senior brother Fang Yuan out, as expected, he shocked everyone and sealed the deal, obtaining Hu Immortal blessed land!"

"Fang Zheng has a good brother, the guts Gu on Dang Hun mountain can strengthen the soul. I can bet that Fang Zheng used the guts Gu. Otherwise, with just his own hard work, how can he raise his cultivation to rank five in one year? Furthermore, his enslavement path attainment improved at lightning speed, he is actually going to take the flying crane manipulation test!"

The tone of these people was sour and bitter, Fang Zheng heard them as his smile slowly vanished, his fists which were hidden in his sleeves were tightly clenched.

"Brother!" Fang Zheng's eyes shone with a trace of darkness.

Ever since Fang Yuan used some unthinkable method to snatch Hu Immortal blessed land, Immortal Crane Sect had declared publicly that Fang Yuan was Immortal Crane Sect's disciple.

During this year, Fang Zheng felt like life had returned to the past, when he was suppressed by Fang Yuan.

No matter what great results he obtained or how many improvements he made, others would only praise him briefly before mentioning the even more impressive Fang Yuan.

"Calm your spirit, my disciple." Lord Sky Crane's voice came from the spirit incubating flea.

Lord Sky Crane's experiences were much richer than Fang Zheng. After these years of staying together, he had grasped a firm understanding of Fang Zheng.

He consoled Fang Zheng: "These years, I have seen all of your hard work. You are in no way inferior to your brother. Don't forget, you are now a rank five Gu Master, a quasi enslavement master! I bet your brother is not your match right now. In any case, Fang Yuan is going to face extermination soon. The sect has mobilized three supreme elders in this plan, they are tasked to take back Hu Immortal blessed land, your brother has no way to survive."

Three supreme elders... that is the battle strength of three Gu Immortals.

Fang Zheng heard this and licked his lips, before his gaze turned a bit dimmer.

Lord Sky Crane knew what he was thinking, he laughed and said: "Fang Zheng, don't feel any guilt towards this. Your brother had ventured into the wrong path, he is walking on the demonic path now. He actually slaughtered his entire clan, this makes him a beast worse than pigs or dogs! Fang Yuan is a true and blue demonic head, you cannot feel any sympathy towards him. Killing him is equivalent to benefitting the people of the world. Think about it, if he is alive, how many innocent people would be harmed?"

"That's right. Brother's hands are full of blood, he is a murderer! A killer! I will take revenge for my clan, for my uncle and aunt, for Shen Cui Er!" Fang Zheng inwardly shouted, urging himself.

"Good, that's it." Lord Sky Crane was evidently very happy with Fang Zheng's attitude: "Think about these years, you were training in Fu Hu blessed land, how dangerous and terrifying was it! One year outside was eight years inside Fu Hu blessed land! You became a rank five Gu Master, suffering so much and enduring so much, wasn't it for the greater plan of taking back Hu Immortal blessed land? Don't screw up at the last moment, you cannot disappoint everyone at this most crucial juncture."

"Don't worry, master! I understand, I will do my best and contribute to the sect, I will exterminate all evil, and take down my brother in the name of justice! I will not disappoint you!" Fang Zheng assured resolutely and unhesitantly.

Chapter 657: Dong Fang Chang Fan, Miniscule Mountain

The light of wisdom dyed the cave walls with beautiful lights.

Fang Yuan quietly stood in it for a good while before opening his eyes, slowly stepping out of the wisdom light halo.

The wills in his mind were almost fully consumed. Mortal Gu could only produce limited wills and could not compare to wisdom path Immortal Gu.

"My deduction of Immortal Crane Sect's plan has failed, not because I don't have enough wills, but because I don't have enough clues." Fang Yuan reflected inwardly.

After being in the wisdom light halo many times over these days, he had summed up his experiences.

Wisdom Gu was different from natural inspiration.

Wisdom Gu emitted the light of wisdom which could provide unending insights to Gu Master. But the result of the thoughts and deductions were based on the Gu Master's foundation as well as the clues they had accumulated.

Fang Yuan's attempt at deducing Immortal Crane Sect's conspiracy against Hu Immortal blessed land failed because he did not have enough evidence.

In summary, the deeper the Gu Master's foundations and the more evidence they gathered, the more accurate the outcome of the deduction would be.

Naturally, when there was more evidence, there would be more factors to consider, and the amount of thoughts and will consumed would also become larger. Especially when deducing Immortal Gu recipes, the factors to consider were too many, thus the wills consumed were enormous.

As for natural inspiration, it was a precious experience when a Gu Master advances to a Gu Immortal.

During this process, the Gu Master questions heaven and earth, and heaven and earth would directly provide the solutions with no need for the Gu Master to think.

Let's take a difficult mathematical problem from Earth, for example, solving a multivariate equation.

If the Gu Master used wisdom Gu, his thoughts would quickly consume while he would obtain numerous insights, causing there to be many paths to the solution. Some of these paths might be dead ends while some might give wrong results. Only a few would be correct paths which could deduce the solution.

While natural inspiration would be akin to directly giving the correct answers.

The Gu Master would obtain the correct answer, but they had to know how to use it.

Thus, during natural inspiration, the Gu Master should not ask overly profound questions. Fang Yuan did not directly ask about eternal life; maybe heaven and earth would give him an answer but he would absolutely not be able to comprehend it.

It was like a child who had not learned mathematics seeing a linear equation, they naturally would not be able to comprehend the answer.

To comprehend this answer, the child would have to learn numbers, unknown variables, positive and negative numbers, and so on. But this would only be the foundation of the foundation.

To Gu Masters, even if they obtained answers to excessively profound questions, they would not be able to comprehend it or be able to use it.

Even if they asked about all aspects of this difficult problem during natural inspiration and comprehended the basics, the time consumed would be too high, the amount of information would also be so large that the mind would not be able to bear it.

As such, the best way to make use of natural inspiration was to ask according to the state of one's current foundation, then stabilize the foundation and progress step by step.

"But within wisdom path, there is an Immortal Gu that can allow a Gu Immortal to directly obtain answers. That is heavenly secret Gu. Gu Masters do not need to have their thoughts collide nor make deductions, as long as they grabbed onto that strand of heavenly secret, they would directly obtain the answer. In the records of history, this Gu was created by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable; he possessed a rank eight heavenly secret Immortal Gu but after his death, this heavenly secret Immortal Gu disappeared without a trace and there has been no news regarding it since then."

Fang Yuan suddenly recalled heavenly secret Immortal Gu.

Gu worms had one ability, and even the rank nine wisdom Gu was no exception. The higher the ranks of the Gu, the more powerful their ability was. If wisdom Gu was truly activated, its effect would definitely be terrifying. But even if it was stronger, it could not replicate the effect of heavenly secret Immortal Gu.

"It was rumored that Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable was the rank nine Gu Master who could detect and react to the heavenly fate most closely. He created heavenly secret Immortal Gu to interact with heaven and earth, and also to experience natural inspiration again. If I have heavenly secret Immortal Gu, it would combine exquisitely with wisdom Gu. Meanwhile, if anyone else used heavenly secret Immortal Gu to investigate me, all of my secrets would likely be exposed..."

Heavenly secret Immortal Gu could let Gu Masters directly question heaven and earth.

There were no events in the world that heaven and earth did not know of.

It was as the saying goes, except you and me, only heaven and earth know.

As for other wisdom path Gu worms, Fang Yuan did not need to worry for the moment. The wind veil of assimilation had swallowed everything, cleaning up all the traces of crimes Fang Yuan had committed in Imperial Court blessed land.

Without heavenly secret Immortal Gu, wisdom path Gu Masters would have to make deductions according to normal methods and that was to gather as much evidence and clues as possible.

They were unable to plunder any crucial clues from Imperial Court blessed land and could only begin investigating from the Imperial Court contest. It was not impossible to deduce Fang Yuan's true identity with this, it was only that the probability was low and the time required would be longer.

Northern Plains, Jade Pool blessed land.

From a bird's eye view, the blessed land was covered with innumerable large and small deep pools with the color of a mixture of blue and green.

Lead by Chanyu tribe's Gu Immortal, Tong Zu, around ten Gu Immortals of northern plains' righteous path slowly descended from the air.

"The noble Jade Pool blessed land is truly unique and fresh. These innumerable jade pools are like the stars in the sky, their beauty unmatched." A female Gu Immortal strolled through the sky, expressing her admiration. Her hair that was twenty to thirty feet long draped behind her and was extremely eye catching.

"All of these jade pools have different types of water, raising countless aquatic species. Dong Fang tribe's fish groups and water vegetation have been famous for a long time in treasure yellow heaven." A male Gu Immortal opened the third vertical eye on his forehead and gazed at the jade pools with a shining gaze.

"Lord Murong Qing Si and Lord Guan Shen Zhao are exaggerating. My tribe's Jade Pool blessed land has only been in operation for just over six thousand years; the landscape cannot compare to Murong tribe's Yin-Yang blessed land, while in terms of productivity, it still falls short of Guan tribe's Shi Huang blessed land." Gu Immortal Dong Fang Yi Kong who was attending to them, welcomed them with a smile, modestly talking of Dong Fang tribe's specialities.

Jade Pool blessed land was the headquarters of the Huang Jin family's Dong Fang tribe, a super force.

A group of Gu Immortals slowly descended.

This, among the myriad jade pools, did not appear to be a remarkable location.

Beside a jade pool was a small hut.

An elderly man was sitting beside the pool in front of the house, in the midst of fishing.

"These are underworld eels." Guan Shen Zhao's vertical eye on his forehead gazed at the pool before blurting out in shock at the scene inside the clear pool.

When the other Gu Immortals heard it, some of them also showed slightly moved expressions.

"Sir Dong Fang, we have already not seen each other for over ten years. Thinking of back then when we charged into Snowy Mountain and fought side by side.. Sigh, time really flies by..." Everyone stood still, as Gu Immortal Tong Zu who had the highest cultivation made a greeting.

"Lord Tong Zu, you are still as graceful as ever while this old man has one foot in the grave, I don't dare to compare with you." The elderly man who was fishing stood up slowly; he was Dong Fang Chang Fan, northern plains' number one wisdom path Gu Immortal.

Dong Fang Yi Kong walked to Chang Fan's side, as Chang Fan continued: "Dong Fang tribe is honored with the presence of all of you, being able to welcome everyone to my humble abode is an extreme honor. Everyone, please come in."

Dong Fang Chang Fan led everyone inside the hut.

The inside of the hut was spacious; there was a plaza and also halls. There were sixteen stone statues at the plaza, seemingly arranged in order as well as randomly, as they were separated by varied distances. The expressions on them were subtle, as if containing some kind of mystical pattern.

"This is Dong Fang tribe's rank six Immortal Gu House — Modest Thatched Hut? It truly is brilliant." One Gu Immortal praised directly.

Dong Fang Chang Fan led everyone to the administration hall and seated them. Northern plains' righteous path Gu Immortals, representing all the different forces, had gathered under one roof!

Dong Fang Chang Fan sat at the main seat and smiled as he observed everyone: "This time, I have invited everyone here personally in order to make a transaction with you."

Guan Shen Zhao and the others glanced at each other with no one taking the initiative to speak, it was still Tong Zu who responded: "Sir Dong Fang already decided to not make deductions for others tens of years ago. But in the letter, you said you were making an exception for us, and will deduce the true culprit of the destruction of True Yang Building or perhaps other aspects. But I wonder how we can pay for this transaction?"

Dong Fang Chang Fan coughed several times before sighing: "This old man's lifespan is at its end and I know there is no hope in prolonging my life. But before I depart, I have some concerns lingering in my heart. One is the tribe's growth and the other is my tribe's descendants, I hope I can make this transaction with everyone. This old man shall make deductions for each of your tribes once, and after I die, I hope everyone can ally with my Dong Fang tribe."

"Alliance?"

"Yes, this old man has already roughly prepared the alliance contracts, everyone can examine them and if you have any objections, we can modify it right here." Dong Fang Chang Fan took out two east window Gu which he then handed to the Gu Immortals.

The Gu Immortals skimmed over the contract one after another. The alliance conditions were extremely lax. Dong Fang Chang Fan did not even request for mutual help and protection among the allies, he only requested that after he died, they had to protect Dong Fang tribe's peace for fifty years. In this time period, the parties in the contract could not target, suppress or attack Dong Fang tribe.

The Gu Immortals involuntarily felt a rush of excitement.

Dong Fang Chang Fan was currently the number one wisdom path Gu Immortal of northern plains. Besides him, there was no one else suitable to deduce the true culprit of True Yang Building's destruction!

In the cultivation of Gu Immortals, who would not encounter some difficult problems relating to their cultivation? Or perhaps, they might obtain Immortal Gu remnant recipes that require deductions? With Dong Fang Chang Fan, these issues were very likely to be resolved.

Even more importantly, after Imperial Court blessed land perished and Eighty-Eight True Yang Building collapsed, large numbers of Gu worms were brought over by the formless fists to all regions of northern plains. The aura of Immortal Gu manifested in many places, causing the Gu Immortals to contest over them.

At this crucial time, if Dong Fang Chang Fan deduced the location of an Immortal Gu, then they were very likely to get that Immortal Gu!

Everyone was more than moved and they couldn't help but praise Dong Fang Chang Fan's shrewdness.

If it were during normal times, Dong Fang Chang Fan's bargaining chip might be somewhat less important. But now, when one deduction was very likely to represent one Immortal Gu, all the Gu Immortals were moved.

"Great, Sir Dong Fang, Our Chanyu tribe accepts your conditions."

Tong Zu spoke first, then Hei tribe, Murong tribe, every tribe's representatives also accepted.

This situation was within Dong Fang Chang Fan's expectations. His smile became even brighter: "Since this is the case, Fairy Li Shan, please take action."

"Fairy Li Shan?"

While everyone was surprised, a rank six female Gu Immortal walked from behind the hall and appeared in front of everyone.

"Fairy Li Shan, I trust you have been well." A Gu Immortal greeted.

Another Gu Immortal laughed: "Sir Dong Fang sure has made ample preparations, even inviting over Fairy Li Shan. It is just that this Jade Pool blessed land does not have any mountains or rivers, how will we make the oath?"

Dong Fang Yi Kong, who had been silent all this time, stood from beside Dong Fang Chang Fan, and spoke: "Everyone, please wait and see."

He then opened his palm, lights in vibrant colors floated in the center of his palm, revealing a miniature mountain peak.

"Could this be — Miniscule Mountain?!" Murong Qing Si opened her graceful eyes wide as she reacted first, saying in a disbelieving tone.

"Exactly." Dong Fang Yi Kong gave a modest smile, but the pride within him could not be concealed.

A commotion erupted among the Gu Immortals.

Chapter 658: Difficulty in resolving the issues, Hei Lou Lan appears

In the underground cave, the light of wisdom flickered back and forth from bright to dim.

Fang Yuan quietly stood inside it. Only when the wills inside his mind were fully consumed did he open his eyes and step out of the wisdom light halo.

The deduction he made had succeeded, but Fang Yuan was gloomy because of it.

"To seal Spring Autumn Cicada, as much as over six thousand mortal Gu are required, among them, almost half are rank five, with rare Gu worms reaching two thousand, and there are also about eight hundred ancient Gu worms. These ancient Gu worms are either extinct or on the brink of extinction. My initial estimate is that I require about twenty-three immortal essence stones to use this method."

Fang Yuan was in a poverty stricken state, twenty-three immortal essence stones were a hopeless number for him currently.

But Fang Yuan had to brace himself to accomplish this task.

Because Spring Autumn Cicada's recovery was becoming faster and faster, making the situation of the first aperture more critical.

Fortunately, with Fang Yuan having turned into a zombie, his first aperture turned into a dead aperture, thus it was able to hold on till now. If the aperture was like before, it might have already burst.

"According to the current situation, I estimate I still have over two months to plan and prepare. If this time limit is crossed, the first aperture will not be able to endure even if it is already dead."

Fang Yuan was feeling a heavy pressure.

He was now a member of the living dead, even if his first aperture was destroyed, he would not die. But losing the first aperture would no doubt greatly reduce his future cultivation potential, and that would be an immeasurable loss.

Fang Yuan was in a difficult situation, and there was only one feasible method to earn twenty-three immortal essence stones within a short period of time - selling Immortal Gu recipes.

Returning to Dang Hun palace, Fang Yuan called in Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

"I have been paying close attention to treasure yellow heaven over these days, taking almost no rest. But Lang Ya land spirit's divine sense has not appeared since the beginning."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's answer made Fang Yuan feel disappointment.

Lang Ya land spirit's divine sense called itself "Lang Ya Old Immortal" in treasure yellow heaven, and it was very active at that. But now, it had not appeared at all, almost like it was missing.

Fang Yuan keenly sensed Lang Ya land spirit was likely to be facing some problems. He recalled his previous life where Lang Ya blessed land had suffered a total of seven waves of attacks.

"Previously when I was in northern plains, the second wave of experts had already attacked Lang Ya blessed land. Could it be, the third wave of attacks has already occured and Lang Ya land spirit is busy dealing with it, thus having no time to refine Gu?"

Memories of Fang Yuan's previous life were not able to help him in this aspect.

He only remembered about the seven waves of attacks, and did not remember the detailed timings of these attacks.

Even if he remembered the exact timing, this world was already influenced by him and had experienced huge changes, who is to say that the changes upon changes might not have shifted the attacks to an earlier time.

"My horizons have been continually broadened these days... A piece of ten thousand year profound ice costs half an immortal essence stone! Half a kilogram of hurricane mountain pepper has the selling price of an immortal essence stone! What are divine jade pearls? Ten of them actually cost half an immortal essence stone. There is also, what's that white spiral silk, its price is even more ridiculous, a pinky sized amount costs three immortal essence stones! Heavens, right now, I realized how poor I am!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng chattered on about his harvest over this time, speaking in an excited tone.

During these days, as Fang Yuan interacted with Tai Bai Yun Sheng all the time, he gradually discovered Tai Bai Yun Sheng had a shortcoming, that was his prattling mouth, he was talkative.

Fang Yuan handed a letter Gu and interrupted his chattering: "This is the letter sent by Immortal Crane Sect, please read."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng sent his consciousness inside, his brows soon frowned into a knot.

In this second letter from Immortal Crane Sect, their tone was even more harsh and fierce, already making their intention to attack Hu Immortal blessed land exceptionally clear. Immortal Crane Sect even used the tone of the victor, demanding Fang Yuan to surrender.

"These guys have gone crazy for Dang Hun mountain. If it were me, I would at least first stabilize you, then carry out hidden attacks. Aren't they afraid their actions will make us take preventive measures?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng said in a displeased tone.

"This is the power and confidence of Immortal Crane Sect. They are one of the ten great ancient sects of central continent and have an incomparably deep foundation, having stood tall and straight at Fei He mountain for hundreds of thousands of years. Besides this, I think they are trying to pressure me and also probe the intention of my backers." Fang Yuan analyzed.

"Yes, Immortal Crane Sect is stronger than any single super force of northern plains by some degree. We are too weak, while they are a colossus becoming more and more overbearing. It will be very difficult for us to protect Hu Immortal blessed land from them..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng spoke carefully, glancing at Fang Yuan several times.

He already had thoughts of retreating, giving up Hu Immortal blessed land and moving far away, he just did not openly express it.

Fang Yuan knew his thoughts. Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a healing Gu Master, he was benevolent and could be said to be feeble, seriously lacking the spirit to make a stand.

Fang Yuan did not rebuke Tai Bai Yun Sheng's intentions.

In fact, Fang Yuan had also thought of giving up and abandoning Hu Immortal blessed land.

Dang Hun mountain represented extremely huge benefits and Immortal Crane Sect and other super forces would definitely want to possess it.

However, that was, of course, only as a last resort.

As long as there existed hope along with benefits, it could be said that Fang Yuan would absolutely not speak of giving up easily.

Fang Yuan thus consoled Tai Bai Yun Sheng: "Immortal Crane Sect is one of the ten great ancient sects of central continent, a super force, a behemoth, but they also have their worries. How many methods can they use to deal with us specifically? I dare to guarantee, it is not as exaggerated as you imagine, especially when they are greatly underestimating our true battle strength."

Life was not easy, Immortal Crane Sect also had its own problems.

New sects were emerging endlessly in central continent, continually bringing huge impacts to the ten great ancient sects.

The ten great ancient sects occupied the most important positions in central continent with the best cultivation resources, they naturally would be subjected to competition from all sides.

In history, Immortal Crane Sect had experienced golden ages several times, but at present, there was a clear disparity compared to their most prosperous periods.

Immortal Crane Sect had not expanded for many years already — this meant they were under some restraints.

"Since junior brother wants to battle Immortal Crane Sect, I shall risk my life to accompany you. Don't worry, no matter how dangerous the situation gets, I will support you till the last moment." Tai Bai Yun Sheng patted his chest and swore.

Fang Yuan nodded: "I also ask Old Bai to not worry, I, Gu Yue Fang Yuan, am not a stubborn man. If there was nothing to be done and the situation was truly unfavorable, I would definitely take the initiative to retreat. Forcing back Immortal Crane Sect's first wave of attacks perhaps won't be difficult, but the main problem does not lie here. Immortal Crane Sect is a very big sect, if we repel them, they will at once arrive with another wave. After this continues for few times, Immortal Crane Sect's offense will become stronger and they will start treating us more seriously. We need to rely on another great force to resolve this issue, making an alliance with another ancient sect."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng repeatedly nodded in complete agreement: "But junior brother, you have already sent a letter to Spirit Affinity House, but until now they have yet to reply. Was our letter Gu intercepted by Immortal Crane Sect, how about we send some more letters?"

Fang Yuan shook his head, the letter Gu he contacted Spirit Affinity House with was not his, but the rank five letter sending green bird Gu created by Feng Jiu Ge.

Back then, Fang Yuan defeated Feng Jin Huang and obtained Hu Immortal blessed land. Feng Jin Huang was indignant and sent a challenge letter using this letter sending green bird Gu.

But Fang Yuan did not respond to the challenge and instead had been detaining this letter Gu.

He had already speculated this letter Gu's owner was very likely to be Feng Jiu Ge. The reason being that Feng Jin Huang had yet to reach rank five back then.

Besides Feng Jiu Gu, it was also likely to be his wife, Feng Jin Huang's mother — Fairy Bai Qing.

Regardless of who the owner was, this letter Gu had already been lent to Fang Yuan, its original purpose being to allow Fang Yuan to respond to the challenge letter.

And Fang Yuan used this letter Gu to contact Spirit Affinity House.

Fang Yuan had been very confident regarding this letter, but Spirit Affinity House still had yet to reply after so long, so he was somewhat unsure now.

According to the common sense conjecture: letter sending green bird Gu was created by Feng Jiu Ge, which represented this expert's will and prestige to some degree. To intercept this green bird Gu and risk offending his impressive and dignified presence, this was not at all likely.

However, this possibility could not be completely excluded as well.

Thus Fang Yuan nodded and accepted Tai Bai Yun Sheng's suggestion: "Okay, let's wait seven days, if we still don't receive a reply by then, we will send another letter."

Time passed day by day, Hu Immortal blessed land was in a predicament.

A strong enemy was approaching from the outside, while on the inside, cultivation resources were lacking. Even if Fang Yuan used his zombie body and wisdom Gu to deduce and sell Immortal Gu recipes of the highest grade, the regretful part was that he did not have the capital to kickstart this plan and could only put it aside for the time being.

Lang Ya land spirit and Spirit Affinity House were the keys to break through these predicaments.

But it was a pity that these two keys stayed in the dark with no messages from them. Who knew when Fang Yuan would receive news from them, perhaps he wouldn't for his whole life.

Destiny created obstacles, the road ahead of Fang Yuan was once again shrouded in obscurity.

"It seems my luck is still not too good." Fang Yuan scoffed at himself.

There was nothing he could do, since he possessed Spring Autumn Cicada, his luck was likely to only get worse.

He tried asking Mo Yao about improved Immortal Gu remnant recipes, but Mo Yao claimed that she did not know them.

She was residing in Fang Yuan's body and had gone through the final battle in northern plains with him; she knew Fang Yuan possessed wisdom Gu and thus it was not hard for her to speculate Fang Yuan's intentions.

Mo Yao was a refinement path grandmaster, she very likely knew Immortal Gu remnant recipes which matched Fang Yuan's criteria. But she did not reply and since Fang Yuan lacked wisdom path methods, he could do nothing to her.

Under this kind of situation, Hei Lou Lan suddenly arrived at Dang Hun mountain.

Fang Yuan lost a stargate Gu and was already not able to return to northern plains alone. Hei Lou Lan being able to come to Dang Hun mountain was naturally because of Fixed Immortal Travel.

As for how she knew the scenery here, that was because Fang Yuan had sent a will to her of his own accord.

This was the agreed upon plan, but Fang Yuan was still somewhat surprised: "If I am not wrong, there is still half a month left before the limit of our agreed upon time, right?"

"The situation has changed, my friend." Hei Lou Lan tone's was grave, revealing a trace of worry.

Making this formidable and ambitious person anxious, the situation in northern plains indeed did not seem to be optimistic.

However, Hei Lou Lan soon realized her flaw and concealed all her emotions, speaking with a cold smile: "Naturally, I have another goal, that is to make sure you are not on guard. After all, this is your headquarters, in case you arranged traps against me, I would be messing up your plans by arriving earlier!"

Fang Yuan laughed, appearing unperturbed, as if there were no issues that could perplex him: "After the battle of northern plains, you and I are already tied together for better or for worse. But for complete cooperation, your previous conditions are still insufficient!"

Chapter 659: The dirtiness of humans

Hearing Fang Yuan say "insufficient", Hei Lou Lan snorted in displeasure: "Fang Yuan, you are not very clear about northern plains' situation, I will tell you right now. Not long ago, northern plains' number one wisdom path Gu Immortal, Dong Fang Chang Fan, invited all of the super tribes and personally made deductions for them. His condition was that they had to ally with Dong Fang tribe, and within the fifty years of his death, they are not allowed to target or suppress Dong Fang tribe."

"Oh?" Fang Yuan's gaze focused: "There's such a thing? Then, what did he deduce?"

"Reportedly, Dong Fang Chang Fan made one deduction for each tribe, regarding Gu recipes, appearance of Immortal Gu, or some tips for killing desolate beasts. He has already deduced much of your information, though I do not know the deeper details. But now, everyone knows that you are not a northern plains Gu Master, but there is also a northern plains Gu Master colluding with you."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's pupils shrunk, he said with some fear: "He actually deduced so many things? As expected of Dong Fang Chang Fan..."

Hei Lou Lan snickered, continuing: "Fang Yuan, our lives are tied together now! If I die, who is to say that I will not expose you and Tai Bai Yun Sheng. Other than that, is wisdom Gu in your hands?"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression changed, he firmly wanted to deny it, but he stopped himself from acting rashly.

Fang Yuan calmly laughed: "How is that possible! Wisdom Gu was already destroyed in the wind veil of assimilation, how could I have brought it here?"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng immediately praised him in his mind, Fang Yuan's skills in lying were simply spectacular. His tone and expression were flawless, it was filled with pity, regret and other sad emotions, it was as if he really had narrowly missed out in obtaining wisdom Gu.

Hei Lou Lan could not see any flaws in his performance, but next, she squinted, saying in a thuggish tone: "I don't care if you really lost wisdom Gu, I only know that wisdom Gu could have taken the initiative to follow you under the pressure of survival. Hehe, you don't have to deny it now. I'm sure you understand my idea, it is not safe for you to hide in central continent. It doesn't matter if wisdom Gu is really in your hands, as long as I spread information that wisdom Gu is with you, there will be nowhere for you to hide! The entire world's Gu Immortals will chase you down like lunatics, until they get to the truth."

"Are you threatening me?" Fang Yuan's expression turned cold, he slowly stood up.

"Hei Lou Lan, you have some guts. Do you not know that you are now on Dang Hun mountain. As long as we instruct it, the land spirit will use Dang Hun mountain and kill you right here." Tai Bai Yun Sheng shouted.

Hei Lou Lan laughed with her head high, she said fearlessly: "Hahaha, even if this is a dragon's nest or a tiger's den, what can you do to me? I made some arrangements before I came, as long as I do not return in three days, the entirety of northern plains will know that you apprentice brothers are the culprits behind the collapse of True Yang Building, furthermore, the entire world will know that wisdom Gu is with you!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression froze, Hei Lou Lan indeed came prepared, this was targeting his weakness.

But at this time, Fang Yuan's eerie words made Hei Lou Lan's laughter stop —"Hei Lou Lan, I know you are not afraid of death, but have you forgotten your hatred?"

Hei Lou Lan's expression changed, her aura diminished as her eyes were like lightning, looking at Fang Yuan: "State your conditions."

"You have to agree with my first condition, that is, you have to return Fixed Immortal Travel to its owner, me." Next, Fang Yuan raised four fingers: "Secondly, after we cooperate, during the process of your revenge, the loot will be split four to six, for you and us respectively. After all, Tai Bai Yun Sheng and I make up two Gu Immortals."

Hei Lou Lan snorted: "Do you think you have a helper while I don't? But never mind, I accept these conditions."

She hesitated for a bit, but she still chose to give in, even though she had a tough personality.

Fang Yuan smiled lightly, he could see her sincerity from this, he continued: "Lastly, I need to know the entire story of this, as well as the reason why you need to kill your father personally."

Hei Lou Lan was silent for a while, but she soon agreed: "You are indeed overly suspicious, I can satisfy all three of your conditions, this is nothing I can't speak of anyway."

Next, in their conversation, Fang Yuan finally understood the secret behind Hei Lou Lan's thirst for revenge.

The root of all this was actually Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

In True Yang Building, there was a true inheritance called "yin-yang life extension method", it had been taken by Hei Cheng long ago.

Fang Yuan had actually seen the empty light lump of the yin-yang life extension method by coincidence in the past.

This true inheritance was created by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable when he researched about Ren Zu for life extension methods.

To use this method, a male and female Gu Immortal have to cooperate, using copulation to extend the lifespan of one of them.

But there was a flaw in this.

If one gains lifespan, the other must lose lifespan.

In other words, it was to transfer the lifespan of one person to the other.

The story of Su Xian's Night Elopement had long since been widely spread in northern plains, it had given many young women in northern plains the courage to find their true love, to take the first step.

Two hundred years ago, Su Xian Er was the daughter of a concubine in Su tribe, her status was not high and she was often serving wine to guests in banquets, like a servant.

Once, when Su tribe leader was attending to Hei Cheng, Su Xian Er poured wine for him and fell in love with him at first sight.

However, Su tribe leader harmed Hei Cheng in secret, using a poison Gu on him, causing his strength to fall to rock bottom, and he was chased down by enemies.

Su Xian Er learnt of this and ran out of her tribe's campsite in the middle of the night, to save Hei Cheng who had only met her once.

Back then, she only had rank one cultivation, but during the night there were wild wolf groups roaming, it was extremely dangerous and she was simply courting death.

But due to coincidence, she found the unconscious Hei Cheng.

Hei Cheng was thus saved, and their following conversation became a classic that was passed down in northern plains.

He had asked Su Xian Er: "I was plotted against by your tribe leader and you are a Su tribesman, why would you save an enemy of your tribe?"

Su Xian Er then answered: "Lord has a noble spirit, this humble girl fell in love at first sight. Su tribe leader is short-sighted and plotted against lord under the persuasion of some petty people, but he never considered the result of offending Hei tribe. If he was allowed to have his way, Su tribe is destined to become a sacrificial pawn between two super tribes. People say lord repays a favor received by a hundred times. This humble girl saved lord today and only hopes lord can give me a place to stay. It is just and proper for lord to take revenge against Su tribe, but I hope lord can be merciful and leave behind a trace of bloodline for Su tribe."

Hei Cheng was overwhelmed at this sight, he tightly held Su Xian Er's hand and swore: "Your love is as deep as the sea, I, Hei Cheng, am not a cruel person, how could I not repay you? From today onwards, you will be my only wife! I will not care for any other beauties, no matter how beautiful they are. In this life, I will never betray you!"

From then on, the two of them became a loving couple that respected each other equally.

A hundred years later, they both became Gu Immortals, and the story was a legend of northern plains.

But most people did not know that Su tribe faced extermination soon after.

Hei Cheng had many wives and children, Su Xian Er was neither the first, nor the last.

Hei Cheng and Su Xian Er had a daughter, she followed her father's surname, while getting the name Lou Lan. Years later, Su Xian Er died, and Hei Cheng was extremely aggrieved, he announced to the public: His wife's body had deteriorated after giving birth to Hei Lou Lan, she fell heavily ill and her strength fell drastically, thus she died a few years later in her blessed land's earthly calamity.

"He had obtained the yin-yang life extension method in the true inheritance secluded domain, he kept it very secretive. For his own selfish desires, he lied to my mother with ill intentions. My mother did not know the details and because she trusted and cooperated with him, almost all of her lifespan was taken by him mercilessly."

"After my mother died, he concealed the truth, thus he could still openly be a righteous path Gu Immortal. He absorbed my mother's aperture and took all the Gu worms that she accumulated in her life. He is a coward, a dirty and despicable scoundrel, in order to live longer, he actually plotted against the person who loved him the most!"

"Before mother died, she saw his true colors and told me to be careful of him! As expected, mother was right. There was a problem with his cultivation, the lifespan that he took away was consumed very quickly, he is now facing another crisis of dwindling lifespan. This time, his target is me."

"I have the Great Strength True Martial Physique, once I advance to a Gu Immortal, my foundations will be extremely firm. If he uses the yin-yang life extension method on me, less lifespan would be wasted in the process, and he would gain much more lifespan!"

Hei Lou Lan spilled all of the secrets hidden in the dark, in her calm tone, one could nonetheless sense her utter hatred.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng shook his head as he listened: "To think that Lord Hei Cheng is such a person, this is really disappointing..."

He was a prospective Gu Immortal candidate in the past, with high hopes to become one, he had interacted with Hei tribe's Gu Immortal, Hei Bai, in secret, and he was even recruited.

Thus, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's impression of Hei tribe had always been good.

Hei Lou Lan's words destroyed this good impression.

"Hmph, this is the so-called righteous path, who knows how many dirty and disgusting things are going on underneath this glorious surface. In contrast, the demonic path consists of countless characters that are more straightforward!" Hei Lou Lan scoffed.

"No wonder you didn't respond to Hei Cheng when he called you at the point when the wind veil of assimilation was cut open." Fang Yuan nodded, he looked at Hei Lou Lan again, feeling a different emotion.

Hei Lou Lan was born with a golden spoon, yet this actually was a tragedy.

Her own father harmed her mother, and was now targeting her, attempting to take her lifespan.

Lacking the warmth of a family, under threats and dangers for many years, she had no option but to disguise herself while secretly putting in immense effort, swearing to take revenge for her mother.

This was likely the reason why she obtained such a formidable personality.

Where there is a cause, there will be consequences.

There is a saying called "heroes often meet their end", the "hero" here could also be replaced with formidable characters.

But in fact, it is not that heroes and conquerors often meet desperate situations, it is the desperate situations that create them. In this way, they are people with very pitiful lives, they often encounter and feel much greater pain than normal people. But because of this pain, they learn and become who they are.

Those who live in happiness, living like an upright person, being open and honest without any rough rides in life, while attaining numerous achievements and gaining reputation and praise. Are there truly such people in real life?

Fang Yuan thought about Earth, about the five hundred years of his previous life, and scoffed.

Where there are high achievers, there are sacrifices. Those who are higher ups often need to sacrifice their morals.

Of course, there are outliers, lucky people, and those who rely on their family, but how long can they last, how many will be left in the end?

Legend says, when Ren Zu started walking on the road of life, his vision changed, it was pure darkness.

He took the first step.

PIop.

At the next moment, he stepped into the mud.

He raised his foot, wiping it with his hand, it was full of mushy mud and extremely smelly.

He was hesitant to move forward.

At this moment, self Gu said: "Oh human, do not hesitate, if you want to walk on your own road, you will need to rely on your own legs. When your leg steps on the road, do not be afraid of dirtiness."

Chapter 660: Snowy Mountain Alliance

Outside the window of a room, snow was silently falling down.

The fragrance of tea pervaded inside the quiet room.

A woman was sitting beside the vermillion red window frame.

She was wearing an embroidered leather skirt, characteristic of northern plains' women. The leather skirt was embroidered with purplish-red flower buds, while the edges were glittering with silvery light. She bound her hair with a sapphire blue ribbon which had a pure white pearl inlaid in the middle.

Her eyes were drooping, emphasizing her thick eyelashes. Her breathing was soft and her hands that were as white as the snow moved slowly, concentrating completely on brewing tea.

The quiet room was not large and she was the only person inside. But on the table there were four tea cups.

A rich jade-green light suddenly appeared in the quiet room.

The light dissipated to reveal an elderly figure.

The elderly man was tall with an eccentric appearance. His hair was grey and his face was filled with wrinkles. His eyes displayed one who had gone through the vicissitudes of life, warm and tenacious, containing wisdom accumulated in all of his lifetime.

The woman who was brewing the tea stood up at the sight of the elderly man and smiled with interest: "You are Tai Bai Yun Sheng."

The elderly man was Tai Bai Yun Sheng, he quickly looked around him before greeting the woman: "Junior greets senior Fairy Li Shan."

The woman nodded with a smile. She was an influential figure in the limelight among northern plains' Gu Immortals, a rank seven Gu Immortal, Fairy Li Shan.

She looked youthful and beautiful, but her true age was much greater than Tai Bai Yun Sheng's.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng confirmed the safety of the surroundings before opening his immortal aperture, from which two human shadows leaped out.

One turned into Hei Lou Lan while the other was an eight armed immortal zombie as tall as six metres with a fierce appearance, it was none other than Gu Yue Fang Yuan.

"Little aunt, I am back." Hei Lou Lan walked towards Fairy Li Shan, her expression was still cold but her gaze revealed a trace of affection.

Fairy Li Shan glanced at Hei Lou Lan warmly and sighed, then turned her gaze towards Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng: "The relationship between me and Little Lan has always been a secret, to the extent that outsiders aren't even aware we know each other. Today, she exposed this secret of her own accord, it can clearly be seen that she sincerely wishes to cooperate with you two guests. Especially you, Fang Yuan, Little Lan had mentioned you to me many times over these days. You accomplished such a huge matter, bringing even Eighty-Eight True Yang Building down."

Fang Yuan laughed heartily and said with the hoarse voice specific to zombies: "Fairy is exaggerating, all this commotion is not what I wished for. To speak the truth, I had been doubting Hei Lou Lan's proposal for cooperation since the beginning, but who could have thought, Hei Lou Lan had such a close relationship with you. This is the best situation, fairy, with the oath to your Immortal Gu, Mountain Pledge, our alliance can be firm and solid."

Not long ago, at Hu Immortal blessed land, Hei Lou Lan exposed the reason for her hatred. Then she revealed her relationship with Fairy Li Shan.

Fang Yuan was surprised and yet also not surprised.

Hei Lou Lan was under the strict supervision of Gu Immortal Hei Cheng, it would be difficult for her to obtain her current achievements just by relying on her own strength. Besides her own efforts, there definitely was outside help.

"Please take a seat, this snow oil tea has just been steeped." Fairy Li Shan extended her hand to indicate Fang and Tai to be seated.

Fang Yuan waved his hand in refusal: "Let's make an oath and establish the alliance first, it won't be too late to drink tea then."

"Virtuous junior Fang is quite decisive." Fairy Li Shan lightly praised before calling out an Immortal Gu.

This Immortal Gu resembled a beetle. It was thick and solid, even bigger than an adult's palm. Its body was ash gray with a stony texture, a pair of large pincers grew on its head, its back was not glossy and was instead rugged like mountains, and there were specks of stripes, like moss, on the joints of its legs.

Fairy Li Shan aptly explained: "This is a rank six information path Immortal Gu, as famous as sea oath Gu. As long as you choose a mountain to pledge to and as long as this mountain still exists, the oath cannot be violated. Virtuous junior Fang, I wonder which mountain you want to choose?"

Fang Yuan slightly raised his brows, then he pointed outside and laughed hoarsely: "What other place can be better than this mountain?"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng asked, not understanding the situation: "What mountain is this?"

"This mountain is called Snowy Mountain." Fairy Li Shan smiled and introduced.

"Snowy Mountain, where have I heard this name, wait a second, could it be this is that nest of northern plains' demonic path Gu Immortals — Snowy Mountain blessed land?!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng cried out in shock.

"Where else did you think it was?" Hei Lou Lan sneered.

Fang Yuan provided an introduction for Tai Bai Yun Sheng: "There are differences between immortal and mortal. Old Bai, you just recently advanced and you only have heard me mention some information about the northern plains' Gu Immortal world in passing. This Fairy Li Shan is the owner of the third branch peak of Snowy Mountain blessed land, you can also call her the third leader."

"Third... leader." Tai Bai Yun Sheng stared at Fairy Li Shan with wide open eyes, he had never expected for this gentle and refined woman to be a demonic path Gu Immortal, moreover she was the third leader of the largest demonic path nest of northern plains!

　　...

"Cough cough cough." Dong Fang Chang Fan was lying on a sickbed, coughing incessantly. With every cough, his pale white face would wither a bit more.

"Lord..." A handsome young man was standing beside the sickbed with a mournful and grieving expression.

He was wearing a white robe, his face was white like jade and his eyes were deep, revealing a calm, mature temperament, it was Dong Fang Yu Liang.

"No need to grieve, Liang Er, cough cough, to be born, get old, be sick and die is the way of nature." Dong Fang Chang Fan gasped for breath after saying this, and continued after recovering some strength, "Your talents are better than mine, among the whole tribe I feel most optimistic about you. The responsibility of Dong Fang tribe's growth can only be shouldered by you. I, Dong Fang Chang Fan, would not misjudge this."

"Lord supreme elder!" Dong Fang Yu Liang's eyes reddened, sobbing silently.

The old man nearing death in front of his eyes was his benefactor!

Dong Fang Yu Liang lost his parents at the age of eleven, after that he had to maintain his livelihood and also care for his six year old sister, Dong Fang Qing Yu.

To preserve their lives, he gave away all the inheritances left by his parents.

But it was exactly because of this, that he was noticed by Dong Fang Chang Fan, not only becoming a trusted aide, his sister was also given great care.

Later, Dong Fang Yu Liang even received Dong Fang Chang Fan's personal guidance. And despite the obstructions and oppositions from many sides, Dong Fang Chang Fan appointed Dong Fang Yu Liang as the tribe leader.

After Dong Fang Yu Liang lost in the Imperial Court contest and returned to the tribe, he was suppressed and pushed aside by various factions; it was Dong Fang Chang Fan who protected and shielded him again, paying a considerable price.

Dong Fang Chang Fan was becoming weaker and weaker, he opened his mouth several times but no words came out. Finally, he spoke in an extremely weak voice: "Your hand."

Dong Fang Yu Liang extended his hand and grabbed the old man's right hand.

The old man was holding a Gu on his hand.

"Thi... this Gu... take it." Dong Fang Chang Fan's face turned red from the strain, extracting the last bit of energy from his dying breath.

He closely stared at Dong Fang Yu Liang and reminded him: "Although Dong Fang tribe has signed an alliance agreement with the other righteous path tribes, the affairs of world are changeable and hard to predict. My death will cause Dong Fang tribe to fall down from its prosperous period, you are my successor, you must be careful. This Gu, once you activate it, it will bring you to a secluded place which contains the cultivation resources I prepared for you, insights about immortal ascension, the tribe's secret history as well as all my comprehensions of wisdom path cultivation. Remember, always prioritize your safety, don't be impatient. The tribe has... has demonic path spies."

Dong Fang Chang Fan's expression froze, the flush on his face turned fainter and the final trace of radiance in his eyes faded.

"Lord!!" Dong Fang Yu Liang's face was already covered with tears, and this moment, he could no longer hold them back, crying in sorrow.

Northern plains' number one wisdom path Gu Immortal, Dong Fang Chang Fan, had passed away.

The news spread, Dong Fang tribe cried for three days and three nights. And when the great forces of northern plains received the information, both demonic and righteous path Gu Immortals let out breaths of relief.

Dong Fang Chang Fan was a legendary character.

At the time of his birth, Dong Fang tribe was already declining rapidly, with only the name of a super force but with no power.

Dong Fang Chang Fan became a Gu Immortal and led the tribe; scheming in all directions, using wisdom path methods to devise strategies, tying bonds to powerful friends, killing the weak, and even plotting for his enemies to fight each other, causing Dong Fang tribe to rapidly rise again.

Dong Fang tribe's growth was almost entirely because of Dong Fang Chang Fan.

But because of this, all the Gu Immortals of northern plains became aware of Dong Fang Chang Fan's might! Wisdom path Gu Immortals often did not need to use their own hands to humiliate their enemies. Making schemes that connected like a spider web, one thing would lead to the other, enemies would feel like they were sinking into a swamp but unable to extricate themselves.

Gu Immortals feared Dong Fang Chang Fan and secretly reached an agreement. Banning the sale of lifespan Gu to Dong Fang Chang Fan and even secretly destroying Dong Fang tribe's plans of searching for lifespan Gu.

Dong Fang Chang Fan schemed against others, and finally was also schemed by others.

　　...

The sun was high in the sky, crescent lake gleamed in the sunlight with the occasional dragonfish leaping out of the lake.

Leftover snow piled up beside the lake, this was the remnant of the once in ten years blizzard disaster.

Fang Yuan destroyed Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's arrangement; the blizzard disaster poured into Imperial Court blessed land, thus the destruction caused by the disaster in northern plains was many times lighter than the past.

Imperial Court blessed land existed no longer while True Yang Building was also destroyed; there would be no more of the once in ten years blizzard disaster in northern plains.

The remaining snow slowly melted under the sunlight.

Grass was already poking out of the snow. There was a mixture of green and white grasses mixed together.

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng moved together, seeing many water wolves and solitary tri-horned rhinos in their path. Water chestnut trees used to fill this place, but now it was a scene of barrenness, the trees already freezing to death or breaking down from the accumulated snow.

The intense change in the scenery brought Fang Yuan some trouble.

He was searching for the passage to Lang Ya blessed land — that purple stone tree left behind by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable.

Three days had passed since the alliance with Hei Lou Lan.

Little Hu Immortal was at Hu Immortal blessed land, paying attention to treasure yellow heaven all the time but still not seeing Lang Ya Old Immortal's divine sense.

Fang Yuan took back Fixed Immortal Travel and used this Immortal Gu to go to crescent lake.

Fang Yuan did not directly teleport to Lang Ya blessed land to prevent any unnecessary misunderstandings. He planned to use Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's arrangement again and enter properly.

Because the surroundings had changed, he was unable to directly teleport to the purple stone tree. Being able to directly appear beside crescent lake was thanks to Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

When he was wandering over northern plains, he had once dug a cave beside crescent lake and made simple arrangements, staying for two to three months.

The cave had not collapsed, Fang Yuan first lent Fixed Immortal Travel to Tai Bai Yun Sheng, then entered his immortal aperture, arriving at this place.

Chapter 661: Seeing Swamp Crab again

"Found it." Fang Yuan's eyes shone, he had arrived before a purple stone pillar.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng looked in the direction of his voice, merely to see that this crucial pillar was very ordinary. Just that at the base of the stone pillar, there was a rock, flat and smooth like a bench, it looked slightly special.

"This is it." Fang Yuan stretched out a large monstrous arm, sweeping the snow off the stone bench, confirming it.

After Tai Bai Yun Sheng went into his immortal aperture, Fang Yuan sat down on the bench, using a Gu worm to cut his arm and letting the blood drip onto this purple stone pillar.

His blood was not red like normal people, it was a jade green color and had no warmth, it was ice cold.

The purple stone pillar had once been modified by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable with the use of his mysterious Gu worm, the jade green zombie blood was quickly absorbed.

Ma Hong Yun's figure swiftly flashed across Fang Yuan's mind.

This opportunity originally belonged to Ma Hong Yun, Fang Yuan could be said to be a thief.

After Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun were sent out of the wind veil of assimilation by the luck path true inheritance, they were snatched by northern plains' righteous and demonic Gu Immortals, it was a scene of chaos.

Right now, there was no news on the two of them, one could confirm that they were captured by a Gu Immortal. Whether they could escape or what ordeals they were going through, no one knew.

Compared to his previous life, Ma Hong Yun was much more pitiful in this life.

One could see that even with fortune that rivals heaven, it is not omnipotent.

Luck only provides opportunities, whether one could use them well, that depends on the Gu Master's strength and abilities.

Right now, everyone was still looking for Ma Hong Yun, but no one knew which Gu Immortal had hidden them. The allure of the luck path true inheritance was too great, especially for northern plains' Gu Immortals.

"My Spring Autumn Cicada has the weakness of impairing my own luck, if I can use the luck path true inheritance to fix this flaw, it would be the best method. Since rebirth, I have already suffered many difficulties from bad luck." Fang Yuan sighed in his heart.

Not only was Ma Hong Yun a good target as a valuable treasure, most importantly — during this northern plains trip, Ma Hong Yun was an eyewitness, he was an insider and would likely expose Fang Yuan and the others.

Thus, Ma Hong Yun also posed a death threat to Hei Lou Lan.

Killing Ma Hong Yun was one of the agreements in the Snowy Mountain Alliance.

Entering Lang Ya blessed land again, Fang Yuan did not enter the cloud building's room like last time.

Lang Ya blessed land's unique terrain was that it was situated on vast white cloud soil.

Twelve buildings, at equal lengths apart, were situated on the cloud soil, they were the twelve cloud buildings.

But what Fang Yuan saw was a messy sight.

The fertile cloud soil was full of holes. There was ice forming in some holes, while black smoke was rising in some holes.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng came out of Fang Yuan's immortal aperture, upon seeing this, he said: "A battle had occurred here not long ago. It seems that Lang Ya land spirit was really in trouble."

Fang Yuan did not speak, he only looked at the twelve cloud buildings far away.

These twelve buildings had their respective features, some had immortal cranes flying around them, some had feathermen living in them, some had beautiful auroras, while some had the smell of incense.

But right now, only eight of these twelve buildings were intact, the remaining three were in bad shape, walls were collapsed and structures were crumbling.

"What happened? We are already in Lang Ya blessed land, yet the land spirit has yet to appear?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng frowned, feeling very alert in his heart.

"Let's go in and see first." Fang Yuan pondered.

The two flew over, slowly getting close to the twelve cloud buildings.

"Quickly look, there is a desolate beast corpse there!" After moving for some time, Tai Bai Yun Sheng suddenly pointed at one direction, saying.

Only to see that a huge fish was lying on the cloud soil, not moving.

It had the size of a normal whale, but it looked like a carp. There were bones protruding out of its back, along the spine, extending outwards.

Its scales were blue in color, its eyes were as large as a horse carriage, with some starry radiance in them.

"This is the desolate beast, spinefin star dragonfish." Fang Yuan said.

He knew that Lang Ya land spirit had a beast enslavement Immortal Gu and enslaved twelve desolate beasts, each kept in one of the twelve cloud buildings.

Was this spinefin star dragonfish one of the twelve?

"Oh? Someone came in." In a dark secret room, Lang Ya land spirit opened his eyes, sensing Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

In front of him, there was a Gu Immortal. He was middle aged and had a mighty disposition, his appearance was not that of a normal man, he had black skin and white hair, he was an inkman Gu Immortal.

"What? Another strong foe?" The inkman Gu Immortal heard the land spirit and became nervous.

"Oh, it is that rascal! Pfft, he scared me. No worry, I know this person. Half a year ago, he came here before." After Lang Ya land spirit focused his mind to detect them, he breathed out deeply.

The inkman Gu Immortal raised his brows in surprise, he did not think that there would be other guests coming to Lang Ya blessed land besides himself.

"Since they are friends and not foes, then all is well. It has been three days and three nights since we entered the secret room, in just a moment, we can release one layer of the seals on you. At this time, we cannot be disturbed." The inkman Gu Immortal's heart settled.

"But we cannot let them near the cloud building. Old friend, you might not know this, but that kid is crafty and scheming, he is Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritor, I suffered a loss from him in the past. Let me mobilize the desolate beast and stop him from coming temporarily." Lang Ya land spirit gritted his teeth and said.

"We've been in here for so long, yet Lang Ya land spirit has not appeared yet, it seems something huge happened here! The attack on Lang Ya blessed land was definitely not done by one person. Such a force is not to be trifled with, we should search the battlefield and retreat for now."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was speaking, when suddenly, a large 'golden metallic mountain rock' drilled out of the cloud soil.

The 'cubic rock' moved quickly, blocking the way of the two.

"Desolate beast!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng readied himself to face this enemy.

The desolate beast had no eyes, a large pair of pincers were right in front of it. No one dared to doubt the power of these fearsome weapons.

Furthermore, it had nine pairs of legs, coming out of the cubic rock as they extended.

The crab legs stabbed into the cloud soil, propping the desolate beast's large body up.

At this point, Tai Bai Yun Sheng recognised the origins of this desolate beast: "This is the lord of swamps — swamp crab!"

Fang Yuan snorted, he was very familiar with the swamp crab. After all, when he had just obtained Hu Immortal blessed land, he faced a swamp crab in his tribulation.

Most importantly, that swamp crab had the gruel mud Immortal Gu, causing great destruction to Dang Hun mountain.

In order to save Dang Hun mountain, Fang Yuan had to enter northern plains and attempt to take Tai Bai Yun Sheng's landscape as before Immortal Gu. Now, after braving many dangers, not only did he succeed in saving Dang Hun mountain, he even recruited Tai Bai Yun Sheng to join him, one could say he obtained both the Gu and the Gu Master.

The swamp crab blocked their path, Tai Bai Yun Sheng stopped in his tracks and asked Fang Yuan: "What do we do now?"

Fang Yuan's gaze was locked on the desolate beast, he said one word: "Fight."

"Be careful." Tai Bai Yun Sheng nodded, swiftly retreating, pulling some distance from Fang Yuan. He was a healing Gu Immortal, in most situations, he would not charge forward and take a risk, this was also in line with his usual personality.

Fang Yuan floated in the air, looking at the swamp crab silently. Next, he breathed in deeply, straightened his back and stretched his eight arms.

The muscles on his body bulged, resembling an iron monster. His eyes were blood red, his green face and sharp fangs gave off a ruthless and terrifying aura.

At the next moment, Fang Yuan moved, his body was like a meteor crashing towards the swamp crab.

The swamp crab was huge, but it was unbelievably agile, nine pairs of legs moved quickly, as it dodged sideways.

But Fang Yuan was a flying master, even though it seemed like he would miss, with just a turn, he crashed into the swamp crab's back.

Bam!

With a thunderous sound, the swamp crab was pushed into the ground by Fang Yuan's forceful impact.

His over six meters tall body stood in a crater. This was the damage caused by his attack.

"Tough enough!" Fang Yuan grinned, pulling back four of his right arms.

His fists, without exception, were torn open and showed the white bones inside.

But Fang Yuan had lost his sense of pain, even though his fists were injured, they was healing at an insane speed, in just a few breaths' time, his four right fists recovered completely.

Puff puff!

Two waves of fierce winds approached to assault him.

Fang Yuan's wings opened, as he tread into and flew in the air like lightning, dodging the fierce winds.

Hearing two sharp sounds, Fang Yuan turned around to look, only to see that the swamp crab's huge pincers were bending at an unbelievable angle, towards his back and snapping together.

If Fang Yuan dodged slower, he would've been hit already.

The battle strength of a desolate beast was comparable to a rank six Gu Immortal. Even with the absurd defense of Fang Yuan's heavenly zombie body, he did not want to endure the attack.

"The swamp crab's armor is extraordinarily hard, there is almost no flaws in its defense. I do not have cutting or drilling abilities, I can only break through with pure strength, using power to force my way through is the best method." Fang Yuan's thoughts collided intensely in his mind.

His body continued to rise, as he looked down. In just a few breaths of time, the swamp crab's body was full of crabs.

These crabs were as large as tigers, they were fearless. Some has sharp crab legs, resembling needles. Some had claw like limbs, and were very fast.

This was the special ability of the swamp crab — it could reproduce at any time and place, summoning a crab army that would move according to its will.

"Very good." Fang Yuan's gaze was cold and dark, he breathed in deeply and activated the killer move, myriad self!

With the expenditure of one bead of green grape immortal essence, he activated the core Immortal Gu.

Thereafter, large numbers of Gu worms started activating in a certain pattern.

Fang Yuan's eight fists pounded at the swamp crab below him.

Bam bam bam...

Each fist exploded with a formless fist qi, the shadows of the fists were flying as his punches rained down like a torrential storm!

The swamp crab cried out pitifully, it was being pressed into the ground by the unceasing fist qi.

Thousands of fist qi slammed on the swamp crab's back, causing its hard shell to become deformed. The fist qi that dispersed formed and gathered, becoming one of Fang Yuan's strength path phantoms.

Ten breaths later, an army of strength path phantoms formed on the swamp crab's back.

"This is..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng was shocked, this was the first time he had seen this killer move.

The strength path phantom army surrounded the swamp crab, and the crab army collapsed at once, the swamp crab was unable to endure the attacks and cried out, trying to put up resistance, but it could not prevent its imminent defeat.

No matter how many strength path phantoms it killed, Fang Yuan continued to attack, and more strength path phantoms were produced every moment.

"Ahhhh, my desolate beast! What killer move did this rascal use, I have never seen it, it is actually so strong! This killer move has definitely got to be an immortal killer move!" In the secret room, Lang Ya land spirit could see all that was going on, he lost his cool as he started shouting.

Chapter 662: Inkman King

Lang Ya land spirit felt heartache when he looked at his swamp crab.

The swamp crab was lying down flat on the ground, unable to stand up. Its nine pairs of legs were almost entirely torn to pieces, and even one of the enormous steel pincers at the front was shattered.

Such a battle outcome caused the inkman Gu Immortal and Tai Bai Yun Sheng to feel a chill from the depths of their hearts.

Fang Yuan struck with over ten thousand strength path phantoms, of which over three thousand still remained. He calmly stored the remaining phantoms into his immortal aperture.

These phantoms could only exist for a period of time and beyond that limit, the fist qi would dissipate and the phantoms would disappear along with it. But as long as they could be used, Fang Yuan would not waste even one of them.

Ever since he returned to Hu Immortal blessed land from northern plains, he had been penniless; he did not even have one immortal essence stone, thus he was not able to replenish large numbers of mortal Gu.

From the battle just now, he had already probed: With just the eight armed immortal zombie body, it was hard for him to pose much threat to the heavy armored swamp crab.

The only option thus was to use his killer move, myriad self.

The core of this killer move was a soul path Immortal Gu that Fang Yuan possessed, and so it required green grape immortal essence to be activated.

The situation earlier was not clear, thus Fang Yuan decisively gave up a bead of green grape immortal essence to take control of the situation.

The killer move myriad self was indeed created from the convergence of enslavement and strength path, its might was extraordinary. The swamp crab, which had brought huge trouble to Fang Yuan once before, causing him to use all his strength in order to barely deal with it, could not even raise its head from the beatings of myriad self, it continued to be in a disadvantage with no hopes of freeing itself.

"You rascal, entering my home without a word and also injuring my desolate beast, how will you compensate me?!" Lang Ya land spirit furiously chided Fang Yuan.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was engrossed in looking at this land spirit from behind Fang Yuan.

Lang Ya land spirit was thin with white hair, having a beard that reached his chest and a ruddy face like that of a baby's. He was wearing a loose robe over his whole body and the two sleeves were fluttering in the air. If not for him seething with anger and staring at Fang Yuan with his eyes wide open, his demeanour would no doubt look elegant and sagely.

Fang Yuan was already familiar with Lang Ya land spirit, he stared at the shackles around Lang Ya land spirit, frowning: "You have been sealed, no wonder I could not hear any news of your divine sense in treasure yellow heaven. According to northern plains' time, we have not met for merely more than half a year, how could you end up like this?"

Lang Ya land spirit's eyes opened even wider as he snarkily retorted: "Talk about yourself, how did you become like this? Neither human nor ghost! Advancing to a Gu Immortal and yet degenerating into a zombie, hehe, you should still have plenty of lifespan though."

"Hmph, Lang Ya land spirit, you have lived for so many years yet you don't even know the simplest logic of give and take? Only by giving up one thing can you gain another, if I didn't turn into a zombie, how could I be in front of you again and hold such powerful strength? But you, the longer you lived, the more you regress, now you can't even refine Gu. You are really making your main body lose face." Fang Yuan sneered, intentionally provoking the land spirit.

Lang Ya land spirit's sore spots were prodded and he immediately stamped his foot in anger.

Not long ago, Lang Ya blessed land had suffered an attack from a mysterious force; Lang Ya land spirit was able to repel the invaders but he ended up sealed by a qi path killer move.

Thus, he ended up having to invite his best friend to remove the seals.

Lang Ya land spirit started cursing at Fang Yuan: "You shitty kid, you still have the nerve to talk about me? True Yang Building's fall was definitely caused by you, right?! Hehe, so many people died, two super forces lost their tribe leaders, the whole of northern plains' Gu Immortals are searching for you, the main culprit. You are now everyone's target, your life must be pretty hard now, right!"

The inkman Gu Immortal and Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expressions changed.

The inkman Gu Immortal's pupils shrunk slightly, feeling an intense urge to cover the land spirit's mouth.

But the land spirit had already said everything, it was too late.

'How could you blurt out such a matter? Are you not afraid those two will attack to silence us?!' The inkman Gu Immortal's heart could not help but tremble with fear; these two were actually the people who had turned northern plains on its head and even wrecked Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's arrangements! Too dangerous! The situation was going south!

The next moment, both Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng gazed coldly at the inkman Gu Immortal.

Even if the inkman Gu Immortal had high position and authority normally and had extraordinary strength himself, right now he could feel his heart going cold under the gaze of these two ruthless monsters.

"Lang Ya land spirit, why are you not introducing us to this person?" Fang Yuan chuckled, his voice was so hoarse that it was borderline uncomfortable to hear.

'I can't let Lang Ya land spirit reply, who knows what this loose-lipped guy will say?'

Thus, the inkman Gu Immortal summoned his courage and stood up, greeting: "My name is Mo Tan Sang, I live in inkman city and am the king of northern plains' inkmen."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng raised his brows, he had not expected this person to have such an origin and immediately looked at the Inkman King in another light.

Currently, the five regions were dominated by humans. Variant humans were living while pressured on all sides; many were sold as slaves or raised as pets, their livelihood was rather difficult.

But in northern plains, inkmen had the most favorable status among the variant humans.

Many variant humans had no fixed residence and would have to wander around like vagabonds. But inkmen had established a city in northern plains, which possessed three inkman Gu Immortals.

Mo Tan Sang was the inkman city's king. Under his leadership, the inkmen were able to resist pressure from various forces and withstand the covetous gazes of countless Gu Immortals. It was not easy to maintain the inkmen's survival, it served to show how talented and skilled the Inkman King was.

"Inkman King Mo Tan Sang..." Fang Yuan muttered inwardly.

He had an impression of this name.

In the chaotic war of the five regions during his previous life, the Inkman King took advantage of the lack of attention paid to him due to the human tribes being too busy in their internal conflicts, to grab the opportunity and develop rapidly, greatly expanding the inkman forces.

When northern plains' human forces wanted to suppress him, he actually disregarded his dignity as the king and threw himself to Liu tribe. He took a servant's rite to Liu tribe's supreme elder and became a servant to him.

Liu tribe was one of the super forces, thus the inkman forces were protected. The inkman forces grew stably under this layer of protection.

Later, when Liu tribe weakened, the Inkman King immediately gave up on Liu tribe to collaborate with Ma Hong Yun on equal terms.

Before Fang Yuan self-detonated, the inkmen had hundreds of cities and occupied one-third of northern plains' lands.

From this one could see how talented and insightful the Inkman King Mo Tan Sang was. Not only did he have unique foresight and courage to take resolute actions, he could also bow and submit when necessary; he was not someone who could be belittled.

Fang Yuan lightly praised: "So it is the Inkman King, sure enough, you have a majestic aura beyond that of ordinary people."

"I am not worthy of such high praise." Inkman King quickly replied modestly.

The person before him was the main criminal in destroying Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, he had to be extremely vigilant against such a dangerous person.

He took the initiative to explain: "Lang Ya land spirit and I have been very good friends for many years. In truth, inkman city has always had close relations with Lang Ya blessed land. We in inkman city have some attainment in qi path, and it turns out Lang Ya land spirit was sealed using a qi path method. Thus I hurried over to help. Sir is a dragon who roams the sky, stirring up a storm and causing the whole of northern plains to be in a state of unrest. I cannot help but admire such grandeur. All along, our inkman city has been jointly suppressed by the Huang Jin tribes. Back then, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was even more overboard, demanding inkman cities to offer tribute in terms of countless female inkmen. In a way, you have helped us inkmen take revenge by destroying Imperial Court blessed land. You are also the land spirit's friends, so you are my, Mo Tan Sang's, friends as well. If you have any plans in the future, feel free to visit inkman city."

He was indeed the Inkman King, such outstanding eloquence that completely expressed his goodwill in just one conversation, especially speaking in neither a servile nor overbearing tone, it was extremely hard to come by.

"Who is friends with this rascal?" Lang Ya land spirit shouted in dissatisfaction.

However, he felt happy in the depths of his heart when he heard Fang Yuan praising his friend, and the anger he felt previously had reduced.

Fang Yuan nodded to the Inkman King, replying with deep intent: "If there is an opportunity, I will definitely come to experience life in inkman city."

He then looked at Lang Ya land spirit and continued provoking him without concern: "Land spirit, even if I am not your friend, you should still welcome me and refine a Gu for me. Did you forget I still have one chance left to make you refine Gu! If I want you to refine Gu, you will do it even if you don't want to!"

Lang Ya land spirit could not put up a facade at all, his temper flaring up immediately.

Normally, Gu Immortals would be polite and even flatter him to request him to refine Gu.

When had he ever received heard disrespectful words like Fang Yuan's?

But Fang Yuan was speaking the truth, he still had the final chance to request for Gu refinement. Lang Ya land spirit was Long Hair Ancestor's obsession, and he must abide by the agreement his main body had agreed to back then.

"You damned scoundrel, I am so angry, my anger is going to explode!" Lang Ya land spirit shouted, his face completely red with fury.

But suddenly, he grinned with happiness: "Ahahaha, I am trapped, this qi path seal is too troublesome, there are a total of seventeen or eighteen layers of seals. Just now, Inkman King only unsealed the first layer! Hahaha, I really can't help you refine Gu right now, my hands are tied, this is wonderful!"

He had been bored to death since he was sealed, not being able to do refinement meant his greatest hobby had been taken away.

But right now, he was feeling quite happy about it.

It was all Fang Yuan's fault.

Seeing this weirdo Lang Ya land spirit shouting and laughing like a buffoon, Tai Bai Yun Sheng felt this trip was worth it, his horizons were broadened!

Inkman King was silent, he was the leader of a large force and was not willing to easily offend Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan coughed before speaking solemnly: "Alright, let's talk about serious affairs. Since you can't refine Gu, forget about it. I have another matter for coming over this time, I want to make a transaction with you."

"Transaction, what transaction?" Lang Ya land spirit asked.

Inkman King immediately turned vigilant, Lang Ya land spirit might have high intelligence but his nature was frank, it was hard to say that he wouldn't be cheated. Inkman King was the land spirit's good friend, if Fang Yuan truly was conspiring, he would stand up and expose Fang Yuan's scheme.

"The transaction is simple, you should remember the thing about me being a wisdom path Gu Master, right? I will deduce Immortal Gu recipes for you while you will pay immortal essence stones as remuneration. This is a win-win deal." Fang Yuan replied.

"Deduce Gu recipes?" Lang Ya land spirit opened his eyes wide as he became dazed, but at the next moment he started laughing loudly.

He was swaying back and forth in his laughter, if his hands were not bound, he might have been slapping his thighs together in laughter.

Lang Ya land spirit ridiculed: "Fang Yuan, oh Fang Yuan, you are now a zombie and still think you can deduce Gu recipes? Moreover, Immortal Gu recipes? This old man advises you to get rid of this thought!"

Inkman King, however, said: "An Immortal Gu recipe, even if it is a remnant recipe, has a high price. If we give it to sir to deduce it, but you fail in the process, then wouldn't we be handing you the contents of the Immortal Gu recipe for nothing?"

Lang Ya land spirit was startled to awareness, immediately yelling in rage: "Great, you actually wanted to swindle me of Immortal Gu recipes!"

Fang Yuan had already prepared for this and laughed, opening his monstrous palm to reveal an Immortal Gu: "Look, what is this?"

Chapter 663: Recognising Immortal Gu

At once, everyone's attention was attracted to the Gu worm in Fang Yuan's palm.

The immortal aura of the Gu worm was radiating with the laws of the world, without doubt, it was an Immortal Gu. But no one knew which Immortal Gu it was.

Only Tai Bai Yun Sheng's heart shook, as he remembered what Fang Yuan had revealed to him in the past.

"This Gu, this Gu..." Lang Ya land spirit watched with shining eyes: "I have never seen this Gu before, this is a new Gu."

He jumped in front of Fang Yuan, his nose was only two inches away from the Gu, next he sniffed like smelling a flower.

He screamed: "Ah, this is the aura of luck path, this is a luck path Gu worm. Good lad, you destroyed True Yang Building, but it seems you had many gains."

Fang Yuan immediately mocked: "To think that the grand Lang Ya land spirit would have such shallow knowledge. This is not a new Gu, it had appeared ten thousand years ago. Let me teach you, this Gu's name is Calamity Beckoning, it was invented by a certain generation's fairy of central continent's Spirit Affinity House, Mo Yao."

"Mo Yao?" Inkman King heard this and his eyes shone: "If I remember correctly, this woman is a rare legend in inkman history. She cultivated to rank seven, and had overwhelming charm, even the grand Sword Immortal Bo Qing was attracted to her!"

Inkman King talked with a fanatical expression, like he was speaking of a treasure: "I apologise about my demeanor, but I have been looking up to senior Mo Yao as my role model since youth, thus I am very familiar with her stories."

Fang Yuan found this a little humorous, to think that this Inkman King was a fan of Fairy Mo Yao.

But now was not the time to chit chat with the Inkman King. Fang Yuan used this chance to mock Lang Ya land spirit.

Lang Ya land spirit was so ashamed from his words that his face turned red, he wanted to find a hole to hide himself in.

He grumbled under his breath, but he did not rebuke Fang Yuan. After all, he really did not know this Immortal Gu.

After Fang Yuan made some snide remarks in a mystifying tone for a while, he saw that the time was right and took back calamity beckoning Immortal Gu, fishing out another Immortal Gu.

"Lang Ya land spirit, didn't you say you were well learnt and knowledgeable? I will give you another chance, see what Gu worm this is?'

Lang Ya land spirit stared with wide open eyes, he moved forward to take a closer look.

After a few breaths' time, he took a deep breath, his nervous expression became smug: "Of course I know this Immortal Gu, its name is Cleanse Soul, it is a cultivation assistance type Gu for soul path Gu Immortals. The cultivation of soul path includes strengthening the soul, refining the soul, and pacifying the soul. The best way to strengthen the soul is Dang Hun mountain's guts Gu, the best way to refine the soul is Luo Po valley's bewilderment fog and Luo Po wind, as for pacifying the soul, it would be the pacifying soul soup in Bewitching Lake. This cleanse soul Immortal Gu can refine a Gu Immortal's soul, getting rid of all the impurities. But if it was used excessively, it would get rid of even the essence of their soul."

"Oh? You actually recognise this Gu!" Fang Yuan pretended to be shocked, thinking in his heart: "So this Immortal Gu is called Cleanse Soul, I called it Split Soul in the past, I guess I was wrong."

This cleanse soul Immortal Gu was the core Gu of the killer move myriad self.

The killer move, myriad self, could form strength path phantoms of Fang Yuan, these strength path phantoms had a trace of his soul, thus Fang Yuan could manipulate them freely like an extension of his own body, it was agile and flexible.

But precisely due to this, the killer move myriad self expended Fang Yuan's soul foundation.

Lang Ya land spirit saw Fang Yuan's shock and his smugness intensified on his face.

But Fang Yuan quickly said: "Count yourself lucky, you coincidentally recognised this Immortal Gu."

"Hey, what do you mean luck, this is my strength."

"If you really have strength, how could you not recognise calamity beckoning Immortal Gu?"

"You!"

"Never mind, take a look at this Gu, I'm sure you cannot recognise it."

"Show me, I will definitely know what it is!" Lang Ya land spirit shouted.

Fang Yuan took out another Gu.

Lang Ya land spirit concentrated his attention on analyzing, he laughed a few breaths later: "Haha, this is the cloud path Immortal Gu, Rising Azure Cloud."

"Rising Azure Cloud?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng interjected.

"That's right." Lang Ya land spirit said proudly, shaking his head: "This Gu is a movement type Immortal Gu, it has a long history. Gu Immortals can use it to easily travel through mountains and cross water bodies. But what is most valuable, is that this Gu's ascending and descending speed is extremely fast, it far exceeds most other Gu of the same rank."

"So this Immortal Gu is called Rising Azure Cloud." Fang Yuan thought about it, appearing as if he was not satisfied, he took out another Immortal Gu.

"Land spirit, it seems you might possibly have some skill. Look at this Gu." Fang Yuan said.

"What do you mean might possibly, of course I have skill!" Lang Ya land spirit rebuked, his eyes were shining as he looked at Fang Yuan's palm.

After a few breaths, his expression changed: "Oh, it's you."

"What Gu is this?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng asked again at an appropriate time. At this point, he had already understood Fang Yuan's intention.

Although Fang Yuan had captured these Gu in True Yang Building, he did not know their origins, he had been guessing.

There was no doubt that familiarizing oneself with unknown Immortal Gu was very troublesome.

The most direct method was to consume immortal essence and activate the Immortal Gu, to directly see their effects. But this had some flaws.

Firstly, immortal essence was precious. Secondly, Immortal Gu had huge power, it might cause harm to oneself if used wrongly. For example, calamity beckoning Gu and Spring Autumn Cicada could not be used blindly. Thirdly, some Immortal Gu have very peculiar uses, even if they were activated, they would not show any effect if the target or environment was inappropriate.

Even though wisdom Gu could help Fang Yuan, Fang Yuan could only make deductions based on the information he already had.

Lang Ya land spirit did not suspect a thing, he flaunted his knowledge: "This Immortal Gu is peculiar and vile, it is a one time consumable Gu. Although I have never seen it personally, I have heard about it in historical records, back then I paid close attention due to having a special impression of it. This Gu's name is Woman's Heart. It is different from ordinary Immortal Gu, its refinement and nurturing occur together."

Fang Yuan was immediately intrigued.

Gu worms were classified into nurture, use, and refinement, these three aspects. Generally with the three aspects, although they affected each other, each still stood alone.

An Immortal Gu with nurturing and refinement combined into one, Fang Yuan had never seen any. But Fang Yuan was very familiar with a type of Gu worm that combined use and nurturing, this was the rank five blood guillotine Gu that had a vile reputation.

Then, what exactly was this woman's heart Gu that combined refinement and nurturing?

Fang Yuan was curious, but he could not ask directly. At this point, Tai Bai Yun Sheng cooperated and asked: "It can actually combine nurturing and refinement, this is the first time I've heard of this despite my long life."

Lang Ya land spirit gave Tai Bai Yun Sheng a look: "Lad, you are still young, you have not lived for long enough. The variety of Gu worms is as wide as the sea. The three aspects of nurturing, use, and refinement are extremely vast and profound. As the saying goes: A woman's heart is the deadliest poison. This Immortal Gu, Woman's Heart, is a poison path Immortal Gu, with a lethal poison. To nurture it, you will need the hearts of women. The process of feeding would also be the process of continually refining and promoting the Gu. The more hearts fed to it, the more powerful its poison."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression changed: "It needs the hearts of women? Such evil and cruelty, this is a demonic Gu!"

"Mm, actually, you can use the hearts of female variant humans to replace it, but the effect would be worse than human hearts. To achieve the same toxicity, you will need many more hearts." Lang Ya land spirit recalled.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression was solemn: "Even variant humans are people, they have parents, they have flesh and blood, love and hatred, how can they be sacrificed so easily? Just to feed a demonic Gu?"

Saying this, Tai Bai Yun Sheng looked at Fang Yuan in worry.

Fang Yuan was expressionless, he put away the Immortal Gu Woman's Heart, and took out another Immortal Gu: "Lang Ya land spirit, I admit you have a degree of skill. But this level is still slightly inferior to me. Hahaha, the Immortal Gu in my hand now, there is no way you can guess it!"

Fang Yuan seemed to have complete confidence, Lang Ya land spirit's gaze was immediately attracted to the new Immortal Gu.

"This is also a luck path Immortal Gu." He sniffed with his nose, turning nervous.

But a few breaths later, his nervousness vanished, he breathed out deeply: "I know this Immortal Gu, haha, back then, my main body had seen this Immortal Gu during a discussion about cultivation with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable."

"Oh? Such a coincidence?" Fang Yuan showed a look of disbelief.

"Of course!" Lang Ya land spirit's eyes were burning with fire, Fang Yuan's disbelief made him extremely upset.

To prove himself, he spilled all that he knew: "This Immortal Gu is called Connect Luck. It has a very special use, it can allow a Gu Master's luck to be connected to other people's luck. If one has good luck, it will be shared to the other person. Similarly, if one has bad luck, it will also affect the other party."

"If you have luck inspection Gu, you can inspect the formless luck of other people. If you see a person with good luck, you can use this connect luck Immortal Gu. But this is not the best method to use it, because luck is like a tide, its rises and falls are uncertain. If you do this, you still would want to use another Immortal Gu, Break Luck, in tandem."

"Another better method is to coordinate this with other luck path Immortal Gu, to connect your own luck to the luck of mountains and valleys, to the luck of a long river, or the luck of a blessed land or grotto-heaven, or even the luck of an immemorial desolate beast."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng immediately understood the reasoning behind this, he stated praise: "That's right, famous mountains and valleys have been around for ages, blessed lands and grotto-heavens are unlikely to be destroyed, and immemorial desolate beasts are on par with rank eight Gu Immortals. The luck of these things is much more reliable than humans."

Lang Ya land spirit sighed: "Luck path takes a peculiar direction, while also piercing deeply into the Great Dao of heaven and earth. Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, who first created it, had amazing talent, he was extraordinary. Back then, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable discussed about Dao with my main body for seven days and seven nights, even my main body was full of admiration for him."

Inkman King continued: "In history, the ten venerables were all supreme existences. Even as an inkman, I am full of admiration for them."

He had understood Fang Yuan's intentions since long ago, it was to obtain knowledge about the Immortal Gu from Lang Ya land spirit.

But he did not expose this.

Fang Yuan did not harm Lang Ya land spirit, Inkman King had no need to ruin his tenuous relationship with Fang Yuan for no reason.

Fang Yuan nodded at the Inkman King, before turning to Lang Ya land spirit and saying: "Let's go back to the deal, I am full of sincerity, I had never thought of taking your Immortal Gu recipes for myself. Land spirit, when I deduce the Immortal Gu recipe for you, I will place an Immortal Gu with you as collateral. By then, if I fail to analyze it, but had already seen the Immortal Gu recipe, you can take this Immortal Gu. You will feel assured in this case, right?"

The value of an Immortal Gu far exceeded any Immortal Gu recipe.

Lang Ya land spirit exchanged eye contact with the Inkman King, before shouting: "Rascal, it seems you are very confident in yourself. Okay, this deal is not risky for me at all, in fact, I profit from it. I will say this first, I will give you only three Immortal Gu recipes. It doesn't matter which one it is, but you need to completely deduce an Immortal Gu recipe to count as a success. If you succeed in deducing the recipe of an Immortal Gu, hand it to me and I will pay you the immortal essence stones, as well as another remnant recipe."

"Okay." Fang Yuan did not hesitate, he immediately agreed.

Chapter 664: Bountiful Harvest

After successfully coming to an agreement with Lang Ya land spirit, Fang Yuan breathed out a sigh of relief.

This transaction was simply too crucial, the profits would be the key for Fang Yuan to break free of his current problematic situation.

Although he knew of many ways to earn immortal essence stones from his previous life's memories, these methods needed time and planning, or involved great risk.

The deal with Lang Ya land spirit was the only one with little risk, coupled with high rewards.

After thinking about it for a while, Fang Yuan left the cloud path Immortal Gu, Rising Azure Cloud, in Lang Ya blessed land as the collateral of the deal.

Rising Azure Cloud was a movement type Gu, Fang Yuan did not lack a movement Immortal Gu, he already had Worldly Wave Trace. The latter was suited for water path Gu Immortals, its effect was greater when used in an environment that had rivers, lakes, or the sea. Meanwhile, Rising Azure Cloud's strong point was in ascending and descending, its normal movement speed across places was slower than Worldly Wave Trace.

Fang Yuan only cared about practical use, to him, Worldly Wave Trace was much more useful.

That night in northern plains, Fang Yuan returned to Hu Immortal blessed land alone, while Tai Bai Yun Sheng stayed in Lang Ya blessed land.

Fang Yuan was very satisfied with this trip.

Although he consumed one bead of green grape immortal essence, under that situation, without knowing the real circumstances inside Lang Ya blessed land, he needed to quickly defeat the swamp crab and gain the initiative of the situation.

Immortal essence was indeed precious, but it should be used when needed. Immortal essence that was not used had zero value!

Not mentioning one bead of green grape immortal essence, even if he had to use eight or ten, Fang Yuan would use them without hesitation if needed.

He concluded that this time, he put in little investment, but made huge gains.

Firstly, he took back Fixed Immortal Travel.

The return of Fixed Immortal Travel was an extremely pleasant surprise. With Fixed Immortal Travel, Fang Yuan could cross the regional barriers, he could step into all five regions. Using the advantage of his rebirth, he could set up schemes everywhere, obtaining the biggest benefits.

Even at worst, if Immortal Crane Sect breaks into Hu Immortal blessed land and destroys it, Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng could retreat while bringing along Dang Hun mountain and wisdom Gu.

They could attack if they progressed, and defend if they retreated.

Although Fixed Immortal Travel was a rank six movement Immortal Gu, it gave Fang Yuan the greatest advantage in this situation.

Rising Azure Cloud and Worldly Wave Trace added together could not achieve something like this.

At this point, Fang Yuan felt his pressure reducing.

Secondly, he had formed the Snowy Mountain alliance with Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan.

Hei Lou Lan had the Great Strength True Martial Physique, one of the ten extremes, she had huge potential and once she advances into an immortal, her battle strength would be terrifying.

Fairy Li Shan was a famous character in northern plains, on one hand, she was the third leader of Snowy Mountain blessed land, but on the other hand, she had a wide range of friendly relationships, and had dealings with many of northern plains' righteous path Gu Immortals.

There were scumbags and weirdos among righteous path Gu Immortals, and the demonic path even more so had its outliers. Every conflict originates from benefits, the righteous and demonic paths were not just enemies out to kill each other. They also cooperated, made transactions, and even worked together secretly.

Fairy Li Shan had the mountain pledge Immortal Gu, this Gu was the reason why she was so popular with everyone.

Dong Fang Chang Fan had created an alliance with the righteous forces, he needed mountain pledge Gu. Demonic path Gu Immortals were even more suspicious of each other, such a huge organisation like Snowy Mountain blessed land could be built all because of the foundation of mountain pledge Gu.

Because the alliance created using mountain pledge Gu could not be broken, this was the key to gaining the trust of demonic path Gu Immortals.

Fang Yuan allied with them because on one hand, he could gain powerful assistance, while on the other hand, he could settle his biggest problem of not getting timely updates about information in the world.

Fairy Li Shan had wide connections, it was much easier for her to gain information compared to Fang Yuan.

And thirdly, Fang Yuan obtained the information of four Immortal Gu.

He had snatched them when destroying the formless fists, they were Cleanse Soul, Rising Azure Cloud, Woman's Heart, and Connect Luck.

In terms of value, starting from the lowest, the first would be Rising Azure Cloud. To Fang Yuan, this Gu had the least value, he was exerting its greatest use by leaving with Lang Ya land spirit as collateral.

Poison path Immortal Gu Woman's Heart, a one time expenditure Gu that combined refinement and nurturing, it had slightly greater value. Generally speaking, these one time use Gu had powerful effects, like the Immortal Gu Gruel Mud.

Above Woman's Heart was Immortal Gu Cleanse Soul. Cleanse Soul could refine the soul, its effect was far greater than Fang Yuan's wolf soul Gu. Fang Yuan had guts Gu, it was easy to strengthen his soul. Before he enters Luo Po valley, Immortal Gu Cleanse Soul would be the best replacement..

In addition, Cleanse Soul was the core Gu of the killer move myriad self. This had even greater value.

Fang Yuan made an evaluation, if he did not use the killer move myriad self, his battle strength was lower than ordinary rank six Gu Immortals. But once he used this killer move, his battle strength surged, he would be equivalent to a first rate rank six Gu Immortal.

Of course, compared to Fang Yuan's blood path battle strength in his previous life, he was still weaker.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, he was a demonic path overlord, at the peak of rank six, and was only a step away from rank seven. His battle strength was truly fearsome, he was at the top of rank six, he even had the shocking battle result of winning twice against ordinary rank seven Gu Immortals.

Last was connect luck Immortal Gu.

This luck path Immortal Gu was unexpectedly Fang Yuan's greatest gain! Its value even surpassed Cleanse Soul.

Even though Cleanse Soul was myriad self's core, it was not irreplaceable.

But the importance of connect luck Immortal Gu, to Fang Yuan, was simply unique!

Fang Yuan's first vital Gu was Spring Autumn Cicada. This Immortal Gu was the cause of his rise, without this mystical Gu, he would not have reached this stage. But at the same time, this Gu had always been dragging him down.

Be it the pressure towards his aperture, or Spring Autumn Cicada's weakness — the constantly low luck of the user, it gave huge problems to Fang Yuan, and even resulted in many fatal crises.

If not for Fang Yuan's ability and ruthless personality, coupled with his many methods, ordinary people in his place would have died long ago.

Spring Autumn Cicada was Fang Yuan's trump card, but it was also his greatest flaw.

With connect luck Immortal Gu now, it could resolve Spring Autumn Cicada's luck flaw.

Lang Ya land spirit had provided many uses for the connect luck Immortal Gu, the best way was to use other luck path Immortal Gu along with it, using them together to link the Gu Master's luck to a famous mountain or river, an immemorial desolate beast, or even blessed lands and grotto-heaven. These existences have boundless and long lived luck, they were not easy to destroy.

But Fang Yuan was not going to use this method.

Because he could not, he only had one luck path Immortal Gu, he could not use it with other luck path Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan's method was: To use connect luck Immortal Gu to link his luck with other people's luck.

Lang Ya land spirit had earlier said: A person's luck was like a tide, its rises and falls were uncertain. In connecting your luck to others, you had to be careful, otherwise the user would be dragged down at times. If this was used with break luck Gu, it would expend precious immortal essence, and it would also force the user to be on constant alert.

But this weakness was non-existent to Fang Yuan.

Why?

Because he was someone who was reborn using Spring Autumn Cicada!

He knew who the lucky, famous, or extremely successful people were of this generation, he even knew what their achievements would be, and when their downfalls would occur.

"I can totally use my previous life's memories to find these future important people, and use connect luck Gu to link my luck with them. Since I have Spring Autumn Cicada, my luck will always be abysmal, after connecting our lucks, the one taking advantage will always be me."

Fang Yuan thought about this and recognised the great advantage that Fixed Immortal Travel gave him even more clearly.

If not for Fixed Immortal Travel, he would not be able to freely move between the five regions, where would he have time to travel far and wide to look for those people who were currently still nobodies.

The final gain from this trip were the three Immortal Gu remnant recipes he brought back from Lang Ya blessed land.

These Immortal Gu recipes had very high completion rates, they were ninety percent and above, there was even one piece with ninety-nine percent completion rate!

After resting for a while, Fang Yuan arrived at the underground cave.

Deducing an Immortal Gu recipe had too many elements to consider, the wills created by mortal Gu were definitely insufficient, Fang Yuan had no hesitation, he activated delight in water and mountain Gu.

He decided to do the easy one first, to settle the remnant recipe with ninety-nine percent!

At the same time, in Lang Ya blessed land.

"Lang Ya land spirit, what do you think of my restoration?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's hands were behind his back, he stood before Lang Ya land spirit and the Inkman King.

Inkman King saw the restored cloud soil as amazement shone in his eyes uncontrollably.

Earlier, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had taken the initiative to stay behind, when he had suggested to heal Lang Ya blessed land, he did not see much hope. But to think that Tai Bai Yun Sheng did such a great job, the effect was out of his expectations!

Lang Ya land spirit assessed Tai Bai Yun Sheng for a while, saying: "To think that at such a young age, you are quite impressive. How did you do it?"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng laughed bitterly, he was old and had white hair, to hear someone call him young was a really peculiar and weird experience.

He took out landscape as before Immortal Gu, displaying it before the two of them, and introducing it clearly.

Inkman King praised loudly: "To think that there is such an amazing Immortal Gu. With this Immortal Gu, we can restore the blessed land's terrain and river flow, it can greatly reduce the losses caused by heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities! This Immortal Gu's value is immense!"

Lang Ya land spirit was also interested: "I have heard of this Immortal Gu, it once belonged to Immortal Jiu Hui. Immortal Jiu Hui had inherited a certain true inheritance from Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, not only did he have Landscape as Before, he also had Man as Before. I have not seen this Gu of yours personally! Let me research it, it is bound to give me new inspiration, I will give you five immortal essence stones as compensation."

Lang Ya land spirit had many businesses, he was very rich and did not lack immortal essence stones.

"Five immortal essence stones..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng hesitated before rejecting and shaking his head.

Immortal Gu were one's personal secrets, they should not be exposed easily.

But Tai Bai Yun Sheng, for the sake of his future, learned from Fairy Li Shan and had no choice but to expose landscape as before Immortal Gu. How could he hand this to Lang Ya land spirit? He said he would research, but what if he ruins it during the process?

Seeing that Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not agree, Lang Ya land spirit was very disappointed, but he still footed the bill: "You restored all the cloud soil for me, according to our deal, this is three immortal essence stones."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng waved his hand and rejected: "I will not accept these three immortal essence stones. When Fang Yuan comes to hand in the recipe, give it to him along with his compensation."

Lang Ya land spirit was stunned, before laughing wildly: "What? Don't tell me you believe that the rascal can really succeed and complete the recipe? Hahaha, do you know how many years these recipes have troubled me? Especially that recipe at ninety-nine percent completion rate, even my main body could not finish it!"

Chapter 665: Three 100% Immortal Gu recipes!

"Lang Ya land spirit, isn't this a little inappropriate?" Inkman King glanced at Tai Bai Yun Sheng, as he said this with worry. The other party included the fierce people who wrecked Imperial Court blessed land and toppled Eighty-Eight True Yang Building! Inkman King was very worried Lang Ya blessed land would be harmed if Fang and Tai were angered.

Lang Ya land spirit was extremely frank and as if he had not heard Inkman King's words, he satisfiedly said: "Hmph! That brat is too crafty, he dared to treat this old man in such a vile manner, so I did it on purpose! I am teaching him a lesson to let him understand the principle of respecting the old. Hahaha, what Gu recipe can he deduce? What foundation does he have? He is clearly a strength path immortal zombie, did he think this old man could not see it? Hmph, little Tai Bai has blind confidence in him. If he can deduce the Immortal Gu recipe, this old man will personally crush his medicine grinder and eat it!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not respond, instead looking at the arrogantly laughing Lang Ya land spirit with pity. He really wanted to say: It is not Fang Yuan whom I have confidence in, but the wisdom Gu.

...

Fang Yuan quietly stood within the wisdom light halo.

After a while, he slowly opened his eyes, they were shining with joy.

"Success." He was deeply moved. In a few moments worth of time, he had deduced the first remnant recipe to one hundred percent.

This perfected Gu recipe was the ninety-nine percent remnant recipe.

Fang Yuan gasped in surprise when he looked at this Gu recipe again: "This last step was simply mystical, to think this was a Gu recipe I perfected."

He himself found it incredulous.

Deducing Gu recipes depended on one's foundations and inspirations. If one did not have enough foundation in refinement path, it would be very difficult to deduce Gu recipes. But even Gu Masters with deep foundations would often encounter problems when deducing Gu recipes. They would be stopped at these steps, not able to progress even an inch for years, there were even cases where Gu Masters would not make any progress for decades or even a century.

To break through these barriers would require inspiration.

But inspiration was extremely hard to obtain, it could appear continuously over a short period of time or not even appear once in many years.

Even if they had inspiration, that was only a possibility and it would have to be tested and verified.

If it was successful, that would be true inspiration. If it failed, that would only be an idea, a failed attempt.

"Wisdom Gu's might lies in being able to provide unlimited inspiration to Gu Masters. I am a refinement path master, my foundation is enough and I only lack inspiration." Fang Yuan once again sensed the power of a rank nine Gu.

This was still the case in which he had only stepped inside the wisdom light halo, if there came a day when he truly activated wisdom Gu, who knows what the results would be.

Fang Yuan suppressed the flood of thoughts and examined his mind.

There were still large amounts of joyful will in his mind.

The remnant Gu recipe had been extremely close to completion and had only lacked the final push. Thus, Fang Yuan did not use much joyful will.

He concentrated and began deducing another Gu recipe.

The second Gu recipe was the Immortal Gu remnant recipe with ninety-seven percent completion.

Fang Yuan did not have to consume much joyful will this time around either, only expending one third to cross the barriers that were blocking the completion of the Immortal Gu recipe.

Crossing these barriers meant resolving the greatest troubles, the thinking process could then smoothly progress with everything else being obvious. Fang Yuan could deduce them completely even if he relied only on his own ability.

But at the third Immortal Gu recipe, Fang Yuan encountered slight trouble.

He had to use up three beads of green grape immortal essence in a row before he was able to perfect this Immortal Gu recipe.

The difficulty of this Immortal Gu recipe was quite high; when one problem was solved, another would appear. Thus, even though its completion rate was already as high as ninety-six percent, the amount of green grape immortal essence expended to deduce it was two to three times as much as than the previous two.

But even so, when considering the deal, Fang Yuan profited hugely!

Fang Yuan hurriedly connected to treasure yellow heaven and contacted Lang Ya land spirit with divine sense Gu.

Lang Ya land spirit laughed wildly and was thinking Fang Yuan had made contact to admit defeat. So when Fang Yuan handed him a one hundred percent complete Immortal Gu recipe, he was stunned for a while.

After a few breaths of time, all his attention was absorbed into the contents of the Immortal Gu recipe.

"Amazing, amazing! This barrier could actually be broken in such way. Why didn't I think of it, how could I not have thought about it!" He shouted. Were it not for both his hands being trapped in the qi path seal, he would probably be slapping his thigh fiercely.

The praise suddenly stopped, and an embarrassed expression showed on Lang Ya land spirit's face.

He had not forgotten that a short while ago he had been extremely pessimistic of Fang Yuan's ability. How could he have expected Fang Yuan would hand over a completed Immortal Gu recipe to him not long after?

Lang Ya land spirit felt embarrassed, muttering: "Brat, who could have thought that your line of thought is so weird, you actually hit the target while blindfolded, and wildly deduced this Immortal Gu recipe. Consider it your luck this time, according to our contract, perfecting a rank six Immortal Gu remnant recipe of a ninety percent or over completion rate will be paid with ten immortal essence stones! Should I hand them to you using treasure yellow heaven or will you come personally to take them?"

Transactions in treasure yellow heaven naturally required a fixed service charge. But Fang Yuan would have to use Fixed Immortal Travel if he went to personally receive the payment.

And every activation of Fixed Immortal Travel required one bead of green grape immortal essence, it was a considerable price.

Fang Yuan thought it over, using treasure yellow heaven would mean a cheaper cost, but it was hard to avoid leaving behind some traces which might be deduced by some wisdom path Gu Immortals with harmful intentions.

But personally going to take them would mean too high of a cost, Fang Yuan was somewhat troubled.

Lang Ya blessed land was in northern plains while Hu Immortal blessed land was in central continent. The two were not in the same region so using hole earth Gu was not possible. Only stargate Gu could be used.

"Land spirit, with your personality, you should have stargate Gu there, right?" Fang Yuan asked.

"Hehe, brat, you really understand me." Lang Ya land spirit frankly admitted.

He had obtained stargate Gu's recipe from Fang Yuan. He first refined a set of stargate Gu and gave them to Fang Yuan, refining another set afterwards for his own collection.

Fang Yuan nodded and transmitted his thoughts: "Treasure yellow heaven is not safe, our transaction will be sensed by many and once the frequency of this increases, it will bring us great trouble. Fixed Immortal Travel is convenient but the price to use it is too high. It is better for us to link our two blessed lands and establish a stargate."

"Build a stargate?" Lang Ya land spirit shook his head and refused Fang Yuan's suggestion without consideration, "Brat, I have been deceived many times by you. Building a stargate is not a small thing, any calamity over your side will immediately afterwards be directed here as well. If Lang Ya blessed land is discovered by someone, my life will be difficult!"

Fang Yuan laughed loudly and did not attempt to persuade him, instead handing over the second Immortal Gu recipe.

"You actually completed another one?!" Lang Ya land spirit received a huge shock.

This speed, wasn't it simply too fast?

"This method of resolving the problem is simply marvelous! You actually thought of using this Gu and there is also refinement Gu material like intimate grass, how did you think of them?" Lang Ya land spirit chattered on and exclaimed as he appreciated the wonders of this one hundred percent completed Immortal Gu recipe.

"Hahaha, old man, the new generation replaces the old! You are already old and stay all day in Lang Ya blessed land without knowing the developments in the outside world. Even if you have your best friend, Inkman King, he is an inkman, how could he come across the key aspects of human cultivation? Moreover, who am I?! I am a peerless genius of wisdom path! One day, I will surpass Star Constellation Immortal Venerable." Fang Yuan laughed arrogantly while spouting nonsense.

Lang Ya land spirit was dumbfounded.

He really wanted to retort, but the truth was right in front of his eyes. The two Immortal Gu remnant recipes which had troubled him for countless years were solved so easily by Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan suddenly heaved a sigh: "Sigh, do you know the loneliness of a genius? Since my birth, I knew I was extraordinary, there was no one around who could have an equal conversation with me. Some people even believed I was a monster, they were afraid of my wisdom and envied my talent! I could only hide myself and appear to be like a normal person, it was to the extent that no one could see that I was overflowing with heaven defying talent. Wisdom path seemed to be the path the heaven arranged for me, but from a twist of fate, I ended up becoming a strength path immortal zombie. Tell me, isn't my life full of setbacks, even heaven was envious of my talents!"

Lang Ya land spirit could no longer bear to listen to this, stamping his foot: "Hey brat, don't be so self-important! What is amazing about deducing two Immortal Gu recipes! If you are really a genius, then deduce the final Immortal Gu recipe, only then will this old man admire you."

Fang Yuan was silent.

Lang Ya land spirit raised his head: "Hmph, kid, this old man admits you have some talent. But so what? Even my main body was stumped by that final Immortal Gu recipe. Ponder over it properly for seven to eight years, maybe you will know how profound this world is and how many stars there are in the sky. You will then learn to be humble, ahahaha..."

"You mean, this Immortal Gu recipe?" The corners of Fang Yuan's lips pulled back as he tossed out the third Immortal Gu recipe.

This was simply the final blow!

Lang Ya land spirit's laughter came to an abrupt stop, shortly afterwards, he shouted in shock: "This, what is this? What, what in the world is this?!"

His voice contained a trace of panic.

Fang Yuan heaved a long sigh and said with a slow, sad voice: "I said it earlier, my talents often provokes fear and envy. Sigh, nothing can be done, I am such a genius, I was born this way..."

Lang Ya land spirit's panic this time was no small thing.

He was only formed from an obsession and was not shrewd.

This final Immortal Gu recipe was a huge impact to him.

"You really succeeded in deducing it? Incredible! Incredible! This Immortal Gu recipe can actually be solved like this, your train of thought went in a completely different direction! No wonder even my main body could not deduce it... This old saying has come true: The mountain road twists around every new peak; a glimmer of hope shines at one's darkest hour! The mountain road twists around every new peak; a glimmer of hope shines at one's darkest hour!"

Lang Ya land spirit kept on mumbling to himself, he was at first completely shocked before becoming ecstatic, finally he calmed down, his heart filled with frustration.

This Immortal Gu recipe had been perplexing him all along and even his main body was stumped, unable to take the final crucial step.

Sometimes Lang Ya land spirit even thought that this Immortal Gu recipe was a complete dead end and there was no way for it to be resolved.

He had given it to Fang Yuan to deliberately make things difficult, and had never imagined it would truly be solved.

However, he obtained the complete recipe now.

The problem he and even his main body could not resolve, was solved by Fang Yuan.

His heart could not help but feel frustration and listlessness.

Chapter 666: Huge profit!

"Don't tell me that this kid truly is a wisdom path genius, one rarely seen in a hundred years? No, such ability and wisdom is heaven defying, this talent is not just rarely seen in a hundred years, there might not be one in a thousand years or even ten thousand years!"

When he thought of this, Lang Ya land spirit immediately felt there was some sense in Fang Yuan's repulsive character.

"Right, only a genius like this can have such a repulsive character. Like my main body..." Lang Ya land spirit started to feel Fang Yuan's repulsive character was no longer so disagreeable, and even felt a sense of appreciation for similar talents.

At Hu Immortal blessed land, Fang Yuan was calm and unruffled. He might have become a zombie and his thoughts might have slowed down, but it was still more than enough to bully a land spirit.

If it were possible, Fang Yuan did not want to take such risks. He would rather hand over the Immortal Gu recipes one by one over long intervals, and not directly provide the three Immortal Gu recipes like he was doing now.

This action was too eye-catching, it was sure to attract doubts and suspicions from others.

Lang Ya land spirit was frank and open but he still had a good friend called Inkman King, this variant human was a genuinely formidable character.

But Fang Yuan could do nothing about it, as the situation was forcing him.

He must earn a large number of immortal essence stones in a short period of time and increase his strength, both to break through the current perils he was facing, and also to delay the time before he was exposed.

If he worries over this and that, holding back on releasing the Immortal Gu recipes, who would Fang Yuan cry to if this led to his defeat and death?

Fang Yuan smiled, Lang Ya land spirit had not responded but he knew: these three Immortal Gu recipes were tossed out one by one like three bombs, they had already shaken Lang Ya land spirit's mind. This was a good time to talk about conditions!

Therefore, he spoke: "Lang Ya land spirit, I will speak frankly with you, I need immortal essence stones and you need Immortal Gu recipes, we will be collaborating a lot in the future. Building a stargate will be beneficial to both of us."

"Stargate..." This time, Lang Ya land spirit hesitated and did not immediately refuse.

Fang Yuan displayed his exceptional talent in wisdom path which caused Lang Ya land spirit to have a newfound respect for Fang Yuan. Thus, the land spirit began to pay serious attention to Fang Yuan's suggestion.

Fang Yuan persuaded again: "Land spirit, do you think your Lang Ya blessed land will be safe just because we don't build a stargate? Don't forget, you have already suffered from three waves of attacks, every wave stronger than the previous. No doubt, Lang Ya blessed land's location has already been discovered, you are already being observed by some great force. After we build a stargate, we can even take this collaboration to the next step; at crucial times, I could come to protect you through the stargate."

"Protect me..." Lang Ya land spirit was finally moved.

He thought of the impressive battle scene when Fang Yuan beat down the swamp crab, it was truly a formidable display.

Moreover, these three waves of attacks had completely disrupted Lang Ya blessed land's peaceful environment, creating an enormous sense of danger in Lang Ya land spirit.

Fang Yuan asked at this time: "You haven't sold stargate Gu at treasure yellow heaven, right?"

"Not yet, I have no lack of immortal essence stones." Lang Ya land spirit replied.

Fang Yuan laughed brightly: "This is even better. Stargate Gu is a new innovation, it is not like hole earth Gu which has to be planted on the ground and therefore discovered easily. You would need to activate stargate Gu every time you want to open a stargate, thus it is very hidden. Even if you feel something wrong, you can destroy the stargate Gu in your hands at the crucial moment, won't that work? There is simply no threat in building a stargate."

Fang Yuan talked gliby, his words impacting on the depths of Lang Ya land spirit's heart. Lang Ya land spirit finally agreed: "Alright, we will build a stargate. But let's put the collaboration aside for now, and first handle the transaction of deducing Immortal Gu recipes."

The land spirit added another sentence: "I will be in charge of refining the stargate Gu, I will lend it to you."

With this, he would be in greater control of the situation, after all he still felt a little uneasy.

Over at Hu Immortal blessed land, Fang Yuan exposed the smile of a winner and clenched his eight fists in joy.

Success!

With this, he had attained initial approval of collaboration with Lang Ya land spirit, connecting to Lang Ya blessed land would make future transactions much profitable. Not only could it save some money, it would also give an additional retreat path.

Besides this, Fang Yuan was able to prevent the supply of stargate Gu to treasure yellow heaven's market which could have given huge advantages to other Gu Immortals.

Lang Ya land spirit provided the stargate Gu which also saved Fang Yuan some trouble.

If Lang Ya land spirit could feel safe with this, Fang Yuan was happy to comply.

"I must form a good relationship with Lang Ya land spirit. I won't be cheated by doing transactions with him, and can also earn large amounts of immortal essence stones. As long as I handle this relationship properly and continue to deepen it, who knows, one day Lang Ya land spirit might lend me some Immortal Gu to use." Fang Yuan calculated inwardly.

Lang Ya blessed land contained many Immortal Gu, among them were beast enslavement Immortal Gu and Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus.

By borrowing Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan would be able to save a large expense in nurturing them.

How cost effective was it!

Fang Yuan was taking one step but had already planned the next ten steps. Lang Ya land spirit was also very happy, feeling his luck was truly good for finding a wisdom path genius rarely seen in ten thousand years. All the Immortal Gu remnant recipes in his possession had hopes of being perfected!

Fang Yuan had intended to receive stargate Gu through treasure yellow heaven, but the cautious Lang Ya land spirit refused.

Fang Yuan could only use green grape immortal essence and make a trip to Lang Ya blessed land to take the stargate Gu.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng still remained there as there were still several rivers in the blessed land that he needed to restore.

The round trip, as a result, cost Fang Yuan two green grape immortal essence.

But with this journey, he brought back one stargate Gu, three new Immortal Gu remnant recipes and also thirty immortal essence stones.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng wanted Fang Yuan to take the three immortal essence stones he was being paid, but Fang Yuan refused and left it to Tai Bai Yun Sheng. After all, Tai Bai Yun Sheng also required cultivation resources, the stronger he became, the more help he would be to Fang Yuan compared to three immortal essence stones.

The stargate could not be immediately built — Fang Yuan did not have any more starlight firefly Gu.

Without the starlight from starlight firefly Gu, the two stargates were unable to be activated.

Fang Yuan summarized the transaction this time.

He used a total of five beads of green grape immortal essence to deduce Immortal Gu recipes. When he returned alone from Lang Ya blessed land earlier, he used up one bead of green grape immortal essence. To take one stargate Gu, he had to go to Lang Ya blessed land and return back to Hu Immortal blessed land, consuming two green grape immortal essence beads. He had invested altogether eight beads of green grape immortal essence.

And his gains were a whole thirty immortal essence stones.

"I have only nine green grape immortal essence remaining now." Fang Yuan had formed a middle grade blessed land and the few green grape immortal essence he had obtained were heavily used up in this back and forth trip from northern plains.

However, Fang Yuan was not anxious.

He had become a zombie and his immortal aperture was dead, no longer able to produce green grape immortal essence by itself. But he could extract immortal essence from immortal essence stones and turn them into his own green grape immortal essence.

Back then, First Gen Gu Yue, who had turned into a blood wight, also used primeval stones to recover his primeval essence. The logic between the two was the same, it was only a difference of ranks.

That is to say, Fang Yuan could use up all these thirty immortal essence stones to turn into his own green grape immortal essence. One immortal essence stone could be treated as one bead of green grape immortal essence which meant the amount of his green grape immortal essence had increased to thirty-nine beads!

"But immortal essence stones are worth more than green grape immortal essence, the former is used as currency while the latter can only be used by an individual. Unless necessary, I should not rashly refine these immortal essence stones to green grape immortal essence. Anyway, as long as I can continue transacting with Lang Ya land spirit, I will have more and more immortal essence stones. Now, let's connect to treasure yellow heaven and check."

Fang Yuan was full of confidence when connecting to treasure yellow heaven this time.

The purchasing power of immortal essence stones was extremely strong. Back then, Fang Yuan used one immortal essence stone to buy a myriad wolf king and a wolf group with over thirty thousand wolves.

Thirty immortal essence stones were sufficient to be called a large sum.

In his previous life, Fang Yuan had established the Blood Wing Demon Sect and as a demonic path overlord, the greatest amount of immortal essence stones he had at one time was also no more than sixty-four. Naturally, he spent a lot in his previous life. This number was the result of his expenditure and profits constantly offsetting each other.

Fang Yuan sat down and closed his eyes, sending his consciousness towards his immortal aperture.

The immortal aperture was a scene of deathly stillness, the sky was grey and the ground was black, and the air was filled with a putrid odor.

Mo Yao's will was still imprisoned inside, monitored from time to time by Fang Yuan. The mirror willow planted earlier had already died, becoming a collapsed pile of rotten wood on the ground.

With a shift of Fang Yuan's mind, a new connecting heaven Gu fluttered up to the air in his immortal aperture and formed a passage to treasure yellow heaven.

Fang Yuan then activated divine sense Gu, forming a continuous stream of divine sense which followed the passage created by connecting heaven Gu and entered treasure yellow heaven.

He was now an immortal zombie, no longer needing the help of Little Hu Immortal, and could make transactions himself.

Treasure yellow heaven was still the same, the vast space rippling with lemon-like yellow light. There were no mountains, rivers or forests, and also no birds, beasts, insects or fish, there was not even a sky or ground, the only things here were was all sorts of treasures and goods.

Gu worms, Gu recipes, killer moves, beast groups, variant humans, vegetation, ore veins, soil, water, fine wine and all sorts of goods. Each of them quietly floated in air, releasing all sorts of colors, giving off large or small treasure light.

The brighter and larger the treasure light was, the more the good was worth. But treasure light was only an initial estimation, one might not be able to infer from the treasure light if the item was tampered by the Gu Immortals or not.

This was the largest exchange market among the five regions' Gu Immortals, it allowed for bargaining, while taking a fixed service charge. This also tested the Gu Immortal's discernment skills; if they bought counterfeit goods, they could only blame their bad luck as treasure yellow heaven would not be liable for any loss.

Fang Yuan wanted to buy starlight firefly Gu first.

This type of Gu worm emitted pure azure starlight, it was a prerequisite for activating a stargate.

His divine sense searched around and soon found a large group of starlight firefly Gu, there were over one thousand.

Fang Yuan was familiar with the seller, it was Star Lord Wan Xiang.

Star Lord Wan Xiang seemed to be star path Gu Immortal; he not only sold starlight firefly Gu, but also star dart Gu, stellar fire Gu, falling meteor Gu, star river Gu and so on.

It was obvious that Star Lord Wan Xiang's blessed land produced star path mortal Gu and he sold these Gu worms to generate revenue.

Even Gu Immortals who did not cultivate star path would often buy some star path Gu worms for refining, researching killer moves or other purposes.

Chapter 667: Eight Arm Immortal, Spring Star Rain

"How much are you selling this group of starlight firefly Gu for?" Fang Yuan's divine sense sent over.

"How may I address you, sir, and how many starlight firefly Gu do you need?" Although Star Lord Wan Xiang was not around, he left behind a will near his goods.

But this will could be seen to have a great appearance, it was dazzling like the stars, extremely appealing to the eyes. Fang Yuan's wisdom path attainment was low, he did not recognize its origins.

"You can call me Eight Arm Immortal, I want to buy this entire group of starlight firefly Gu." Fang Yuan transmitted.

Fang Yuan was using his own blessed land to connect to treasure yellow heaven, and he had also changed his divine sense Gu and connecting heaven Gu, thus Star Lord Wan Xiang did not realise that Fang Yuan was the former 'Fox Immortal', he thought Fang Yuan was a stranger.

But listening to Fang Yuan's tone, he seemed like a big spending customer, thus Star Lord Wan Xiang's will immediately became enthusiastic: "Starlight firefly Gu is an olden antiquity Gu worm, now it is almost extinct. My starlight firefly Gu are in excellent condition, and I have over a thousand and two hundred of them. How about this, I will sell them to you at a price of four immortal essence stones."

Fang Yuan laughed: "You're trying to scam me, don't think I am unaware of the normal selling price. I was introduced to you by someone, thus I came here. You are not the only one selling starlight firefly Gu, there is still Fairy Yao Guang and Di Yuan, I can get the starlight firefly Gu from them as well."

Fang Yuan had once instructed Little Hu Immortal to deal with all three of these Gu Immortals. Not only did he buy over a hundred thousand starlight fireflies, as well as their food, star fragment grass, he also bought the experiences of the three of them in planting star fragment grass, he spent a lot.

Star Lord Wan Xiang's will was slightly startled, he now knew Fang Yuan was well aware of the market rate, his words changed: "Hehehe, I was kidding earlier, don't take it seriously Sir Eight Arm Immortal."

Fang Yuan interrupted him, saying: "I will pay two immortal essence stones to buy a thousand and five hundred starlight firefly Gu."

Star Lord Wan Xiang immediately rejected this, saying: "Sir, this is simply too low, I cannot sell it at this price."

After some bargaining, both of them took a step back, using three immortal essence stones, he obtained one thousand and two hundred starlight firefly Gu.

After buying the starlight firefly Gu, he did not leave, instead he asked: "Do you sell any star path killer moves?"

"Could it be that sir is also a star path Gu Immortal? Hehehe, of course I sell them, take a look. I have three star path killer moves here."

Fang Yuan started browsing.

The first star path killer move was called 'dazzling star armor', it needed large numbers of starlight Gu, a few bane star Gu, several star shield Gu and so on to be activated. This was a defensive killer move, once used, a full body armor would form on the Gu Immortal's body, shining like starlight.

The second killer move was called 'spring star rain'. It needed large numbers of star rain Gu, small numbers of spring wind Gu, some star shoot Gu and others, once used, it would form a jade colored rain, drizzling non stop for three days and three nights. The rain would be rich like oil, it could provide nutrients to crops and greatly increase productivity. This killer move was used to nurture plants, and manage the blessed land.

The third was called 'spiral drill star spear'. Like the name implied, it was an offensive killer move. It needed small numbers of spiral bone spear Gu, several star river Gu, countless star dart Gu, and large numbers of shooting star Gu.

These killer moves' details were very interesting.

The numbers of Gu worms were usually classified into large numbers, several, some, and a few, vague terms like these without actual real numbers. At the same time, the ways to construct these killer moves were also not specified, including the sequences of activating the Gu worms, as well as the relationships between different Gu worms.

Only the general statuses of the killer moves were mentioned, like what rank five Gu were needed, and what effects the killer moves had.

Only after the killer moves were bought would their details be clearly stated.

Star Lord Wan Xiang spoke at an appropriate time: "Killer move dazzling star armor is sold at half an immortal essence stone. Spring star rain was created by my main body personally, only a few Gu Immortals have bought it now, thus the value is slightly higher at one and a half immortal essence stones. Spiral drill star spear costs one immortal essence stone."

Killer moves were priced according to their rarity, flaws, strength and power, backlash, whether they can be easily countered, and the conditions of the Gu worms that compose the killer move. But they had one common point, they were usually not cheap.

In treasure yellow heaven, ordinary mortal killer moves were priced higher than mortal Gu recipes of the same rank. But at rank six and above, the price of immortal killer moves were far less than Immortal Gu recipes.

Dazzling star armor, Fang Yuan knew this killer move even though he was not a star path Gu Immortal, it was extremely common. Half an immortal essence stone was too expensive.

Fang Yuan had planned to buy a star path offensive killer move, he remembered a mortal killer move called icy stardust. This killer move had a wide range, the star path Gu worms that were used in it were common, and it was also very effective in dealing with enemies. The stardust had defense piercing ability, and even if it could not break the defense, it would stick to enemies and emit frost energy that would slow them down.

As for Star Lord Wan Xiang's spiral drill star spear, Fang Yuan had not heard of it.

This meant that this offensive killer move's value was not high.

In the five hundred years of Fang Yuan's previous life, during the chaotic five regions war, the war ruined old and inefficient systems, causing the birth of many new inventions.

Fang Yuan did not remember spiral drill star spear, that meant it was not outstanding, it had been out of use since long ago back then. A killer move that was out of use definitely had many weakness.

But the spring star rain killer move made Fang Yuan's eyes shine.

This was a surprising find.

Fang Yuan thought of the star fragment grass, it was the food of the starlight fireflies, as well as their home. The stronger and larger the starlight fireflies, the more starlight firefly Gu could emerge from them. Fang Yuan's desire towards starlight firefly Gu was going to persist for a long time.

This, he needed this killer move.

Fang Yuan looked over this spring star rain killer move another two times.

He noticed a problem.

The Gu worms that made up this spring star rain had one star path Gu worm called star shoot Gu, it was a consumable Gu.

Fang Yuan had never heard of this Gu, this was the first time he had heard of it.

Fang Yuan thought about it and realized: This was Star Lord Wan Xiang's ploy.

After Gu Immortals bought the killer move, spring star rain, every time they wanted to use it, they would need to expend star shoot Gu. Meanwhile, only Star Lord Wan Xiang sold this star shoot Gu.

Star Lord Wan Xiang wanted to turn this one time killer move purchase into a continuous trade.

Fang Yuan probed and asked: "I will offer two immortal essence stones for your spring star rain killer move and the star shoot Gu's recipe."

Star shoot Gu was only rank three, such a mortal Gu recipe was not worth half an immortal essence stone, this price was extremely high. But as expected, Star Lord Wan Xiang rejected him without hesitation. His explanation was that this star shoot Gu was naturally formed in his blessed land, there was no recipe.

This was a really good excuse.

Some blessed lands, if managed well, due to the peculiarity of the environment, would give birth to new Gu.

Not only can Gu Immortals refine and create new Gu worms, nature could do the same.

Fang Yuan knew that this was very likely to be an excuse, but he could not request to enter Star Lord Wan Xiang's blessed land to check.

The blessed land was the Gu Immortal's headquarters, it involved their most private matters. Only if they had a really good relationship and trusted each other deeply would they invite another Gu Immortal into the blessed land.

Fang Yuan saw that Star Lord Wan Xiang was unwilling, thus he suggested: "Alright, I will pay two immortal essence stones to buy spring star rain and dazzling star armor, these two killer moves along with some star shoot Gu. I want enough star shoot Gu to activate spring star rain ten times."

Star Lord Wan Xiang heard this and shook his head: "The expenditure of star shoot Gu for six uses of the killer move would be worth half an immortal essence stone. Sir is only offering two immortal essence stones, yet I have to provide dazzling star armor as well. This is a loss for me, I will not do it."

Fang Yuan snickered: "Star shoot Gu is only a rank three mortal Gu, each activation only uses about five hundred at most. Activating the killer move six times would consume three to four thousand of them, you are selling that for half an immortal essence stone?"

"Sir might not know, star shoot Gu is naturally created in my blessed land, its production is very slow. It cannot be bought outside because it is a unique product of my Myriad Star blessed land." Star Lord Wan Xiang was very courteous, but his underlying meaning was, buy it if you want to, but if you do not buy it, you will not find it elsewhere.

He had the confidence of dominating the market of this Gu.

Fang Yuan laughed, continuing to bargain, while the other party refused to relent.

During this process, he realized that in the other party's mind, dazzling star armor's value was still very high.

"It seems that before the war of the five regions, dazzling star armor had not been spread by the respective forces, thus this killer move's value is still very high."

War was a very efficient method of interaction.

Especially in this world.

During peacetime, primeval stones, immortal essence stones, all these had great value and could not become widely used currency, the economy could not prosper.

But during times of war, battle merits, sect contribution points, all these replaced primeval stones and immortal essence stones as currency, they pushed for the development of all aspects of the economy.

After realizing this, Fang Yuan stopped being forceful. He used two immortal essence stones to buy spring star rain and enough star shoot Gu to activate the killer move ten times.

After completing this transaction, Fang Yuan continued to search in treasure yellow heaven.

He found out that in treasure yellow heaven, Gu Immortals had increased air bubble fish's price up to at least ten times that of before.

Fang Yuan investigated for a bit and realized that the situation was the same as in his memories. During the end of last year, two Gu Immortals had fought above air bubble sea, causing intense poison to spread in the sea, turning it into a death zone.

Rare goods were more expensive, with the production of air bubble fish falling drastically, the price naturally shot up.

"The five regions have regional walls that isolate one another, this causes them to have their own independent events, and they barely influence one another. Since rebirth, I have affected southern border, northern plains and central continent. Among them, northern plains' influence was the largest, it is now a huge mess. Second was central continent, followed by southern border, after all, what I changed in southern border were only events at the mortal level. As for western desert and eastern sea, they are still the same."

Using Spring Autumn Cicada, Fang Yuan learnt about the inertia of the river of time as well as the butterfly effect. This sort of lack of change and change interweave together, it was evident that Fang Yuan's understanding towards this world's law of time was becoming deeper.

As for air bubble fish, Fang Yuan remembered that during the five regions war, this fish group would be extremely popular among Gu Immortals, the price would be even higher than now.

That was because an air bubble fish group could boost the rate of mortal Gu appearing in insect groups.

Chapter 668: Little Immortal Xing Luo

During peacetime, Gu Immortals raised Gu, their demand to purchase large quantities of mortal Gu was not high. Purchasing was a secondary option, in most cases, the primary method was the blessed land's own production. The time flow was different in blessed lands compared to the outside world, one day in the outside world was many days inside the blessed land. One year outside would mean many years in a blessed land, while each year, there would be a certain output harvested. Gu Immortals would normally not choose air bubble fish, because the price was too high, they would rather simply wait for some time.

But during wartime, when Gu Immortals frequently fought against each other, they would avoid using their Immortal Gu trump cards often, mortal Gu would be the common method of attacking, and their expenditure would be huge. Thus, air bubble fish became a sought after commodity among all Gu Immortals during the five regions war.

In fact, Fang Yuan had once bought air bubble fish to increase the production of his starlight firefly Gu.

But unfortunately, towards the end of his northern plains trip, he lacked money, thus he had to sell almost all of his wolf group, fox group, and large numbers of air bubble fish and hairy men.

Fang Yuan had a chance to profit from air bubble fish, but life was full of unexpected changes, because he sold them too soon, he made a loss instead.

Right now in Hu Immortal blessed land, there were very few air bubble fish.

"I still have to buy air bubble fish, but not now. In a few years, air bubble sea would be repaired, and the price of air bubble fish will be lower. By then, I will invest some immortal essence stones and buy a huge group of them. Maybe I should breed these air bubble fish in large numbers, so that during the five regions war, I can make a huge profit..."

Fang Yuan had just bought over a thousand starlight firefly Gu, they could last him for a long time, he was not in need of air bubble fish to boost their production.

"Are you Little Immortal Xing Luo?" A moment later, Fang Yuan found his target.

Coincidentally, his target was also looking at yellow treasure heaven.

"That would be me. Senior, what would you like to buy? The price is negotiable." Little Immortal Xing Luo's divine sense transmitted, it was quite enthusiastic, even as much as having a tone of flattery.

Fang Yuan looked, the goods she was selling were not only small in quantity, they were very common, almost nobody would pay attention to her, she was evidently quite poor.

She was indeed a Gu Immortal, but not all Gu Immortals were wealthy. Battle, refining Gu, research, undergoing tribulation, all these would greatly expend the Gu Immortal's foundation and wealth.

Fang Yuan knew from his memories: This Little Immortal Xing Luo was a lone cultivator, a newly advanced female Gu Immortal with weak foundations, she was at the toughest part of her career in starting her trading.

Little Immortal Xing Luo was a huge figure in the mortal realm, she would be revered and respected by mortals. But in treasure yellow heaven, among the many Gu Immortals, she was not outstanding at all.

"But who would know, during the five regions war, this Little Immortal Xing Luo would starting shining brightly, using her killer move icy stardust to quickly accumulate wealth from battle, becoming quite the famous figure later on."

Fang Yuan sighed and admired the mystical powers of time and destiny.

According to the prophecy of the three venerables, the five regions war was the start of the great era, when this generation's Great Dream Immortal Venerable would be born.

The great era where each rank nine Gu Immortal was born had a common point, that was during the chaotic battles, large numbers of new Gu Immortals would rise up.

The new replaces the old, the waves of an era would cause brilliantly shining ripples. Among paths, forces, individuals, they would collide and interact, causing the way of Gu to develop at a rapid pace, it would be an era of change.

Fang Yuan was one of them.

He started off with blood path, becoming a central continent Gu Immortal. But unfortunately, he had only experienced the first half of this new era before he had to use Spring Autumn Cicada to self-detonate.

"Do you sell killer moves?" Putting his mood aside, Fang Yuan asked Little Immortal Xing Luo.

"Mm, I have one killer move here." Little Immortal Xing Luo was a bit embarrassed: "This is an ice path killer move that I obtained coincidentally, it is called icy yarn. Its price is half an immortal essence stone, this is the lowest price for a rank five killer move." Her last sentence showed her fear of Fang Yuan suppressing the price.

Fang Yuan took a look at the content, humming in discontent: "This icy yarn killer move needs so many rank five Gu, and the defense is a wide range defensive effect..."

To use large numbers of rank five Gu at once, the user had to be a Gu Immortal, mortals have limited primeval essence and could not do that in most cases.

A wide area defense meant that the defensive strength would be lower than a single target defensive killer move. Meanwhile, Gu Immortals often fought alone, unless they were enslavement path Gu Immortals. But enslavement path Gu Immortals had their own enslavement path defensive methods, why would they choose an ice path killer move?

Little Immortal Xing Luo laughed bitterly in her heart, Fang Yuan hit the nail on the head, because of these reasons, the killer move icy yarn was not easy to sell.

But Little Immortal Xing Luo had no choice, she had limited goods in her possession, and she was a lone cultivator, she needed huge amounts of resources to kickstart her cultivation.

Although she became a Gu Immortal, she was left penniless after the tribulation, most of her Gu worms were destroyed. She had made an elaborate development plan, she wanted to plant a vast number of shiver trees in her blessed land. Her blessed land's environment was very suitable to grow shiver trees, but she lacked the most crucial start up fund.

She had billions of primeval stones in her possession, but not a single immortal essence stone.

The sellers of shiver tree seeds numbered in only a few people, most of them wanted specific items for trade, or immortal essence stones. They had no need for the stuff that Little Immortal Xing Luo had.

Hearing Fang Yuan say that, Little Immortal Xing Luo's heart lost all hope.

After the last few months, she had gotten used to disappointment.

But the next moment, Fang Yuan said: "I am researching star path killer moves recently, I am a little interested in this icy yarn killer move. But half an immortal essence stone is too expensive! If you have any innovative small killer move, add it in and I might buy this for half an immortal essence stone."

"Innovative small killer move?" Little Immortal Xing Luo's hopes were reignited, she thought about her own star path killer move 'six-nine stardust'.

'Six-nine stardust' was her personal creation, it used six rank three Gu and nine rank four Gu, but could unleash the attack power of a rank five Gu.

She had once been extremely proud of it, but soon her horizons broadened, and she understood that there was a mountain above a mountain, a man above another man, she became more modest.

Little Immortal Xing Luo only hesitated for a moment, her desire towards immortal essence stones had won her over.

"Junior has a small killer move, but I'm afraid it might be useless to senior." She said carefully.

Fang Yuan's heart jumped, but his tone was still very calm: "Oh? Tell me about it."

After seeing the six-nine stardust killer move, Fang Yuan held in his joy and evaluated: "Mm, this killer move is barely acceptable, who knows, it might bring me some inspiration. Well, since my mood is great today, I'll take care of a newbie like you. Hahaha, this is half an immortal essence stone!"

"I finally have half a piece, I'm just half short!" Little Immortal Xing Luo was overjoyed, when they parted, her tone was full of well wishes for Fang Yuan.

Afterwards, Fang Yuan spent another two immortal essence stones, buying large amounts of Gu refinement material and mortal Gu worms.

After spending another two stones, he bought a group of elderly hairy men.

Hairy men were almost always the most expensive among slaves.

These hairy men, although they were old and would die in a few years, were very experienced in Gu refinement.

Fang Yuan had intended to refine a few sets of stargate Gu, but this Gu's success rate was very low, back then, even though Lang Ya land spirit refined it himself, he still failed many times. If Fang Yuan tried, it would waste a huge amount of his time, he was going to let these old hairy men refine it for him.

Central Continent, Immortal Crane Sect, Fu Hu blessed land.

Fang Zheng had a solemn expression as he stepped into the tunnel.

The tunnel was huge and wide, every one hundred steps, there would be an elite rockman guard, the defense was like an iron fortress.

These rockmen were all trained by the blessed land's owner, all of them had at least rank four battle strength and were skilled in earth path Gu worms.

Every one thousand steps, there would be a huge rockman, his size would be at least three times that of a normal rockman. Even in such a wide tunnel, they could only squat down on the ground.

But rockmen were born to dig tunnels and live underground, these rockmen did not feel any discomfort.

Every time Fang Zheng walked in this tunnel, he would feel apprehensive. Especially when he could feel the rank five Gu Master aura permeating from these huge rockmen.

"Our Immortal Crane Sect's strength is simply too great! If these rank five rockmen were all brought outside, I'm afraid all the other sects would be shocked." While he passed a huge rockman, Fang Zheng muttered to the spirit incubating flea.

Lord Sky Crane, who was inside the spirit incubating flea, said: "Not really. Which sect would not have their trump cards and foundation? Especially the other nine great ancient sects, they are no weaker than us. But the current owner of Fu Hu blessed land is the third supreme elder of our sect, Lord Tiger Demon. The rockman slaves that he nurtures are the best in central continent! Even in treasure yellow heaven he has huge influence, his wealth and abilities are not something us mortals can begin to imagine."

Fang Zheng's heart had a longing feeling: "What sort of realm is Gu Immortal, they can actually rear so many rockmen, this is truly amazing!"

Lord Sky Crane replied: "Each Gu Immortal is an elite of the elites, an absolute genius, a dragon among men, they all have great opportunities and chance encounters. They have all cultivated step by step from a mortal identity, Fang Zheng, you are rank five now, maybe one day, you will become a Gu Immortal!"

Fang Zheng shook his head continuously: "Master, I know my limits. My rank five cultivation was mostly due to the sect's relic Gu. The sect is nurturing me with all its effort, using the resources on me. My rank five cultivation cannot compare to you, master, who cultivated step by step. But now, I think that rank five is not something rare, look at this tunnel, there are at least thirty huge rockmen."

"Fang Zheng, it is good that you feel indebted to Immortal Crane Sect's generosity towards nurturing you. But do not put yourself down, man is the spirit of all beings, although variant humans call themselves humans, these rockmen might look strong and brave, but in one on one battles, they are unable to compare to the rank five Gu Masters in our sect, what they specialize in are group battles." Lord Sky Crane laughed.

"Is that so?"

"Lord Sky Crane said: "These rockmen are very stupid, it was because they encountered a rich master that they could have such accomplishments. Do you think these rockmen can compare to the elders in our sect? If I was still alive, I could deal with more than ten of them at once. Alright, we are at the blood pool."

Fang Zheng heard the words 'blood pool' and his muscles contracted involuntarily.

He pushed the door in front of him, entering a cave.

Chapter 669: He Feng Yang’s scheme

This cave was as large as a plaza; blood colored light filled the cave along with a dense bloody odor. In the center of the cave, a round hole had been dug out, inside of which blood gurgled and emitted hot air.

Fang Zheng took a deep breath before taking off his clothes in a familiar fashion, when naked he then entered the blood pool, immediately taking large gaping breaths due to the scalding blood.

He soon adapted to the temperature of the blood and stood still at the center of the blood pool. The blood pool reached up to his waist, revealing his chest and most of his arms.

"Begin. Do it one by one, don't be anxious. First is iron blood Gu." Lord Sky Crane reminded.

Fang Zheng slowly closed his eyes and activated iron blood Gu as instructed.

Immediately, the Gu worm's power started transforming his blood. His red blood began to darken and become denser, the blood flow also became extremely slow.

As a result, Fang Zheng's fair skin also darkened.

"Maintain iron blood Gu, activate blood blade Gu." Lord Sky Crane said again.

Fang Zheng activated blood blade Gu; his body shuddered, his skin burst open forming over a hundred wounds from which large numbers of blood blades shot out - they were all pitch black iron-blood blades!

Shortly afterwards, blood like molten iron slowly flowed out of the wounds.

Fang Zheng had a cold expression, he did not feel any pain, instead, intense pleasure attacked his mind. This was the effect of iron blood Gu, it could turn pain to pleasure and help the Gu Master to adapt to battles, even a weak Gu Master could turn into a warrior addicted to battle.

This was one of the achievements of Immortal Crane Sect from years of researching blood path.

This blood slowly flowed into the bright red blood pool, dying the nearby area around Fang Zheng black.

"It is the crucial step now, use blood merge Gu." Lord Sky Crane reminded.

Fang Zheng gritted his teeth as he activated blood merge Gu.

Immediately, under the effect of the Gu worm, the more than one hundred wounds on his body burst out with an intense suction force. The surrounding blood was being absorbed without pause.

"Ahh...." Fang Zheng groaned softly, the intense pain had turned into intense pleasure. He gritted his teeth hard, his body trembling nonstop.

As large amounts of blood were absorbed, his body inflated, turning into an abnormal fatty. His body was over three times the size of his original self. His skin burst open and the thick, snake-like veins twisted around in his body.

The elegant and handsome young master had transformed into a nauseating, ugly monster.

"Don't forget your goal, you need to resist this pleasure. Fang Zheng, activate failed blood demon flower Gu!" Lord Sky Crane was monitoring Fang Zheng's situation and hurriedly reminded him.

The words 'failed blood demon flower Gu' shook Fang Zheng's mind and he was barely able to get past the intense pleasure, gasping as he activated failed blood demon flower Gu.

Fang Zheng tightly clenched his fists, a large amount of blood in his body was rapidly being corrupted. Under the effect of the Gu worm, vines started growing out of his blood.

These thin vines pierced Fang Zheng's skin and soon coiled around his body.

Flower buds started growing out of the vines and quickly blossomed, turning into pretty blue flowers resembling chrysanthemums.

"Urghh—! Fang Zheng tightly gritted his teeth, groaning softly in pain. His face was pale, his whole body was like soil with many demonic flowers growing forcibly on him. This intense pain was ten times more terrifying than a woman giving birth!

Even iron blood Gu's effect was not able to resist this kind of pain.

Fang Zheng almost shattered his white teeth from the pain. His face turned pale white and blue veins popped up on his forehead, making him look malevolent and terrifying.

"Your blood is boiling, your organs and your body will be burned by your own blood if this goes on. Use cold blood Gu quickly." Lord Sky Crane reminded nervously.

Fang Zheng activated cold blood Gu with great difficulty.

His blood quickly cooled down till he was shivering from the cold; he was finally out of the deadly crisis.

"That will do, demon flowers will greatly increase the effects of your blood path Gu worms. You are just a step away from success, use blood sense Gu!" Lord Sky Crane said with a hurried tone.

"Blood sense..." Fang Zheng lowered his head, his gaze had turned blurry from the pain. From the many drills he had done before, he was finally able to persist and activate this blood path investigative Gu worm.

Several breaths later, Fang Zheng spoke: "I... I can sense... underground, southeast, distance is five to six thousand steps."

"Great, you did it again! You are on the verge of success, it is the final step, use blood scar Gu to mark the position."

"Arghhh..." Fang Zheng started to shout unconsciously at this time. His gaze was completely blurry, the weakness caused his body to be on the verge of collapse. He exerted all his strength to extract all the potential he had to activate blood scar Gu.

He was delirious, there was still enough primeval essence in his rank five aperture but he could only mobilize a small portion. The primeval essence was like a small creek flowing slowly into blood scar Gu.

However, blood scar Gu had extremely large demand for primeval essence; Fang Zheng could only persist for eight breaths of time before he finally collapsed, falling down into the blood pool, unconscious.

...

An incense burner was letting out wisps of smoke, this quiet room had no windows and was extremely dim.

He Feng Yang was wearing a white robe with a black belt, sitting on a meditation mat with wide sleeves.

He looked young and mild like jade. His dark green brows were sharp and long, reaching up to his waist. At this moment, his serene and deep eyes were staring at the spirit incubating flea in front of him.

The spirit incubating flea was floating in the air, and Lord Sky Crane's soul was reporting the results of Fang Zheng's training.

He Feng Yang said with a dissatisfied tone: "Sure enough, despite letting him live in Fu Hu blessed for eight years and also giving him many relic Gu to become a rank five Gu Master in a short period of time, he still can't achieve a simple thing like simultaneously activating six to seven Gu worms."

Lord Sky Crane considered his words before speaking: "Fang Zheng is young, he is still lacking in the basics of multitasking. But this subordinate feels he is a very hard worker and he has made large progress rapidly. Recalling the first attempt, he only lasted a breath of time after activating blood merge Gu before he fainted."

"Therefore I added iron blood Gu, the result was that in the second try, the pleasure was too much for him, the blood flowed out wantonly till he fainted. He lasted for three breaths of time." He Feng Yang interrupted Lord Sky Crane in displeasure.

Lord Sky Crane quickly said: "Lord Supreme Elder, truthfully speaking, even this subordinate would find it hard to multitask under such intense pain and pleasure. Fang Zheng is not far from success, he was able to persist for eight breaths of time this time. One needs to last for ten breaths of time to activate blood scar Gu successfully. And he is only lacking the last two breaths of time. As long as we can train a few more times and allow a little more time, we can..."

"Enough! How much more? You still want to train more? Time, time, just hear yourself, how much time has been wasted in your plan? How long? Years! There is still no improvement, Dang Hun mountain is still not in our hands. Don't you know how many dissatisfied voices are there in the sect, how many disciples are requesting the higher ups to open the exchange of guts Gu?"

"Subordinate is incompetent and even implicated Lord Supreme Elder, I have committed a heinous sin!" Lord Sky Crane begged for mercy when he saw He Feng Yang become furious.

He Feng Yang took some deep breaths before waving his sleeve: "Leave now, there is only a month before the sect convention. Before I go to the sect convention, I want to hear the good news of your training succeeding, and that we can start our plan to capture Hu Immortal blessed land!"

"But lord, a month is too short, Fang Zheng will not be able to endure excessive training. We can nurse his physical health with Gu worms, but the intense pleasure and pain will injure the soul and can even cause his soul to shatter!" Lord Sky Crane inquired.

He Feng Yang chuckled: "Isn't the collapse of his soul exactly what you want to see? Thus, you can seize his body and resurrect. Wasn't this your initial plan?"

His smile turned gentler as he said this: "This Fang Zheng has only gone on a crash course to reach rank five Gu Master, his nature is still childish. He is insufficiently tempered, how could he compare to you, Lord Sky Crane? After we use him to seize Hu Immortal blessed land, you can return. Sigh, since Su San and Zhou Wu were killed by that demon Song Zi Xing, there are fewer and fewer capable subordinates like you at my side."

The gentler He Feng Yang's tone became, the colder Lord Sky Crane felt in his heart, he replied in a grateful tone: "Receiving such importance from Lord Supreme Elder, this subordinate will definitely repay lord's kindness greatly and offer my life in sacrifice!"

"Good, take your leave now." He Feng Yang waved for Lord Sky Crane to leave.

The quiet room now only had He Feng Yang, his smile gradually disappeared before being replaced by a grave expression, his gaze somewhat tense.

After Fang Yuan seized Hu Immortal blessed land, he had been in charge of this matter and now a year had passed, the sect's pressure on him was growing larger day by day. Especially his enemy in the sect — Gu Immortal Lei Tan, who had publicly ridiculed his incompetence several times.

The sect convention a month later was a tough barrier. If He Feng Yang could not show any progress, it would be very difficult to cross this barrier. He could almost hear Lei Tan's mockery echoing throughout the convention.

"But it won't be long... as long as this plan succeeds, I can shut the mouths of all those petty people like Lei Tan. I would have the greatest contribution to the sect over these last years! In the attack against Hu Immortal blessed land, I will personally make a move. Moreover, I have invited Fairy Cang Yu and Old Lord Can Yang. Fairy Cang Yu has similar battle strength to me, and has at least three mortal killer moves. While Old Lord Can Yang is a rank seven Gu Immortal with an offensive Immortal Gu!"

"The only problem is that the land spirit can prohibit the use of all mortal Gu. I don't have any Immortal Gu to use, so I might not be able to do much. The only method is to consume green grape immortal essence. Fortunately, Hu Immortal blessed land was originally barren and not managed properly, how much green grape immortal essence could it have accumulated? I don't believe Fang Yuan can exhaust our three Gu Immortals' combined strength! As long as Hu Immortal's immortal essence is consumed, the land spirit will be powerless and won't be able to restrict mortal Gu. At that time, hmph!"

He Feng Yang mumbled to himself, gradually calming his tensed mind.

At the same time, in an underground cave in Hu Immortal blessed land.

Fang Yuan slowly stepped out of the wisdom light halo, a satisfied smile on his face.

Just now, he had successfully deduced the killer move, icy stardust.

Chapter 670: Icy Drill Stardust

The starlight firefly Gu were like a swarm of bees, flying in the air, giving off blue starlight.

The starlight was being drawn in by an invisible force, gathering into a stargate.

This was a huge circular door, it was made up of starlight, it shined like an illusion, it was like a scene within a dream.

As time passed, the starlight firefly Gu continued to dwindle in numbers, as the dead starlight firefly Gu fell to the ground from midair.

One leg stepped out of the stargate into Hu Immortal blessed land, next, the entire person walked out of the stargate.

It was an old man, he had white hair and deep wrinkles, his eyes were tired but bright, it was Tai Bai Yun Sheng who had returned from Lang Ya blessed land.

"I am back again..." Tai Bai Yun Sheng was covered in dust, he looked at the scenery in Hu Immortal blessed land, sighing to himself.

Although he had not lived here for a long time, he felt that this was his home.

He had a sense of belonging to this place.

At this time, Fang Yuan flew over from the sky: "Hahaha, Old Bai you came back at a good time, come, see the killer move that I just deduced."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng saw this familiar figure and laughed heartily: "Oh, is that so? I bought a cloud path defensive killer move from the Inkman King, why don't we fellow disciples have a friendly match."

Saying this, he flew into the air.

Fang Yuan heard this and raised his eyebrows, he stretched out one of his right arms, with his palm facing the sky, and his fingers straight.

A lump of starlight soon began to form in his palm.

"Oh? Is your killer move a star path killer move?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng saw this starlight lump and was shocked.

He flew into the sky, as a ring of white clouds appeared around him.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was at the center of these white clouds, the clouds were like a huge belt, moving around along with Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Fang Yuan slowly moved his fingers, grabbing the starlight lightly in his hands.

"Old Bai, get ready to take this." He growled, as he flicked a finger, a speck of starlight shot out like lightning.

The starlight speck's size was small, but extremely fast, it flew in the air, shooting towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

"Decent speed." Tai Bai Yun Sheng evaluated, from such a long distance, with him completely focused, he had a chance to dodge it. But because they were exchanging blows, he wanted to test his own cloud path killer move, thus he stood still and took the starlight head on.

When the starlight got close to Tai Bai Yun Sheng, the white cloud ring suddenly rotated, at an extremely fast pace!

The cloud ring blocked the starlight for him.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng stopped the cloud ring, he gazed with rapt attention, only to see that at the area where the cloud ring had blocked the starlight, it had turned blue, and frost energy was oozing, creating a layer of frost.

In response, he said laughingly to Fang Yuan: "It seems this killer move that you deduced isn't too amazing. You have to know, my killer move has not been fully activated yet."

The corners of Fang Yuan's mouth opened, showing his sharp, uneven teeth: "Neither has mine, take this!"

He flicked his fingers, as countless specks of starlight were shot out instantly.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was still at the same spot, but the cloud ring around him was rotating faster and faster, it was almost like a white ball had formed around him.

Fang Yuan's specks of starlight were blocked by the cloud ring completely.

Fang Yuan did not stop attacking, he showed an interested gaze. The pure white cloud ring was gradually turning blue from the starlight, and its speed was getting slower.

"Your killer move has a great freezing effect, it can slow your enemies." Tai Bai Yun Sheng evaluated: "My killer move also has another effect."

Saying this, he continuing activating his killer move.

The cloud ring that had almost been frozen into a blue ice statue exploded, with a loud bang, the blue frost turned into vapor as it spread towards the surroundings.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng showed joy, praising himself: "My cloud ring can store the attacks of enemies, when it reaches its limits or when I activate the following effect of my killer move, I can make the cloud ring explode, to let my enemies face their own attacks! Junior brother, it seems my killer move is stronger than the one you deduced."

Fang Yuan snickered: "Old Bai, it is still too early to say that."

Saying so, he flicked his wrist, and threw the entire starlight lump towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's heart shuddered, he quickly activated his killer move, and five cloud rings formed around him. With him as the center, the cloud rings expanded out with varying sizes, the cloud rings were like five concentric circles surrounding him, protecting him in the center.

The starlight lump came attacking, but the five cloud rings rotated rapidly, their afterimages produced an illusory white ball.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng laughed loudly, he was in the middle and felt extremely safe.

But right at this moment, the starlight lump exploded.

Ding ding ding, dang dang dang...

Large amounts of starlight specks flew everywhere, colliding into one another, the explosion covered Tai Bai Yun Sheng's entire body, as frost energy burst out.

"The force of this explosion far surpasses the force of the individual starlight specks added together." Tai Bai Yun Sheng's expression changed, the five cloud rings had turned blue, and their speed fell.

"Again!" Fang Yuan raised his eight arms, with his monstrous arms simultaneously grabbing at the air like claws.

The next moment, lumps of starlight formed in his palms.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng saw this and his pupils shrunk, he did not dare to be overconfident, he quickly activated his Gu worms and rapidly rotated the rings.

Fang Yuan stood on the spot, his eight arms fired shots consecutively, the starlight lumps flew like a meteor, bombing in the direction of Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Bam bam bam...

The explosions were right next to his ears, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's appearance turned pathetic, as he dodged around. The five cloud rings had reached their limits, they self-detonated one by one, while the force of the detonation allowed him to regain his momentum.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng quickly replenished the five cloud rings, as Fang Yuan continued to unleash his explosions, but he managed to maintain his defense.

"Enough." Fang Yuan suddenly stopped.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng breathed roughly, he slowly flew towards Fang Yuan: "What is the name of this killer move? What percent of its full power did you use?"

Fang Yuan replied without any shame: "I named this icy drill stardust, this is my unique creation. When I activate it fully, I can unleash a water vat sized starlight lump up to six times, but the bigger the lump, the slower the speed of movement. Because the more stardust there is inside, the more they collide, and the energy used up would reduce their speed."

"That is to say, you did not even use fifty percent of the killer move's power! How is your killer move so strong? Although it cannot compare to an immortal killer move, the power is already far superior to most mortal killer moves." Tai Bai Yun Sheng gasped.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "When I was in Imperial Court blessed land, I found an inheritance, it came from a famous poet of northern plains, Dou Min Jun. He was creative and created a brand new star Gu. This star Gu can increase the attack power of star path Gu worms, it is like the weakened version of amplify effect Gu. When I deduced this killer move, I fused this Gu into it, thus the power was this great."

This was the true reason why Fang Yuan chose a star path attack method.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng realized at once: "So that is it. I knew it, my defensive killer move is called nine cloud ring, when activated at full force, nine cloud rings can exist at once. Not only is the defense incredible, it can be replenished at any time, and can even return the attacks of enemies back to them. This cost me two whole immortal essence stones!"

Fang Yuan nodded: "Your killer move is definitely worth the price, in fact, this will be priced at two and a half immortal essence stones in treasure yellow heaven. Inkman King is giving you a favor."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng laughed: "I understand this clearly, he was considering my landscape as before Immortal Gu. He is also a Gu Immortal, he needs to undergo tribulations and calamities, when his blessed land suffers damage, he would need to ask me to repair it! Landscape as before Gu is my way to earn a fortune from now on."

"Old Bai, when your business expands in the future, I am sure many Gu Immortals will come to you for help. Come, let's talk while flying."

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng slowly flew towards Dang Hun mountain.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng looked back, only to see that on the battlefield earlier, there were still dozens of blue star clouds. The insides of these clouds were still emitting a cracking noise, it came from the collision of starlight specks.

As the frost energy spread around the star clouds, their color faded with time.

"Junior brother, you are incredible. This icy drill stardust is worth at least four immortal essence stones if you sell it in treasure yellow heaven." Tai Bai Yun Sheng sighed.

"If not for wisdom Gu, how would I have endless inspiration?" Fang Yuan replied plainly.

Actually, with just wisdom Gu, if he did not have Little Immortal Xing Luo's ice path killer move, icy yarn, and her smaller killer move, six-nine stardust, he would not be able to deduce the killer move icy drill stardust.

When Little Immortal Xing Luo started rising up, she was extremely poor, using the opportunity of the five regions war, she used her self-created icy stardust killer move to accumulate her wealth, finally gaining prominence and becoming a relatively famous character.

Fang Yuan's intention was to make an attempt of buying the former version of icy stardust from her.

When he saw icy yarn and six-nine stardust, he guessed that these two killer moves were the foundation of Little Immortal Xing Luo's new self-created killer move.

After he spent half an immortal essence stone to buy it, he rushed towards wisdom Gu and used the light of wisdom to make deductions.

Wisdom Gu's halo brought him unlimited inspiration, and Fang Yuan was a person who had been reborn, he had seen the power of icy stardust with his own eyes, this gave him the proper direction, avoiding the need to deduce blindly.

Eventually, he combined Dou Min Jun's inheritance within, deducing the killer move icy drill stardust.

This killer move was different from icy stardust, it had a smaller range but much greater power.

One could say that using the inheritance of Dou Min Jun, he had already slightly surpassed icy stardust.

"Rank nine wisdom Gu is truly phenomenal. I simply cannot imagine the effect when it is used fully. Honestly, I am a little envious of you. After becoming a zombie, you could receive such benefits!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng looked at Fang Yuan with admiration.

Fang Yuan shook his head: "There are a lot of flaws by becoming a zombie. Firstly, I have to thank Red Lotus Demon Venerable, next, I could reach this step because of coincidences and lucky opportunities. If not for the peculiar situation back then, allowing me to reach an arrangement with wisdom Gu, how could I utilize the light of wisdom?"

"That's right, if not for Red Lotus Demon Venerable breaking fate Gu, after we die, our souls would be sucked into the door of life and death, slumbering in the death domain for all eternity. How would anyone be able to remain in the world, to become a zombie!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng sighed deeply.

"Alright, before I left, I urged you to indirectly ask about the details of luck path from Lang Ya land spirit. Now that you've returned, what information did you obtain?" Fang Yuan asked.

Ever since he learned that Long Hair Ancestor had discussed about Dao with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable for seven days and seven nights, this idea emerged in him.

Lang Ya land spirit was far easier to deal with than Mo Yao's will.

But Tai Bai Yun Sheng shook his head, he showed a strange smile: "After I repaired a few rivers, I was chased out by Lang Ya land spirit in a hurry. He has to eat his medicine grinder chips, he is very busy."

"Eat his medicine grinder chips?"

Chapter 671: Sealing Spring Autumn Cicada

Half a month later, Fang Yuan went to Lang Ya blessed land again.

Clouds and mists filled his vision, it was a scene of white, among the turbulent sea of clouds, the twelve cloud buildings were motionless. Many large rivers resembling dragons were flowing above the cloud soil.

After Tai Bai Yun Sheng's restoration, Lang Ya blessed land had returned to its former state.

Fang Yuan was brought into a cloud building, meeting Lang Ya land spirit.

Lang Ya land spirit still had layers of qi path seals. But there were originally eighteen layers of seals, under the Inkman King's help, three layers were removed, only fifteen were left.

Inkman King stood beside Lang Ya land spirit, he did not dare to act arrogantly in front of Fang Yuan, he initiated greetings: "Sir Fang Yuan, how have you been?"

Fang Yuan smiled at him, his protruding fangs made his smile look very scary.

He turned to look at Lang Ya land spirit, tossing a rank four east window Gu towards him: "Look."

The east window Gu was floating silently before Lang Ya land spirit.

Lang Ya land spirit could not stretch out his arms, but Fang Yuan lent him the east window Gu so his consciousness could enter it.

After checking the contents, he nodded in satisfaction, praising: "Not bad, quite impressive! You completely deduced these three Immortal Gu recipes! Incredible, this thought process is spectacular!!"

"Land spirit, I did not come here personally to listen to your rubbish." Fang Yuan interrupted Lang Ya land spirit rudely, pointing out his intentions.

Lang Ya land spirit was not stupid, he willed and summoned thirty immortal essence stones: "This is your remuneration!"

Fang Yuan took these immortal essence stones and placed them in his immortal aperture.

His earnings this time was not as much as previously. That was because deducing these Immortal Gu recipes had costed him six beads of green grape immortal essence. If not for the stargate which had already been built, he would have to waste another two green grape immortal essence beads, raising his cost to eight..

Even though these Immortal Gu recipes were also remnant recipes with at least ninety percent completion rate, each of them needed in-depth analysis. Some Immortal Gu recipes were very hard to deduce, there were hurdles one after another, the longer he had to think, he would expend more wills.

But even so, the profits were still immense.

Inkman King watched with an envious gaze as the two finished their transaction, before smiling: "Sir Fang Yuan, actually, each transaction need not be done using immortal essence stones, right? Over here in Lang Ya blessed land, there are many valuable goods that cannot be found in treasure yellow heaven. We can trade using them. To speak the truth, my inkman city also has some precious goods that sir might be interested in. Not long ago, your senior brother, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, had bought a killer move from me."

Inkman King saw that Fang Yuan had ample funds and wanted to do business with him.

Fang Yuan heard this and smiled: "Inkman king, your suggestion is great, I just happen to lack three small swamp Gu, and six pine island Gu, I wonder if you have them?"

This problem stumped the Inkman King. He showed an awkward expression: "I am ashamed, this is the first time i've heard of Small Swamp and Pine Island."

"These are all olden antiquity Gu worms, small swamp Gu can change the terrain, forming a small swamp. Pine island is the same, it can create a floating island on top of a sea. There is a huge tree in the middle of the island, the tree roots would extend and hold the soil together." Lang Ya land spirit explained.

Next, he asked Fang Yuan curiously: "These Gu worms have all been eliminated from use, right now, Gu Immortals have better and cheaper ways to change the terrain of their blessed lands. Why do you want these Gu worms?"

"You don't need to ask about my intentions, from your tone, I assume you have these Gu worms in Lang Ya blessed land?" Fang Yuan asked mysteriously.

"Of course!" Lang Ya land spirit raised his head, saying arrogantly: "Every time I obtain a new Gu recipe, I will refine a few Gu worms to keep them as part of my collection. I have collected up to a hundred small swamp Gu and pine island Gu, I can sell them to you. But the materials to refine these Gu worms are now all extinct. You will need to pay an immortal essence stone."

Goods were more expensive when they were rare, small swamp Gu and pine island Gu were not even sold in treasure yellow heaven.

Fang Yuan had no hesitation, he tossed an immortal essence stone to Lang Ya land spirit and obtained three small swamp Gu and six pine island Gu.

Next, he looked at Lang Ya land spirit curiously: "Strange, you collect so many Gu worms, how do you settle the issue of feeding them?"

Fang Yuan had been troubled in these last days over the feeding of Gu worms, especially the Immortal Gu that he had.

Lang Ya land spirit gave him the answer: "The problem of feeding mortal Gu is easy, just create a special environment and let them hibernate. But you can't do this for Immortal Gu, even if they hibernate, you need to feed them, but the food that you feed them will be halved compared to normal times."

This answer was a little disappointing to Fang Yuan.

"Can you go into detail?" He asked.

"I believe you have gone to Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's true inheritance secluded domain, right? True inheritance secluded domain is a special environment, it can cause Gu worms to hibernate, mortal Gu will not need to be fed, and the feeding cost of Immortal Gu would be greatly reduced."

Fang Yuan frowned: "Even so, true inheritance secluded domain had so many Immortal Gu of many different kinds, I do not believe that Eighty-Eight True Yang Building could plunder sufficient resources at every interval of ten years to feed these Immortal Gu."

"That is because Giant Sun Immortal Venerable used food path methods. Food path is a very secretive path, it specialises in research on how to feed Gu worms, variant humans, wild beasts, and even humans, these very tough questions. Don't ask me questions about food path, I know nothing about it. The Immortal Gu that I have are all fed in the most traditional methods."

Fang Yuan did not give up: "Back then, your main body and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable refined Eighty-Eight True Yang Building together, would you not know the food path methods that he used?"

Lang Ya land spirit rolled his eyes: "The main body had once made an oath with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to not reveal any information regarding the food path methods. This is a huge secret, actually, I want to know about it too. But in the memories that I inherited, there is no such information."

Fang Yuan nodded, he knew that land spirits were honest and could not lie, he was only asking casually.

Although he had completed the transaction, Fang Yuan did not leave yet, he had another objective in coming here.

He took out a star shoot Gu, placing it before Lang Ya land spirit: "Can you reverse refine the recipe of this Gu?"

Lang Ya land spirit could not stretch out his hands, he could only sniff this star shoot Gu, saying: "This Gu has obviously been tampered with, the Gu recipe is very hard to recreate, at the very least, a refinement path grandmaster is needed. With just this rank three star path Gu, it is impossible to reverse refine its recipe! Because this is a new Gu, it will need to be researched and that would result in some costs..."

Fang Yuan smiled, stretching out one of his right palms, and spreading the five fingers: "I have over five thousand star shoot Gu."

Star shoot Gu was a necessary Gu worm in formulating the killer move spring star rain, Fang Yuan tried using it once and found that the killer move was very effective.

He had bought so many star shoot Gu at once, precisely with the intention of reverse refining it. But right now, his intention was even stronger.

"Five thousand... of course I can reverse refine the recipe. What a pity, I am currently sealed, I can't do anything." Lang Ya land spirit sighed.

Fang Yuan frowned: "This qi path seal still has fifteen layers, how long would it take to remove them all?"

"At least a year." Inkman King said.

"So long?"

"There is no choice, this seal is definitely an immortal killer move, the more it is unsealed, the more difficult it becomes." Inkman King showed a bitter smile.

Long Hair Ancestor was one of the three supreme grandmasters in refinement path history, their names were commemorated in legends throughout the ages. Lang Ya land spirit's current refinement path realm was at least at grandmaster level. Meanwhile, Fang Yuan was only a refinement path master.

If he could get Lang Ya land spirit to help, that would be the best. But now that Lang Ya land spirit was sealed, he could not refine Gu, and would not be able to reverse refine the recipe.

"Actually, it is not impossible to reverse refine the recipe." Inkman king suggested: "Lang Ya blessed land has many old hairy men, right? These old hairy men all have refinement master attainment. When the time comes, let them work for the land spirit while Lang Ya land spirit directs them personally, wouldn't that work?"

Lang Ya land spirit rolled his eyes at Inkman King: "A layman's silly words! Refinement path is profound and deep, many methods and killer moves require the relevant wisdom, cultivation, and talent, as well as huge amounts of practice. Do you think that many refinement masters would add up to one refinement grandmaster? Bullshit!"

Inkman King was stunned by the scolding, but he only laughed and did not dare to rebuke.

"In that case, forget about it. When you are unsealed, we'll discuss it again." Fang Yuan said his goodbyes, turning around and leaving.

This matter was not urgent at the moment.

"Lad, even if I am unsealed, I will not reverse refine it for you for free. Prepare three immortal essence stones!" Lang Ya land spirit shouted towards Fang Yuan who was leaving.

Fang Yuan did not turn around, he waved his hand as he stepped into the stargate, vanishing.

"Hmph, rascal kid." Lang Ya land spirit muttered as he watched him disappear.

After Fang Yuan returned to Hu Immortal blessed land, he entered Dang Hun palace, starting on the matter of sealing Spring Autumn Cicada.

He had already obtained small swamp Gu and pine island Gu, these were the final missing pieces.

Seven days and seven nights later, Fang Yuan planted large numbers of Gu worms in his first aperture as well as the area around his stomach.

These Gu worms' effects were interlinked, they amplified each other and formed a strong seal. On one hand, they helped the first aperture to alleviate Spring Autumn Cicada's pressure. On the other hand, part of Spring Autumn's Cicada's aura was expelled to be directed towards the outside of his body after some modifications.

Thirdly, and most importantly, the seal would not affect the activation of Spring Autumn Cicada.

"The seal can last for four years. This way, I have resolved the problem of Spring Autumn Cicada bursting the first aperture for the time being." Fang Yuan checked that there was no problem and sighed in relief.

This tough problem was finally settled, he felt a heavy weight being lifted off his shoulders.

The process of sealing Spring Autumn Cicada was not easy. After all, he was using mortal Gu to seal an Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan's soul was so exhausted it faded slightly.

After succeeding in the sealing, Fang Yuan fell asleep, not wanting to get out of bed for three days.

Chapter 672: Difficult problem of feeding Immortal Gu

Three days later, Fang Yuan slowly woke up.

His heart was in serenity, he did not feel tired or restless anymore.

"It seems that the zombie body cannot compare to a live physical body in one more aspect, that is, not only does my soul gets weakened more easily, it also is more prone to agitation." Fang Yuan found another drawback of the zombie body.

If the soul was weak, it could be easily resolved by using guts Gu to strengthen his soul. There were many guts Gu on Dang Hun mountain, these were all items of the highest quality for strengthening his soul.

But the irritation of the soul required pacifying the soul. The best way to pacify the soul was to use the Bewitching Lake's water, found in Obsession Death Domain. This water was recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, it was praised by Verdant Great Sun as an excellent wine.

Fang Yuan did not have the waters of Bewitching Lake, but even if he did, he would not dare to drink it. He used the ancient method, the most effective one — sleeping.

"If I had a normal person's body, I would just need to rest for a while in order to pacify the irritation in my soul. But after becoming a zombie, I would need to sleep for three days straight. Soul path involves strengthening the soul, refining the soul, and pacifying the soul, these three aspects, but most soul path Gu Masters focus on the first two. Now that I think about it, that should be because sleeping is an excellent way to pacify the soul, thus they did not need to invest in this aspect."

After sealing Spring Autumn Cicada, Fang Yuan gained a deeper understanding of soul path.

Next, he calculated this month's balance.

After dealing with Lang Ya land spirit twice, he earned sixty immortal essence stones. But he also spent a lot.

In treasure yellow heaven, he bought more than a thousand starlight firefly Gu, the killer moves spring star rain, icy yarn and six-nine stardust, large amounts of Gu refinement materials, large numbers of mortal Gu, as well as a group of old hairy men. And finally, to seal Spring Autumn Cicada, he bought small swamp Gu and pine island Gu, he spent a total of twenty immortal essence stones.

Right now, Fang Yuan had thirty and a half immortal essence stones left.

Do not think that this was a lot of immortal essence stones, Fang Yuan also spent much of his green grape immortal essence.

When deducing Immortal Gu recipes, he could only do it by himself, the first time he traded with Lang Ya land spirit, he only had nine green grape immortal essence beads left. After the second deduction, he spent six immortal essence beads, and improving the sealing method on Spring Autumn Cicada consumed one bead, right now he had two beads left.

It was necessary to improve Spring Autumn Cicada's seal. Earlier, his estimated cost was twenty-three immortal essence stones. After the improvement, it fell to twenty. This way, he saved two immortal essence stones.

Only having two beads of green grape immortal essence left was very dangerous. If he met with a mishap, Fang Yuan would only be able to use myriad self twice before he would be unable to deal with the situation, especially now, when Immortal Crane Sect was close to attacking.

Fang Yuan used fifteen immortal essence stones, converting them into his own green grape immortal essence.

This way, his green grape immortal essence rose to seventeen beads, while his immortal essence stones fell to fifteen and a half pieces.

Right now, the crisis with Spring Autumn Cicada's aperture had been temporarily resolved. And his predicament was also relieved after allying with Hei Lou Lan. Dealing with Lang Ya land spirit earned him huge amounts of immortal essence stones, it was the source of the strength to resolve Fang Yuan's problems.

The absolutely terrible situation was alleviated slightly. It was like a land of darkness with dark clouds looming, after Fang Yuan's immense efforts, he managed to create an opening, allowing sunlight to pierce into the land of darkness.

Right now in front of him, was another problem, and this problem had to be resolved quickly.

That was the feeding of Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan was not worried about feeding mortal Gu. But feeding Immortal Gu was becoming a huge issue.

All in all, Fang Yuan had too many Immortal Gu, he had Spring Autumn Cicada, Fixed Immortal Travel, Calamity Beckoning, Delight in Water and Mountain, Worldly Wave Trace, Rising Azure Cloud, Cleanse Soul, Connect Luck, and Woman's Heart.

Ordinary Gu Immortals did not even have a single Immortal Gu. Fang Yuan had nine.

This was a great boon, as well as a huge burden.

Spring Autumn Cicada was fine, it consumed the water in the river of time, it did not need feeding.

Fixed Immortal Travel was once fed with one bead of green grape immortal essence a year ago in central continent time, that could last for six years. But one year in central continent was not one year of time passing by for Fixed Immortal Travel. During this time it was in Imperial Court blessed land, Fang Yuan's aperture, and Hu Immortal blessed land, all of these had faster time flow than central continent.

And this six years was a theoretical number, the more Fang Yuan activated Fixed Immortal Travel, the more this time would shrink.

Right now, although Fixed Immortal Travel could still hold on for a while, it was close to needing to be fed again.

The remaining Immortal Gu were troublesome.

These recent days, Fang Yuan had been investigating and finally obtained crucial information.

Calamity beckoning Immortal Gu's food was the black blood of the desolate beast, six headed snake.

Delight in water and mountain Immortal Gu needed large amounts of earth qi, water qi, and some laughter stones.

Worldly wave trace Gu needed tens of thousands of underworld jellyfish, as well as thousands of deepsea lightning eels.

Rising azure cloud Gu needed the dragon scale of the desolate beast, cloud dragon, as well as tens of thousands of eyeballs from wind scythe birds.

Cleanse soul Immortal Gu needed the flesh and blood of over ten thousand white lotus giant silkworm Gu.

Connect luck Immortal Gu needed five thousand kilograms of sand from the resting area of the ancient desolate beast, worldly sand gull.

As for the poison path Immortal Gu, Woman's Heart, Lang Ya land spirit had earlier said that it fed on women's hearts. This Gu combined nurturing and refinement, the more hearts used to feed it, the stronger the poison.

"Among these Gu worms, calamity beckoning Gu was just refined, it already needs feeding and is very weak now. The Immortal Gu, Delight in Water and Mountain and Worldly Wave Trace, are components of the Immortal Gu House Water Pavilion, they had been inside Imperial Court blessed land all these years and have been fed well. Cleanse Soul, Connect Luck, Woman's Heart and Rising Azure Cloud were all hibernating inside true inheritance secluded domain, during these many years, Giant Sun's will had only fed them half of the resources they needed. Now that they are out of the true inheritance secluded domain, they have woken up fully and are extremely hungry, they need food."

"Thankfully, I passed Rising Azure Cloud to Lang Ya land spirit, with him feeding it, it will not die of hunger. I have also left two Immortal Gu, Landscape as Before and Man as Before, with Tai Bai Yun Sheng, that's his problem to deal with." Fang Yuan analyzed.

Even so, the pressure on him was quite intense.

Feeding Immortal Gu was not merely a question of immortal essence stones.

This world was not like Earth, Earth was a highly commercialized society, as long as one had money, they could buy nearly anything.

But in the Gu world, the economy was not developed, there were monopolies in many markets, and countless precious and rare resources. Immortal essence stones were a hard currency, but they could not serve all purposes.

For example, looking at the food he needed, the desolate beasts six headed snake and cloud dragon, as well as the ancient desolate beast worldly sand gull, they were hard to come by and had great strength equivalent to Gu Immortals.

Although treasure yellow heaven occasionally sold the flesh, bones and other parts of desolate beasts, they showed up infrequently and would be purchased within moments when they were available in the market.

Even earth qi and water qi were not easy to extract.

White lotus giant silkworm Gu and laughter stones were very rare goods, they were hardly seen in treasure yellow heaven.

In contrast, Woman's Heart was much easier to feed, although it was slightly troublesome, the difficulty was lower.

There was another crucial point, that was time.

Fang Yuan did not have ample time to slowly prepare these foods.

Thus, he had no choice but to purchase these rare resources in treasure yellow heaven, even though this would make the price higher, and wisdom path Gu Immortals would be left with huge amounts of traces to make their deductions.

But Fang Yuan was now known as Eight Arm Immortal, for the time being, no one would connect it to Hu Immortal blessed land.

Even if they would, he had to do this.

After all, the survival of the Immortal Gu was much more important than being suspected!

Of course, he had asked Lang Ya land spirit long ago, as well as Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan, unfortunately he did not get ideal results from them.

Lang Ya land spirit had once owned laughter stones, but he had used them up when refining Gu.

And several years ago, there was a Gu Immortal who returned from eastern sea, sending Fairy Li Shan a batch of deepsea lightning eels. But there were only a hundred of them, and they were merely used as ornamental attractions. Later, because Fairy Li Shan did not take good care of them, all of these eels died.

But this gave Fang Yuan a reminder.

Eastern sea...

In Fang Yuan's previous life, when he was a mortal, he traveled over the five regions, he went everywhere and had once stayed in eastern sea for a while.

Eastern sea had abundant resources, the most in the five regions, even central continent could not compare to it.

Moreover, over these recent years, eastern sea had been in turmoil, there were many opportunities available there, and the benefits would be huge too.

If Fang Yuan had not been stuck with Dang Hun mountain's problem, and due to Tai Bai Yun Sheng being the easiest path to resolving it, his first choice would have been eastern sea.

Thinking about Lan Xu blessed land, blue dragon whale, rainbow island and so on, Fang Yuan made his decision.

He summoned Tai Bai Yun Sheng: "Old Bai, how has your cultivation been?"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng laughed heartily, he could not stop talking: "Its great, my progress is very smooth. I helped Lang Ya land spirit repair his cloud soil and earned three immortal essence stones. Next, I restored several rivers and earned another two immortal essence stones. I then bought the defensive killer move nine cloud ring, spending two immortal essence stones. Finally, I bought seeds of float ball tea in treasure yellow heaven, spending another stone."

"Float ball tea seeds are very common, you actually spent an entire immortal essence stone, it seems you bought a huge quantity. But your choice is correct, I have seen your blessed land, there are far more time path resources than space path resources. Float ball tea grows slowly and floats in the air. You can maximize your advantages and minimize your weaknesses. In a few years, when the float ball tea plants mature, you will be able to reap the harvest and sell them." Fang Yuan evaluated.

"That is exactly the case." Tai Bai Yun Sheng patted his leg: "After the float ball tea plants reach a certain scale, I will bring in a group of jade hummingbirds, developing my blessed land with that as the base."

Fang Yuan looked at Tai Bai Yun Sheng, saying: "Jade hummingbirds are mutated beasts, the price of a jade hummingbird group will not be cheap."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng replied calmly: "I have already thought about it, from now on I will use Landscape as Before to earn immortal essence stones, and learn from Fairy Li Shan's example. I believe my Landscape as Before is not inferior to Fairy Li Shan's mountain pledge Gu."

Fang Yuan nodded: "You have landscape as before Gu, wherever you go, you will be extremely popular."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng sighed: "It is a pity that showing myself in public is inconvenient now, we are the only survivors after Imperial Court blessed land was destroyed. Right now, we are already considered the top suspects by northern plains' Gu Immortals. If we are exposed, the consequences would be unthinkable. Also, the most crucial witness, Ma Hong Yun, has vanished, it seems a certain Gu Immortal is holding him captive, it is possible that we might have already been targeted by some Gu Immortals."

"That is why I think that eastern sea would be a good place for you to go." At this point, Fang Yuan finally stated his true intentions.

Chapter 673: Thousand wish tree

"Eastern sea?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was surprised.

"Right. There are many sea areas in eastern sea, the culture and style there are greatly different from northern plains. You will certainly have great benefits when you go there. Especially in one of the sea areas, air bubble sea. This sea produces abundant air bubble fish but due to a fight between Gu Immortals recently, it has been poisoned. The owners of this sea area, Ni clan, Qiu clan and Ba clan are having headaches because of this." Fang Yuan explained.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng immediately became excited: "This feels like a major business opportunity. Junior brother, you are right, we can't move in northern plains but we can go to eastern sea. There are regional walls between the five regions, and the higher one's cultivation, the more difficult it is to cross these barriers. But we have Fixed Immortal Travel and can thus ignore the regional walls."

"However, Old Bai, you need to be careful. Gu Immortals might not be able to casually travel between regions, but the disturbance in northern plains is too large and is already known by the other four regions, too. Central continent's ten great sects have deep foundations and even their own pawns in all the other regions. I had planned to seize Immortal Gu Dark Limit before going to eastern sea, but there has not been much progress at Hei Lou Lan's side. Danger will lurk everywhere in this trip, you need to be extremely careful." Fang Yuan sincerely reminded.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was deeply moved: "I understand, but junior brother, you don't need to worry. I have been wandering around in northern plains for most of my life, I might not be too skilled in a head-on confrontation but I still have more than enough ability to protect myself."

Fang Yuan nodded. He also acknowledged this point, otherwise he would not have arranged for Tai Bai Yun Sheng to go to eastern sea.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was experienced and knowledgeable along with being a flying master, thus his escaping ability was top-notch. Moreover, he now possessed a formidable cloud path defensive killer move, nine cloud ring.

"When you enter eastern sea, don't immediately make dealings with Ni, Qiu and Bai clans, instead proceed to Hai Shi blessed land. Among the five great trading markets in the world, treasure yellow heaven is first and Hai Shi blessed land is second. Hai Shi blessed land should have missions for saving air bubble sea, you can then use this pretext to get in contact with the three clans and save a lot of trouble." Fang Yuan reminded.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng agreed: "I will definitely go make a trip to Hai Shi blessed land."

Fang Yuan continued: "I need some specific food to feed my Immortal Gu: tens of thousands of underworld jellyfish and thousands of deepsea lightning eels. These two are specialities of eastern sea. Also, see if there are any laughter stones in Hai Shi blessed land, the blood of the desolate beast, six headed snake, and cloud dragon scales. This is the list of items I require, here."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng accepted the list and revealed a serious expression: "Junior brother, your matters are my matters as well. I will be sure to settle this with all my effort."

Fang Yuan gave a bright smile: "Old Bai, just do your best. Before departing, I hope you can make a trip to Dang Hun mountain and consume some guts Gu. This Gu is among the highest quality Gu around for strengthening one's soul, it is always best to be prepared just in case."

"Junior brother, here we go again! I have said it many times, these guts Gu are your property, how can I covet your wealth as a senior brother!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng immediately refused. This was already his sixth time refusing such an offer.

Fang Yuan was already his benefactor, he, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, placed this favor deep in his heart, never to be forgotten, so how could he covet Fang Yuan's guts Gu?

Fang Yuan mumbled before conceding: "Strengthening the soul is extremely beneficial for you, how about this, I will sell these guts Gu to you for one immortal essence stone. It just so happens that I lack immortal essence stones to buy food for my Immortal Gu."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng wanted to say something but Fang Yuan waved his hand and continued: "Senior brother, danger will be lurking on all sides during this trip to eastern sea, I hope you will arm and prepare yourself properly, otherwise, if some accident occurs to you, I will feel guilty. I try to pay attention to all details when I do something, I hope you can understand."

His words contained sincerity and genuine friendship.

Especially when Fang Yuan called him 'senior brother' which he rarely said, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's eyes reddened, he rapidly blinked his eyes and breathed out: "Alright, I understand your intent, junior brother, we will make this transaction."

A day later, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had made all the preparations and left Hu Immortal blessed land together with Fang Yuan, arriving at eastern sea.

"I will hand over both moving perspective cup Gu and stargate Gu to you. We will maintain contact frequently, if there is any significant matter, please inform me beforehand." Fang Yuan reminded.

"Junior brother, go back without any worries. If Immortal Crane Sect attacks, don't forget to call me!"

Fang Yuan nodded and without saying anymore, he activated Fixed Immortal Travel, disappearing from the spot.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng stored the stargate Gu and looked at the surrounding sea, after identifying the direction, he rapidly began flying.

When he appeared again, Fang Yuan had arrived at western desert.

He was standing on an exceedingly tall sand dune, all around him was a boundless desert with countless sand dunes extending everywhere.

The scorching sun shone down, there was no wind and the temperature was so high it made one have the feeling of being broiled. But Fang Yuan had an immortal zombie body and did not feel even a trace of warmth.

The coarse and fine sand granules shone like gold under the sunlight.

Fang Yuan looked at the sand dune under him. This sand dune was several times taller than other sand dunes. It shone with golden light and its contours were soft and smooth; the whole sand dune was a scene of nothingness except for a short tree on the peak.

This tree was not even eight feet tall, the branches were short, thin and twisted like monstrous claws, making it look extremely ugly. But the strange thing was, it had an enormous shadow of light.

This shadow of light was extremely large, reaching five or six hundred feet. The shadow of light was like a flourishing tree with many branches and leaves. The tree branches were white as snow, the flowers were pink like cherries. There were clusters of small fruits among the floral leaves that had yet to ripen, with all sorts of colors.

This tree's origin was huge; it was an ancient desolate tree, named thousand wish.

It would finish growing in three hundred years, flower at its six hundredth year and bear fruit at the nine hundredth year.

The number of fruits it produced was always precisely one thousand.

Right when the fruits completely ripened, people could bring Gu recipes and make a wish under the tree. If the wish succeeded, the fruits would open and the corresponding Gu worms would fly out.

These Gu worms could be mortal Gu and also could be Immortal Gu!

But if a wish for Immortal Gu succeeded, the amount of fruits would decrease accordingly.

In Fang Yuan's previous life, this desolate tree had caused a huge battle among western desert's Gu Immortals. Finally, several super forces came to an agreement and tried to partition this tree between themselves.

But on the day the fruits ripened and fell down, all sizes of forces, big and small, allied and burst through the blockade created by the super forces, causing chaos throughout the place.

A lone cultivator rank five Gu Master, with the surname Han and name Li, unexpectedly became the first to arrive under the thousand wish tree, his wish gave him a space path Immortal Gu named Phantom Heaven.

Fang Yuan was a rank four Gu Master back then who sought to obtain profits in the chaos. After experiencing great dangers and difficulties, he arrived before the ancient desolate tree, and was also able to obtain a Gu worm.

But this Gu worm was only a rare rank four Gu.

Even so, this rare rank four Gu gave a tremendous boost to Fang Yuan's battle strength.

"Back then, I had to fight through such a tight siege defense to arrive in front of this tree, and the fruits were already sparse by then, only fifty or sixty were left. I have now arrived here in this life, but it's too early. The fruits still require over two hundred years to completely mature."

Fang Yuan's heart was deeply moved and he smacked this ancient desolate tree, but the thousand wish tree did not even budge.

This desolate tree had astonishing defense and could continue to stand tall against the attacks of Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan had a deep impression of it.

The regretful thing was that not long after that chaotic battle, Xi clan's rank eight ancestor, Xi Jian Ping, exited his seclusion and suppressed all the experts forcefully, his might awing the entirety of the great desert; the thousand wish tree was taken away by Xi clan and planted at Xi clan's blessed land. Since then, Fang Yuan had not been able to see the thousand wish tree again.

Fang Yuan did not have methods to transplant the thousand wish tree, even if he had, he did not have any place to plant it in.

Hu Immortal blessed land had a terrain of grassland and not desert terrain.

The thousand wish tree required this kind of extreme environment to survive. Moreover, if the thousand wish tree was moved impulsively now, the floral leaves along with the thousand wish fruits would wither and fall, wasting the previous millennium of effort.

Fang Yuan walked down the sand dune and left this place.

Only after walking for a whole half a day and countless li, he had truly left the range of the thousand wish tree.

Fang Yuan glanced back; there was only flat desert with no signs of sand dunes let alone the gorgeous shadow of light of the five to six hundred feet tall tree.

He was not surprised.

This thousand wish tree had an ability of shrouding a radius of a huge distance in illusion. When leaving this illusion, one must leave on foot. And approaching it was extremely troublesome; the illusion would emerge repeatedly and could even make people move around the same spot without realizing.

"It was because of this that I and others could fish for benefits." Fang Yuan smiled. He had Fixed Immortal Travel so he could ignore this illusion.

However, the goal of this trip was not this ancient desolate tree.

It was instead the person who had gained enormous benefits from a thousand wish fruit and became a Gu Immortal expert later.

This person's name was Han Li.

"Han Li was a mortal. But after repeated fortuitous encounters, his nature became steadfast and courageous. His starting point was much lower than mine, when he had just started his cultivation, I was already a rank three Gu Master in southern border. But at the time of my self-detonation, he had already become a Gu Immortal at the peak of rank seven, a famous powerhouse of western desert. Many influential figures of central continent's ten great sects suffered losses from him. But right now, he is only just a child. According to the <Biography of Han Li>, he should be living in a mortal hamlet near Huang clan."

Fang Yuan's target was Han Li.

Ever since Fang Yuan understood the effect of connect luck Immortal Gu, he had intended to use his rebirth advantage to get rid of the weakness of Spring Autumn Cicada wearing down his luck.

He planned meticulously and ruled out many people, leaving behind only a few targets.

Han Li was one of them.

These targets were people who would attain great success in the future, having large potential, as well as huge luck.

People like Hunting King Sun Gan of southern border, who would only be at rank five all their lives, were simply ignored by Fang Yuan.

Little Immortal Xing Luo was a Gu Immortal but her luck was not good and she would at most reach a small scale of fame, Fang Yuan ignored her too.

There was Shi Chao Yu, who would be able to become a rank seven Gu Immortal, but his journey was filled with ups and down, his luck was definitely not good and he was also excluded.

Only people like Han Li and Ma Hong Yun, who had smooth journeys with repeated fortuitous encounters, were Fang Yuan's targets.

However, Ma Hong Yun's whereabouts were unknown at present and Fairy Li Shan was exerting her full efforts to investigate it; Fang Yuan's first target thus became Han Li.

After leaving the thousand wish tree, Fang Yuan used mortal Gu to disguise as a man with a yellowish face and a robust body. Then he directly flew towards Huang clan.

Chapter 674: Monolith Luck

The entirety of western desert was a vast desert. Oases were like stars in the sky, shining among this sea of sand.

Humans lived here by relying on the oases.

Western desert, Sha Jing oasis.

Huang clan as an upper tier force had hundreds of years of history here, they occupied the most important resources at the center of this oasis.

At the outer parts of the oasis, there were small sized forces that submitted to this Huang clan.

At the even further outer areas, near the fringe of Sha Jing oasis, there were mortal villages. These mortals had a tough life, they had huge numbers and were all under the control of Huang clan and other forces of Gu Masters.

In these villages, there was a Han village, near Han village, there was a small natural grassland.

Although it was called a grassland, it was much more desolate than northern plains, there was sand everywhere and blades of red dagger grass were sharp as swords, stabbing into the deep parts of the sand, trying to absorb the meager water content.

A group of children were bending their backs, holding sickles as they laboriously cut down these grasses.

These children were not even ten years old, but they had to come out and work, to make money for the family, this was common in mortal families.

The dagger grass had sharp edges, these children were all wearing leather gloves, but there was one without gloves.

This bare handed child sniffed his mucus as he held the sickle, cutting the dagger grass and placed them into the basket on his back.

The radiance of the setting sun was still very hot, these children were all breathing roughly as it shined on them, sweat pouring on their backs.

Finally, the sky turned darker, as the sun was at the horizon, only half of it could be seen now, as the children stopped their work.

"Quickly leave, it is night time, the small ghost jackals are coming out to hunt for food." The child with the largest body frame spoke, like he was their leader.

"How much did you gather? Wow, that's a lot!" As usual, they started comparing with each other.

"I ate until I was full today, that's why I have strength, hehe."

"But the grass that you cut is still less than Han Li."

"Hey, Han Li, you are amazing, you can cut the grass without wearing gloves, yet there are no injuries on your hands, how did you do it?" A small lass with a ponytail asked.

Han Li giggled.

The children returned to the village together, they were talking excitedly along the way, when they returned to the village, they split up, returning to their homes.

Han Li returned home too, he pushed the broken wooden door and realized that his parents were not back yet.

His father was a farmer, he was planting wire cotton at the west part of the village, he had been plowing the fields these days, going out early and returning home late.

His mother had a job that everyone in the village admired. Every day she would enter the outer area of the oasis, doing odd jobs and cleaning for a small sized Gu Master clan.

Han Li stood beside one quern-stone, he poured the dagger grass in his basket inside, then he picked up a wooden pole and ground the grass down.

He put in a lot of effort, before long, he was full of sweat.

After the grass was turned into paste, he took out a bag and poured a portion of the rice husks inside into the quern-stone as well.

He mixed them together, creating a paste-like food ingredient.

He poured the food into a wooden basin.

Next, he brought the wooden basin to the side of the house.

There was a flimsy looking stable beside the house, inside were three fat sand scorpions.

These sand scorpions were fat like pigs, they were no threat at all. Upon hearing Han Li's footsteps, the three fat sand scorpions rushed out from the shadows of the stable.

"Go ahead and eat, these were all cut down by me painstakingly." Han Li flipped over the wooden basin, pouring the paste-like food on the ground.

The three fat sand scorpions surrounded the food and ate, they chewed loudly and made a humming noise.

"Eat, eat, eat more and grow faster..." Han Li's small body was sprawled on the stable, he looked at these sand scorpions as he muttered.

These fat sand scorpions were not Gu, they were ordinary creatures.

But the meat of the scorpion was plump and delicious, the money obtained after selling the meat would be a huge sum for the entire mortal family.

To Han Li's family, these three fat sand scorpions were their most important assets. Thus, even if Han Li did not get to eat dinner himself, he had to feed these three fat sand scorpions.

Gulp, gulp, gulp...

At this time, Han Li's stomach started growling.

Han Li jumped down from the fence, he rubbed his tummy and returned home, starting to cook dinner.

He had to cook dinner for his family every day.

The rice they ate was the most common sand rice in western desert, the texture of this rice was very bad, it was hard to swallow. But it was easy to cultivate, it was the main crop that mortals ate.

As Han Li worked next to the stove, he did not know that someone had been watching him for half the day.

As night descended, at the graveyard that was several li away from Han village, Fang Yuan was sitting still like a statue.

The reason he chose this place was because of how deserted it was.

At night, Fang Yuan came here and activated up to a thousand investigative Gu, he put the whole of Han village under his supervision.

The primeval essence of Gu Immortals was unlimited, as long as they had enough Gu worms, they could do things at the efficiency of thousands of mortals or more.

In the darkness, Fang Yuan slowly opened his eyes, he assessed: "The age fits, it should be this kid."

As he thought about it, he activated the rank five luck inspection Gu.

Looking from afar, he saw that above Han village there was a lump of a luck cloud. This luck cloud's size was not big, it was grey-white and looked very thin.

This was a collection of luck, these villagers had a sense of belonging, thus they felt that they were a collective body, resulting in their luck gathering together.

Fang Yuan looked below the luck cloud.

Smoky traces of luck were rising from the villagers, after rising for two hundred meters, they merged into the luck cloud.

And among the traces of luck in the luck cloud, there was one especially eye-catching portion of luck.

This luck was like a huge stone, it was floating in the air above Han Li's family, a hundred steps away from the ground. There was a crack on the surface of the stone, and a trace of luck was leaking from that crack, it had a golden color and was rising up, fusing into the collective luck cloud.

"What luck is this?" Fang Yuan looked in amazement.

He did not obtain the luck path true inheritance, he was quite unfamiliar with the meaning of the different forms of luck.

For the time being, he decided to name this form of luck, calling it monolith luck.

Only Han Li was at his home right now, seeing this, Fang Yuan could confirm that Han Li was the future rank seven Gu Immortal, the guy with countless fortuitous encounters.

Fang Yuan then tried to look above him, but saw nothing.

"What a pity, after becoming an immortal zombie, I cannot detect my own luck anymore, unless I get the rank six luck inspection Gu. But who knows how my luck is now? Is it still the black coffin luck?" Fang Yuan muttered to himself, he had always been very curious towards luck.

But just as he was about to take out connect luck Gu, he heard someone shouting: "Little thief Ling Hu, you are hiding here, do you think I, Plump Lady, can't find you! I chased you for countless miles, quickly return my immortal essence stones!"

Fang Yuan was secretly shocked, he turned around and looked, only to see a human figure made of moving sand, shouting at him from far away.

Fang Yuan's heart sank, he shouted: "Plump Lady? You got the wrong person, I am not the person you are chasing."

"Bullshit! Little thief Ling Hu, everyone knows you are an expert in disguise, do you think that I would not recognize you when you disguise your appearance like this! You have some guts, stealing from me, I will beat you till your intestines are blown out!!"

Not only was the human shaped moving sand figure shouting, at the same time, there was a furious growl in the air as well.

The voice was like thunder, it pierced heaven and earth. The entire oasis was shocked by this and went into chaos!

Fang Yuan frowned deeply, he did not think that by disguising as a normal human and hiding his zombie appearance, he would unexpectedly be treated as a thief by someone else.

He stood up and turned around to look.

Only to see that at the north-east area, yellow sand was flying in the air and intense winds were blowing, the sound of the wind was like the roaring of beasts, continuous and loud.

The yellow sand on the formerly peaceful ground was whipped up like tidal waves in the sea.

The sand waves attacked one after another.

Fang Yuan took a deep look at the monolith luck, before moving his body and charging towards the attacker head on.

Soon after, he saw the culprit.

This was an extremely fat female Gu Immortal, she had a thick waist and broad shoulders, she was like a water tank. She stood on the yellow sand waves as she arrogantly and furiously looked at Fang Yuan.

She stretched out a finger, scolding: "Little thief Ling Hu, you..."

Just as she spoke, Fang Yuan attacked!

"Heavenly zombie transformation!" Fang Yuan purposely shouted, before removing his disguise, showing his immortal zombie appearance.

At once, a six meter tall monster with a green face and sharp fangs, blood red eyes, eight monstrous arms and bulging muscles appeared before the female Gu Immortal, Plump Lady.

He looked ruthless and terrifying, radiating killing intent.

Plump Lady was shocked, she said: "You..."

Fang Yuan stepped on the ground, causing a loud sound, the ground was cracking under his pressure, as he flew towards Plump Lady like a cannonball.

Plump Lady saw Fang Yuan's ruthless charge and her heart shook, she quickly raised her arms.

Swish swish swish!

Three huge sand waves immediately rose into the air, reaching hundreds of meters in height.

The huge waves came crashing, Fang Yuan snickered as he raised his speed, crashing towards them.

Bam bam bam!

In the blink of an eye, he scattered the three huge sand waves and appeared before Plump Lady.

Plump Lady's heart was pounding, she finally realized she had found the wrong person. But she was someone with a fiery temper, Fang Yuan's fierce and ferocious actions aroused her anger.

"I'll let you taste my killer move — martial sand armor!" She shouted loudly, as two traces of yellow sand gushed out from her ears, the sand quickly gathered and enveloped her entire body.

In a few breaths of time, she had turned into a sand giant that was about the size of Fang Yuan, but she had a thicker body.

Fang Yuan charged forward, as the sand giant roared, slamming with both its arms, displaying unrivalled fearlessness.

Boom boom!

With two loud bangs, the eight armed immortal zombie's fists met with the sand giant's.

The sand giant's fist scattered into yellow sand, while Fang Yuan's fists were fractured.

Plump Lady took a step back, as the scattered yellow sand merged to create the sand giant's fists again. Fang Yuan, however, took a huge step forward, while his fractured fists were recovering rapidly, his remaining six fists slammed at the sand giant.

Crash crash crash...

At once, the two engaged in fierce combat, yellow sand was flying in the air as the sound of bones breaking could be heard continuously.

Plump Lady was more shocked as she fought on: "Who is this person? Why is he so insane like a demon, he is even more ruthless and fearless than me!"

Chapter 675: Dead

Fang Yuan laughed wickedly, his eight arms turned into fists and slammed, they opened into palms, slashing and smacking, they also became claws or piercing fingers, he showed his immense attainment in close combat.

Plump Lady relied on martial sand armor's thick defense normally to engage in her relentless assaults, she was used to bullying other Gu Immortals. But in front of Fang Yuan, she was at the losing end.

Fang Yuan's fist shadows were flying, he moved nimbly as Plump Lady desperately dealt with his attacks, she could only parry his attacks but not retaliate.

Suddenly, Fang Yuan saw an opening and got close to her, his eight arms were like pythons coiling around her, as his two monstrous claws destroyed the sand giant's two arms like a drill.

The sand giant roared, knocking its fat tummy towards him.

Fang Yuan snickered in his heart, he had been expecting this, his figure moved quickly as he flew to the sky above the sand giant.

His left knee slammed towards it, and with a bang, the sand giant's head was scattered.

Before the yellow sand regenerated, Fang Yuan's right leg chopped at it like a battle axe.

Bam!

The yellow sand scattered, as the defensive killer move was broken, Plump Lady vomited a mouthful of blood, collapsing to the ground like a falling meteor.

Fang Yuan tore the yellow sand open, like an eagle scavenging for food, he flew down from the sky, bringing the intense winds with him, he was bent on killing Plump Lady.

Plump Lady who was falling saw Fang Yuan chasing her and showed an expression of fear.

She attempted to pull some distance from him, but Fang Yuan's speed was faster.

Bam!!

With a loud explosion, Fang Yuan charged down from a high altitude, directly slamming Plump Lady into a deep part of the desert.

Large amounts of yellow sand was sent flying, the huge impact created a large circular crater, it was a thousand steps wide and about thirty meters deep.

"Oh?" Fang Yuan stood at the pit of the crater, he had a surprised look as Plump Lady's 'corpse' suddenly disintegrated into a pile of sand.

At the same time, he heard her shrill laughter from the air: "Oaf, I will let you taste my attacking killer move — Burial Dragon Sand Coffin!"

As she said this, the yellow sand around the crater gushed down like tidal waves, filling up the entire round crater.

Fang Yuan could not dodge in time, he was buried within.

The surface of the desert was as flat as a mirror, Plump Lady's mouth was oozing with blood as she sat on a lump of yellow sand, her palms were placed together as her eyes were staring wide open, activating her killer move maniacally.

On the surface of the mirror-like desert, the sand statue of a certain horned dragon appeared.

This horned dragon statue coiled around, the dragon's head bit its tail, gathering the surrounding sand and forming a great force to suppress Fang Yuan who was under the sand.

The intense battlefield had turned peaceful once more.

"Huff!" Plump Lady let out a breath of turbid air, she wiped her sweat as she finally relaxed: "It is over. My burial dragon sand coffin can form an incomparable pressure, emitted on my enemy in all directions. Once my enemy is trapped, they cannot move until they are turned into meat paste. In the past, I forcefully suppressed a desolate beast, evil dragon, not to mention restraining a lone zombie?"

Plump Lady muttered to herself, her words had great effect as she quickly calmed herself down.

But right at this moment, there was a loud explosion from beneath the ground —

Bang!

"What sound is that?" Plump Lady's body shook, she became nervous again.

Bang!

The loud bang could be heard again, it was like there was a giant underground beating a drum.

"Damn it, it is my burial dragon sand coffin!" Plump Lady became alert, she stood up abruptly, but her vision turned dark, her body was swaying as she almost fell onto the yellow sand on the ground.

She was indeed injured.

When Fang Yuan tore the martial sand armor, his strong punch had heavily injured her.

At the crucial moment, she used her killer move as a body double, attracting Fang Yuan's attention as she hid inside the yellow sand that was flying all over the place.

After that, she used her killer move burial dragon sand coffin and trapped Fang Yuan underneath the sand.

"Impossible! Even a desolate beast, evil dragon met its end under my killer move's power. This killer move is worth at least three immortal essence stones in treasure yellow heaven!" Plump Lady spoke to herself.

Bang!

Right at this moment, there was another explosion.

The originally fearsome and powerful evil dragon statue shook, it was covered in cracks as sand fell off the statue.

Plump Lady's heart shuddered along with it, she stared with her eyes wide open, her gaze was fixed on the desert below her feet.

Boom! Boom! Boom!

The loud sound descended again, it became more and more frequent, the ground was shaking along with it.

Plump Lady's mouth was dry, her heart was pounding from shock as she felt that her killer move was not trapping a person, she was trapping a fearsome monster that was even fiercer than the desolate beast evil dragon!

Bam!

The huge dragon statue could suppress him no longer, it completely disintegrated.

The surface of the desert swelled up like a tumor, sand burst out and rained down, as a huge figure appeared before Plump Lady once again.

It was a moonless night, winds were blowing intensely, giving off an eerie and scary feeling.

An eight armed monster that was six meters in height, Fang Yuan who had a green face and sharp fangs was like a demon god incarnate, he bought fear and nightmares to this world.

Different from before, he was covered in a black armor, the armor was spiky and looked very fearsome. It was extremely thick and could make Fang Yuan's tall and mighty heavenly zombie body become even more imposing, his demonic aura was oozing everywhere.

This was Fang Yuan's defensive killer move!

If Plump Lady lived for another four hundred years, she would recognize this: During the chaotic five regions war, this was the most common defensive killer move, 'hair armor'. It had the rank five indestructible steel mane Gu as its core, with several hundred Gu worms as assistance, it allowed a Gu Immortal to grow an absurd amount of hair all over their body, to form body armor. Not only was this cheap and efficient, it had great defense and the Gu worms used were easy to replenish if they were damaged.

After Fang Yuan became an immortal zombie, his hair had become tough as steel, when he used hair armor, the effect was greater than most ordinary bodies of Gu Immortals.

Using hair armor and his immortal zombie body, he took on burial dragon sand coffin directly without taking any injury!

This killer move had appeared four hundred years in advance, Plump Lady could not recognize it, but it did not hinder her from evaluating this killer move's value.

"This defensive killer move is stronger than my martial sand armor. If it is sold in treasure yellow heaven, it would be sold at two and a half immortal essence stones!"

Thinking of this, Plump Lady's battle intent fell again: "Sir, I am Mo clan's Gu Immortal, I am chasing a thief, I mistook you for him. I believe that you are not Ling Hu Xu now, this is a misunderstanding! It is said that friends are often made after a fight, we should..."

Fang Yuan laughed coldly: "Hehehe, interesting. Mo clan's Gu Immortal, if I kill you, it will surely be very enjoyable."

This was the first time Fang Yuan had spoken in this battle. His voice was hoarse and terrible to listen to, Plump Lady shuddered when she listened to him.

Mo clan was a super force in western desert, an overlord that dominated a territory.

But Fang Yuan was fearless, he had no consideration for Mo clan at all.

Plump Lady's heart sank to rock bottom: "Where did this demonic cultivator come from? Such incredible battle strength, high quality among rank six Gu Immortals, yet he is so arrogant and ruthless!"

Next, Plump Lady saw a pair of wings growing on Fang Yuan's back, his wings were black that of a bat's, black and huge, they flapped!

The bat wings vanished like an illusion, but it caused Fang Yuan's body to shoot forward at lightning speed.

"So fast! This is a killer move especially for movement!!" Plump Lady's pupils shrunk, she had made up her mind to run.

She screamed shrilly, her plump face could not conceal the immense fear and shock she felt.

Seeing that Fang Yuan was getting close, Plump Lady's body burst out with a dazzling yellow light. The yellow light caused her body to move back rapidly, she escaped in the opposite direction at lightning speed.

Fang Yuan activated the movement killer move 'light illusion bat wings' again, but could not catch up to her.

A few breaths later, Plump Lady vanished into the horizons.

"Plump Lady suffered a huge loss, she even used her killer move light sand escape, her foundation will definitely be affected. This guy is so absurd, he actually fought till Plump Lady escaped!" Far away, Ling Hu Xu hid deeply within a sand dune as he suppressed his aura, not daring to show any flaws in his concealment.

"She escaped quickly." Fang Yuan snorted, he stopped at the battlefield and used investigative Gu to search.

Ling Hu Xu did not dare to breathe loudly, he felt that the investigative Gu's aura had been sweeping the area where he was hiding in.

Fang Yuan searched for a long time, but seeing that there was no effect, he left.

"He's finally gone, eh, weird! Why is my heart in so much unrest!" Ling Hu Xu had just wanted to come out, when suddenly his heart shook and he changed his mind.

Time had slowly passed and it was already late at night.

A figure moved like a phantom, descending from a high altitude, it was Fang Yuan.

He had purposely left, turning around and flying into the clouds, secretly inspecting the ground. He had waited for a long time but did not see anyone.

He snorted coldly, giving up on his search and returning to Sha Jing oasis.

"So close, so close! This demon is really scheming and cunning, thankfully I was careful, otherwise, I would've fallen for his trap." Ling Hu Xu curled up in the sand nearby, breaking out in cold sweat from fear.

In the darkness, his eyes were moving randomly: "What is the origin of this demon? Where did he come from? What unspeakable secrets does he have?"

Ling Hu Xu was extremely curious: "But this demon's investigation methods cannot discover me, should I trail him and see what he is up to?"

But when he thought about Fang Yuan pretending to leave and returning, his thoughts were extinguished like a candle.

"This demon is not only ruthless and cruel, he is also very crafty and cunning, I should forget about it. Anyway, the immortal essence stones are already mine..."

Ling Hu Xu discarded this thought, he did not dare to come out of the desert's surface, he drilled underground.

He did not have much battle strength, but he had many movement killer moves, his speed underground was unexpectedly not slower than an ordinary Gu Immortal's flight.

He chose the opposite direction as Fang Yuan and left.

Fang Yuan returned to Sha Jing oasis once again.

Lights lit up the oasis, as loud noises resounded everywhere.

Even though Fang Yuan had purposely gone far away, the battle of the Gu Immortals still caused quite the commotion, the mortals were all panic-stricken.

Fang Yuan ignored them, he used luck inspection Gu and found Han Li again.

He was extremely alert, he concealed his traces as he used connect luck Gu secretly. This time, it was smooth sailing and there were no more accidents.

The two had their luck connected, Fang Yuan could see that Han Li's monolith luck was shrinking at an shocking pace.

Soon after, the monolith luck was filled with cracks, it crumbled.

A few breaths later, Han Li's luck fell to an ordinary mortal's smoke trace level.

Next, his faint gray-white smoke turned black.

"Oh no." Fang Yuan saw this and his heart sank.

At the same time, Han Li was eating with his parents who had returned.

He was extremely hungry, he gobbled up the food.

"Eat slowly, son." His mother laughed dotingly, she was very concerned about her son.

"Guh, guh!" Suddenly, Han Li grabbed his throat, his eyes were wide open, he choked!

"Son, quickly spit it out!" His parents were shocked, they moved frantically.

But they did not manage to save Han Li.

He was dead.

Chapter 676: Human Medicine Gu

Han Li woke up in his bed, he slowly regained consciousness and opened his eyes.

Beside his bed, his parents were kneeling on the ground, kowtowing to an elderly Gu Master non-stop, they were expressing their gratitude.

"Doctor Mo, thank you for saving our son!"

"Doctor Mo, we will remember your kindness for the rest of our lives!"

"Father, mother..." Han Li spoke with much difficulty, he muttered softly.

"My son, my precious son! You are finally awake!" Han Li's mother heard his voice and jumped onto the bed, crying from joy.

"Little rascal, you are finally awake! Quickly thank Doctor Mo, if he was not here by chance, you would have died." Han Li's father was overjoyed, he quickly reminded him.

"Doctor, Doctor Mo, thank you for saving my life." Han Li saw Doctor Mo and fear flashed across his eyes.

"Mm, I am the Gu Master that is stationed in Han village, it was natural for me to save you. You were lucky today, you met me when I was patrolling the village." Doctor Mo laughed.

Next, he left quietly while Han Li's parents were thanking him with all their hearts.

"Oh? This is interesting." Fang Yuan did not leave, he was lurking nearby, watching this scene.

After he succeeding in connecting their luck, Han Li's luck fell drastically, it rapidly turned into a thin layer of deathly black luck.

If Han Li was a Gu Master with ample strength, he could ignore this luck. But he was a mortal, and a weak child among mortals, he was immediately killed by the backlash of this deathly black luck, choking on his food.

Fang Yuan wanted to save him immediately.

He had large numbers of mortal healing Gu, a matter like choking could be easily resolved, he could be saved as long as a long time had not passed.

As long as a person is not dead, their luck would not stop. If Han Li died like this, Fang Yuan's disastrous luck would only be alleviated for the moment, but it would continue getting worse, the root of the problem would not be solved.

If Han Li was alive, then by connecting his luck to Fang Yuan's all the time, Fang Yuan's horrible luck would slowly improve.

But the moment he was about to make a move, a figure jumped out of a large house in the village, rushing towards Han Li's house.

Seeing the movement Gu he was using, this was evidently a rank two Gu Master.

Fang Yuan squinted his eyes, he silently got closer to the village, deciding to watch the event unfold.

When this rank two Gu Master arrived at Han Li's house, he straightened his clothes and pretended to be carefree, next he 'accidentally' discovered Han Li choking.

Because of the pleas of Han Li's parents, he saved Han Li and revived him.

"From their conversation, this Doctor Mo should be a healing Gu Master that is stationed in the village. But it seems that Han Li and this Doctor Mo have some secret connection." Fang Yuan thought.

In order to control mortals, Gu Master forces would send one or two Gu Masters to look after the respective villages in turns.

Like Gu Yue Jiang Ya on Qing Mao mountain, he was this kind of stationed Gu Master.

When Han Li and his family fell asleep, Fang Yuan sneaked into the house. He went to Han Li and used a mortal Gu, causing him to fall into deeper sleep.

Fang Yuan stretched out his eight huge arms, he searched all over Han Li's body and soon, he found something amiss.

There were quite a few Gu worms on Han Li's body, his entire body's flesh and blood seemed to be influenced by Gu worms.

These arrangements felt very familiar to Fang Yuan.

A weakness of a zombie was that their cognition would slow. Fang Yuan could not find the key point and had to use the wills he stored in his mind to assist in thinking.

He looked through his memories and soon found the truth: "It turns out this so called Doctor Mo is refining human medicine Gu."

This human medicine Gu is a rank three Gu. It uses a human child as the main refinement material, taking years to slowly nurture and grow.

Once the human medicine Gu was refined, it could only be used once to increase a person's lifespan, but it had huge drawbacks.

"That Doctor Mo is no longer young, it seems he wants to use human medicine Gu to increase his lifespan, thus he placed his sights on Han Li. No wonder Han Li could grab the leaves of the dagger grass without any gloves, that was because his body had already been modified secretly. This is also why Doctor Mo came over quickly when Han Li choked, that was because he had placed a Gu worm in Han Li's body that could monitor him. And finally, even though Han Li choked to death, he could still be revived easily, that was because the human medicine Gu's refinement process caused his vitality to increase greatly." Fang Yuan realized at once.

Even though he found out Doctor Mo's scheme, he did not do anything to stop him.

"If Doctor Mo mysteriously dies, Han village would definitely be investigated. If he does not die, in order to refine human medicine Gu, he would need to take good care of Han Li. There are still three to four years until human medicine Gu finishes refining, while I just need Han Li to be alive."

Fang Yuan activated luck inspection Gu again, checking Han Li's luck.

Ever since the luck connection had succeeded, Han Li's luck had fallen drastically, his special luck was gone, becoming like that of a normal mortal, a thin layer of luck resembling faint smoke.

Fang Yuan observed for a while, noticing that the black color in Han Li's luck had vanished, turning into a grey-white color.

Fang Yuan heaved a sigh of relief.

He summed up his experiences this time to reach a conclusion: Black color represents death, without the black color in his luck, Han Li was in no danger of dying for the moment.

As the saying goes, every cloud has a silver lining, there could be great fortune after surviving a near death experience, after Han Li's crisis just now, his luck had been improving.

"Thinking about it, I narrowly survived a disaster in northern plains by relying on my own strength and schemes. Ever since I escaped from the wind veil of assimilation, half of my black coffin luck has most likely dissipated. But even so, Han Li was nearly killed by my luck. It seems I have to find a few more targets and connect our luck together."

Fang Yuan's gaze shined for a bit, in the end, he secretly placed some Gu worms on Han Li's body before leaving.

Using his superior methods, there was no way the rank two Doctor Mo could find them.

One day, if Doctor Mo tries to harm Han Li, he will definitely suffer severe consequences.

"Lad, I gave you three lifelines. From now on, you will have to rely on yourself. Hehe..."

Fang Yuan arrived silently, and left unnoticed, not leaving behind a single trace.

He first went far away from Sha Jing oasis, before activating Fixed Immortal Travel at an empty location.

At the next moment, he appeared in central continent.

A huge heavenly river flowed down from the sky, it flowed through the entirety of central continent, towards the eastern side of central continent, into eastern sea.

At the downstream parts of the heavenly river, because of the impact caused by the water, it formed a huge fertile plain.

There were abundant resources in the plain, people and nature flourished in abundance, countless small and middle sized sects were established here.

Among these sects, there was one small sect that was inconspicuous, but had quite the grand name, it was called Universal Life Academy.

Fang Yuan hid in a forest, observing them from afar.

The academy was in a mountain valley, there were only a few rooms here with only one square. It seems that they were currently holding a sect competition, as there were two stages in this square, with hundreds of Gu Masters watching below the stages.

This battle between mortal Gu Masters was extremely short, there was nothing too outstanding. But in the eyes of the spectators, it was extremely exciting.

Especially for the youngster, Hong Yi, who was standing among the crowd, this competition had great meaning.

"I have bull strength, tiger strength, and even obtained the Gu worm 'rewind' by chance, my battle strength is first-rate among rank two Gu Masters. During this competition, I must shock everyone with my skill and obtain the number one spot in the academy. This way, I can force my father to relent and place my mother's memorial tablet in the ancestral hall!" Hong Yi clenched his fists, deciding in his mind.

At the same time, Fang Yuan who was far away muttered with bright shining eyes: "Found you, Hong Yi."

This Hong Yi's luck was not worse than Han Li, he was also a rank seven legend that appeared during the five regions chaotic war. He cultivated strength and soul path, he had exemplary talent and was extremely skilled in self-creating killer moves.

He had many fortuitous encounters, he obtained the body of an ancient rockman king, he deciphered an inheritance left behind by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, and even through a lucky coincidence managed to subdue an ancient desolate beast, white horn qilin, as his steed.

Even though he found his target, Fang Yuan did not strike immediately.

"Right now, this scene is in the middle of broad daylight, I will cause quite a commotion when I use Connect Luck, I might be discovered."

This was not Han village.

In Han village, there was only one rank two Gu Master stationed, but here, it was an entire sect full of Gu Masters.

Not only this, there were three to four other small to mid sized forces in the valley.

In this entire plain at the downstream of the heavenly river, there were countless sects. Among these mortals, there were even some lone cultivator Gu Immortals. These Gu Immortals were all creators of the sects, if Fang Yuan used connect luck Immortal Gu here, he might be discovered by them.

"I can only wait until night when everyone is asleep. I will arrange many mortal Gu and try to conceal the area, it is worth a try..."

Fang Yuan was very experienced and cunning, he would never be lacking in patience.

When it was night time, Universal Life Academy became silent, as Fang Yuan opened his eyes: "Very good, I have arranged over ten thousand Gu worms in the vicinity of the valley, my preparations are complete. To conceal the aura of the Immortal Gu, I will need to use Connect Luck for half the night... hmm?"

Right at this moment, there was the sound of a spatial disturbance in his aperture.

A moving perspective cup Gu appeared out of nowhere in his immortal aperture.

There was a letter in the moving perspective cup Gu.

"Is Tai Bai Yun Sheng in trouble?" Fang Yuan's consciousness entered the Gu, he soon found out that the letter did not come from Tai Bai Yun Sheng, but from Fairy Li Shan.

After the Snowy Mountain Alliance, Fang Yuan passed Fairy Li Shan and Hei Lou Lan a moving perspective cup Gu each, while he kept the other half of their respective moving perspective cup Gu.

The contents of the letter made Fang Yuan frown deeply.

This was a letter asking for help by Fairy Li Shan on Hei Lou Lan's behalf.

Hei Lou Lan was being chased down by her father, she was in great danger.

"How can this be? Damn it!" Fang Yuan sighed deeply, because of their oath, he had to put aside his own matters and swiftly return to northern plains to assist Hei Lou Lan.

In any case, for the time being, Hong Yi was going to stay here, it would be easy for Fang Yuan to find him.

"I'll let you off for now." Fang Yuan hurriedly retrieved most of his Gu worms, avoiding leaving behind traces as much as possible, before he sneaked into a cave and used Fixed Immortal Travel.

At the next moment, he arrived in a secret room at the third peak of Snowy Mountain blessed land.

In the secret room, Fairy Li Shan was pacing back and forth worriedly, upon seeing Fang Yuan, she got close to him: "You are finally back! I am extremely anxious, the situation is terrible, Little Lan is being pursued by that evil scoundrel."

"Why aren't you helping her?" Fang Yuan frowned.

"I was going to act, but Little Lan urged me to continue hiding our connection, she did not want our relationship to be disclosed. You came alone? Where is Tai Bai Yun Sheng?"

"He has other matters now." Fang Yuan asked again: "How many Gu Immortals are pursuing her?"

"Only two, one is Hei Cheng while the other is Xue Song Zi. I placed an investigative Gu on Hei Lou Lan, her situation is very dangerous now. Quick, I will use my thoughts to transmit the scenery to you, quickly go save her!"

Fang Yuan inspected the thoughts and used Fixed Immortal Travel. At the next moment, he appeared beside Hei Lou Lan.

Chapter 677: First Battle with Hei Cheng

"Lou Lan, stop running. You are my daughter, why would I harm you? Don't listen to other people's defamation. We as father and daughter have a huge misunderstanding. I admit, it is true that I have the yin-yang life extension method, but this method cannot harm lives. Your mother really passed away because of the earthly calamity." Hei Cheng floated in the air, using a tone like one who felt unjustly treated, trying to persuade Hei Lou Lan.

He wore a black robe and had fair skin, his eyes were dark and his face was like jade. He had beautiful facial features and gave off a vibrant aura, he was truly a famously handsome man among northern plains' Gu Immortals.

When he urged Hei Lou Lan, his tone was sincere, it was overflowing with emotions, coupled with his good looks, outsiders who did not know the details might have truly believed him.

But Hei Lou Lan already had clearly seen this man's true colors, she gritted her teeth: "Evil scum, who would believe your hypocritical lies? If the yin-yang life extension method really cannot harm lives, why don't you let me see it? Hehe, I believe that Xue Song Zi at your side will also be very interested."

Xue Song Zi was tall and thin, he wore blue clothes and his snowy-white hair extended to his feet, he stood beside Hei Cheng without saying a word.

He was a demonic path Gu Immortal, he controlled the seventh peak of Snowy Mountain blessed land. Earlier, he had sponsored Ma tribe and Ma tribe lost in the Imperial Court contest, thus he was heavily suppressed by Hei tribe.

Next, in order to obtain the strength path Immortal Gu, Hei Lou Lan exposed the secret of Hei Cheng causing harm to Su Xian Er to him.

Xue Song Zi thus had a secret weapon to restrain Hei Cheng.

Hei Lou Lan had wanted to use Xue Song Zi to ruin Hei Cheng's reputation, but to think that the two of them had actually ganged up.

Upon hearing this from Hei Lou Lan, Xue Song Zi's eyes moved about as he turned around towards Hei Cheng with much interest: "Maybe I can help your daughter evaluate it?"

Hei Cheng snorted, ignoring Xue Song Zi's words. He changed his attitude, his eyes shining with cold light as he spoke to Hei Lou Lan calmly: "Daughter, you do not know what is good for you."

Hei Lou Lan spat in response to his words, but what came out was blood.

She was in her true form now, she was bathed in blood as her armor was broken, she was in a pathetic state. Her gaze however, turned more ruthless as her killing intent boiled.

She showed a mocking expression on her face: "Father? Hehe, the grand righteous path rank seven Gu Immortal, Lord Hei Cheng, actually brought along a demonic path Gu Immortal with him to coerce his daughter. If this scene was shown to the world, I wonder what would happen?"

Hei Cheng was indifferent towards such mocking words, he smiled lightly and showed his deep and unfathomable shrewdness: "Lou Lan, you have nowhere to run. You have the Great Strength True Martial Physique, it is ten times as hard for you to become a Gu Immortal compared to normal people. Without my help, you cannot become a strength path Gu Immortal."

"Hmph, kill me if you have the guts!" Hei Lou Lan showed her fierce nature, her expression turned ruthless as her aura surged: "If you force my hand, I will self-detonate! I will let all your efforts go down the drain, when your plans fail, I wonder what you can do!"

Hei Cheng laughed: "If you die, how will you avenge your mother? You've endured this and lurked for so many years, painstakingly developing, wasn't it all for revenge? Unfortunately, mortal and immortals are worlds apart, even if you have one of the ten extreme physiques and are able to bully some bottom-tier rank six Gu Immortals. For you to kill me, a rank seven Gu Immortal, hmph, delusional!"

Although he said that, Hei Cheng still felt some agitation in his heart.

Hei Lou Lan pointed out Hei Cheng's concerns, although he had the Immortal Gu Dark Arrow, this Immortal Gu could only be used to attack.

Hei Cheng did not have capturing methods, if he forced her hand, and Hei Lou Lan self-detonates, he could not stop her.

Most importantly, such acts of harming his daughter could not be known to the public, he could only work in secret.

Otherwise, with Hei Cheng's reputation and influence in northern plains' righteous path, he could bring at least five to six Gu Immortals with him.

But now, he only brought Xue Song Zi.

And Xue Song Zi was a demonic path Gu Immortal of Snowy Mountain. He only would care about benefits and could not be trusted. Although he seemed to be an ally, Hei Cheng from the beginning was guarding against him.

Earlier, Hei Lou Lan had exposed his secret, after Xue Song Zi obtained this weakness, he did not expose it to the public.

Destroying Hei Cheng's reputation could decrease Hei tribe Gu Immortals' pressure on Xue Song Zi. But if he used it to threaten Hei Cheng, he would be able to gain more benefits.

Thus, before the wind veil of assimilation appeared, Xue Song Zi found Hei Cheng in person and threatened him with this secret.

Hei Cheng was stunned at that moment, his secret that had been hidden for so many years was known by an outsider, he almost lost his bearings.

But he was an old and shrewd person, he quickly calmed down and used his glib tongue to accede to a portion of Xue Song Zi's requests.

Next, Hei Cheng even urged Xue Song Zi to cooperate, as long as he assisted in the plan and it succeeded, he would gain more benefits.

Xue Song Zi gave an overbearing request, he was interested in the yin-yang life extension method.

Although Xue Song Zi was middle aged and also had lifespan Gu, who among Gu Immortals would not be interested in a life extension method?

Hei Cheng was furious and helpless, he could only agree for now.

Thus, Hei Cheng and Xue Song Zi's seemingly united but internally divided alliance was formed.

Just as Hei Lou Lan, Hei Cheng and Xue Song Zi were at a stalemate, a bright jade green light burst out beside Hei Lou Lan.

The jade light dissipated, revealing Fang Yuan's huge body.

He was six meters tall and had eight arms, he had a green face and red eyes, his entire body was covered in a black shiny armor which had many spikes on it.

Facing strong foes, Fang Yuan did not dare to be careless, he first used the defensive killer move, hair armor, before using Fixed Immortal Travel to come here.

Although Fixed Immortal Travel could only transport humans, when Gu Masters use Gu worms, they can form clothes and armor, and would not have to teleport naked every time.

Back when Fang Yuan teleported from Three Kings blessed land to Hu Immortal blessed land, because he was short on time and did not have the relevant Gu worms, he had to teleport naked, and gave Feng Jin Huang an unforgettable experience.

"You are finally here." Hei Lou Lan saw that her reinforcement had arrived, her expression brightened.

"Which Gu Immortal is this? Who are you?!" Xue Song Zi quickly asked in shock.

Fang Yuan rapidly looked at the two in the air, his voice was hoarse as his surging killing intent was displayed: "The person who will kill you."

As he spoke nonsense with them, he transmitted to Hei Lou Lan: "Quick! We cannot stay here for long, enter my immortal aperture and I'll bring you away."

Hearing that Fang Yuan was trying to kill him, Xue Song Zi flew into a rage: "Such words."

Next to him, the Gu Immortal Hei Cheng reacted more quickly: "Attack! That Immortal Gu is Fixed Immortal Travel, he only needs three breaths of time to escape. We cannot give them any opportunities!"

As they spoke, Hei Lou Lan had already entered Fang Yuan's immortal aperture.

Xue Song Zi's expression turned severe, he waved his sleeves and created a curved moon blade wheel that was the size of a horse carriage.

The blade wheel spun in the air, slashing at Fang Yuan.

Killer move — Icy Wind Blade Wheel!

The blade wheel made of ice was extremely sharp, it was oozing with frost energy and was extremely fast when pushed by the wind.

Before the blade wheel had reached him, Fang Yuan could feel the icy winds blowing on him.

"This killer move is very fierce, it has the essence of both ice and wind path, its value is at least three immortal essence stones!" Fang Yuan squinted, he logically chose to evade it.

Killer move — Light Illusion Bat Wings!

Two large phantom black bat wings appeared behind him, after the phantom wings flapped, they vanished.

Fang Yuan gained a huge boost in speed, he moved like lightning and flew sideways, dodging the icy wind blade wheel.

The blade wheel hit the ground, making a loud sound as it dug deep into the ground like cutting tofu.

On the grassland, the blade wheel carved out a huge trench, and ice that was tough as rocks formed on the sides of the trench.

Although Fang Yuan dodged the icy wind blade wheel, Hei Cheng's attack was right in front of him.

This was a very inconspicuous small black arrow.

The body of the arrow was short, it was about half a person's arm length, it was black and did not give out any aura of danger.

But precisely because of this, Fang Yuan was on extreme alert.

This was the attack of the Immortal Gu Dark Arrow.

Hei Cheng was experienced in battles, he was ruthless and used his trump card from the start!

Fang Yuan quickly activated his killer move, light illusion bat wings, but the black arrow was like a magnet attracted to him, it changed directions agilely and was fixed on Fang Yuan, he could not shrug it off at all.

Immortal Gu Dark Arrow's attack could home in on enemies and turn in different directions, its speed was fast. Even though Fang Yuan was a flying master, he could not shake it off. As the distance between him and the dark arrow shortened, he fell under greater threat!

Fang Yuan's defensive killer move, hair armor, although it had a high price to performance ratio, and was widely spread during the five regions chaotic war, it was only a mortal killer move, Dark Arrow could pierce it in one hit.

Even though Fang Yuan's immortal zombie body was strong, it could not resist the might of Dark Arrow.

Especially when this dark arrow ignored Fang Yuan's body, heart and other areas, only aiming for his sole weakness — his brain.

After becoming an immortal zombie, Fang Yuan's heart, throat, anus, and all other areas were no longer weak points in his body, even if they were destroyed, he would still function fine and would not take too much damage.

But his brain was different.

If his brain was destroyed, his mind would also perish. Fang Yuan would be unable to think, unable to act, and would be at his enemy's mercy.

Activating Fixed Immortal Travel required three breaths of time, but the dark arrow chased relentlessly, Fang Yuan did not have the time for it.

Fang Yuan moved around rapidly, the many mortal Gu that made up his killer move, light illusion bat wings, were starting to be worn down.

"It is over." Hei Cheng laughed coldly, waving his sleeves and shooting out another dark arrow.

"My dark arrow Immortal Gu is merely rank six and can only shoot out up to three dark arrows at the same time. No matter who you are, making me use two dark arrows to deal with you, it should be your honor." Hei Cheng looked at Fang Yuan struggling at the brink of death as he evaluated arrogantly.

"Hmph, what are you so proud of, I was just toying with you." Fang Yuan spoke in a hoarse voice and laughed suddenly.

Two dark arrows attacked him at once, he knew he could no longer avoid using green grape immortal essence, activating the Immortal Gu Worldly Wave Trace.

Swoosh!

A huge wave appeared below Fang Yuan's feet.

The waves moved quickly, Fang Yuan stepped on them as he quickly created some distance from the dark arrows.

The power of an Immortal Gu was truly extraordinary.

Earlier, Fang Yuan had used light illusion bat wings no less than a hundred times, but he could not escape from the dark arrows. But right now, he had just used Worldly Wave Trace once and immediately moved far away from it.

Chapter 678: Number Four in the List of Mystical Gu

"Another Immortal Gu!" Xue Song Zi's expression changed, his gaze was heated, looking extremely jealous and envious.

To think that in order to obtain wooden chicken Immortal Gu, he spent so much effort in scheming, yet his plans still failed him.

The immortal zombie in front of him actually had Immortal Gu, which most ordinary Gu Immortals did not have, and he even had two!

"Hehehe, Hei Cheng, Xue Song Zi, that will be all for today. Enjoy your life from now on, because you do not have much time left." Fang Yuan's tone was chilling.

He stepped on the flying wave, at the same time, a jade green light flashed on his body.

Three breaths of time later, Fixed Immortal Travel carried him across space, leaving this battlefield.

Two dark arrows arrived at his former location, only hitting the last trace of jade light remaining.

"Oh no, they ran away!" Xue Song Zi's expression was extremely ugly, he questioned Hei Cheng: "Aren't you a rank seven Gu Immortal? Why couldn't you stop them!"

"Xue Song Zi, mind your tone." Hei Cheng was expressionless, he gave Xue Song Zi a cold glance.

Xue Song Zi was pressured by Hei Cheng's grand aura, his expression became less overbearing.

Hei Cheng spoke calmly: "The other party has two movement Immortal Gu, unless we have an Immortal Gu that can seal the environment, we can only watch them escape. However, the tracing method I used on Hei Lou Lan is extremely secretive, it is a killer move at the peak of the mortal level. As long as she shows up in northern plains again, I will detect her."

"Also, this was not a fruitless trip, we have already found out that Hei Lou Lan has a force backing her. Without help, there is no way she could've reached this stage. I just did not expect an immortal zombie with two movement Immortal Gu to show up. It seems the force behind Hei Lou Lan is not simple at all. Hehe, the situation is getting interesting."

Saying this, Hei Cheng showed a faint smile, he felt no dejection after this loss.

He did not strike against Hei Lou Lan, on one hand, he was wary of her self-detonation, on the other hand, he wanted to draw out her mysterious backer.

"What are you saying?" Xue Song Zi's gaze focused.

"Immortal zombies are often the result of Gu Immortals who are forced by circumstances when they have no way of extending their lifespan. Do you think this immortal zombie is truly the person supporting Hei Lou Lan behind the scenes?" Hei Cheng asked with deep meaning.

Fang Yuan did not fight against them, he only displayed his flying master attainment when he dodged the dark arrows.

But this attainment was nothing special for Gu Immortals who had lived for hundreds of years.

At this moment, Hei Cheng and Xue Song Zi did not know Fang Yuan's true battle strength, and Fang Yuan did not receive much of their attention, they thought he was a normal immortal zombie.

Xue Song Zi's gaze flickered: "I understand what you mean. This immortal zombie is not the crucial person, his two movement Immortal Gu are most likely loaned to him by others."

Hei Cheng nodded: "That's right, this mysterious person is likely to be someone we know. They sent an unfamiliar immortal zombie over here to help, that means it was not convenient for them to appear."

"This mysterious person is leaving no clues for us, how will we investigate?" Xue Song Zi felt a headache, an enemy hiding in the dark was the most troublesome kind, not only did he feel restrained, he did not know who to trust and who to target.

"They have already shown a flaw." Hei Cheng laughed loudly: "Be it Fixed Immortal Travel or Worldly Wave Trace, they are both related to central continent. Such an obvious clue is enough for us to discover many things. As long as I can uncover the true identity of that person, I will be able to take them down all at once!"

Saying this, Hei Cheng showed a ruthless expression on his face.

Fixed Immortal Travel brought Fang Yuan back to Fairy Li Shan's residence.

"Little Lan, how are your injuries?" Seeing that Hei Lou Lan was leaving Fang Yuan's immortal aperture while covered in blood, Fairy Li Shan was very nervous, she quickly went over and checked.

"Little aunt, it is not a problem. That scoundrel did not attack me seriously, he was only putting on a show." Hei Lou Lan laughed, as if she was not the one injured.

Fairy Li Shan's heart was eased, she let out a breath of turbid air: "It seems that your guess is right, Little Lan, that scoundrel really planted some tracking method on your body. This method is extremely well hidden, we could not find it even after searching intensely several times."

Fang Yuan heard this and his gaze turned cold, he looked at Hei Lou Lan closely: "That is to say, you were discovered by Hei Cheng on purpose?"

"I would not say it was on purpose." Hei Lou Lan looked into Fang Yuan's eyes without any fear: "Earlier, little aunt found some crucial information, it was regarding the whereabouts of Ma Hong Yun. Ma Hong Yun was taken away by a northern plains Gu Immortal, Qin Bai Sheng, his blessed land is situated in crimson reed marsh. I went there intending to sneak into the blessed land and see if the information was true. I didn't expect that Hei Cheng was also nearby, the moment I stepped into crimson reed marsh, he detected me."

Fang Yuan nodded, he believed what Hei Lou Lan said.

Of course, this was not because he trusted Hei Lou Lan, but because this was part of the Snowy Mountain Alliance — allies could have personal secrets, but they could not lie. If you did not say it, then that is fine. But if you spoke, it had to be the truth, otherwise the oath would kill you.

"Ma Hong Yun, as his name suggests, has fortune that rivals heaven. If I connect my luck to him, it would be far more effective than Hong Yi and Han Li." Thinking of this, Fang Yuan asked: "How reliable is the information that Ma Hong Yun has been captured by Qin Bai Sheng?"

Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan looked at each other, as Fairy Li Shan said: "According to our analysis, there is a seventy percent chance that we can believe it. During the battle inside the wind veil of assimilation, dozens of Gu Immortals from the righteous and demonic path were involved. I was there at the time, it was a chaotic scene. After the battle, everyone had their own guesses on who captured Ma Hong Yun, and that resulted in dozens of small conflicts, but they were all proven to be wrong."

"This time, our information is different from the rumors, we have reason and evidence. Evidently, an insider had purposely leaked the information, Qin Bai Sheng is a rank seven lone cultivator Gu Immortal, he is a famous expert in the metal path, and also has his blessed land to defend himself. But Ma Hong Yun's matter involves Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's luck path true inheritance, this has too much of an attraction to northern plains' Gu Immortals. Especially when Qin Bai Sheng does not have the Huang Jin bloodline, everyone is jealous of him."

Fang Yuan nodded: "That is to say, this is a troublesome matter, if Ma Hong Yun was really captured by Qin Bai Sheng, then soon, a band of Gu Immortals are going to attack crimson reed marsh."

"That is exactly so!" Hei Lou Lan laughed heartily, her beautiful black pupils radiating with light: "The way I see it, this information should be true to a huge extent. Luckily, little aunt did not expose her identity this time, when the righteous and demonic Gu Immortals team up, they will need little aunt's mountain pledge Gu. At that time, we will be able to find a chance and intervene in this matter. If there is a chance for us to obtain the luck path true inheritance, we will strike. If not, we will take a step back, using the time in which that old scoundrel Hei Cheng is engaging in battle, I will have a chance to ascend to immortal!"

Hei Lou Lan was a formidable person, like Fang Yuan, she was very skilled in scheming.

Fang Yuan asked coldly: "Although this was the first time I met Hei Cheng, I can confirm that he is no simple character, if he refuses to join this, what will you do?"

To Hei Cheng, although the luck path true inheritance was important, it could not compare to his lifespan. There are so many people fighting for the luck path true inheritance, it is like a battle of tigers and wolves, he might as well stay uninvolved and settle the issue of Hei Lou Lan instead.

Fang Yuan's words directly addressed the problem, Hei Lou Lan's brows rose, she replied enthusiastically: "I do not have much time left, it has been fortunate I have had little aunt's help these recent days. In half a month, I will have to ascend regardless of the situation! If Hei Cheng comes to find trouble then, it will be a perfect time to deal with him once and for all!"

In her words, she had already disregarded the possibility of death, her fearless and resolute disposition was fully displayed.

"That means, there is a possibility I have to fight Hei Cheng? By then, we cannot escape, in order to protect you, I will to fight him head on?" Fang Yuan's gaze was uncertain.

Fairy Li Shan said: "Fang Yuan, don't forget, when a Gu Master ascends to the realm of immortal, there will be a huge influx of heaven and earth qi. Under that special environment, Hei Cheng's battle strength would be heavily suppressed. Little Lan's ascension is extremely important, I will be there personally. Together with Tai Bai Yun Sheng, we have three Gu Immortals on our side."

Hei Lou Lan replied graciously and understandingly: "Fang Yuan, in order to save me this time, you used Fixed Immortal Travel three times, and lost three green grape immortal essence beads. You also used one bead to activate worldly wave trace Gu, according to our alliance, you will be compensated twice the amount, that is eight immortal essence stones."

"That's right." Fang Yuan looked at Hei Lou Lan, it was so easy for intelligent people to communicate.

Fairy Li Shan spoke suddenly: "Eight immortal essence stones, I can give that to you right now. But I also have other things, Fang Yuan, perhaps you should take a look, you might be interested in them."

Saying this, she took out two killer moves and one Gu recipe.

Fang Yuan looked through them and was very interested.

Of the two killer moves, one was called 'poison breath', a poison path killer move. It could turn a Gu Immortal's breathing into a poisonous gas. The killer move had little strength, but its advantage was sustainability. If a long time passes, the Gu Immortal's surroundings would be covered in a layer of poisonous gas, it would unceasingly poison all the surrounding people and things.

But this killer move had a flaw, it was easy to hurt oneself. Especially an ordinary Gu Immortal's body, they needed to protect and heal their nostrils, throat, and lungs.

This weakness was non-existent to an immortal zombie like Fang Yuan.

The other killer move was called 'Kong Sheng Tian'. Kong Sheng Tian was the name of a person, he was the Gu Immortal who created this killer move. He was quite famous within Gu Master history, he controlled the number four Gu in the list of Top Ten Mystical Gu, qi escape Gu.

Spring Autumn Cicada was only ranked at seventh, while qi escape Gu was fourth, it was reverse refined from the legendary reputation Gu. In terms of flying speed in a straight line, it was the number one Gu in the world, no Gu was its match!

And this killer move was also a movement killer move. Back then, Kong Sheng Tian referred to qi escape Gu to create it. It could open the small pores on the Gu Immortal's body and blow out small air currents, causing the Gu Immortal to fly forward quickly. Not only was it fast, it could change directions very agilely.

The killer move Kong Sheng Tian was very suitable to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had a zombie's body, his body's pores were tough and durable, even if they were destroyed, his terrifying recovery speed would heal them quickly.

As for the Gu recipe, it was an ancient strength path Gu recipe, it could refine the rank five group strength Gu.

Undeniably, these three items had been collected by Fairy Li Shan for some time, they were specially prepared for Fang Yuan.

They were allies who had made an oath under Snowy Mountain, it was a good thing for Fairy Li Shan and Hei Lou Lan for Fang Yuan to be strong.

Chapter 679: Immortal Gu is hungry

Fang Yuan thought a moment and said to Fairy Li Shan: "I will take this poison breath killer move and the ancient Gu recipe. How many immortal essence stones for them?"

Fairy Li Shan replied: "Poison breath is two immortal essence stones and the group strength Gu's recipe is two immortal essence stones as well, so altogether it is four immortal essence stones."

Fang Yuan nodded, agreeing with Fairy Li Shan's quotation.

Poison breath was not an ordinary killer move and was indeed worth two immortal essence stones.

Group strength Gu might only be a rank five mortal Gu, but it was already extinct and as such its high price of two immortal essence stones was normal.

Fairy Li Shan took out three things, but this group strength Gu recipe which was the most unremarkable among them had the greatest attraction to Fang Yuan.

However, although the offer was fair, Fang Yuan was low in cash and wanted to haggle to save as many immortal essence stones as possible.

Thereupon, he said: "This group strength Gu recipe might be rare but it is an ancient Gu recipe; the refinement materials are very ancient and are now hard to find."

Fairy Li Shan smiled: "Fang Yuan, I have already considered this. I had originally planned to give this group strength Gu to Little Lan, the reason I am selling it to you now is because the main material in refining this Gu, stone monkey fur, has recently appeared in the market."

Hei Lou Lan added: "Right, in treasure yellow heaven, a Gu Immortal by the name of Shi Lei who calls himself Immortal Monkey King has managed to research and produce stone monkey fur in his blessed land. This Gu refinement material that had been extinct for countless years has now actually reappeared in his hands, causing quite a big commotion in treasure yellow heaven."

"In group strength Gu's recipe, the rarest material is stone monkey fur, while the others might be rare but as long as you look for them, you will be able to buy them, search for them or find substitutes using your own refinement path foundation."

The implied meaning of this was that no haggling would be accepted.

Fang Yuan was not discouraged: "Stone monkey fur? This ancient material might have reappeared now but it is entirely monopolized by Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei, the price will definitely not be cheap, right?"

"There is an old saying, 'good things are not cheap'. Fang Yuan, I have personally witnessed your immortal killer move, myriad self, and I still remember its astonishing might. There is no need for us to continue probing each other, group strength Gu is worth much more to you than to normal Gu Immortals. Two immortal essence stones is already quite cheap." Hei Lou Lan refused to yield any benefits.

If the other party understands you clearly, the situation would be rather troublesome to deal with.

However, Hei Lou Lan was right as well, four immortal essence stones in total was a fair price.

Fairy Li Shan did not cheat Fang Yuan of immortal essence stones, but she would not incur losses as well.

"Alright." Fang Yuan observed the situation and did not persist. Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan were not Lang Ya land spirit, excessive haggling would only be insulting their intelligence.

Both sides completed the transaction shortly afterwards.

Fang Yuan obtained the poison breath killer move and the ancient group strength Gu's recipe, as well as four immortal essence stones.

As for the movement killer move, Kong Sheng Tian, it was not suitable for Fang Yuan.

Kong Sheng Tian opened all the pores in one's body from which air would shoot out and propel the body. This killer move had extreme speed and could also give great flexibility in changing direction.

However, the opening of the pores in the whole body would greatly reduce Fang Yuan's defense.

Moreover, Fang Yuan's defensive killer move, hair armor, covered the whole body without leaving behind any gaps. If Kong Sheng Tian was used, he would not be able to use hair armor. If he used hair armor, Kong Sheng Tian could not be used.

These two were not compatible.

Fang Yuan thus gave up on the killer move Kong Sheng Tian.

His quantity of immortal essence stones increased to nineteen and a half, but he had huge pressure in converting them to green grape immortal essence and feeding his Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan was still lacking in cash and could not casually buy the relatively useless killer move.

When leaving, Fang Yuan did not extravagantly use Fixed Immortal Travel, instead opting to use a stargate.

Before leaving, he checked Hei Lou Lan's luck.

Hei Lou Lan was at rank five peak stage, her luck could be perceived by the rank five luck inspection Gu.

Hei Lou Lan's luck had already recovered from the extremely low state when she went against Ma Hong Yun. Her luck was like a giant pillar with the color of an azure sky, giving a feeling of being long lasting.

"Hei Lou Lan's luck clearly is at the level of Han Li's and Hong Yi's. From this, it seems her Gu Immortal advancement has a high probability of succeeding. But one can't just look at luck in everything, otherwise why would Hei Lou Lan die so suddenly in my previous life? One's luck might be good, but it depends on whether they can grasp it. Now it seems, Hei Cheng might be involved in Hei Lou Lan's unexpected death?"

Although Hei Lou Lan's luck was strong, it was written in detail in the Snowy Mountain Alliance that allies could not intentionally inflict harm to each other.

Fang Yuan was plagued with bad luck, and connecting his luck with her's would mean having an intent to harm.

Moreover, according to his previous life's memories, Fang Yuan was not too optimistic of Hei Lou Lan's future. Fang Yuan did not have break luck Gu, thus he could not carelessly connect luck and must choose his targets carefully.

Back in Hu Immortal Blessed Land, Fang Yuan took out eight immortal essence stones and converted them to his own green grape immortal essence.

He had used Fixed Immortal Travel many times, going back and forth from western desert, central continent, eastern sea and northern plains. He also used worldly wave trace Gu in the fight against Hei Cheng, using up a total of six green grape immortal essence.

He originally had seventeen green grape immortal essence beads, but only eleven remained now.

In consideration of the frequent battles recently, Fang Yuan refined eight immortal essence stones and increased his green grape immortal essence to nineteen beads.

With this, the amount of immortal essence stones on Fang Yuan was eleven and a half.

Fang Yuan reviewed his battle with Hei Cheng and felt satisfied about it.

Whether the result was victory or defeat was of no concern to Fang Yuan. He would not become angry or feel humiliated just because of failure. He would also not feel overjoyed and arrogant because of victory.

What he prioritized were the gains and losses.

He used up four beads of green grape immortal essence in this battle, but was able to obtain even more trust from Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan. At the same time, he also obtained four immortal essence stones, the poison breath killer move and group strength Gu's recipe.

He had clearly made a good profit.

"But if I were to speak of a loss, it would be worldly wave trace Immortal Gu." Fang Yuan took out the Immortal Gu Worldly Wave Trace.

Right now, the Immortal Gu's aura was no longer as stable as before and revealed a trace of weakness.

The Gu worm did not have a healthy luster, instead appearing dark and gloomy.

Fang Yuan was aware of why: "Worldly wave trace Gu was not fed properly back at Imperial Court blessed land. When the wind veil of assimilation appeared, Mo Yao's will activated Water Pavilion to battle, and after I obtained her Gu worms, I activated this Immortal Gu several times. It has already reached a certain limit and need to be fed. If it is still not fed and I activate it excessively, it might die from hunger."

Worldly wave trace Gu was the first Immortal Gu in Fang Yuan's possession that was 'crying of hunger'.

It could be foreseen that as time passed, many more Immortal Gu would cry out in hunger and would need to be fed.

However, worldly wave trace Gu's food was tens of thousands of underworld jellyfish and thousands of deepsea lightning eels.

Fang Yuan inquired Little Hu Immortal land spirit. After Tai Bai Yun Sheng left, the land spirit took over Tai Bai Yun Sheng's work of paying attention to movements in treasure yellow heaven.

However, although Fang Yuan had taken the initiative to post requests for the goods in treasure yellow heaven, there were few who responded.

This was not a highly commercialized society like that on Earth, the economy here was not developed and one could not buy whatever they wanted to buy.

Fang Yuan used moving perspective cup Gu to send a letter to Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng gave him a piece of good news. He had already arrived at Hai Shi blessed land and smoothly got into contact with some Gu Immortals, moreover, he also saw someone selling underworld jellyfishes in Hai Shi blessed land.

Only deepsea lightning eels were rarely seen as Gu Immortals had to enter the deep sea to capture them, which was not only dangerous, the sea areas where they were abundant were already controlled by Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance.

Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance housed the headquarters of Zombie Alliance within all five regions. They were very powerful, a level stronger than even the super forces of eastern sea.

Thus, Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance was domineering and rampant in their actions. They blockaded several large sea regions and controlled the large numbers of resources within themselves.

This maintained and fostered their strength, making them become even more domineering to others.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng suggested Fang Yuan to join Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance and then purchase the deepsea lightning eels internally. This was not only convenient, the price within Zombie Alliance would also be cheaper than outside.

Fang Yuan was moved but he had ascended to Gu Immortal in northern plains, his immortal aperture had northern plains' heaven and earth qi.

There were differences between the heaven and earth qi of the five regions. With just a simple test, one's origins would be clear.

It was not impossible for Fang Yuan to join Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance with the status of a northern plains immortal zombie status. But he had to join Northern Plains Zombie Alliance for his major plan.

This major plan had huge prospective yield, and Fang Yuan had been thinking of risking an act of disguise even if he was not an immortal zombie to join Northern Plains Zombie Alliance.

However, as an immortal zombie now, it was no doubt much more convenient to join Northern Plains Zombie Alliance.

"Joining Eastern Sea Zombie Alliance might make it convenient to purchase lightning eels, but if Tai Bai Yun Sheng is given some time to make connections, he would be able to purchase them, just that the price might be a bit higher. Although I won't be able to activate worldly wave trace Gu as much as I wish, it should hold on for some time." Fang Yuan was not willing to give up on his major plan, thus he refused Tai Bai Yun Sheng's suggestion in the end.

After resting and reorganizing for a while in Hu Immortal Blessed Land, Fang Yuan activated Fixed Immortal Travel to arrive at central continent again.

Universal Life Academy was located in mountain valley, and under the curtain of night, lights were lit up, making it appear quiet and tranquil.

Hong Yi was sitting cross-legged on the bed, finishing his daily routine of nourishing his aperture. He opened his eyes, his pupils shining brightly, revealing a look of expectation and excitement.

"I have placed in the top ten in today's competition without even having to reveal my true strength. Heaven is helping me, letting me coincidentally get a bye in the competition. People are treating me as just a lucky fellow. Tomorrow is the competition of the ten strongest, they will underestimate me and won't expect my true strength. The day after tomorrow is the decisive battle, as long as I use this Gu to break the opponent's defense, there is no need to mention what will happen next."

As he thought of this, Hong Yi took out a rank two Gu worm, Rewind. This was an extremely rare time path Gu worm which could be used to both attack and defend, its ability was to rewind an enemy's Gu worm to its state before the activation.

For instance, the enemy condensed a fire ball, but under rewind Gu's power, the Gu worm would return back to before activation and the fire ball would disappear.

However, rewind Gu had extremely huge demand on primeval essence; even Hong Yi with his A-grade aperture and over ninety percent primeval essence could only activate it once.

Chapter 680: Zhi Forest, Earth Horse

Hong Yi had decided long ago, he was going to use rewind Gu to deal with his opponent's defensive Gu.

As long as the other party did not use two defensive Gu at the same time, Hong Yi would just need to hit the opponent's body with one strike to heavily injure him, obtaining victory.

But if the opponent had two defensive Gu activated at the same time, Hong Yi would not go on the offensive immediately, he would start a drawn out battle. The enemy would definitely expend primeval essence faster than him if he uses two defensive Gu.

One could say, with this Gu in Hong Yi's hands, he had a great advantage, he was most likely the winner of this competition.

"If I get first, mother's memorial tablet would be placed in the ancestral hall, she would be given a proper status. Hmm?"

Suddenly, Hong Yi frowned, for one instant, he felt like his heart was empty, like something precious had been stolen from him.

"Don't tell me, because my wish is finally going to be fulfilled, I am starting to feel apprehensive? There is nothing valuable on me besides rewind Gu, what could be worth stealing?"

Hong Yi shook his head, he laughed bitterly, forgetting that weird sensation he felt earlier.

Far away in the valley, Fang Yuan breathed out deeply: "Connect Luck succeeded."

For the luck connection this time, he purposely made the best use of his time, rushing here immediately after resting in Hu Immortal blessed land for a while, thus, he did not come across any surprising disturbances.

Fang Yuan used luck inspection Gu to check Hong Yi's luck.

His luck was previously a milky white color, it was very special, giving people a feeling of vigor and vitality. His luck was gathered into a lump, forming the tall image of a scholar sitting and reading. The scholar's image was rather similar to Hong Yi, he had a lively expression.

But after connecting with Fang Yuan, this white scholar luck shrunk, it was not even thirty percent of the original.

The scholar's clean and smooth robe became a tattered shirt with random patches sewed onto it everywhere to maintain it. It was like a rich young master had turned into a poor man's child, a pitiful student. His expression was not so lively anymore, his face was thinner and his expression was darker, like he had experienced a terrible encounter.

"It seems that connecting my luck to these targets had its use. When I connected my luck to Han Li, I almost killed him. But this time, the connection to Hong Yi did not cause his luck to become deathly luck. It seems my own luck has improved greatly." Fang Yuan was gratified in his mind.

Just when he was about to leave, he suddenly felt a tug in his heart. He found two hidden Gu Masters lurking in this valley.

In order to undergo the luck connection, Fang Yuan had set up many Gu worms near Universal Life Academy's valley. On one hand, he wanted to conceal the aura of the Immortal Gu, but it was also to surveil the surroundings and provide early warnings to him.

One could say that the entire valley was under Fang Yuan's supervision.

Fang Yuan closed his eyes and concentrated.

These two hidden Gu Masters were not weak, they were rank five Gu Masters.

They were at the other end of the valley, secretly moving while talking softly.

"Sect Leader Fan Yi, are you sure that there is a zhi forest and earth horses underneath the surface of this valley?"

"Valley Lord Yuan Bai, there is no mistake, I saw it personally! Don't be anxious, follow me into the cavern, when you see it for yourself, won't you believe me?"

"Hmph, this is the territory of Universal Life Academy, if the principal of Universal Life Academy, Hong Xuan Ji, discovers us, we will be forced to bear the consequences of failure."

"Although Hong Xuan Ji is strong, he is lacking in investigative methods, otherwise, he would've found the great resources lying here already. We are intentionally hiding ourselves while he is unaware, how can he discover us?"

"Sigh, if we are discovered, our reputations would be ruined, the leaders of two sects venturing into Universal Life Academy late at night."

...

Fang Yuan heard the entirety of their conversation.

"Zhi forest, earth horses?" He thought.

Zhi forests grew underground, usually for dozens of li. The lingzhi inside were as large as trees, their meat was plump and juicy, they could be fed to Gu worms, used as Gu refinement materials or sold.

Earth horses were mutated beasts native to zhi forests. There were usually two or three in a single portion of zhi forest, they lived as a family. The hoof of the earth horse was the main ingredient of the rank five earth escape Gu. The eyes of the earth horse could refine the x-ray vision Gu, the tail hair of the earth horse could refine the smoke dust Gu.

The earth horse's body was full of treasures, it was no wonder the two rank five Gu Masters, Valley Lord Yuan Bai and Sect Leader Fan Yi, were interested.

But to Fang Yuan, the earth horses and zhi forest did not have any appeal.

An earth horse was a mutated beast that could be on par with a myriad beast king. But a family of earth horses was only two to three myriad beast kings. There were many people selling zhi forests in treasure yellow heaven, it was a common good and did not even require immortal essence stones to purchase.

"But for Universal Life Academy, the underground zhi forest is a huge benefit and an important stockpile of resources. Unfortunately, they are still kept in the dark now."

Fang Yuan thought about it, he followed behind the two rank five Gu Masters from afar, successfully entering the underground zhi forest.

As he estimated, this was an ordinary zhi forest, it was about ten li in size, and there were three earth horses. They were a family living in the zhi forest.

"What a huge zhi forest!" Sect Leader Fan Yi exclaimed as he walked in the forest.

"This is a land of treasures, why did it not appear in my valley? Sigh!" Valley Lord Yuan Bai touched the branches of the lingzhi, saying in jealousy.

Fang Yuan took a detour around them and got to the center of the zhi forest.

There was the largest lingzhi here, it was six meters tall, reaching the ceiling of the cave. The flesh of the lingzhi was like a huge umbrella, spreading out in a circular manner.

This was the lingzhi king.

Fang Yuan lowered his head and came to the lingzhi king.

Next to the lingzhi king, there were three earth horses guarding it, along with some metal consuming ant groups. Among the ant groups, there were some wild metal path Gu, and the lingzhi king also had some wild wood path Gu worms.

But these were all mortal, Fang Yuan did not conceal his immortal zombie aura, he came here without any obstruction.

Fang Yuan stretched out one monstrous claw, grabbing the stalk of the lingzhi king.

The lingzhi king trembled intensely, causing the ceiling of the cave to shake and debris to fall. The earth horses were suppressed by Fang Yuan's immortal zombie aura, they did not dare to get close, and only made cries from afar.

After Fang Yuan searched for a while, he pulled back his zombie claw.

In his monstrous claw, there was a heart.

This was the lingzhi king's heart, it was soft and hot, the surface was milky white, this was completely made of lingzhi flesh and gave off a meaty fragrance.

"As long as I plant this lingzhi king's heart, soon, a new forest will form." Fang Yuan took the treasure from right under their noses.

The soil of Hu Immortal blessed land was not suited to plant large areas of zhi forests. But to sustain a small area of it, there were no issues, of course, there were also not much benefits in doing so.

Fang Yuan was doing this purely for fun.

As for this huge zhi forest and the earth horses, Fang Yuan had no need for them. It was troublesome and time consuming to move them into Hu Immortal blessed land, he would rather purchase them directly in treasure yellow heaven if needed, it was more convenient.

After losing the heart, the lingzhi king would not die, but the zhi forest would stop growing, it would have to recuperate for over a decade.

"What sound is that?" Far away, Yuan Bai and Fan Yi glanced at each other, Fang Yuan taking away the lingzhi king's heart caused quite a commotion, along with the wailing horses.

But when Yuan Bai and Fan Yi got to the lingzhi king, Fang Yuan had vanished without a trace, he had left.

The remaining earth horse family exerted their anger and furious emotions on the two of them instead.

The intense battle quickly attracted the attention of Universal Life Academy.

Hong Xuan Ji lead a band of Gu Masters and rushed here, in shock and joy.

Yuan Bai and Fan Yi sighed in their hearts, feeling extremely unlucky.

After an intense battle, Hong Xuan Ji chased away Yuan Bai and Fan Yi, he gave orders to the elders of the academy who were in ecstasy: "The matter of the zhi forest is extremely important, from today onwards, we will halt the sect competition, and call back the disciples and elders who are out on missions. From now on, there will certainly be difficulties, Yuan Bai and Fan Yi are sure to gather other sects to exert pressure on us. We have to defend this zhi forest, it is our foundation to rise up!"

"Yes, lord principal!" The Gu Masters responded.

On the other hand, Hong Yi, who was sound asleep, had no idea that the sect competition that he was looking forward to had been canceled.

His desire to give his mother a proper status, that dream was going to have to be delayed for a long time.

Swish swish swish...

Waves were crashing on Fang Yuan's face, but such mild force could not make him feel anything.

This place was not in central continent, it was in southern border.

The river before him was the number two river of southern border — Jade Dragon River.

Southern border had three great rivers, the first was red dragon river, the second was jade dragon river, and the third was yellow dragon river.

Red dragon river had water red as blood, jade dragon river had green waves in it, while yellow dragon river was something Fang Yuan had traveled on in this life, it was yellow in color and had the most sediments.

Fang Yuan toyed with the lingzhi king's heart in his hands, after taking this heart, he did not leave immediately using Fixed Immortal Travel, he went to a corner of the valley and left behind many Gu worms before activating Fixed Immortal Travel.

These Gu worms all self-detonated as he was leaving, eliminating the aura of Fixed Immortal Travel, by doing this he could avoid anyone tracing him.

Right now, he was waiting for a person.

This person was another one of his targets, he had amazing luck and many fortuitous encounters, rising to a legend from a nobody. During the five regions chaotic war, he was a rank seven Gu Immortal, a famous person on the same level as Hong Yi and Han Li.

But different from Han Li who joined a clan later, and Hong Yi who was a member of a sect, this person was a lone cultivator from start to finish, he had several good friends and family, but he did not join a particular force.

When Fang Yuan was about to self-detonate in his previous life, there were rumors that central continent's Heavenly Court was about to recruit him.

As for whether this information was true or not, Fang Yuan had no way to verify it.

But now that Fang Yuan had been reborn, that was not important.

"In my memories, this person had been ostracized his entire life after his clan banished him. By this riverside, he obtained the inheritance of a rank four Gu Master, it was just enough for him to use. Using this inheritance, he earned a living while repelling the dangers of the wild. He grew stronger step by step, grabbing onto a huge opportunity and obtaining the black yellow mother qi Gu, the inheritance of a daoist master, he won nine out of ten times when rock gambling, and dominated all of the southern border gambling dens."

Fang Yuan recalled.

He knew this place due to the 'Biography of Ye Fan'. Every important person's history was usually recorded down in words and pictures.

Ye Fan was Fang Yuan's target this time.

And here was the start of Ye Fan's rise. Tonight, he would have his first fortuitous encounter.

Chapter 681: Nine Dragons Coffin Protection Luck

The stars were like diamonds brightening the night sky.

River winds blew softly, the howling of beasts and cries of birds could be heard, contrasting with the otherwise quiet environment.

Fang Yuan waited patiently, but he did not see Ye Fan's arrival over the entire night.

As time passed, after the second and third day, Ye Fan did not appear at any point.

"Don't tell me, 'Biography of Ye Fan' was wrong?" Fang Yuan could not help but think, but he quickly rejected this thought: "No, the Gu Master inheritance near the riverside is still around, Ye Fan has not taken it. I'll wait..."

What Fang Yuan did not know was that, a thousand li away, Ye Fan had met with trouble.

Huff huff huff...

Ye Fan breathed roughly, he looked at the huge shadow of a sprawling beast near the cave entrance with much fear.

"Damn it, why am I so unlucky? I was just banished from the clan, I hid in a cave to stay for the night, but I woke up to find out that the cave entrance was sealed!" Ye Fan cursed in his heart, he was nervous but helpless.

This cave only had one entrance, but this fierce beast was blocking it.

Ye Fan did not have any method to dig holes, his strength was very low but this beast's body was huge, it was a beast emperor.

"Why did this beast emperor come here alone without a single beast as its guard? Don't tell me it is an old emperor that was chased out by the new emperor?" Ye Fan looked at the beast in front of him, analyzing nervously in his heart.

As he continued observing, he quickly found out that this beast emperor was a paper tiger.

This dog shaped beast emperor was covered in wounds, its body was not too big, but it was sprawled on the ground, its eyelids were drooping weakly.

On its snow-white fur, there was multi-colored markings resembling flower petals on a snowy field.

"Haa... haa... haa..." Ye Fan listened closely, hearing the dog emperor's extremely weak, whimpering cries.

Watching its dry belly that was so thin its bones could be seen, Ye Fan finally understood: "Although this is a beast emperor, it is extremely hungry, it has little to no battle strength."

Reaching this conclusion, Ye Fan let out a breath of turbid air, at the same time, he felt a bit of pity in his heart.

They were in similar situations, this beast emperor's fate was very much like his own.

Ye Fan slowly got close to the dog shaped beast emperor, the beast emperor had no reaction, it allowed him to get closer.

Ye Fan did not dare to breathe loudly, he squatted by the beast emperor's side and stretched out his arm, placing it on its forehead.

The soft fur was extremely comfortable to Ye Fan, it was a little warm and wet.

This beast emperor had a fever, it was covered in sweat that made its fur wet, its bodily functions were barely functional.

"Beast emperor, oh beast emperor, you are about to die, maybe one day, I will be just like you. But meeting me is your good luck, after all, I was the village's most famous beast doctor." Ye Fan muttered to himself, he felt great pity for this beast emperor and started to heal it.

He activated his Gu, healing the beast emperor's injuries, and also alleviating its illness. Next, he took out some precious food and water, feeding them to the beast emperor slowly, letting it recover its strength.

Ye Fan was in no hurry, he stayed in this cave for seven days, as this dog shaped beast emperor finally recovered.

Although it was still weak and did not have a single wild Gu, not even capable of defeating a thousand beast king. But it was out of danger now, its fever subsided and it could run freely, it was running around Ye Fan excitedly.

Ye Fan saved it, it treated him as its closest person. Every time Ye Fan returned to the cave bringing food and water, it would run over and wag its tail happily around him.

Later, when it recovered some battle strength, it went out to hunt with Ye Fan, helping him to find food.

The human and dog quickly established a deep relationship.

When Ye Fan decided to leave the cave and venture far away, the dog shaped beast emperor followed suit.

"This is the eighth day, why has Ye Fan not appeared yet?" At jade dragon river, Fang Yuan was anxious.

In about five to six days, Hei Lou Lan would be undergoing tribulation.

By then, Fang Yuan needed to defend her, not only to help her survive the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity, but also to deal with the combined attacks of the rank seven Gu Immortal Hei Cheng, and the rank six Gu Immortal Xue Song Zi.

To estimate a Gu Immortal's battle strength, there were many elements to consider, but the most crucial four were — immortal essence, killer moves, Immortal Gu, and the Gu Immortal's personal attainment in fighting.

During his northern plains trip, Tai Bai Yun Sheng who had newly advanced to a Gu Immortal was at the bottom of all rank six Gu Immortals in terms of battle strength.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had immortal essence and healing Immortal Gu, but he did not have killer moves or sufficient mortal Gu. Most importantly, his personal attainment in fighting was terrible.

Thus, he was heavily suppressed by Hei Lou Lan who had the Great Strength True Martial Physique.

Right now, Fang Yuan had little immortal essence, although he had many Immortal Gu, they were all waiting to be fed and it would be difficult for them to bear immediate use. Even though he had the killer moves icy drill stardust, light illusion bat wings, and hair armor, during his normal form, his battle strength was only at the upper-tier of rank six. But if he used the immortal killer move myriad self, his battle strength would reach the peak of rank six.

Fang Yuan defeated the western desert Gu Immortal Plump Lady, her battle strength was also at the upper-tier of rank six. She had three powerful mortal killer moves, especially in the end when she used the movement killer move to escape, Fang Yuan could not even catch up to her.

But Fang Yuan had the immortal zombie body, together with light illusion bat wings and hair armor cooperating together, the most important part was his ruthless and rich battle talent, that resulted in Plump Lady's battle intent dissipating, and she could only run.

Xue Song Zi's battle strength was also at the upper-tier of rank six.

He was a rich person among Gu Immortals, even though he lost a huge sum in funding Ma tribe, he still had thick foundations, he did not lack immortal essence. According to Fairy Li Shan's information, he had collected a lot of killer moves long ago, as someone from the demonic path, he had always focused on battle strength, his attainment in fighting was also not ordinary.

Xue Song Zi, all in all, was an experienced Gu Immortal, if Fang Yuan did not use myriad self and Immortal Gu to fight with him, the result would be unclear.

Meanwhile, Hei Cheng's battle strength was at the middle-tier of rank seven!

Compared to Xue Song Zi and Hei Bai, Hei Cheng's rank seven blessed land had greater qualifications, it produced red date immortal essence that was one rank higher than green grape immortal essence.

He was a Gu Immortal of a Huang Jin tribe, he did not lack killer moves. He had the Immortal Gu Dark Arrow since a long time ago. According to Fairy Li Shan's information, Hei Cheng had fought and obtained an Immortal Gu in northern plains several months ago, as to what Gu it was, Hei Cheng did not expose it.

Speaking of Hei Cheng's battle records, they was not ordinary, he had fought against several righteous path Gu Immortals, and even fought to the death with demonic path Gu Immortals, he had killed several demonic path Gu Immortals.

Hei Cheng did not lack immortal essence and killer moves, he had uncommon fighting attainment, and only lacked Immortal Gu, if he had one or two more Immortal Gu to use in battle, his battle strength would rise to the upper-tier of rank seven.

Although Fang Yuan had fought with Hei Cheng once before, it was for an extremely short time and Fang Yuan did not fight him directly, his goal was to retreat with Hei Lou Lan.

Honestly speaking, although Fang Yuan had many Immortal Gu, there was not a single one that was used for attack or defense. When the dark arrows were shot out, Fang Yuan could only dodge and not take them directly. Thankfully, with cleanse soul Immortal Gu as the core Gu of the killer move myriad self, Fang Yuan had his own immortal killer move.

Precisely because of this trump card, Fang Yuan had the qualifications to fight one on one with Hei Cheng

Fang Yuan compared the battle strength of both sides, he was clear in his heart. Hei Lou Lan's impending tribulation would bring great pressure to Fang Yuan.

"Ye Fan has not arrived here yet, I have less time to prepare for when Hei Lou Lan undergoes tribulation now. Maybe I should give up on waiting and return to Hu Immortal blessed land to make preparations, and try to raise my battle strength to the limit."

After waiting for so many days, Fang Yuan's heart was wavering.

Especially when he recalled that the last two times he attempted a luck connection, accidents occurred, causing them to fail. During Han Li's attempt, Plump Lady appeared and fought with Fang Yuan, only after he showed off his ruthlessness did she run away. When he did it with Hong Yi, Hei Lou Lan was being assaulted and Fang Yuan had no choice but to save her instead.

"Don't tell me that this time, when I attempted to connect my luck to Ye Fan, an accident occurred again? But this time, it did not happen to me but Ye Fan instead?"

Fang Yuan's guess hit the nail on the head.

Luck was ever changing, it was like tides, rising and falling at times.

There could be great fortune after surviving a near death experience, after Fang Yuan escaped with his life from the wind veil of assimilation, his black coffin luck had dissipated by half.

And after that, he connected his luck to Han Li and Hong Yi, they were all chosen due to their strong luck, only inferior to Ma Hong Yun. Fang Yuan's luck thus improved drastically.

This time, when he tried to connect to Ye Fan's luck, the contest of luck between the two no longer resulted in Fang Yuan encountering trouble, but instead, Ye Fan's luck was induced to avoid him, and give Ye Fan an opportunity to dodge this crisis.

Ye Fan made good use of this opportunity, dragging on time for seven days and seven nights, and subduing a beast emperor.

But it was a pity, when he got close to jade dragon river, Fang Yuan's heart had only wavered, he had not left.

"Oh? This dog emperor beside Ye Fan, isn't it that Ying Ming inside Three Kings blessed land? It actually survived, and is following Ye Fan now?" Fang Yuan recognized the dog emperor, he felt a little surprised.

This was something not recorded in 'Biography of Ye Fan'.

The luck connection to Ye Fan was very successful, there were no accidents, or rather, Ye Fan's lateness was already the accident.

Ye Fan was much weaker in strength, from start to finish he did not discover Fang Yuan or his scheme against him. This proved once again: Good and bad luck are not decisive elements, as long as one's strength was sufficient, they could resist bad luck and grab onto opportunities.

Ye Fan's luck was rather special as well.

His luck had a coffin.

But this coffin was not like Fang Yuan's black coffin. It was bronze and ancient, mysterious with nine dragons of luck guarding the surroundings of the coffin.

After connecting to Fang Yuan's luck, the nine dragons shrunk to four, and the bronze coffin was half as big as before.

Fang Yuan was satisfied with this result.

Ye Fan's luck had shrunk in half, but a large portion still remained.

"Hong Yi, Han Li, and Ye Fan's luck have been connected to mine, the four portions of luck are equally distributed. Ye Fan's current luck is at the same intensity as mine, Han Li and Hong Yi."

After going through so much, Fang Yuan had finally settled the second weakness of Spring Autumn Cicada.

Not only was his absolutely terrible luck gone, it was even better than ordinary people, he could be said to be a person with strong luck.

"It is a pity that such candidates are hard to find. Although there are still a few in my memories, they have not been born yet." Fang Yuan sighed out in pity, targets with thick and sustainable luck were very rare, at this point in time, Fang Yuan could find only these three.

At this moment, the matter regarding luck connection had come to an end, Fang Yuan looked at Ye Fan getting close to the river inheritance as he smiled lightly.

With a flash of jade light, he vanished.

Chapter 682: Refining Group Strength Gu

Fang Yuan could faintly sense Hei Lou Lan's tribulation would result in a huge battle.

Hei Cheng was an experienced rank seven Gu Immortal, his battle strength surpassing Fang Yuan's. Xue Song Zi was the owner of the seventh peak of Snowy Mountain blessed land and was also not an easy opponent.

Even if Hei Cheng and Xue Song Zi did not create trouble, a tribulation of the Great Strength True Martial Physique would far surpass the severity of those of normal people.

Fang Yuan immediately started making preparations after he returned to Hu Immortal blessed land.

He needed to raise his battle strength in a short period of time. Battle strength usually depended on four aspects: immortal essence, killer moves, Immortal Gu and battle attainments.

Fang Yuan was already very strong in his individual fighting attainment and it would be difficult to raise in a short period of time.

He could only concentrate on the other three aspects to raise his battle strength.

Fang Yuan first looked at his funds.

To connect luck with Ye Fan, Fang Yuan made a trip to southern border and returned, costing him two beads of green grape immortal essence, which meant he had seventeen remaining.

It was clear this amount was far from enough in a huge battle. According to Fang Yuan's previous life's memories, it was normal to spend dozens of beads of immortal essence in a huge battle, and sometimes it could even surpass a hundred.

Fang Yuan also possessed a lot of Immortal Gu, thus he urgently needed to replenish his green grape immortal essence.

And to replenish his green grape immortal essence, Fang Yuan only had one way and that was to refine immortal essence stones.

However, Fang Yuan only had eleven and half immortal essence stones on him.

Fang Yuan entered the underground cave and appeared before wisdom Gu again.

"Wisdom Gu, I brought you some rather interesting stuff." He greeted.

In \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, wisdom Gu communicated with Ren Zu frequently, but legends were not exempt from exaggeration.

Fang Yuan was also probing in regards to this.

No matter what he said, wisdom Gu would remain silent, instead, the wisdom light halo flickered a few times.

Fang Yuan laughed.

According to his previous experiences with wisdom Gu, the flickering of the light of wisdom represented wisdom Gu's agreement.

Upon this, he smoothly took out the lingzhi king's heart and planted it on the spot.

Within a few breaths of time, the soil ruptured and stems of small lingzhi mushrooms sprang out, which then rapidly grew and hardened, reaching the heights of tables and chairs.

Hu Immortal blessed land's soil quality was different from the soil quality in Universal Life Academy's land, and was not suitable for the growth of mushrooms.

This was the limit that the mushrooms could grow here.

Fang Yuan did not feel any regrets as it was just a passing thought from him. He then casually sat down on a lingzhi mushroom.

The lingzhi trembled violently, but unexpectedly was able to bear the heavy weight of Fang Yuan's immortal zombie body.

This cave had been empty before, but now it was no longer dull; wisdom Gu was like a curious baby, flying and fluttering around the shorter mushrooms. At first, its speed was slow and careful, but soon its flying tracks revealed its cheerful state, like a baby finding an interesting toy.

"Wisdom Gu, let's get back to the main matter." Fang Yuan looked on for a while before speaking.

Wisdom Gu stopped on top of a lingzhi and emitted the light of wisdom again, which shrouded Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan silently activated delight in water and mountain Gu and began to deduce an Immortal Gu remnant recipe.

Seven days later, he had succeeded in perfecting three Immortal Gu remnant recipes. Using a stargate, he completed the transaction with Lang Ya land spirit, gaining forty immortal essence stones.

According to the price agreed upon beforehand, perfecting an over ninety percent complete Immortal Gu remnant recipe would pay off ten immortal essence stones, while perfecting an eighty percent or more completed Immortal Gu remnant recipe would pay off twenty immortal essence stones.

Among the Immortal Gu remnant recipes Fang Yuan perfected this time, two were ninety percent completed remnant recipes while one was an eighty-nine percent completed remnant recipe.

Not all Immortal Gu remnant recipes with Lang Ya land spirit were ninety percent or over completed remnant recipes, there were many with lower completion rates.

Fang Yuan obtained many immortal essence stones in every transaction but he also had to spend a lot of immortal essence stones to completely deduce the Immortal Gu remnant recipes. Normally, his net profits were around twenty-six immortal essence stones in every transaction with Lang Ya land spirit.

He got a piece of good news from Little Hu Immortal land spirit when he returned to Hu Immortal blessed land: A Gu Immortal seemed to have found the dead body of a six headed snake and its parts and organs were being separately sold in treasure yellow heaven.

Fang Yuan immediately activated divine sense Gu and connected to treasure yellow heaven using his Eight Arm Immortal identity to contact the seller.

His calamity beckoning Gu fed on the black blood of the desolate beast six headed snake.

However, when Fang Yuan saw the store, there was skin, flesh, bones, eyes and snake tendons, but there was no blood for sale.

"When I found this desolate beast carcass by accident, the six headed snake had already been dead for close to a hundred years. Thus, the black blood had completely seeped out. I am truly sorry." The seller replied.

Fang Yuan discerned the corpse of the six headed snake and saw that the Gu Immortal was indeed telling the truth.

Fang Yuan was not discouraged, however. And still decided to buy the bones of this six headed snake.

The six headed snake was a desolate beast with strength comparable to rank six Gu Immortals. Its whole body was a treasure and every part could be used in the process of Gu refinement.

Fang Yuan had a lot of money on hand, directly buying off the whole skeleton, spending three immortal essence stones.

The bone marrow in the bones could produce blood. In his previous life, Fang Yuan in his previous life was a blood path expert and excelled in extracting blood. With this skeleton, calamity beckoning Gu's food was taken care of.

After buying the skeleton, Fang Yuan then went to the store of Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei.

As expected, divine senses were moving around frequently here and the business was thriving, all because of the Gu refinement material - stone monkey fur.

Shi Lei did not personally stay in treasure yellow heaven, instead leaving behind a proud will to look over the store.

Wisdom path inheritances were rare, but wisdom path Gu were not rare in treasure yellow heaven. Almost all Gu Immortals had some for the convenience in trading in treasure yellow heaven. If not, Fang Yuan would not have bought so many wisdom path Gu back then.

"How much are you selling this stone monkey fur for?" Fang Yuan inquired Shi Lei's will.

Shi Lei's will stiffly said: "One immortal essence stone for one hundred pieces of fur!"

Even Fang Yuan who was very experienced was shocked by this price: "How is it so expensive?"

Shi Lei's proud will raised his head: "Expensive? You can go buy in other places then."

Fang Yuan snorted inwardly, this stone monkey fur was researched by Shi Lei, how could other places sell it? This was the benefit of monopolizing the market, the price could be casually set. On the contrary, even though the price was so high, many Gu Immortals were buying it.

Which Gu Immortal did not have Gu recipes and Immortal Gu remnant recipes! Maybe one or two them might happen to require this stone monkey fur as a refinement material.

There were also a portion of Gu Immortals who had other intentions.

They bought stone monkey fur to attempt to research the secret of its production. If their blessed lands could also produce it, they could get a share of these exorbitant profits.

"Don't say I didn't tell you later, if you want to research the production of this stone monkey fur, you need at least a thousand strands of fur. If it is any less, you won't be able to research anything." Shi Lei's proud will also knew of the Gu Immortals' intention and instead used this to peddle the goods, not in the least worried of the secret of stone monkey fur's production being researched by others.

Fang Yuan attempted to haggle but Shi Lei's proud will did not yield, impatiently saying: "Go away, go away, don't make a disturbance if you are not buying! There are plenty of other buyers! A poor wretch, and still wishing to buy ancient Gu refinement material!"

Fang Yuan snorted.

Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei was a rank seven Gu Immortal with a fiery and arrogant temper. Not only was he good at managing his blessed land, he also had outstanding battle strength.

He was conceited but it was true he had the capital to be conceited.

During the five regions chaotic war, he had dominated a territory. Later when Feng Jiu Ge perished while invading Lang Ya blessed land, there was no one that could suppress Shi Lei and his battle strength grew to the extent that even central continent's ten great sects could not restrain him.

He was unruly and untamed, not willing to be under anyone, creating chaos in central continent and even publicly announcing he would attack leading immortals!

A great battle was imminent and Fang Yuan urgently required stone monkey fur to refine group strength Gu, thus regardless of how haughty Shi Lei's proud will was, he could only suffer this grievance silently and buy stone monkey fur.

He used five immortal essence stones to buy five hundred stone monkey fur.

With stone monkey fur on hand, Fang Yuan started refining group strength Gu.

Group strength Gu was an extinct Gu classified under strength path; its ability was to converge the strength of a group into one. If it was matched with the killer move myriad self, it would greatly raise Fang Yuan's strength.

Fang Yuan did not want to refine just one rank five group strength Gu, the more he had the better. At this moment, the old hairy men he had purchased before could finally display their worth.

These old hairy men did not have long to live but each of them was a refinement path expert. Fang Yuan divided the group strength Gu recipe into different parts, leaving the unimportant, high success rate and repetitive procedures for the hairy men to work on. And he, as a refinement path master, concentrated on the crucial procedures.

They worked for three days and three nights without any rest, refining a total of forty-five rank five group strength Gu.

Gu refinement had its own difficulty, the higher the rank, the easier it was to fail. If every Gu refinement had succeeded, the five hundred stone monkey fur would have turned into five hundred group strength Gu.

However, after spending large numbers of refinement materials and all the stone monkey fur, Fang Yuan only obtained forty-five in the end.

This success rate was the result of the group strength Gu recipe already being easy to refine and having a high success rate.

Fang Yuan could also naturally use the light of wisdom to improve group strength Gu's recipe or find substitute materials for stone monkey fur.

However, Fang Yuan did not have the time to slowly deduce these.

Even if he had time, he might not have the necessary refinement path foundation. After all, this was an ancient Gu recipe and was vastly different to the current systems of refinement path.

Even if had the foundation and time, he had to calculate his expenses and benefits. The deduction process would cost him green grape immortal essence. And he was unable to estimate this amount of green grape immortal essence.

After refining group strength Gu, Fang Yuan did not rest, instead he used the light of wisdom to ponder upon his killer move, myriad self. He spent a day of time before he was finally able to perfectly merge the forty five group strength Gu with myriad self.

While Fang Yuan was refining, Little Hu Immortal finally completed her assignment, finishing the construction of the blood pool in the western part of Hu Immortal blessed land.

The blood pool was extremely large, like a lake. In the center of the pool, the six headed snake's skeleton was bobbing up and down; the intense odor of blood pervaded over a huge surrounding area. There were large numbers of Gu worms in the pool, creating a formation which continually consumed the skeleton to create black blood.

The core of the Gu formation was the rank five Battle Bone Wheel which Fang Yuan had obtained from northern plains.

Hu Immortal blessed land's time flow was five times faster than the outside world of central continent. Because of this, Fang Yuan was able to make as much preparation as he could when there were only five to six days remaining till the appointed time in northern plains.

Time passed and the day of Hei Lou Lan's tribulation approached closer and closer.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng returned to Hu Immortal Blessed Land through a stargate.

He brought a pleasant surprise with him.

Chapter 683: Hei Lou Lan's Immortal Ascension (1/3)

"Underworld jellyfish... deepsea lightning eels... you actually managed to gather these ingredients." Fang Yuan inspected the goods as he looked at Tai Bai Yun Sheng in surprise.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had singlehandedly obtained the food to feed worldly wave trace Gu without any issue!

This was out of Fang Yuan's expectations.

"When I displayed landscape as before Immortal Gu, I was greatly welcomed by many Gu Immortals. They took the initiative to interact with me, at the moment, there are already Gu Immortals who have invited me to join Hai Shi blessed land. However, this matter can only be approved after half of the elders in Hai Shi blessed land agree." Tai Bai Yun Sheng said.

Fang Yuan nodded, Hai Shi blessed land was the biggest lone cultivator force in eastern sea.

Gu cultivators that joined Hai Shi blessed land were mostly lone cultivators, but this was different from northern plains' Snowy Mountain blessed land.

Snowy Mountain blessed land was the base camp of demonic path cultivators, they were at odds with the righteous path forces. But Hai Shi blessed land mixed both demonic and righteous path members, there were even more Gu Immortals here than in Snowy Mountain, and there were many different factions which together controlled the largest market in eastern sea. Precisely because of this, Hai Shi blessed land became the most popular spot for Gu Immortals to sell their loot.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a lone cultivator, his landscape as before Immortal Gu was much needed by many Gu Immortals.

But Gu worms were hard to snatch, one thought from Tai Bai Yun Sheng would destroy Landscape as Before. It was completely understandable that the Gu Immortals wanted to make Tai Bai Yun Sheng one of their own.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng continued: "I bought sufficient underworld jellyfish in Hai Shi blessed land. After getting your letter, I left Hai Shi blessed land, searching for a secluded island to use stargate Gu. But by coincidence, I met an immortal zombie who called himself Shark Demon, he was a member of Zombie Alliance, and was bringing large amounts of goods to Hai Shi blessed land to sell."

"He had many deepsea lightning eels with him, if these eels were sold in Hai Shi blessed land, there would certainly be many buyers. I approached him and asked if I could purchase them. Shark Demon was unwilling at first and had a terrible attitude. But after knowing I was Tai Bai Yun Sheng, he changed his mind. He was willing to sell the deepsea lightning eels to me, but I had to help him repair a secret blessed land. I agreed to his request, and obtained the deepsea lightning eels without spending any immortal essence stones."

"This Shark Demon actually trusted you this much?" Fang Yuan heard this and frowned deeply.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng laughed, replying nonchalantly: "Oh, he had a rule path Immortal Gu called Death Sentence Awaits. I cooperated with him and accepted the use of Death Sentence Awaits, obtaining his trust."

"Death Sentence Awaits is a rank seven Immortal Gu that belongs to the rule path, it can set a person's time of death. Once the time was up, even a Gu Immortal would die." Fang Yuan's frown intensified.

"That is right, this Shark Demon is a rank seven immortal zombie." Tai Bai Yun Sheng chuckled.

"Old Bai, you are handing him your weakness. Actually, even without food to feed the Immortal Gu, it would have been fine for the moment." Fang Yuan looked at Tai Bai Yun Sheng, sighing.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng laughed, patting Fang Yuan's leg, his height was obviously not enough to reach Fang Yuan's shoulders.

He purposely explained: "Do you think I did it for you? No. That secret blessed land is not owned by Shark Demon, it is Yu Lu blessed land. Fairy Yu Lu was the second disciple of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable. It is a pity that Yu Lu blessed land's entrance had already been destroyed. Shark Demon needs my Landscape as Before to restore the entrance. I used this opportunity to gain his trust and also a chance to explore Yu Lu blessed land."

Fang Yuan looked at Tai Bai Yun Sheng deeply in the eye, not continuing this conversation.

Two days later, the six headed snake's large skeleton had completed melted in the blood pool, Fang Yuan obtained a great amount of black blood.

He fed calamity beckoning Immortal Gu this black blood, before using Tai Bai Yun Sheng's jellyfish and eels to feed worldly wave trace Immortal Gu.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had indeed helped Fang Yuan greatly.

In an intense battle, worldly wave trace Immortal Gu would definitely be needed, after feeding this Gu, Fang Yuan could use it without worries.

Checking his assets, Fang Yuan still had twenty-nine and a half immortal essence stones, as well as seventeen green grape immortal essence beads.

Without hesitation, he used almost all his immortal essence stones and converted them into his green grape immortal essence. He now had forty-six green grape immortal essence beads and half an immortal essence stone.

"Forty-six beads... it's not enough." Fang Yuan went to borrow from Fairy Li Shan and Lang Ya land spirit.

Fairy Li Shan lent him thirty immortal essence stones straight away without saying anything.

As for Lang Ya land spirit, after urging him for so long, he only lent fifteen.

These three deals with Lang Ya land spirit did not establish too deep of a relationship. Fang Yuan had wanted to borrow Immortal Gu from him, but seeing this, he did not engage in fantasy.

He converted the forty-five immortal essence stones into green grape immortal essence. At this point, he had an unprecedented amount of green grape immortal essence, ninety-one beads.

The grand powers of the river of time was unstoppable by men.

As time continued to pass, the day when Hei Lou Lan went through the immortal ascension tribulation had finally arrived.

Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng used a stargate to reach northern plains as per the agreement.

Looking left and right, it was a field of snow with absolute silence. In the snowy field, Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan had long since arrived.

"This place is..." Fang Yuan's gaze was hesitant.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng answered: "This is the absolute ice battlefield at the north-most part of northern plains, legend says that Reckless Savage Demon Venerable had once fought strong enemies in here and destroyed the place, creating an area of void. After the battle ended, he turned into the immemorial desolate beast ice phoenix, breathing out absolute profound ice to freeze and restore this place."

"That's right." Fairy Li Shan nodded: "Because this place has little vitality, the heaven and earth qi here are not very thick."

Fang Yuan looked at Hei Lou Lan, smiling: "You purposely chose this place to undergo the tribulation, are you afraid that the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity would be too fierce? But without sufficient heaven and earth qi, the foundation of your immortal aperture would be affected, as well as your future potential as a Gu Immortal."

Fairy Li Shan opened her palm, as a Gu worm appeared: "If heaven and earth qi are insufficient, we will use these Gu."

Fang Yuan looked over and his heart jumped: "Oh? The ancient qi path rank five Gu worm — small family qi Gu? This is the first time I've seen it. Rumors say that this Gu can absorb all sorts of qi from heaven and earth, storing them. It can advance to become the Immortal Gu Big Family Qi!"

Qi path appeared before strength path, but it also declined earlier.

Fairy Li Shan was prepared to explain, but seeing that Fang Yuan recognized it, she praised: "Fang Yuan, you are truly knowledgeable, not bad, not bad at all."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng heard this and his eyes shone: "This Gu worm is great! Heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities form when heaven and earth qi are too thick and accumulate. With this Gu worm, can we indirectly control the heaven and earth qi, to reduce the force of the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity?"

"The immortal ascension of one of the ten extreme physiques has a terrifying heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity. Oh, if I did not obtain this small family qi Gu, I would have no confidence towards Little Lan ascending to Gu Immortal realm." Fairy Li Shan sighed, staring at Hei Lou Lan with much concern and worry.

Next, her gaze flickered and she turned to Fang Yuan: "Fang Yuan, if Hei Lou Lan's ascension succeeds, you will only need to return me half the immortal essence stones you borrowed. At the same time, I will give you the recipe of small family qi Gu."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's gaze shone with joy, while Fang Yuan nodded emotionlessly.

"Other than the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity, what I am worried about now is that old scoundrel Hei Cheng. When I entered northern plains last time, he discovered me immediately, evidently, he has placed a tracking method on me, but I could not find it at all."

After pausing for a while, Hei Lou Lan continued: "We have to make plans for the worst possible outcome, Hei Cheng's tracking method is definitely not simple. If he comes and attacks at the crucial moment, there is little possibility of me dealing with him. But if I can endure past the taking in of qi, my body would be washed by the three qi, it would be reinforced by the dao marks and cleansed completely, achieving a qualitative transformation, even if Hei Cheng used an Immortal Gu tracking method, it would be wiped clean. As long as we make it to the second step, we can leave."

"I understand, you can start." Fang Yuan said.

Hei Lou Lan nodded, closing her eyes.

The first step in advancing to Gu Immortal was breaking the aperture.

Apertures of the ten extremes were different from ordinary apertures, the latter required the Gu Master to charge at the aperture walls to break them, but the former's aperture walls had long been over burdened.

The moment Hei Lou Lan released the seal formed by Gu worms on her aperture, the ten extreme aperture shattered on its own.

Her originally intact body immediately had a hole, as a huge attraction force towards the heaven and earth qi burst out.

The deep blue sky started to form clouds. As the icy fields shook slightly, cracks appeared on the thick surface of the ice.

Hei Lou Lan relaxed her body, she allowed the formless force created in heaven and earth to lift her body into the air.

Her skin was white and pale like snow, her black hair was let down as she wore tight fitting black clothing, showing off the curves of her body.

The wind started blowing.

In a dozen breaths of time, the winds were blowing wildly as the small wind became an intense storm.

Clouds merged and covered the sky, looming above Hei Lou Lan. From the shattered surface of the ice, traces of smoke started rising up — this was the sign that earth qi had been drawn up above the ice ground.

Soon, it started snowing in the sky.

The clouds became thicker, and the color turned from grey-white to deep black.

Within the entirety of the surroundings, it was completely dark.

The winds blew and icy cold frost that could chill bones filled the entire area. At the same time, earth qi burst out, cracking noises erupted, earth qi gushed out into the world like a fountain.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Fairy Li Shan retreated, hiding their figures.

Only Fang Yuan remained, looking at the sky. His tall body was like an immovable rock statue, the intense winds and snow could not move him at all.

These were all mortal level winds and snow, no matter how big they were, they could not threaten this immortal zombie.

As snow covered the lands, and intense winds blew, they became louder and louder, like the cries of demons and ghosts.

"As expected of a tribulation of the ten extreme physique, the heaven and earth qi here are so thin, yet so much was still drawn. If this was any other region in northern plains, it would simply be unthinkable!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng hid far away, not showing his figure. Looking at this scene, his heart was shocked.

From the winds and snow, heaven and earth qi slowly became thicker.

Hei Lou Lan started to sprinkle the small family qi Gu.

These rank five Gu flew into the sky or landed on the ground, they started to absorb heaven and earth qi and store them. They greatly reduced the speed of the accumulation of heaven and earth qi.

Chapter 684: Hei Lou Lan's Immortal Ascension (2/3)

"With small family qi Gu, there would be a way to influence the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity." Fang Yuan watched silently by the side.

The intense winds were howling, snow was descending along with sharp icicles, crashing on Fang Yuan's body. Fang Yuan did not move at all, the immortal zombie body was unharmed.

Bam bam bam...

Hei Lou Lan continued to sprinkle the small family qi Gu, when these ancient qi path Gu worms had reached the limit of their capacity, she retrieved them. During this process, many small family qi Gu had self-detonated and the absorbed heaven and earth qi were returned to the world.

When a Gu Immortal ascends, because of the turbulence of heaven and earth qi, both mortal Gu and Immortal Gu would receive backlash.

Even though Hei Lou Lan prepared the small family qi Gu, she could only influence the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity slightly, she could not control it.

As time continued to pass, unavoidably, the heaven and earth qi became thicker, and were at the point of creating the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity.

As the howling of the winds continued, Hei Lou Lan's black hair danced in the air, the snow and ice hitting her face. Clothes made using Gu worms were much more durable than ordinary clothes. Thus, her clothes were fluttering in the air, not tearing even under the pull of the intense winds.

Fang Yuan found it slightly weird: "It has already been so long, where is the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity?"

His eyes shone with radiance, by activating Gu worms to investigate carefully, the wind and snow could not block his vision.

Fang Yuan went into high alert, heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities had many variations, some were powerful and had strong auras, some were mysterious and scary, he could not predict it, Gu Masters could only test their luck and be as prepared as they could to deal with it.

Howl, howl, howl!

The sound of the wind was becoming sharper, it hurt the eardrums as Fang Yuan felt some frustration in his heart.

Suddenly, he jolted to awareness, he activated his investigative Gu forcefully and looked into the clouds. He immediately saw that a purple chime had formed, it was moving slowly and emitting a sound.

It turns out the heavenly tribulation had formed already!

As the noise became louder and sharper, it fused with the wind, spreading over a hundred li!

Even if Fang Yuan covered his ears, he could not block this noise. Although he had prepared some sound path mortal Gu, his sound path attainment was too low, he could not defend against it.

He felt more and more frustrated, his heart was beating faster, following the sound of the chime, and his blood was starting to flow backwards.

Hei Lou Lan was groaning, blood was oozing from her mouth and nose, her state was worse than Fang Yuan's.

Fang Yuan squinted, cold light flashing in his eyes: "This is the heart shocking noise tribulation, when Gu Masters hear it, their blood would flow backwards, and their hearts would beat faster. If a long time passes, their blood will flow towards the seven orifices, and their heart would explode. I have the body of an immortal zombie, my zombie blood is ice cold, it is almost stagnant, thus I am affected the least. But Hei Lou Lan is the Great Strength True Martial Physique, her blood is the most active among us, she is countered by the heart shocking noise calamity! We must destroy the source of it, the purple chime!"

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan stopped hesitating, he activated light illusion bat wings and flew into the sky.

He flew rapidly, but the closer he got to the purple chime, the more his heart was shocked. When he was three hundred steps away from it, his heart was beating so quickly even his muscles and tendons were vibrating.

Suddenly, Fang Yuan's body froze, he opened his mouth and vomited a mouthful of green zombie blood.

A moment ago, his heart was unable to take the pressure and burst.

But Fang Yuan was an immortal zombie, his heart was not a weak point, such an injury awakened his fierce nature.

He laughed freakishly, spreading all eight arms and using his killer move.

Icy Drill Stardust!

Eight starlight lumps formed and crashed towards the tribulation cloud.

They drilled into the tribulation cloud, slamming into the purple chime. The chime was not strong, it broke immediately. The heart shocking demonic sound stopped, and Fang Yuan's pressure was lifted.

But at the next moment, the tribulation cloud rumbled, as heaven qi gathered, a new purple chime was about to be formed.

Fang Yuan's eyes shone with cold light, how could the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity be defeated so easily in one strike? This was not unexpected.

Icy Drill Stardust!

His eight arms gathered, using the killer move again, creating a huge icy drill stardust lump.

Within the dark blue starlight lump, stardust fragments were shining brightly, colliding into each other at a chaotic pace.

Fang Yuan shouted lightly, his eights arms pushed forward, sending the starlight lump towards the tribulation cloud.

The larger the starlight lump, the slower its speed. But after colliding into the purple chime again, a large amount of starlight specks remained, they were emitting a crackling sound as they self-detonated.

Heaven qi gathered, forming more purple chimes, but were instantly destroyed by the starlight lump.

The starlight lump could be seen shrinking with the naked eye, but the enchanting heart shocking noise did not enter Fang Yuan's ears again.

Fang Yuan succeeded in suppressing the heavenly tribulation, but he did not let down his guard. The immortal ascension of the ten extreme physiques, how could it be so simple?

He continued to unleash icy drill stardust, although this killer move was a mortal killer move, it had amazing power, after fusing Dou Min Jun's inheritance into it, this killer move was worth four immortal essence stones.

Icy drill stardust continued to be replenished, as the purple chime continued to form and break down.

Fang Yuan looked down at Hei Lou Lan below him.

The latter's breathing had soothed, her eyes were shut tight. Her expression was determined, she sat cross-legged in the air, unmoving. On her beautiful pale face, there were dried blood traces.

But the recovery of the Great Strength True Martial Physique was the best of the ten extreme physiques, Hei Lou Lan's injuries had already recovered.

Her hands did not stop moving, she scattered small family qi Gu while retrieving the ones that were full. She had changed her battle strategy, she scattered the small family qi Gu on the ground and rarely in the sky.

One could deduce from this that she did not have many small family qi Gu, after all, this was an ancient qi path Gu worm. Even if they had the Gu recipe, it was very difficult to find refinement materials.

Even if Hei Lou Lan had ample time to prepare, she did not have many of this Gu with her.

Fang Yuan retracted his gaze, at this time, he could hear some weeping noises.

The voice was desolate and pitiful, it sounded like the crying of a begrudged wife, or the sleepy talk of a young maiden in love, it was a whisper that was very affectionate and caring, but at times it also had the tone of hatred and grudge.

Fang Yuan heard this and even his immortal zombie body felt a sense of weakness. His entire body could not exert strength, he was like a hero out of breath, together with an endless longing for his homeland, his bravery fell short and his ambitions could not be fulfilled. His firm fists and legs felt like they were hitting on cotton, it was like he had just recovered from a terrible illness, he had no strength in him.

Fang Yuan shouted out in dismay, using his investigative Gu and looking up, he saw that near the purple chime, a pink chime had appeared.

The chime continued to vibrate, creating a weeping noise.

This was the decadent noise tribulation!

Before Fang Yuan used his killer move to shatter the pink chime, enchanting noise assaulted him again.

Bang... bang... bang!

The sound was like thunder, it was like the pounding of a giant, every sound was hitting on the deepest parts of Fang Yuan's mind, in his mind, his thoughts could not move, they were all shattered by this thunderous noise.

Tremor thought noise tribulation!

Immortal zombies have slow cognition, this heavenly tribulation directly countered Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan felt an intense dizziness, he could not think and his body was wavering, he almost fell from this high altitude.

At the moment of crisis, he used his remaining bit of clarity to activate delight in water and mountain Gu.

Three green grape immortal essence beads entered delight in water and mountain Gu, as joyful will burst out and spread in Fang Yuan's entire mind.

Fang Yuan had just stabilized his body when, swoosh!

Suddenly, there was a sharp noise near his ears, approaching rapidly.

Fang Yuan subconsciously tried to block it, but at the next moment, his five fingers were all sliced off, the five fingers were covered by the wind and snow, vanishing without a trace.

Swish swish swish...

The sharp noise continued to emit, getting closer to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk, he focused his gaze and used three investigative methods consecutively. He could faintly see that there were very thin invisible lines in the wind and snow, it was sharp and formed a huge web, moving towards Fang Yuan without giving him any place to dodge.

These invisible lines were not of material nature, they were all formed using sounds.

Fang Yuan watched with his hair on end: "This is the flying blade noise tribulation! Hair armor! Light illusion bat wings!"

He activated his defensive killer move and his movement killer move.

Fang Yuan moved continually, his black armor broke apart and after leaving his body, the fragments turned into black zombie hair.

Fang Yuan twisted left and right, he finally found a rather loose gap and broke through the sound web.

But the invisible sound lines still came for him. The hair armor lasted for another three breaths before reaching its limit and breaking.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, he used his defensive killer move again, forming a new layer of hair armor that barely covered his body.

He dodged left and right, his body moving like a phantom, as lumps of icy drill stardust were shot up.

The stardust touched the sound web and were blocked, cut into pieces of fragments.

At the same time, Fang Yuan's fingers grew rapidly, his shattered heart formed once again.

Howl howl howl...

Without the starlight lump's restraint, the first purple chime formed again.

The ghostly cries resounded again, Fang Yuan's blood flowed in reverse again, his newly formed heart started beating rapidly as it went on the path of self-detonation.

Fang Yuan's gaze concentrated.

Be it the icy drill stardust, light illusion bat wings, or hair armor, they had been used to their limits, yet the dangerous situation could not be alleviated!

This was only Hei Lou Lan's heavenly tribulation, the earthly calamity had not formed yet due to the small family qi Gu's suppression.

In Fang Yuan's mind, huge amounts of joyful will were expended, in a short period, ten percent were used up.

"My current battle strength is upper-tier of rank six, but I cannot do anything to this heavenly tribulation. The ascension of the ten extreme physiques, the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity is truly terrifying, this is several times the power compared to an ordinary Gu Immortal! Hmm?"

Suddenly, Fang Yuan's expression changed, his heart sank.

He found out that in this tribulation cloud, another four chimes of varying colors were forming.

Earlier, with just four chimes, Fang Yuan was already near his limits. Now that four new ones appeared, Fang Yuan could only use the immortal killer move myriad self.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng watched at a hidden location with much fear: "It seems the immortal ascension of the ten extreme physique is not just several times as dangerous as an ordinary Gu Master, it is at least a dozen times as terrifying."

He had thought that his own tribulation was tough. But to think that Hei Lou Lan's tribulation was far more dangerous than his!

"Oh no, this is not an ordinary heavenly tribulation, it is one of the ten catastrophes, eight layer enchanting noise tribulation, when all eight noises are emitted, it would have a range of eight hundred and eighty li, heaven and earth would shake and immortals would be exterminated!" Far away, Fairy Li Shan who had been hiding recognized the eight chimes and almost wanted to help out.

"Eight layer enchanting noise tribulation... if all eight noises are emitted at once, the strength would be unstoppable, this tribulation would end in failure without a trace of hope of success." Fang Yuan's expression was cold, the tougher the situation, the stronger his battle intent.

Crack crack crack.

During the process, all the mortal Gu he used were getting destroyed continuously.

The backlash of heaven and earth was causing him to lose a large number of mortal Gu.

But Fang Yuan made ample preparations, he had prepared a large number of Gu worms and his killer moves had never stopped activating.

Just as he was about to use myriad self, Hei Lou Lan who was below him opened her eyes!

Chapter 685: Hei Lou Lan's Immortal Ascension (3/3)

From Hei Lou Lan's eyes, a dazzling light was bursting out.

The light gathered and took form, like that of a real pillar, it pierced through the tribulation cloud and shot the two chimes.

With a loud bang, the chimes broke, completely eliminated and was unable to regenerate.

The light pillar only lasted for a moment before Hei Lou Lan shut her eyes, the entire process was extremely short, only lasting a breath of time.

This was the light of divert disaster!

Hei Lou Lan used the Immortal Gu Divert Disaster!

The power of an Immortal Gu was extraordinary, it was a stark contrast to Fang Yuan's mortal killer move icy drill stardust.

Hei Lou Lan controlled her breathing before opening her eyes again.

Two pillars of divert disaster light shot out, destroying two chimes again.

Fang Yuan was secretly shocked: "Such power, this was not a simple use of divert disaster Immortal Gu, it was used together with mortal Gu. Using her sight to unleash the attack, it is much more concentrated and precise. In other words, Hei Lou Lan had already developed an immortal killer move using the Immortal Gu Divert Disaster as the core!"

Hei Lou Lan had outstanding talent, not long after obtaining divert disaster Gu, she developed an immortal killer move?

This was very strange and unthinkable to Fang Yuan, but the truth was right before him, it was indisputable!

At this time, Hei Lou Lan opened her eyes again, eliminating two chimes again.

But at this time, she shut her eyes, two lines of fresh blood flowed down the corner of her eyes. her eyelashes were trembling and her body was shaking. On her palm, she held divert disaster Gu tightly, cracks were appearing on it and it was wailing out softly.

This frantically created immortal killer move was not complete, it had very potent weaknesses.

"Two chimes left!" Hei Lou Lan did not care about it, she gritted her teeth and opened her eyes forcefully, destroying the heavenly tribulation's last two chimes in one shot.

Guh! Guh!

Her beautiful eyes had shattered at this moment, as two streams of blood poured out of her empty eye sockets.

With a bang, the divert disaster Immortal Gu burst in her hands, breaking into light particles, slipping from the cracks of her fingers and vanishing.

Hei Lou Lan had gone blind!

Although she had the Great Strength True Martial Physique and had terrifying recovery speed, the injury in her eyes was due to the forceful activation of the Immortal Gu Divert Disaster, dao marks of luck path were in her eye sockets, she could not heal them.

The rank six divert disaster Immortal Gu was also destroyed in this process, becoming history.

Hei Lou Lan was extremely resolute, she had the heart of a formidable character, after paying a terrible price, she destroyed the heavenly tribulation for good, now only the earthly calamity was left!

At this moment, Fang Yuan praised her in his heart: "Resolute!"

The immortal ascension of the ten extreme physiques gave birth to a terrifying heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity. What's worse was that they still had a strong foe waiting to interfere. Under the immense pressure of life and death, Hei Lou Lan had no choice but to sacrifice divert disaster Immortal Gu, as well as a pair of her eyes.

This was a decision common people would find hard to make.

Such sacrifice, it showed Hei Lou Lan's ambitious and ruthless disposition, she had an unrivaled spirit.

As heaven qi poured down like he stream of a waterfall, earth qi gushed up like a golden fountain. Hei Lou Lan's foundation and deep accumulation turned into a large amount of human qi as it burst out from within her.

"This is the human qi of one of the ten extreme physiques?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng watched with a dumbfounded expression.

Hei Lou Lan's human qi was many times more than Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng combined.

The human qi of the ten extreme physiques was usually overwhelmingly thick, this was mostly due to the ten extreme apertures.

Even with enough mental preparation, spectators were still shocked.

As the three qi converged, it formed a huge cocoon that covered up Hei Lou Lan.

At this point, she had reached the second step — taking in the qi.

Hei Lou Lan was focused on balancing the three qi, she took back all her small family qi Gu and would not be able to face her enemies for the time being.

Crack...

Frozen rivers shattered, heaven and earth shook.

At this moment, a thunderous sound could be heard, as a huge frenzied ape jumped out from deep within a frozen river.

With a loud thud, the frenzied ape landed on the ground, it created two huge holes where it stood. The ice fragments were scattered around the huge holes.

The frenzied ape beat its chest, shouting out loudly. Its voice was so loud that even the rumbling tribulation cloud froze for a second.

Its body was like snow, its eyes were red like blood, its monkey fur spiked out like icicles, piercing towards heaven. It was hundreds of meters tall, large like a hill, it has an incredible aura and was extremely fierce. Compared to it, Fang Yuan was like a bug in front of a cat.

"The earthly calamity formed! It is an ancient desolate beast calamity! This is an earthly calamity that only rank seven Gu Immortals encounter." Tai Bai Yun Sheng's heart snak.

One name was echoing in Fairy Li Shan's heart: "Icefall Divine Ape!"

Fang Yuan's expression was still as water, the icefall divine ape's huge shadow was casted down, it had rank seven battle strength. If it had Immortal Gu in it, then it would be even harder to deal with, the battle situation would become much harder.

Hei Lou Lan focused on balancing the three qi, Hei Cheng did not appear, while Fairy Li Shan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng were hiding elsewhere, with this extremely dangerous situation, a ruthless light flashed across Fang Yuan's eyes, he clapped his palms before him, using his killer move earlier than planned.

Immortal killer move — Myriad Self!

Fist qi burst out, grand and overwhelming, like an overflowing river, it was like a raging sea.

In just a few breaths of time, over ten thousand of Fang Yuan's strength path phantoms appeared, surrounding his main body. They were in all directions around him, in the sky and on the ground, in the formation of a sphere.

To prevent the likelihood of him having not enough time because of a fierce battle, Fang Yuan had activated the immortal killer move myriad self several times before going to northern plains.

The strength path phantom army was stored in his own immortal aperture. The strength path phantoms could exist for a period of time, and because they were not living beings, they were not affected by the death energy in his immortal aperture.

When Fang Yuan released a portion of them, his aura finally matched the ape's.

The icefall divine ape was ready to attack, it wanted to charge over, but seeing the grand strength path phantom army, it opened its mouth, showing its sharp fangs as its muscles contracted, it chose to wait and see.

The snow and wind blew, Fang Yuan was expressionless, his body was still like a rock as he pointed at finger at the icefall divine ape.

Immediately, the army moved and war cries filled the battlefield.

Tens of thousands of strength path phantoms moved like a tide, they whipped up a storm as they charged towards the icefall divine ape.

"Such might!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng watched with his heart pounding.

This was not the first time he had seen the killer move myriad self, back in Lang Ya blessed land, Fang Yuan had used it once to beat up the desolate beast swamp crab.

But at that time, Fang Yuan only used one bead of green grape immortal essence to summon ten thousand phantoms.

Right now, an army several times that size was attacking, as the army's momentum rose, they had an imposing aura that could shake the world.

The army pushed forward, towards the icefall divine ape, and then splitting into four along the way.

One went left, one went right, one went up, and the last one charge ahead.

The icefall divine ape's wild nature was awakened, it charged ahead instead of retreating. Fang Yuan's strength path phantom army moved according to his will fluidly, with his command, they spread out, like a huge web, encircling the icefall divine ape.

"Kill! Kill! Kill!" Strength path phantoms roared, they were like ants attacking the icefall divine ape collectively.

The icefall divine ape attacked left and right, it destroyed countless phantoms but could not break through Fang Yuan's encirclement.

"it really is such a formidable killer move in this world! Together with his master level attainment in enslavement path, no wonder Little Lan placed so much importance on him." Seeing this, Fairy Li Shan was overjoyed.

One after another, strength path phantoms flew out of the aperture. Fang Yuan had more than a hundred thousand troops in his immortal aperture, he only summoned eighty thousand now.

Among these strength path phantoms, the most ordinary ones had two arms, some had four arms, or even six arms. The more arms they had, the stronger their battle strength.

The icefall divine ape roared angrily, it battled fiercely, its huge body and monstrous strength, along with the icicles pointing outwards on its body, caused the strength path phantoms to suffer heavy injuries before dying.

But only a portion of the scattered fist qi was expended, the rest would gather and form into strength path phantoms once again.

Because of this, the reduction of the number of phantoms of Fang Yuan's army was greatly slowed.

During the process, the joyful will in Fang Yuan's mind was used up intensely. Manipulating tens of thousands of troops, the expenditure of his joyful will was immense. In just a few dozen breaths, Fang Yuan had activated delight in water and mountain Immortal Gu nearly ten times.

"Strange, this icefall divine ape has no Immortal Gu despite being an ancient desolate beast, in fact, it does not even have a single mortal Gu! Where did the earthly calamity find this oddity?"

Fang Yuan could see the truth behind the icefall divine ape, it had no Immortal Gu, or even any mortal Gu, this ancient desolate beast's threat was greatly lowered.

"In that case, it is time to finish you off!" Fang Yuan's lips curled up, the ruthless light in his eyes burst out as he entered the field directly, charging ahead.

The light illusion bat wings on his back flickered several times, as Fang Yuan's speed increased like he was a shooting star. It was quite a sight, with the explosive sounds along the way, he traveled a huge distance in a few breaths of time, descending like a demon god, right above the icefall divine ape.

"Come, group strength support me!" Fang Yuan shouted excitedly in his heart.

At once, the forty-five group strength Gu in his immortal aperture were activated at once.

Group strength Gu had completely been incorporated into myriad self by Fang Yuan, once activated, it caused a new transformation in myriad self!

Hundreds of strength path phantoms dispersed, their strength had collectively gathered in Fang Yuan under the might of group strength Gu.

Fang Yuan raised one right arm, slamming down on icefall divine ape's skull.

With a loud bang.

His entire forearm slammed on the divine ape's skull mercilessly.

The intense recoil caused Fang Yuan's forearm to burst open, as his bones were shattered and his flesh and blood were reduced to dust.

As for icefall divine ape's skull, there was a huge hole in it. The crack in the hole spread at lightning speed, affecting the entire ape's head.

At the next moment, the icefall divine ape's skull exploded!

Seeing this, be it Fairy Li Shan or Tai Bai Yun Sheng, they were so shocked their eyeballs almost popped out.

Even Fang Yuan was shocked: "What is going on? The entire ape head was destroyed? That shouldn't be, this is an ancient desolate beast!"

Killer move myriad self was completed by him alone, group strength Gu was added in by him as well, he was very clear of his own strength after group strength Gu was added. The most he could do was to cause the icefall divine ape's skull to crack and bleed, but the entire head would not explode.

"Be careful!" At this moment, Tai Bai Yun Sheng could not help but show himself, shouting a warning.

Fang Yuan turned around and looked, his pupils shrinking rapidly.

Icefall divine ape's huge fist had gotten close to Fang Yuan without him noticing anything, it slammed down at lightning speed, like a poisonous snake's assault.

Fang Yuan could not dodge it in time, he was hit directly by the huge fist!

Chapter 686: Fang Yuan learns from Reckless Savage Demon Venerable!

Boom. Fang Yuan was sent flying like an insect, making a huge arc in the air before ruthlessly falling down on the hard ice surface.

Rumble!

Ice chunks scattered crazily, the force sent Fang Yuan flying like an artillery shell, he pierced through the ice layer and traveled for an enormous distance before finally stopping.

Fang Yuan lay amidst the broken ice, seriously injured. Even with an immortal zombie body, he could not budge a bit. His whole body was like a torn sack, the dark green zombie blood flowing out from the innumerable wounds, bones were fractured with some piercing into skin and flesh while some jutted out of the body. Only three of the eight arms were remaining. One torn off arm was lying not far away from Fang Yuan.

A long ice channel was created just now, cut open by Fang Yuan using his own body.

"Cough cough..."

Fang Yuan coughed for a while and stared with an incredulous gaze at the icefall divine ape, it was still standing upright despite losing its head.

"What the hell is this?"

According to common sense, even an ancient desolate beast would die if their head was smashed apart. But this icefall divine ape which had lost its head not only did not fall down, instead it struck Fang Yuan with a very heavy counterattack.

Fang Yuan recalled that enormous punch, common sense would have stated that such an enormous force would have already produced a sonic boom. But it was unexpectedly noiseless during the whole process!

This absolutely was not something the icefall divine ape should have been capable of accomplishing, because it did not have any Gu worms on it!

Fang Yuan tried to move his body; the immortal zombie body shuddered but still lay down on the ice, its strength failing.

However, Fang Yuan could sense his body was rapidly recovering.

Zombies used death energy as life force. As long as they were not destroyed in an instant, the abundant death energy would provide them with astonishing recovery speed.

"Fang Yuan!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng quickly flew over and at the same time, pitch black rays of light shone out from his hand and fell on Fang Yuan's body.

These pitch black rays of light were carefully prepared for Fang Yuan by Tai Bai Yun Sheng, and were not some ordinary healing Gu worms.

Ordinary healing Gu worms would bring vitality and stimulate life force, but this was of no use to Fang Yuan's immortal zombie body.

Fang Yuan needed to increase his death energy, the stronger the death energy, the faster his recovery speed would be. Thus, zombies were also known as 'living dead'.

With Tai Bai Yun Sheng's help, Fang Yuan's recovery speed surged violently.

"Great." Fang Yuan gave a horrifying smile. He soon recovered his movement ability and stood up from the ice surface.

Boom. An astonishing change happened to the icefall divine ape, it unexpectedly self-detonated.

After the detonation, a large group of pegasi were left in the icefall divine ape's place.

These pegasi were anything but ordinary, different from the two winged pegasi of the current era. They were larger than two winged pegasus by two to three times. On their backs were at least two pairs of wings, while some even had three pairs.

These were ancient pegasus, the more wings they had, the stronger their battle strength. Four winged pegasi were at the level of beast emperors while six winged pegasi were desolate beasts!

In the current five regions, the ancient pegasi were already extinct.

Most of these pegasi were four winged pegasi while there were a few with six wings!

The pegasus group neighed before colliding with Fang Yuan's strength path phantom army.

It was a massacre, Fang Yuan's strength path phantom army was steadily losing ground, suffering heavy losses.

"This is not a beast calamity! What in the world is this?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng quickly flew to Fang Yuan's side and looked at this scene with his eyes wide open.

The ancient pegasi and strength path phantom army started slaughtering each other, creating a chaotic battle situation.

Fang Yuan suffered great losses.

It was because the strength path phantom had been in a loose formation to deal with the giant icefall divine ape. Now that the giant beast was changed to a united group of pegasi, the loose phantom army formation instead allowed the pegasus group to rampage unhindered. Despite the strength path phantoms' coordination being exquisite, forming into many small battle groups, they still had more defeats than wins and suffered huge damage.

However, there were no corpses in this slaughter.

There was no need to speak of strength path phantoms which were condensed from fist qi. The crucial point was that the pegasus group had intangible bodies that turned into nothingness after they were killed.

"Could it be...." Fang Yuan's red eyes suddenly shone. He racked his brains, searching for the answer in his memories, before a thought hit him as he considered an elusive possibility.

This possibility made him look towards Hei Lou Lan.

However, Hei Lou Lan was covered in the enormous cocoon of three qi, which was so thick that he could not even see her shadow. As long as she was able to consume this three qi cocoon, her potential after becoming a Gu Immortal would be extremely deep and her future prospects would be filled with bright radiance.

Fang Yuan turned around to look at the pegasus group. His eyes narrowed and a smile appeared on his face; he waved his hand towards the back, transmitting his voice to Tai Bai Yun Sheng who was rushing over: "Old Bai, step back and watch me."

He then showed his sharp teeth and charged forward.

He pierced into the chaotic battle of the pegasus group and strength path phantom army.

In an instant, it was like Fang Yuan had poked a hornet's nest as countless ancient pegasi charged towards him. He activated hair armor and raised his arms, protecting his head.

After he locked in on a target, Fang Yuan suddenly shouted and pounced towards an injured four winged Pegasus, forcibly smashing it down from the sky to the ground.

Bang. Man and horse crashed heavily into the ground, the ice surface cracked, forming a deep pit.

Fang Yuan's whole body was filled with injuries, bones fractured in many places, skin was opened and flesh split. The recovered body was once again crushed into a miserable state.

Who knew how many pegasi attacked him when he charged into the chaotic battle and smashed into the four winged pegasus.

These pegasi naturally would not let him go. Large numbers of pegasi gathered into a white flood that fell down from the sky towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan used all his strength to suppress the intensely struggling four winged pegasus under him, while the wills in his mind surged like boiling water, dissipating intensely.

Two strength path phantom groups in the sky coordinated, and intercepted the diving pegasus group like a giant scissor.

At the same time, large numbers of strength path phantoms surged out from Fang Yuan's immortal aperture and formed a hemispherical formation above Fang Yuan, resisting the fierce offensive of the pegasus group without any regard for the losses.

The four winged pegasus under Fang Yuan was anything but cute as it neighed and struggled with all its power. It had such high strength that even Fang Yuan, a strength path Gu Immortal with an immortal zombie body, was almost unable to contain it.

Time was pressing, the opportunity could not be lost. Fang Yuan raised his fists high and smashed down ruthlessly, immediately bursting the pegasus's head, however the headless Pegasus was still struggling as if the loss of its head had no affect.

Fang Yuan then punched down with all his eight arms, bombarding the pegasus with heavy punches.

The thick ice surface below them could not endure this punishment and started cracking.

A normal four winged pegasus was equal to a beast emperor with rank five battle strength. Even if they had strong wild Gu worms, they would have turned into meat paste under Fang Yuan's offensive.

This strange four winged pegasus did not have any Gu worms on it and when Fang Yuan crushed it, it dissipated into thin air without leaving any hair, bone or even blood.

The next moment, however, Fang Yuan's narrowed eyes suddenly opened wide. Following the complete destruction of the four winged pegasus, a formless will rushed into his mind; his eyes revealed enormous shock and joy.

He kneeled on the broken ice surface and ceased all movement, resembling a statue. Despite the fierce slaughter going on above him, he did not seem to notice anything, as if he was in a dream.

"Fang Yuan!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was extremely worried when he saw this, flying towards Fang Yuan.

"Come back, don't disturb him. This is a golden opportunity for him!" Fairy Li Shan, however, suddenly transmitted her voice.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng narrowed his eyes, immediately asking in anger: "It seems you know what this calamity is? Fairy Li Shan! We are allies, we came specially to protect Hei Lou Lan in crossing the tribulation. You actually were deceiving us! What are you up to?!"

"This is not deceit, don't forget the Snowy Mountain Alliance, if I had deceived you, I would have already died according to the oath! This was only speculation which I am now sure of." Fairy Li Shan quickly explained.

She had only hidden this crucial piece of information without mentioning it, it did not mean she was deceiving them.

Even if they were allied, they could not just share all their secrets. Fang Yuan also would not do that.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's breathing sped up as he flew rapidly while irritatedly asking at the same time: "Then are you still not going to tell me now what the hell is this speculation?!"

Fairy Li Shan let out a breath of turbid air and spoke quickly: "Tai Bai Yun Sheng, you also know the origins of this icy plain. Back then, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable fought a huge battle, destroying a part of northern plains, turning that area into void. To repair the void, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable turned into an immemorial ice phoenix, and breathed out extremely cold profound ice which froze this place, turning it into a large icy plain."

"Get to the point!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng shouted.

Fairy Li Shan understood Tai Bai Yun Sheng's feelings and did not blame him, continuing with her explanation: "Everyone knows Reckless Savage Demon Venerable was a strength path Immortal Venerable, founder of the strength path and also of transformation path. Without exception, every rank nine venerable is a child of the Great Dao, the closest to the true essence of heaven and earth. Not only did laws follow their words, every action of theirs carried true meaning and even the movement of their gazes conveyed the profundities of nature. Even if they perish, their main killer move would be imprinted in heaven and earth, forming a kind of heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng involuntarily recalled the formless hands: "Yes, I know about this."

Fairy Li Shan continued: "Back then, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable turned into an ice phoenix and breathed profound ice to condense into the icy plain we are on now. Don't forget the ice phoenix transformation is a transformation path killer move. As the creator of the icy plain, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable imprinted the true meaning of strength path and transformation path in the midst of this piece of heaven and earth. A piece of speculation was circulated among a few Gu Immortals, or more precisely a rumor. As long as a strength path or transformation path Gu Master ascends to Gu Immortal in this icy plain, it will cause a resonance of dao fragments, evoking the true meaning of Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's strength path and transformation path."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng shook: "Then, then this means, isn't this?!"

"Right. the icefall divine ape was only a false appearance and the ancient pegasi were also the same; they were true meanings of strength path and transformation path, taking on the form of an earthly calamity! When someone completely shatters these external forms, the small true meaning contained within would break out and enter the body of their own accord! What is true meaning? It is the comprehension towards heaven and earth, Great Dao and law fragments. Fang Yuan destroyed a pegasus and obtained the true meaning within it. In other words, Fang Yuan is receiving teachings from Reckless Savage Demon Venerable!"

Fairy Li Shan spoke shocking words and also revealed heavy envy.

How huge was an opportunity to receive the teachings of a rank nine venerable!

If one said the three qi converged to let the Gu Master comprehend heaven and earth and gain natural inspiration, then passing tribulation in this place and obtaining true meaning was to study under Reckless Savage Demon Venerable!

Chapter 687: True Meaning Infusion

Fairy Li Shan continued with a deeply moved tone: "Reportedly, the rumor of Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's true meaning came from the currently rank seven Domination Immortal Chu Du of northern plains. It is said that when he became a strength path Gu Immortal three hundred years ago, it was at this icy plain that he passed his tribulation. It is just that there have been limited numbers of Gu Immortals advancing over these recent years. And among these newly advanced Gu Immortals, there are few that are of transformation path and even fewer of strength path. Thus, this piece of speculation was very hard to prove."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng snorted but no longer hurried towards Fang Yuan.

Although Fairy Li Shan and Hei Lou Lan deceived him and Fang Yuan, this was after all such an enormous benefit, thus Tai Bai Yun Sheng's anger dissipated for the most part.

He turned around and looked deeply at Hei Lou Lan. Hei Lou Lan was covered in the three qi cocoon and she was progressing smoothly. The qi cocoon's volume was slowly shrinking methodically.

'This woman has truly great ambitions, she is not satisfied with being a ten extreme physique immortal, she also wants to learn from Reckless Savage Demon Venerable. She is not afraid that her strength is lacking and she would die because of her greed. Speaking of which, this style of taking risks is actually similar to Fang Yuan's, they are both lunatics!' Tai Bai Yun Sheng heaved a sigh inwardly.

"So it was indeed like this, they are the external forms of true meaning, ahahhaah!" Fang Yuan laughed loudly and slowly stood up from his kneeling position with his expression revealing his high spirits.

He then gazed at the ancient pegasus group again, but the way he looked at them was different this time.

His gaze was extremely heated, like a pervert that had his lust held back for several thousands of years, who then saw an absolutely beautiful woman. Or like a bandit whose greed would never be satisfied, seeing the world's greatest treasury!

"I have advanced to a strength path Gu Immortal but my strength path foundation was shallow and I could only reach quasi-grandmaster realm in strength path! It is extremely difficult to make one's realm progress even a little, and needs a sufficient quantity of regular accumulation in order to initiate a qualitative transformation. But now, as long as I kill these true meaning external forms, I can rapidly raise my strength path realm, elevating it to genuine grandmaster realm!"

Memories and experiences of five hundred years of bitter struggles made Fang Yuan extremely aware of the difficulty in progressing one's realm.

Realm represented the understanding of Great Dao! One's strength path realm was a Gu Master's understanding of the Dao of strength. Realm was generally divided into ordinary, quasi-master, master, quasi-grandmaster, grandmaster, quasi-great grandmaster, great grandmaster, quasi-supreme grandmaster and supreme grandmaster.

Most Gu Masters would only have ordinary realm in their whole lives. Quasi-masters were geniuses or old, experienced Gu Masters.

Masters were extremely rare! For instance, in the Imperial Court contest which was an assembly of heroes of the large northern plains, only Fang Yuan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng had master level attainment in flying among those who reached Imperial Court blessed land. While in enslavement path, there were only Jiang Bao Ya, Yang Po Ying, Ma Zun, Chang Shan Yin (Fang Yuan) and Nu Er Tu, five masters over the entire contest!

And speaking of refinement path supreme grandmasters, even throughout human history, there had only been three: Long Hair Ancestor, Old Eccentric Tian Nan and Old Immortal Kong Jue!

Every advancement of a realm meant an astonishing upgrade in one's battle strength!

It was because higher realm meant deeper understanding of the law fragments in heaven and earth. It allowed Gu Masters to refine new, better Gu worms, create more killer moves and display greater dominance of their paths.

Fang Yuan had the most understanding of blood path among all the major paths. In his previous life, he was an awe-inspiring blood path grandmaster!

His battle strength was outstanding and he had created many new Gu worms of blood path, and these new Gu had even surpassed Blood Sea Ancestor's in some aspects!

He had also researched many blood path killer moves, and despite them being mortal killer moves, they had extraordinary power.

Fang Yuan now had the immortal killer move myriad self, the representation of the convergence of enslavement and strength path, a unique killer move created from squeezing out all his potential, and with the help of natural inspiration and wisdom Gu.

But even with such a killer move, when his battle strength was considered, it was not a match with his peak blood path attainment in his previous life.

Fang Yuan could suppress his immortal killer move myriad self by just using his previous life's blood path killer moves.

He had even created, from initially nothing, some remnant recipes of completely new Immortal Gu with his grandmaster realm. Of course, the completion rates of these remnant recipes were rather low.

This was the world of Gu, and more than that, it was the world of Gu Masters.

Gu worms involved nurturing, use and refinement, and the bulk of these fundamentals relied upon Gu Masters.

Generation after generation of Gu Masters brought forth new developments, constantly using their plentiful creative prowess to research new Gu worms and open new paths, which then created the extremely wondrous way of Gu which covered all aspects! Thus, heroes were able to emerge like stars in the sky over the boundless history of humans.

Gu is the essence of heaven and earth, man is the spirit of all living things!

The famed people of the past had accomplishments as high as the mountains that the later generations would find hard to surpass. However, on the whole, the strength of the five regions was growing steadily and becoming much more profound, surpassing the eras of Immemorial, Olden Antiquity and so on.

"Gu Masters nurture, use and refine Gu, getting down to the basics, it is a process of humans probing and studying nature, the world, and the Great Dao. Be it a xianxia world, a magic-based world, or a scientific world, they are all the same, they are all the exploration and study of nature and the world itself. It is only that the difference in the world's laws make the exploration methods different."

Once can only learn if they explore continuously. Only by learning could they have accumulation. And only with accumulation could they transcend the world!

"And in this world, the measurement of the stage-wise accomplishments of study of heaven and earth, and the Great Dao is the realm of every paths! Great Dao is a closed book, and for a Gu Master to study and explore heaven and earth, they have to use Gu worms to approach the Great Dao with different methods, they need to constantly summarize their comprehensions, need insights and require sufficient experience. However, right now I am obtaining true meaning infusion which is as if I am observing the world while standing on the shoulder of a giant! It is making Reckless Savage Demon Venerable open the pages of the closed book to the parts which I can understand and let me read it directly. This is a shortcut, an extremely rare fortuitous encounter! This will save me a great deal of time and immense effort!"

Fang Yuan was more excited the more he thought of it.

'Hei Lou Lan! You are a lunatic! You actually wanted to learn from Reckless Savage Demon Venerable while gaining natural inspiration, and obtaining the infusion of true meaning. Hmph, are you not afraid you can't manage to comprehend them all and be thrown into confusion, even failing your immortal ascension! However... your greed, I like it a lot. This gift from you, I shall accept it all!'

Fang Yuan shouted inwardly; with such heavy profits ahead of him, he decided to not leave behind even a little!

Myriad self! Myriad self! Myriad self!

He activated his immortal killer move nonstop; for the first time, he disregarded the costs as he activated it frantically!

Countless strength path phantoms emerged, forming a huge army inside the immortal aperture, their scale several times larger than before.

At the same time, large numbers of mortal Gu forming the immortal killer move perished, this was the backlash from heaven and earth, and also the consequences of Fang Yuan's extreme rate of activation.

However, Fang Yuan did not feel any heartache, everything was okay as long as the core, cleanse soul Immortal Gu, did not have any problems. He had made ample preparations for this trip and had brought large numbers of mortal Gu for replenishment and substitution.

"Come!" Fang Yuan lifted his chest as countless strength path phantoms surged out from his immortal aperture.

The strength path phantom army flooded the world, as if it could engulf mountains and rivers. The sparse battle strength just before was immediately replenished and soon surpassed the previous limit, reaching a new height.

Large numbers, no, a sea of strength path phantoms filled the whole battlefield.

"This... there are at least three hundred thousand!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng and even Fairy Li Shan was stupefied at this sight.

The ancient pegasus group was firmly surrounded in the air by the strength path phantom army.

The slaughter between the two sides had reached the climax.

Fang Yuan walked leisurely on the ice surface below the ongoing aerial battle.

Joyful will were created and rapidly expended in his mind. Under his command, the army coordinated to form different groups, and like giant hands, they pounced upon four winged pegasi without caring for losses.

Next, dozens of strength path phantoms worked together to forcefully push the four winged pegasi down to the ice surface.

Then, Fang Yuan would slowly walk over, raise his eight thick giant arms and shower down punches for the kill.

Miserable neighing sounds filled the area as pegasi were shattered apart. True meaning rushed into Fang Yuan's mind and the profundities of the Great Dao were rapidly absorbed. His movement stiffened for several breaths of time before recovering once again.

Fang Yuan thus engaged in crazy slaughter of ancient pegasi.

"Refreshing!" After another true meaning infusion, he excitedly roared, his gaze was so blood red that it was difficult to stare at it directly!

The strength path realm which would have taken years and even dozens of years to raise, was rapidly advancing following the true meaning infusion.

Fang Yuan felt incomparable pleasure and enjoyment.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was watching with a dumbstruck expression, Fang Yuan's madness made him feel a chill from the depths of his heart. Even Fairy Li Shan could not help but be silent.

After less than half of the pegasus group was destroyed, the earthly calamity transformed again. The pegasus group merged together to form thirty-three giant snakes.

These giant snakes were as large as a house and had extremely powerful defense, covered with black armor and shields. When they fell on the ground, they immediately occupied terrain advantage.

"Another transformation and this time to shield snake?" Fang Yuan laughed malevolently; he did not move, the strength path phantom army in the air had already shrouded over the snakes like dark clouds.

By occupying the ground, these shield snakes only needed to defend the attacks from above unlike if they were flying in the air where they could be attacked from all directions.

Fang Yuan's slaughter immediately slowed down.

It took a good while for the huge army to handle one shield snake.

Fang Yuan laughed maniacally as he pounced down upon it.

The shield snake was filled with injuries and before it could raise its head, it was bombarded by Fang Yuan's eight arms. The enormous strength from the overlaying of forty-five group strength Gu directly destroyed the shield snake.

An enormous true meaning that far surpassed the previous ones charged into Fang Yuan's mind.

The snake corpse that had lost its head suddenly dissipated, transforming into small snakes; in few moments, the place was filled with a sea of ferocious and slippery snakes.

Fang Yuan was in the process of comprehending essence of Great Dao and could not budge, thus he fell in the sea of snakes.

The snake sea attacked madly, quickly covering his enormous body.

Fang Yuan's comprehension this time was different from before. In the previous true meaning infusion, Fang Yuan felt like he had turned into a pegasus, living its life from birth to death, from young to old, running on the firm ground and soaring on the vast sky...

He sensed the unique body structure of Pegasus, the use of various strengths and the ingenuity of using power.

And now, he turned into a snake from breaking out of the egg to devouring all kinds of preys. He personally experienced the twisting snake body, the strength of its constriction, the muscle rhythm when it swallowed its food, the force application when its head moved like lightning to capture prey...

Not only was it raising the strength path realm, but transformation path and even flying master attainment were advancing.

These experiences extended and stepped on the maxim of strength path. These maxims covered extremely large information and were hard to describe using words. Because the wonders of Great Dao could not be put to words; words would be too simple, too dull, too shallow and simply not be able to portray its mysteries and wonders!

Chapter 688: Second Battle With Hei Cheng (1/2)

"Fang Yuan!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng's loud shout could be heard, Fang Yuan opened his eyes and woke up from within the sea of snakes.

All around him, from head to toe, there were snakes. Countless snakes were coiling around him, trying to constrict and bite him. If not for Fang Yuan's hair armor protecting him, these small snakes might have drilled into his stomach already.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily, he was joyful instead of shocked!

He stretched out eight huge arms, grabbing with his hands as he destroyed dozens of small snakes. Tens of true meaning infusions gushed into his mind.

His consciousness was foggy for a moment, but recovered immediately.

As he slowly adapted to it, and as his attainment level increased, his true meaning absorption speed became faster and faster.

In the intoxication of killing, he even withdrew the hair armor and opened his mouth, suddenly inhaling.

Immediately, countless small snakes slipped into his mouth.

He opened his mouth to chew, his sharp fangs tearing the snake bodies into shreds, next he swallowed and the snake corpses vanished down his throat, disappearing from this world.

Waves of true meaning filled his mind unceasingly.

Strength path true meaning, transformation path true meaning, all these small traces were continuously absorbed by him. At the same time, with trial and error, he became familiar with the new knowledge, it gave Fang Yuan a much deeper understanding in other areas. For example, his flying attainment.

After Fang Yuan killed the third huge shield snake, his strength path attainment level went from quasi-grandmaster to grandmaster realm.

Strength path grandmaster!

That is to say, if given a bit more time, Fang Yuan would reach the level of blood path in his previous life! Because his blood path attainment level was also grandmaster realm.

Right now, his mind was filled with countless thoughts and countless inspirations. His understanding of strength path had reached a whole new level, he could create many new strength path Gu worms and many mortal killer moves that were related to strength path now.

But Fang Yuan was not satisfied, he continued slaughtering.

The earthly calamity failed after transforming into the icefall divine ape, the ancient pegasi, and the shield snake group. Now, there was a new transformation, it turned onto a group of rockmen.

Fang Yuan manipulated his army, he trampled on their heads and swallowed their bodies in the sea, killing the rockmen, and understanding the power of thickness.

The earthly calamity turned into a bee group next, as Fang Yuan self-detonated his strength path phantoms continuously, learning the power of piercing.

The earthly calamity transformed into a rhinoceros group, as Fang Yuan killed them, he learned about the power of charging.

As his strength path attainment continued to rise, after he stabilized his grandmaster realm, he began a charge towards quasi-great grandmaster realm.

Right at this moment, two bright rainbows, one black and one white, pierced the air and descended.

"We finally found you!"

"You were indeed in the icy plain."

As the rainbows faded, two people, Hei Cheng and Xue Song Zi, appeared.

The powerful enemies had come!

"So many strength path phantoms, what is going on?" Xue Song Zi's pupils shrunk, before they shined in a bright, heated light: "Oh? This is... it seems the rumors were true, undergoing tribulation in the icy plain will possibly attract Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's true meaning!"

Hei Cheng's eyes were eerily looking at the battlefield, next his gaze focused on the three colored qi cocoon.

After such a long time, Hei Lou Lan had not finished absorbing the three qi yet, her human qi was simply too huge in quantity!

"Hehehe, Hei Lou Lan, you guys have nowhere to run, why don't you surrender." Hei Cheng laughed heartily, he opened his right hand and revealed an Immortal Gu.

This Immortal Gu gave off an eerie blue light, it was a time path rank six Immortal Gu.

The aura of the Immortal Gu was surging, it resonated with the two time path Immortal Gu in Tai Bai Yun Sheng's aperture, causing them to vibrate.

Fairy Li Shan's expression changed, she showed herself and stood in front of Hei Lou Lan, she spoke coldly: "Instant Pause?"

This was the rank six time path Immortal Gu Instant Pause, it could freeze the time of the target for six moments, with this Gu around, Hei Cheng did not have to worry about Fang Yuan running away using Fixed Immortal Travel.

Hei Cheng saw Fairy Li Shan and he focused his gaze, he spoke with deep meaning: "To think that the mastermind behind all this was Fairy Li Shan. Why are you sowing discord between us father and daughter? Oh I see, as expected, which Gu Immortal would not be interested in the yin-yang life extension method in my possession?"

Saying so, Hei Cheng laughed sarcastically, he showed a mocking expression to Fairy Li Shan, oozing with confidence.

Fairy Li Shan's expression was solemn, her voice became louder as it filled the skies: "Hei Cheng, you are destined to fail today. Don't think of causing any harm to Little Lan, because the person stopping you will be me!"

Saying so, Fairy Li Shan stopped hiding it, she burst out the grand aura of a rank seven Gu Immortal.

At the same time, the surface of the ice broke, countless tree roots grew rapidly, they coiled around and moved like huge pythons.

The trees grew quickly, it soon became a forested area. After a few breaths, pear blossoms grew, the smell of the flowers was fragrant and spread for several li.

Fairy Li Shan stood under the tree, her body was shielded by the leaves and branches, vanishing.

Meanwhile, Hei Lou Lan was still balancing the three qi, she was on top of a pear tree.

Battlefield killer move — Pear Orchard!

"To think that third leader's cultivation level had secretly reached rank seven. Hei Cheng, be careful, third leader cultivates earth and wood path, she had set up this battlefield earlier, I am also a member of Snowy Mountain blessed land, I cannot battle Fairy Li Shan due to the alliance rules." Xue Song Zi reminded.

Usually when Fairy Li Shan showed up in northern plains, she revealed rank six cultivation. Few knew about her true cultivation level.

Hei Cheng's expression was calm, his gaze shifted to Fang Yuan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Fairy Li Shan for a moment, before turning back to Hei Lou Lan.

"One immortal zombie, one rank six Gu Immortal, one rank seven Gu Immortal..." Hei Cheng muttered, he snorted coldly, saying to Xue Song Zi: "Go deal with that immortal zombie and the rank six Gu Immortal, after I kill Fairy Li Shan, we will take down Hei Lou Lan."

His tone was filled with decisiveness and confidence.

Although Fairy Li Shan was rank seven, her battle strength should be at the lower tier of rank seven, there would still be some disparity from Hei Cheng.

"Okay!" Seeing that the toughest foe was going to be dealt with by Hei Cheng, Xue Song Zi agreed.

He flew down, straight towards the earthly calamity.

He was someone with some knowledge, he knew that the earthly calamity contained a Demon Venerable's true meaning, even if he was not a strength path or transformation path Gu Immortal, he wanted a share of it. Gu Immortals usually ventured into many paths so that they could assist their main path, who would be unhappy with a higher attainment?

"You're courting death!" Fang Yuan saw Xue Song Zi rushing here and shouted angrily, a ruthless light flashing in his eyes.

"Merely a rank six immortal zombie, you dare to speak such words!" Xue Song Zi snorted in disdain, he rapidly got closer.

In his first battle with Hei Cheng, Fang Yuan focused on retreating, to escape from the area. Thus, he did not reveal his true battle strength.

Hei Cheng and Xue Song Zi analyzed the situation, and assumed that Fang Yuan's two movement Immortal Gu were lent to him by other Gu Immortals.

Even though Fang Yuan's strength path phantom army was fighting against the earthly calamity intensely.

But first, the earthly calamity was already mostly destroyed, second, wide range killer moves were very common, third, most immortal zombies had battle strength lower than ordinary Gu Immortals, and finally, there was a rank six Gu Immortal and a rank seven Gu Immortal on Fang Yuan's side, Xue Song Zi subconsciously underestimated Fang Yuan's threat.

Xue Song Zi's speed was very fast, he was right above Fang Yuan in a moment's time.

"I'll let you taste my power!" He growled, he pushed with his hands and used his killer moves.

Drifting Snow! Ice Mountain Awl! Snow Sparrow Crisis!

He used three killer moves at once, this showed Xue Song Zi extraordinary control over manipulation of Gu worms.

These three killer moves were all attack type killer moves. In an instant, intense winds blew as snow filled the air, countless snowflakes gathered into birds, they moved fluidly in the intense wind and snow, with much intelligence, there were thousands of them! Twenty to thirty icicles that were the size of small hills were covered in sharp spikes as they flew towards Fang Yuan, trying to pierce through his body.

Fang Yuan laughed coldly, he waved his hand and the giant army moved!

The myriad self army moved with courage, their shouts overwhelmed the heavens, everywhere the army went, the icicles collapsed, snow sparrows cried, and the sound of the wind halted.

"Eh?!" Xue Song Zi's expression changed, only after fighting did he realize the truly fearsome might of myriad self!

Seeing that the myriad self army was coming for him, Xue Song Zi growled angrily as his hair stood up, traces and traces of frost energy shot out from them.

In an instant, the frost energy spread quickly and formed an ice crystal domain in the air.

Battlefield killer move — Snow Domain!

"Towering pine tree, icy hair dragon stream!" Xue Song Zi growled, using two defensive killer moves at once.

Immediately, pine trees erupted in the snow domain, from nothingness, they grew to become large and bulky trees, the branches tied the trees together, forming many thick walls of defense.

As for his long snow white hair, it extended and gave off a dragon's cry in the air. The long hair turned into dozens of dragon shaped ice, coiling around his body and forming a castle-like defense, with Xue Song Zi protected tightly in the center.

However, when the myriad self army charged over, pine trees collapsed, and ice dragons shattered, the snow domain lasted for a moment before breaking apart.

"It's actually an immortal killer move! Who in the world is this immortal zombie?" Xue Song Zi's expression was pale, his eyes showed panic as he retreated quickly, even faster than when he came, he was in a pathetic state!

At the same time, Hei Cheng and Fairy Li Shan had engaged in intense battle.

The battle of the two had reached the climax right from the start.

Hei Cheng used dark arrow Immortal Gu to its limits, shooting three dark arrows into the pear orchard, flying around and trying to locate Fairy Li Shan's true hiding place.

In the pear orchard, it was dense with vegetation, and pear blossoms fell from the trees. The roots were tangled together and growing, as hundreds of sunflower king lotuses appeared.

As the lotuses opened, beams of burning light shot towards Hei Cheng.

Hei Cheng's body shuddered, dark liquid oozed out of his black robe, dying the area of sky around him black. This was also a battlefield killer move, called dark veil.

From the dark veil, black balls were shot out, pouring down like rain.

The black balls slammed into the pear orchard, forming huge pitch black spirals. This was the killer move that Hei Lou Lan used in the imperial court contest — Dark Vortex.

The dark vortices expanded, corroding the trees and flowers, causing huge holes to form in the pear orchard.

Meanwhile, the heated beams of sunlight also tore open some areas of the dark veil.

As the two continued to attack, the light beams fell in quantity while the number of dark vortices increased, Hei Cheng quickly gained the upper hand.

As expected of a famous rank seven Gu Immortal expert of northern plains!

Chapter 689: Second Battle With Hei Cheng (2/2)

"Found you." Hei Cheng's eyes shined brightly, he laughed sinisterly as he used his investigative killer move, discovering Fairy Li Shan's figure in the pear orchard.

He immediately used dark arrow Immortal Gu to its limit, as three dark arrows shot out into the air, towards its target.

The pear orchard went into action, countless tree roots stretched out, moved and coiled around like dragons, they desperately blocked these three arrows.

At the crucial moment, Fairy Li Shan was gritted her teeth, her eyes bright as a lamp.

She shouted in her heart: "Earth flower lotus burial!"

The ground exploded loudly, as a huge man-eating flower appeared at lightning speed.

The man-eating flower opened its mouth, swallowing a dark arrow. Next, the entire man-eating flower's size shrunk, it was less than half of its original mass, but it could trap the dark arrow temporarily.

Hei Cheng snorted, his gaze was shining as the swallowed dark arrow was trying to escape, forming a sharp pointed bulge in the man eating flower's surface.

But next, more man eating flowers appeared from the ground. The second man eating flower ate the first man eating flower, shrinking after that. The third man eating flower ate the second man eating flower. Repeating the process, after seventeen to eighteen man eating flowers were summoned, Hei Cheng's connection to this dark arrow fell by at least thirty percent.

Hei Cheng knew that this dark arrow could not escape in the short run, his attention was on his two remaining arrows.

Fairy Li Shan's expression was pale, she shouted lowly: "Fading heavenly flower."

A large number of pear blossoms flew, they were pure white as snow, they floated in the air and turned into light specks.

The dark arrow's speed was fast, but the quantity of light specks was numerous, they were thick and densely packed, during the process of the arrow's flight, it was corroded.

The dark arrow was covered in light specks and hot sparks immediately were formed, white spots appeared on the dark arrow, causing its speed and power to fall.

Hei Cheng snorted, he knew the other party was well prepared. He was openly being targeted while his enemies were hidden, everyone knew about this Immortal Gu Dark Arrow, thus his attack was countered.

But he was not to be trifled with, even though he did not develop an immortal killer move using dark arrow Immortal Gu as the core Gu, but in the process of trying, he had obtained several mortal killer moves that could cause changes to the dark arrows.

Hei Cheng stared, as he used a set of mortal Gu in his immortal aperture. The two dark arrows changed directions, meeting in the air and fusing, becoming one again.

After fusing, the dark arrow was pitch black without a single light speck, it regained its former speed and power.

The dark arrow shot like lightning, stabbing into a huge trunk in the pear orchard.

In Hei Cheng's field of vision, Fairy Li Shan was hiding in this tree trunk.

But at the next moment, Fairy Li Shan's voice came from the other side: "You fell for it, Hei Cheng. Tree flower sheds tears!"

A bright flower bloomed in the tree trunk, and thick nectar oozed out from the center of the flower, it was extremely fragrant.

Dark arrow hit a wooden puppet that resembled Fairy Li Shan, the nectar spread and covered this dark arrow completely.

Thereafter, the nectar solidified, becoming like amber as it sealed the dark arrow inside.

"Hei Cheng, today, you will undoubtedly fail!" Fairy Li Shan's body was on top of a tree crown, although she was pale and perspiring profusely, her eyes were bright and she had a vigorous aura.

A large part of Hei Cheng's great strength was due to the dark arrow Immortal Gu.

This was an attack type Immortal Gu, Fairy Li Shan only had mountain pledge Gu, she could not face it head on. She could only exert her methods and use three mortal killer moves to seal the dark arrows.

After the dark arrows were sealed, Hei Cheng lost his strongest means of attacking.

"Really? You think that's all I have?" Hei Cheng stood in the dark veil, looking down at Fairy Li Shan as he showed a mocking smile.

Under Fairy Li Shan's supervision, he stretched out his arm, opening his palm and revealing a black pearl.

This black pearl was about the size of a rice bowl, it was black and shiny, like a black crystal. On the surface of this translucent pearl, one could see a boar shaped animal sleeping inside.

Fairy Li Shan saw this pearl and her eyes immediately widened, she showed an alarmed expression: "This is Dark Prison?"

Hei Cheng nodded slightly: "That's right, this is my Hei tribe's rank six Immortal Gu House — Dark Prison."

His voice was plain, yet it contained a feeling of pride.

Hei Cheng was not Hei tribe's first supreme elder, but to ensure that this trip had no accidents, he paid a huge price and borrowed this item from Hei tribe's first supreme elder.

"This is bad..." Fairy Li Shan's heart sank to rock bottom. Dark Prison was a beast stable, trapped inside was the ancient desolate beast, sharp tusk boar. If it was summoned, Fairy Li Shan would be in deep trouble.

Be it pear orchard, earth flower lotus burial, fading heavenly flower, or tree flower sheds tears, these were all mortal killer move. In order to deal with Hei Cheng's dark arrow Immortal Gu, Fairy Li Shan had thought through it carefully and devised three killer moves that could temporarily seal the dark arrows.

But because of this, her mind was worn out and her head was hurting. Although she had the pear orchard battlefield, she had fallen into a disadvantage against Hei Cheng's dark veil, she could only hang on and hope that Hei Lou Lan's tribulation would finish soon, to allow her to come over and assist her.

However, sharp tusk boar was an ancient desolate beast, destroying pear orchard was as easy as stomping on a garden. Once pear orchard was destroyed, the three 'flower moves' that relied on pear orchard would weaken greatly, the dark arrows would escape.

"If that happens, all the effort I put in earlier would go to waste!" Fairy Li Shan gritted her teeth, but right at this moment, she heard a warning from Tai Bai Yun Sheng — be careful!

Of what?

Fairy Li Shan looked back, seeing that a dark arrow had stealthily flown over, it was thirty centimeters away from her.

"What? But I made arrangements around here..." Fairy Li Shan was shocked, but it was too late.

The dark arrow flew over, piercing into her forehead, through her skull, and coming out of the back of her head.

"Little aunt!" Hei Lou Lan screamed, she had finally digested all three qi and had recovered her mobility. But the moment she opened her eyes, she saw that the relative that had always taken good care of her was killed by a dark arrow piercing her skull, dying a terrible death.

"It's over." Hei Cheng retrieved the ball shaped Dark Prison.

Fairy Li Shan had only sealed two dark arrows, when the two arrows combined earlier, Hei Cheng had covertly shot out a third dark arrow. Using Dark Prison to attract Fairy Li Shan's attention, he secretly utilized several mortal killer moves, together with dark arrow, he took down all of the defenses around Fairy Li Shan.

However, at the next moment!

A flash of light shot over, as Fairy Li Shan returned to the state she was in a moment ago, her injuries were gone and her skull was intact.

Immortal Gu Man as Before!

Far away, Tai Bai Yun Sheng breathed roughly as he said: "So close, I almost failed to make it!"

Hei Cheng's pupils shrunk, his anger was rising.

He was not furious that Tai Bai Yun Sheng had ruined his battle result, but he was angry at Xue Song Zi for not doing his best! They had agreed that he would kill Fairy Li Shan while Xue Song Zi would kill Tai Bai Yun Sheng and the immortal zombie who was Fang Yuan.

But the result was?

Tai Bai Yun Sheng could actually interfere in his battle!

"Xue Song Zi..." Hei Cheng gritted his teeth, he looked at the battlefield far away.

But what Hei Cheng saw was, Xue Song Zi's robe was tattered, he was escaping with an expression of fear. His long hair had become much shorter, he was almost bald.

His face was bruised, a part of it was swollen and his body was covered in blood, one of his arm was hanging awkwardly from his body, the bone had fractured.

Hei Cheng's pupils could not help but contract.

Xue Song Zi had healing Gu in his possession. For Gu Immortals, a fracture was not a serious injury.

But the point was, the opponent gave Xue Song Zi absolutely no time to heal his fracture!

This... exactly how strong was the enemy?

As if answering his question, the strength path phantom army numbering over two hundred thousand shouted, a cry that could shake the earth.

They were a huge mob, even thicker than the tribulation cloud in the sky, chasing after Xue Song Zi alone.

This was simply bullying!

Even this rank seven Gu Immortal Hei Cheng frowned deeply: "What is going on? Why have these strength path phantoms not been destroyed yet, in fact, even more are appearing?"

After that, he saw that half the phantom army was charging towards him.

Hei Cheng snorted coldly, he willed and several mortal killer moves were activated together.

Thousand Demon Rampage! Dark Fire! Black Wind Break!

"Kill!" The myriad self army charged.

In several breaths of time, the wails of demons resounded, the dark fire dimmed, and the black winds dissipated.

Hei Cheng who had always been confident and relaxed finally changed his expression: "This power... this is an immortal killer move! This inconspicuous looking immortal zombie actually has such high battle strength?"

The myriad self army pressed forth, charging into Hei Cheng's dark veil battlefield fearlessly.

The pitch black battlefield that occupied half the sky was quickly being broken down, it resembled the clothing of a beggar, extremely tattered.

Hei Cheng's eyes twitched, he had to retreat!

He was handsome and elegant, even when he retreated, he still kept his cool, his arms were like butterflies fluttering in the sky, activating mortal killer moves one after another.

But this could not stop the advancement of the myriad self army.

Just like a humongous tide, no matter how powerful his mortal killer moves were, they were like rocks in front of a tsunami, or weak little fish, they were all swept away and devoured mercilessly!

Hei Cheng squinted his eyes, his expression turned grim.

He finally understood how Xue Song Zi felt, facing the myriad self army, he was a great rank seven Gu Immortal, a famous expert in northern plains, but now he felt a slight sense of helplessness and weakness.

The army had formed into an overwhelming size, it was hard to resist!

"This immortal killer move... even if I use Dark Prison and release the sharp tusk boar, it might not be its match!" Hei Cheng retreated under the pressure of the army.

Under this situation, if Hei Cheng wanted to turn the situation around, he would need to kill Fang Yuan's main body using dark arrows. But two dark arrows were already trapped by Fairy Li Shan, the remaining one could do nothing to Fang Yuan who had Immortal Gu Worldly Wave Trace.

"This lunatic, how many beads of immortal essence did he use?!" Hei Cheng cursed in his heart, his eyes were fixed on Fang Yuan who was on the ground.

Fang Yuan absorbed another trace of the Demon Venerable's true meaning, sensing Hei Cheng's dangerous gaze, he looked back and gave Hei Cheng a smile of disdain.

At the same time, a large portion of the army charged towards Hei Cheng.

"This fellow!" Hei Cheng finally showed a trace of nervousness. Being pincer attacked by two armies, he could only dodge in the sky. Even after he used countless mortal killer moves, he could only halt the army's advancement slightly.

At this moment, the situation had become — two Gu Immortals being chased down by Fang Yuan alone.

"Good job junior brother!"

Fairy Li Shan stood on the crown of a tree, seeing this, her expression froze slightly. She did not expect the situation to become like this.

Over at Fang Yuan's side, he had finally destroyed the earthly calamity and obtained all of the infusions of true meaning. His strength path attainment was still at grandmaster realm, it did not break through again. But his transformation path attainment rose to become a transformation master. As for his flying attainment, it also grew significantly, he broke through master level and reached quasi-grandmaster realm.

But Fang Yuan was not satisfied, he said to Hei Lou Lan: "Quickly, don't you have small family qi Gu, release all of the collected earth qi, we might attract more earthly calamities!"

Everyone heard this and was speechless.

Hei Lou Lan rolled her eyes, after the infusion of the three qi, the essence of her life had been elevated, she had transcended mortals and became a Gu Immortal. Her body was purified in all aspects, even the heavy injury in her eye sockets had healed completely.

"I have to keep these small family qi Gu to refine Immortal Gu. Time is limited, let's retreat!" Hei Lou Lan rejected Fang Yuan's suggestion and shouted.

Fang Yuan licked his lips, unsatisfied. But since she did not agree, there was nothing he could do.

Everyone gathered and entered Fang Yuan's immortal aperture.

Fang Yuan looked at the icy plain battlefield longingly, finally using Fixed Immortal Travel.

Three breaths later, he vanished, returning to Snowy Mountain blessed land.

"We're letting him leave?" Xue Song Zi and Hei Cheng gathered.

Hei Cheng's brows rose, he said coldly: "Even if I have Instant Pause, can you break through the defense of these strength path phantoms?"

Xue Song Zi looked at the remaining myriad self army in the battlefield and was unable to say a word.

Chapter 690: A Commotion in Northern Plains, A Wisdom Path Inheritance

In the quiet room at the third branch peak of Snowy Mountain.

It was fine weather outside. Clear blue sky, refreshing air and tall white snowy mountains combined to form a tranquil and boundless view.

The fragrance of tea filled the quiet room.

Fang Yuan was gasping as he lay down with his body full of injuries; thin streams of zombie blood flowed out from the wounds and accumulated on the ground.

However, he did not care and also did not feel any pain. Seven minutes had gone by already since he had closed his eyes to rest.

Besides him, there were three others in the quiet room.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was standing next to Fang Yuan, quickly moving his hands, emitting rays of black light that were healing Fang Yuan's injuries.

Fairy Li Shan was sitting at her old spot beside the window, absent-mindedly brewing tea, while most of her attention was focused on Hei Lou Lan who was beside her.

Hei Lou Lan was sitting cross-legged with her eyes closed, her face looked solemn and respectful like a jade statue.

There were three steps in immortal ascension: shattering the aperture, receiving qi and releasing Gu. She had completed the first two steps when undergoing tribulation in the icy plain. And after returning to the quiet room using Fixed Immortal Travel, she had started the third step.

With her foundation, the creation of her immortal aperture was a settled matter. Right now, she was probably refining Immortal Gu in her immortal aperture and resisting the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity formed in there.

By the looks of it, she was going to complete this step alone and did not want an outsider's help.

However, if there was any problem, Hei Lou Lan would immediately ask for help; Fang Yuan, Fairy Li Shan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng would have to quickly enter Hei Lou Lan's immortal aperture and resist the heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity.

By the time the tea was boiling and gurgling, Hei Lou Lan let out a breath of turbid air and slowly opened her eyes.

This movement immediately attracted the other three's gazes.

Fairy Li Shan stopped brewing and placed the teapot down in a hurry, asking in concern: "Success?"

Hei Lou Lan nodded.

Fairy Li Shan took a deep breath, her eyes reddened as she spoke in a choked voice filled with excitement and relief: "Little Lan, you have the Great Strength True Martial Physique and now have succeeded in becoming an immortal, you possess a super grade blessed land and have extraordinary potential. Truly, after a dark cloud comes a clear sky, if sister knew of this in the afterlife, she would certainly be happy!"

When an ordinary Gu Master advanced to Gu Immortal, their blessed land could be classified into one of three grades: high, middle or low.

When one of the ten extreme physiques advanced to Gu Immortal, they would be taking an enormous risk and naturally would have bigger gains. If their immortal ascension succeeded, their blessed land would be a super grade blessed land!

High grade blessed lands were formed with a size of 4700km2 to 6000km2, drew in a large tributary of the river of time and created over thirty beads of immortal essence. There would be plenty of heaven and earth qi remaining which could mutually interact and refine the vital Gu and core Gu into Immortal Gu.

Super grade blessed lands were even larger with a territory of over 6700 km2. The tributary of the river of time it drew in would be gigantic and the amount of green grape immortal essence created would surpass fifty beads! If there was nothing unexpected, it could create at least two Immortal Gu.

Hei Lou Lan appeared tranquil: "I have succeeded in advancing to Gu Immortal but have yet to kill that old scumbag."

Her indifferent tone contained a deep and piercing hatred.

"Hei Lou Lan, I hate to be blunt but the chances of killing Hei Cheng with only the four of us, even if he is alone, are rather low." Tai Bai Yun Sheng coughed, and said.

"Right, defeating a Gu Immortal is easy but killing is another thing altogether." Fang Yuan heaved a deep sigh as he stood up, the injuries on his body had essentially healed.

Previously, in his battle with Gu Immortal Plump Lady in western desert, he had obtained superiority but Plump Lady had still escaped.

This time, he battled Hei Cheng and Xue Song Zi, his phantom army had taken the lead and were able to wreak havoc, but they couldn't trap the two Gu Immortals and could only let them retreat safely.

Myriad self was strong but there was nothing to be done about it if the enemy did not engage you head-on.

Gu Immortals were smart and knew to avoid the enemy's strong points. In truth, Fang Yuan's second battle with Hei Cheng could only be considered a draw.

It was true that Fang Yuan had the upper hand, but it was hard to maintain this dominance for long; if the time was stretched on, the strength path phantoms would dissipate and it would then be Hei Cheng's turn to counterattack.

This immortal killer move indeed could build up to a big advantage, but not to the extent of being at complete dominance against Hei Cheng.

Thus, when Hei Lou Lan said to retreat, Fang Yuan did not oppose. He stopped at the right time and activated Fixed Immortal Travel, bringing them back here.

Hei Lou Lan looked at Fang Yuan and gave a slight smile: "To be able to succeed this time in resisting the enemy and allowing me to pass the tribulation is thanks to your strength."

"Since we are allies, we naturally need to help each other out." A sharp light flashed through Fang Yuan's eyes.

He helped Hei Lou Lan this time, and when Immortal Crane Sect attacks Hu Immortal blessed land later, they would also have to help Fang Yuan according to the alliance agreement.

It involved reciprocity in mutual benefits for both sides.

"According to the previous agreement, here is small family qi Gu's recipe. Also, of the thirty immortal essence stones I lent, you only need to return half." Fairy Li Shan spoke.

She by now had a hint of Fang Yuan's nature, only tangible benefits matched his tastes.

Fang Yuan accepted the recipe for small family qi Gu, then sighed: "In this battle, I won and also lost, consuming over sixty green grape immortal essence. The fifteen immortal essence stones I owe you, I am afraid it might take some time for me to return them."

Fairy Li Shan was in a good mood because of Hei Lou Lan's success in advancing, she immediately stated: "No need to hurry, whenever your circumstances are better, you can return them to me and I also won't collect any interest on them. Also, didn't you ask us about wisdom path inheritances?"

"Could it be that you have some clues?" Fang Yuan was pleasantly surprised.

Fairy Li Shan slowly said: "There is a clue. You are also aware of northern plains' number one wisdom path Gu Immortal, Dong Fang Chang Fan's death some months ago. He left behind an intact wisdom path inheritance for his successor, Dong Fang Yu Liang, but Dong Fang Yu Liang is only a mortal and it will be hard for him to preserve a Gu Immortal inheritance, especially when this inheritance is a wisdom path inheritance."

"According to the tip-off, Dong Fang Chang Fan has placed this wisdom path inheritance in a hidden place and even Dong Fang tribe's other Gu Immortals don't know about its exact position. Only Dong Fang Yu Liang holds the key clue."

Even though just before his death, Dong Fang Chang Fan had formed a non-aggression pact with Huang Jin tribes and other super forces.

However, he had not formed an agreement with demonic path Gu Immortals. His capability had not reached the point where it could sweep through both righteous and demonic.

Dong Fang Chang Fan's wisdom path inheritance had already attracted the covetous gazes of many demonic path Gu Immortals. Even Dong Fang tribe's other Gu Immortals had some thoughts on it.

Thus, Dong Fang Chang Fan made these arrangements, completely hiding his wisdom path inheritance and leaving it to only his approved successor - Dong Fang Yu Liang.

Fang Yuan was forced to think: 'I have the wisdom path Immortal Gu Delight in Water and Mountain, but my use of it is crude at best and I am unable to display the essence of wisdom path. Treasure yellow heaven has wisdom path Gu worms on sale, but a complete wisdom path inheritance would never be on sale. Wisdom path Gu worms are easy to obtain while wisdom path inheritances are rather hard to get. If I can obtain this complete wisdom path inheritance, I believe I will be able to use fewer wills and thoughts to deduce more items.'

Dong Fang Chang Fan was the number one Gu Immortal of wisdom path in northern plains while he was alive. His inheritance would naturally arouse Fang Yuan's interest.

But lying in front of Fang Yuan was a super force, the colossus Dong Fang tribe.

Dong Fang tribe had lost Dong Fang Chang Fan, but it still had several Gu Immortals to maintain the situation. On the contrary, Fang Yuan had just been in an intense battle with Hei Cheng and spent most of his green grape immortal essence, it was not possible for him to display the same mighty presence of the myriad self army in a short while.

"Right now, many demonic path Gu Immortals have already allied in secret to conspire for Dong Fang Chang Fan's wisdom path inheritance. Back when Dong Fang Chang Fan was alive, both the righteous and demonic path of northern plains suffered losses from him, many were schemed against and suffered setbacks under his hands. Reportedly, his successor Dong Fang Yu Liang has talents and aptitude as strong as Dong Fang Chang Fan's. Most of northern plains' Gu Immortals are not willing to see a second Dong Fang Chang Fan." Fairy Li Shan continued.

"Several months ago, some demonic path Gu Immortals already sought me out to use my mountain pledge Gu to reach a temporary alliance in their scheme for the wisdom path inheritance. But I had already made an alliance agreement with Dong Fang Chang Fan by then and could not make any moves against Dong Fang tribe. Fang Yuan, if you want, I can act as go-between and let you join this alliance. They would have a lot more detailed information and will be of great help to you when you contend for the inheritance."

Fang Yuan did not refuse but also did not immediately agree: "I need some time to consider."

"There is no hurry." Hei Lou Lan said, "Right now, the biggest news in northern plains is the matter of Qin Bai Sheng capturing Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun, holding the essence of the luck path true inheritance. This matter has already caused a commotion among most of the Gu Immortals of northern plains, even those rank eight old monsters are said to have come out of their seclusions."

Hei Lou Lan revealed a ridiculing expression: "Hehe, Qin Bai Sheng is a rank seven Gu Immortal, an expert among lone cultivators, having overpowering metal path battle strength and even being somewhat stronger than that old scoundrel Hei Cheng, but this luck path true inheritance is a thorny matter, almost all of northern plains' Gu Immortals are looking to deal with him. Right now, Gu Immortals from all around are rushing over, while Qin Bai Sheng is a lone force and even though he occupies a blessed land, there will be countless difficulties for him in resisting these assaults, his life will certainly be quite hard."

A cold light vaguely flashed in Fang Yuan's eyes before he muttered: "We are the survivors of the wind veil of assimilation. Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun were also involved in the event! Although they escaped early, they know about us and are barriers for us to move freely in northern plains."

Since the destruction of Imperial Court blessed land and the collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, formless hands had carried many Immortal Gu to all parts of northern plains, causing chaos, commotion and frequent battles in the world of northern plains' Gu Immortals.

Afterwards, when most of the escaped wild Immortal Gu had been captured, the situation had calmed somewhat.

Now, however, the news of Qin Bai Sheng capturing Ma and Zhao caused undercurrents revolving around Qin Bai Sheng to surge in northern plains and the luck path true inheritance slowly formed tiny waves. As time passed, these tiny waves would definitely evolve into a huge storm that would engulf the whole of northern plains.

Fang Yuan, compared to other Gu Immortals, had much more reason to be involved in this.

However, his current strength appeared rather weak in front of such an enormous storm.

Without speaking any further, Fang Yuan took his leave and returned to Hu Immortal blessed land alone.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng remained here to heal Hei Lou Lan. Hei Lou Lan had passed the tribulation of her Immortal Gu, her immortal aperture was in ruins and required Tai Bai Yun Sheng's Landscape as Before.

Chapter 691: Quartet Sparrow Battle Tactic

Hei tribe, Iron Eagle blessed land.

This was Hei tribe's base camp, the blessed land was huge and extensive, it was small at the bottom and large at the top.

Because of Hei tribe's first generation ancestor's unique specialties, Iron Eagle blessed land had little land, but the higher up in the air one went, the larger the space.

A sky that greatly exceeded that of ordinary blessed lands had countless circular wooden eagle nests floating in it.

These eagle nests were like small hills, innumerable iron eagles rested in them. The cries of eagles resounded endlessly, when a group of eagles flew, vast numbers of them traveled in formation, it was a spectacular view.

At the highest part of this blessed land, there was a garden.

The garden's artificial mountain had a pavilion on it.

In the pavilion, four supreme elders of Hei tribe were sitting around a square stone table, they had differing expressions.

First supreme elder had a solemn expression, second supreme elder was shutting his eyes and resting, third supreme elder was thinking with a troubled expression, fourth supreme elder's face was full of sweat.

The atmosphere was heavy, it was like the calm before the storm.

"My dear lord third elder, how long are you going to continue thinking?" Fourth supreme elder urged with an impatient tone.

"Rush, rush, rush, you only know how to rush me, don't you know this is a crucial moment? At this point, if I make the wrong move, my dozens of years of hard work would go down the drain!" Third supreme elder yapped away, his emotions becoming even more agitated.

He looked at first supreme elder in front of him, before looking at second supreme elder to the left, both of them had unchanging expressions, third supreme elder could not discern anything from their faces and the pressure in his heart intensified.

Right at this time, a figure slowly rose from below, quickly approaching this pavilion.

Hei tribe's second supreme elder opened a slit in each of his eyes, saying slowly: "Oh, Hei Cheng is back."

Hei Cheng entered the pavilion and paid respects to the four supreme elders.

These four supreme elders had deeper foundations than him in both status and cultivation. But with regards to battle strength, it was unknown until they fought seriously.

But within the tribe, Gu Immortal would spar at most, how could they fight seriously?

Furthermore, in righteous path forces, other than central continent's sect system, the other four regions looked at bloodline and seniority within their clans and tribes, even if Hei Cheng had higher battle strength, he would still need to respect them as a junior when he sees these four supreme elders.

"First elder, this is Dark Prison, I am returning it now." Hei Cheng took out the rank six Immortal Gu House and returned it to first supreme elder after paying respects to them.

First supreme elder took the Immortal Gu House Dark Prison, exclaiming: "You did not use Dark Prison, it seems your operation was very successful?"

Saying this, first supreme elder's gaze was still fixed on the stone table, he was only asking Hei Cheng casually.

Hei Cheng laughed: "It was very fortunate, this time the trip was smooth sailing, we have successfully suppressed Qiao tribe."

Qiao tribe was a large sized tribe, because all of Hei tribe's members inside Imperial Court blessed land had perished, Qiao tribe which was under them had become tempted to try and leave their control.

"Hmph, Qiao tribe's Gu Immortal, Qiao Dong, became an immortal due to my guidance back then. It has only been a few decades, his loyalty has wavered?" Second supreme elder said plainly.

"Therefore, this time, I struck and taught that Qiao Dong a lesson. Within five years, there should be no issues." Hei Cheng laughed calmly.

The suppression of Qiao tribe was an excuse HeI Cheng had prepared long ago.

Hei Cheng wanted to deal with his own daughter, Hei Lou Lan, this was not a righteous thing to do, he could only do it secretly.

He had planned to use Dark Prison to suppress Hei Lou Lan, preventing her from self-detonating. But he could not directly say this to the first supreme elder. Thus, he used Qiao tribe as an excuse, saying: In order to prevent any accidents when suppressing Qiao tribe, he borrowed Dark Prison.

"Five years?" Second supreme elder chuckled, shaking his head: "Northern plains is in a complete mess now, True Yang Building collapsed, the culprit has not been found. Wild Immortal Gu have been appearing constantly, all the different forces are fighting intensely. Especially now, Qin Bai Sheng's incident is becoming more heated, this involves Giant Sun's inheritance, even those rank eight old fossils are getting ready to strike."

Fourth supreme elder sighed: "True Yang Building collapsed, Imperial Court blessed land was destroyed as well, the Imperial Court contest has lost its meaning. What do we do from now on? All of the Huang Jin tribes, what procedures will they follow, we have no idea!"

Hei Cheng understood their intentions after hearing this, he lowered his head: "Junior understands, I will be more strict in handling the tribes, especially Qiao tribe, Huo tribe, and Zhuo tribe, these three vassals."

"That's right, this time, the entirety of Hei tribe died inside Imperial Court blessed land. There cannot be no display of Hei tribe in northern plains, Hei Cheng, go out into the blessed land and pick carefully, bring a portion of the tribesmen out and rebuild Hei tribe in northern plains." Third supreme elder thought about his tough problem as he gave his view on this matter.

"Yes, don't worry third elder. I have already started preparing. In half a month, northern plains' Hei tribe will be rebuilt." Hei Cheng answered.

"Alright, alright, let Hei Cheng handle the matters of the mortal tribe affairs, we have no worries. Third supreme elder, if you have the time to care about this, why don't you decide on the problem ahead. What tile are you playing?" Fourth supreme elder urged.

Third supreme elder's gaze flickered, he was very hesitant, but he finally gritted his teeth and made up his mind, playing a tile.

At the same time, he called out: "Three tiao!"

Immediately, all the other elders had differing expressions.

First supreme elder could not stay serious anymore, he laughed loudly, flipping over his tiles: "Haha, I won!"

"Argh!" Third supreme elder patted his leg with much force, he grabbed his snow white beard as he sighed: "If I knew, I would not have played three tiao, but six wan instead!"

After hearing this, second supreme elder stared with his eyes wide open, he turned over his own tiles, saying to supreme third elder: "Then play six wan, my set could've won with either four wan or six wan."

"Alright, enough, stop arguing. Quickly make the deal, I'm waiting to recoup my losses!" Fourth supreme elder said impatiently.

"Here, this is the Gu recipe that I researched after spending thirty years." Third supreme elder admitted his loss, he slammed one east window Gu on the table in front of first supreme elder.

First supreme elder took the east window Gu: "Alright, let's go to the next round. Same rules, we are not to use any Gu worms to cheat. We will state the wager first, I have two immortal essence stones."

"Ancient Gu recipe of crescent moon Gu."

"Twenty pieces of grey heart rock."

"A group of dragon eye fish, there is a fish emperor included."

Swish swish swish...

Eight arms swept around the stone table, shuffling the tiles.

Hei Cheng was silently standing at the side, he was very used to these four Hei tribe supreme elders' gambling habits.

The game they were playing was called quartet sparrow battle tactic, it was invented by a mortal genius back in earlier years of Hei tribe, mainly to bootlick the first supreme elder.

After first supreme elder obtained it, he had been playing it daily with the other three supreme elders, competing and engaging in 'battle'. Hei tribe's external affairs were almost all handled by Hei Cheng.

"Then, elders, junior will take his leave." Hei Cheng said.

"Go, go." The supreme elders waved their hands, they had started assembling their hand tiles as they replied to him halfheartedly.

A group of iron eagles flew outside the pavilion, they were screeching as suddenly, the eagle group spread and three desolate eagles appeared, with battle strength equivalent to rank six. One was a dragon eagle with a powerful aura, while the other two were iron crown eagles, having great spirit.

"Shoo, shoo." Third supreme elder waved his sleeves unhappily: "So noisy."

"Hehehe." First supreme elder had a kind and merciful smile, he waved his sleeves and a lot of food was sprinkled in the air.

The eagle group made happy cries, fighting for the food in the air.

Hei Cheng left Iron Eagle blessed land, flying towards the southwest direction, after flying for several minutes, he met Xue Song Zi.

Xue Song Zi had rested sufficiently, he no longer looked as pathetic as before, but he sighed when he saw Hei Cheng: "The situation has become troublesome. I just obtained some information, do you know which force has control of fixed immortal travel Immortal Gu?"

Hei Cheng replied: "You want to say, Immortal Crane Sect of central continent's ten ancient sects?"

"You already knew? When?" Xue Song Zi was slightly unhappy.

Hei Lou Lan snorted coldly: "Not too long ago. Earlier, Dong Fang Chang Fan deduced that Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's matter was related to central continent. Now, Hei Lou Lan has a mysterious immortal zombie around her that controls Fixed Immortal Travel. They are likely the same batch of people!"

Xue Song Zi's eyes narrowed, he fell into silence.

Honestly speaking, this information caught him off guard. He originally thought that they were dealing with a small mortal woman, to think that such a huge force like Immortal Crane Sect was involved now.

Although he had joined Snowy Mountain, this was only a loose alliance, demonic path Gu Immortals were usually selfish and only cared about self interest, they were not as united as the righteous path.

Hei Cheng's predicament was very awkward as well.

Although he was a Hei tribe Gu Immortal, something as shameless as targeting his own daughter could not be known to everyone. Even though many righteous path Gu Immortals were two faced and usually acted differently in public, they at least appeared righteous to the world.

Hei Cheng's matter could not be exposed, thus he could only act alone, even Dark Prison had to be borrowed using an excuse.

"Hmph, I wanted to kill a cat, but to think I messed with a tiger. Hei Cheng, I don't care! Since your secret is in my hands, I want five hundred immortal essence stones. Give me a copy of the yin-yang life extension method as well." Xue Song Zi broke the silence, his expression was ruthless.

He was not sincerely working with Hei Cheng in the first place, after realizing that Fang Yuan and others had deep backgrounds, he wanted to retreat now.

A cold light flashed in Hei Cheng's eyes, he stared at Xue Song Zi as he said slowly: "You know my situation. If you force me, at most, both of us will go down, you will get nothing!"

"You! Aren't you afraid..."

"Hmph, if I cannot catch Hei Lou Lan, I cannot gain lifespan, I am about to die, why would I care about reputation?"

Xue Song Zi was shivering in fury after hearing Hei Cheng's unscrupulous words, his eyes were blood shot: "Who could have thought that the grand Lord Hei Cheng is actually like this."

Hei Cheng shrugged nonchalantly: "Hehe, think what you want. Xue Song Zi, you were too naive. At this point, do you think you can keep out of this matter? Hei Lou Lan takes revenge very seriously, she has Fairy Li Shan backing her, do you think Snowy Mountain would care about you, the seventh peak's branch head, as opposed to the third leader?"

"There is something else I want to tell you. Central continent's Gu Immortals are ready to strike, the ten great ancient sects have created an allied force to charge into northern plains. Right now, the entirety of northern plains is in chaos, I'm sure that with Fairy Li Shan's skills, it would not be hard for her to use the central continent Gu Immortals as an excuse to indirectly kill you, that does not violate the Snowy Mountain union pact, right?"

Xue Song Zi's expression paled.

Chapter 692: The hard to deal with Hei tribe father and daughter

"Hei Cheng, you, you are actually threatening me! Rub me the wrong way and I will make sure all your dirty deeds are known by the whole world!!" Xue Song Zi was furious.

Hei Cheng sneered: "Go ahead, do it quickly. Truthfully speaking, Su Xian Er was your Snowy Mountain's pawn, intentionally arranged to get close to me and infiltrate Hei tribe's higher level. The so-called Su Xian's Night Elopement is no more than a conspiracy. Not long later, Su tribe was annihilated, did you think it was my Hei tribe that had a hand in it? Hmph! You guys from Snowy Mountain did it to conclude matters for Su Xian Er, clearing away all the traces!"

"What? This, why haven't I heard of it?" Xue Song Zi showed an incredulous look upon hearing this astonishing piece of news.

"What would you know? You are only the owner of the seventh branch peak. The higher levels of Snowy Mountain always has only had three decision makers. I know you don't believe me, but I have conclusive proof." Hei Cheng took out an east window Gu and threw it to Xue Song Zi.

Xue Song Zi took the east window Gu and cast his consciousness into it, a while later, his forehead was filled with cold sweat.

Hei Cheng gazed at the sky and heaved a long sigh, revealing a bleak look: "Back then, I was publicly recognized as a Gu Immortal seed, but it was because I was ignorant at my young age that I fell into the conspiracy. Su Xian's Night Elopement, hehe, Su Xian's Night Elopement is nothing more than a meticulously planned conspiracy for the demonic and righteous paths to infiltrate each other."

"I married Su Xian Er, we had Lou Lan, I truly thought the days would keep on passing by blissfully. However, one day, a Gu Immortal suddenly appeared before me and threw the conclusive evidence to me. And what you are looking at is only a portion of this evidence."

"How can this be? How can this be?" Xue Song Zi mumbled.

This evidence turned everything upside-down.

Even if Hei Cheng used the yin-yang life extension method to scheme against his own wife, this was actually a matter of enmity between righteous and demonic. Hei Cheng's action of taking down his family when justice demanded it would not create reproach but instead be praised and admired.

"You set me up! You set me up!!" Xue Song Zi pointed at Hei Cheng in extreme fury.

He had thought he was the one holding the initiative by having a handle on Hei Cheng, but he had never expected to be instead entrapped by Hei Cheng.

Xue Song Zi naively followed Hei Cheng to hunt Hei Lou Lan and battle Fairy Li Shan, causing his current worrying plight. Hei Lou Lan, Fairy Li Shan as well as central continent's ancient sect force became a shadow that refused to leave Xue Song Zi's mind.

Hei Cheng restrained his feelings and looked at Xue Song Zi: "And now, I have a new piece of evidence. Do you remember when Hei Lou Lan was transcending the tribulation, how did she address Fairy Li Shan? Fairy Li Shan and Su Xian Er are likely to have a blood relation. I have Su Xian Er's blood with me and also Hei Lou Lan's blood, I will have additional conclusive proof when we confront Snowy Mountain in the future."

Xue Song Zi breathed roughly before he was able to forcibly calm down: "Good, Hei Cheng, you are truly outstanding. I had not even extorted you of a few dozens of immortal essence stones but was pulled into this messy business by you, being plunged into your trap. Right, I must acknowledge that even if you take actions against Hei Lou Lan, making every attempt to capture her, it could just be brushed off as a father educating his daughter who hopes she would be aware of her mistakes. As long as you don't use the yin-yang life extension method on Hei Lou Lan, I won't have any real handle on you! But, your scheme can only stop here, you are a lone force while the other has joined hands with a central continent influence. Hehe, Hei Lou Lan has already become a strength path extreme physique immortal, it is now even more difficult for you to capture her."

Hei Cheng sank into silence.

Xue Song Zi continued explaining, his thoughts becoming keener: "My situation is worrisome but your days also won't pass by well. You harmed Su Xian Er, Hei Lou Lan's hatred runs extremely deeply, and who is to say central continent's force also won't look to trouble you!"

"Thus, you two are tied together, and you only have a hope of victory if you cooperate with my side." A female voice suddenly interrupted Xue Song Zi and Hei Cheng's conversation.

"Who is this?!" Xue Song Zi was truly startled.

A graceful figure slowly appeared. This was a female Gu Immortal who was wearing purple garments; she was charming and lovely, and her beautiful face showed a light smile.

Xue Song Zi was not someone with poor knowledge and after being dazed for a moment, he reacted: "So it is Fairy Jiang Yu."

He then looked towards Hei Cheng.

All of northern plains' Gu Immortals knew that Fairy Jiang Yu was Hei Cheng's twenty seventh concubine who was similarly a dark path Gu Immortal, and possessed dark limit Immortal Gu, which could conceal inspirations and make it difficult for others to make deductions.

The reason why Hei Lou Lan was able to hold on for so long, and not explode because of the Great Strength True Martial Physique, was because Fairy Jiang Yu had used dark limit Immortal Gu to seal the aura of one of the ten extreme physiques on Hei Lou Lan, preventing its induction within heaven and earth.

However, who would have thought that upon seeing Fairy Jiang Yu, Hei Cheng's attitude would turn extremely cold, he snorted: "As expected, you came."

"Many years ago, when I first brought evidence regarding Su Xian's Night Elopement to you, I had said — I will appear when you need me." Fairy Jiang Yu revealed a mysterious smile, "So what do you think? Like I said before, you won't be able to capture Hei Lou Lan by just yourself, you will instead only create a bigger commotion. You can only cooperate with my side to have hope."

Xue Song Zi looked at Hei Cheng then at Jiang Yu, his gaze traveling back and forth between them.

He was shocked at how Hei Cheng and Jiang Yu were conversing. Fairy Jiang Yu's identity was not ordinary, and seemed to be a representative of a mysterious force. The reason Hei Cheng could know of the deceit that was Su Xian's Night Elopement was because of Fairy Jiang Yu's notice.

Hei Cheng lowered his eyes. Fairy Jiang Yu was able to appear so close to him without being discovered, this caused Hei Cheng's apprehension of Jiang Yu to deepen by a layer.

Fairy Jiang Yu was on the surface a lone cultivator of northern plains, and Hei Cheng's beloved concubine, but in truth was shrouded in a fog of mystery.

Hei Cheng fell into deep thought.

He was not at all afraid of Fang Yuan's myriad self army and actually had some disdain towards it inwardly. Despite not having methods to confront it head-on, Gu Immortal combat paid attention to contests in every aspect. Just based on how the myriad self army was not able to chase down Hei Cheng, its threat had heavily decreased to him.

In the previous battle, if not for Hei Lou Lan's side taking the initiative to retreat, Hei Cheng would have no doubt occupied the upper hand when the strength path phantoms dissipated and could even turn around the situation to a victorious one.

Even Xue Song Zi who had been fleeing in disarray from the myriad self was not worried about fighting Fang Yuan again.

The reason was that myriad self was an immortal killer move, Fang Yuan's immortal essence expenditure was too high, and in spite of this it did not have true killing power. Xue Song Zi could just activate mortal killer moves to resist it. After this was repeated a few times, how much more immortal essence could Fang Yuan, as an immortal zombie, still have? Once his immortal essence was expended, Xue Song Zi could display his might and settle affairs with Fang Yuan.

Hei Cheng's apprehension was towards Fang Yuan's background, to Immortal Crane Sect, and central continent's Gu Immortals.

He also had not expected that his investigation of Fixed Immortal Travel would involve such a colossus. Dong Fang Chang Fan had already deduced that the collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was due to the workings of central continent's Gu Immortals.

Central continent's Gu Immortals could destroy even Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's arrangements. Let alone with the insignificant Hei Cheng?

Like Hei Cheng, Xue Song Zi also had similar worries.

They were both scared by Fang Yuan's 'background', if they knew Immortal Crane Sect was thinking of every possible means to deal with Fang Yuan, they absolutely would not be this nervous.

"Looking at the present situation, it seems we can only have the chance of success by collaborating with your side. But before cooperating, as a fundamental part of good faith, shouldn't you tell me which force you are representing?" Hei Cheng asked Fairy Jiang Yu after pondering for a while.

Fairy Jiang Yu thought for a moment, she knew Hei Cheng was an uncompromising person; if she lied or refused, he would probably just turn around and abruptly leave.

She decided to tell the truth: "Well, there is no harm in telling you. The force I represent is spread throughout the five regions and its name is Shadow Sect."

Hei Cheng and Xue Song Zi glanced at each other.

Central continent, Hu Immortal blessed land.

"Twenty-eight green grape immortal essence and half an immortal essence stone." Fang Yuan calculated the wealth he had remaining.

After going through the battle during Hei Lou Lan's tribulation, Fang Yuan's hard earned and accumulated funds immediately returned to their original state.

Before the battle, Fang Yuan had ninety-one beads of green grape immortal essence, but he had activated the killer move myriad self close to fifty times, to form an army of nearly five hundred thousand strength path phantoms.

During the battle, Fang Yuan repeatedly used delight in water and mountain Immortal Gu, Worldly Wave Trace and other Immortal Gu, consuming over a dozen beads of green grape immortal essence.

Thus, the remaining green grape immortal essence did not even total thirty beads.

"I still owe Fairy Li Shan fifteen immortal essence stones and fifteen immortal essence stones to Lang Ya land spirit as well. I can delay the payment to Fairy Li Shan as long as necessary. But I need to return the immortal essence stones I owe to Lang Ya land spirit as soon as possible; if it is delayed, the interest will only get higher."

Fang Yuan's relationship with Lang Ya land spirit was still only ordinary.

When Lang Ya land spirit lent immortal essence stones to Fang Yuan, although he did not demand an exorbitant price, but he still, as per convention, took a ten percent interest.

That is to say, Fang Yuan would have to return at least sixteen and a half immortal essence stones to Lang Ya land spirit. If a month passed, another one and half immortal essence stone would have to be added.

Two months was three immortal essence stones and so on.

Even if a month did not pass, he would still have to pay one and half immortal essence stones, this was the minimum interest.

How could outsiders lend money for no reason and without any benefits?

The alliance between Fang Yuan, Fairy Li Shan and the others had an agreement. When one side helps other, the price they paid would be doubly compensated.

This agreement had been implemented in Fang Yuan's first battle with Hei Cheng.

However, this time, Fang Yuan did not just pay a price, he also obtained enormous benefits.

His strength path realm advanced to grandmaster level, he raised transformation path from practically nothing to master level, while his flying attainment advanced to quasi-grandmaster level.

Adding in small family qi Gu and the fifteen immortal essence stones exempted from the debt, these benefits had far surpassed the price Fang Yuan had paid, thus Fairy Li Shan did not compensate.

"Thinking back now, Hei Lou Lan might have intentionally set this situation up, attempting to use the Demon Venerable's realm's true meaning to make me work myself to the bone." Now that Fang Yuan recalled the situation, he felt he had fallen in Hei Lou Lan's scheme.

If not for the Demon Venerable's true meaning, Fang Yuan absolutely would not have spent so much green grape immortal essence and formed such a large strength path phantom army. If the situation was not good, Fang Yuan could have even retreated. After all, the alliance agreement had no clause that said one had to fight till death.

The Snowy Mountain Alliance was quite lenient.

Fang Yuan had vaguely felt this during the battle. But this was an upright plot, even if Fang Yuan discovered Hei Lou Lan's attempt, he would have still dived right in, because the benefits were just that great!

Chapter 693: Fighting is just a part of cultivating

In the underground cave, the air was filled with the rainbow colored light of wisdom.

A small mushroom forest was growing here. Wisdom Gu was sprawled atop the mushroom king at the center of the forest, not moving.

Fang Yuan sat close by, using the light of wisdom to make his deductions.

Afterwards, he let out a breath of foggy air: "The second Immortal Gu recipe has been completed."

He looked at his green grape immortal essence, he did not have much originally, only twenty or so of them. After deducing two eighty percent remnant recipes, he had eleven left.

"The third Immortal Gu remnant recipe is eighty-six percent complete, eleven green grape immortal essence beads should be enough."

Fang Yuan looked at the delight in water and mountain Immortal Gu, it was glistening brightly and had no issues.

Many days had passed since Hei Lou Lan's tribulation. Because it was used intensely in battle, cleanse soul Immortal Gu was hungry already, while delight in water and mountain Immortal Gu had been activated many times, but its condition was still good, it was not hungry.

Fang Yuan felt baffled at first, but after he asked Mo Yao's will, who was in his immortal aperture, he understood why.

It turned out Mo Yao's fake will needed to be replenished constantly.

Mo Yao did not have a Gu to produce fake will, she used many Gu worms to convert the joyful will into fake will.

Thus, when she fed Gu worms, the one she paid most attention to was the delight in water and mountain Immortal Gu. Delight in water and mountain Immortal Gu was fed till it was completely full by Mo Yao's will, she did not feed it only when it was hungry. Thus, even though Fang Yuan was using it extensively, there was still some time until he needed to feed the delight in water and mountain Immortal Gu.

This was evidently a good thing.

After all, activating a hungry Immortal Gu forcefully could cause it to die.

Cleanse soul Immortal Gu was already hungry, thus, it was much more risky for Fang Yuan to use the killer move myriad self. Perhaps the next time he used this immortal killer move, cleanse soul Immortal Gu would be destroyed in the process.

Deducing Immortal Gu recipes was Fang Yuan's most important source of income now. If delight in water and mountain Immortal Gu could not be used, Fang Yuan would fall into a difficult situation again.

Fang Yuan activated delight in water and mountain Immortal Gu again, he started deducing the third Immortal Gu remnant recipe.

This time, he had obtained the Demon Venerable true meaning infusion, it was quite a bit of help to deducing Immortal Gu remnant recipes.

That was because the true meaning infusion was the same as taking in Reckless Savage Demon Venerable's understanding towards cultivation, it directly increased Fang Yuan's foundation, it could raise his realm of cultivation.

As for the deduction of Gu recipes, it one's own foundation as the basis, the stronger their foundations, the higher the efficiency of the deduction.

Even though refinement path attainment level was the most important, because there were many elements to consider, strength path and transformation path would be involved as well in these thought processes.

Two days later, Fang Yuan completed his deduction, he obtained three complete Immortal Gu recipes.

He brought these Immortal Gu recipes over to Lang Ya blessed land and completed the transaction with Lang Ya land spirit.

Not only did he clear his debt and account for the expenditure of his green grape immortal essence, he still earned eleven immortal essence stones as profit.

Everything was back on track now.

Eight days later, Fang Yuan handed another three completed Immortal Gu recipes to Lang Ya land spirit and completed the fifth deal.

At this point, he had thirty-six immortal essence stones and twenty-seven green grape immortal essence beads.

Fang Yuan slightly relaxed after that.

Because of the battle with Hei Cheng, he almost went into the red and his finances threatened to collapse.

According to the economic term on Earth, he had almost caused the situation of a cash flow shortfall.

"Although the immortal killer move, myriad self, has great strength, I need to consume a bead of green grape immortal essence every time I use it. If I use it many times, the expenditure would be huge. I need to be careful when I use it in the future, otherwise, it will just drain my finances and cause me to lose out, even if I win the fight."

Fang Yuan inwardly alerted himself in his mind.

When Gu Immortals cultivate, they had to consider many aspects, not just victory in battle.

Like the example of Liu Bang and Xiang Yu on Earth. Liu Bang could not defeat Xiang Yu, he lost in battles while Xiang Yu won in battles. But Liu Bang was adept in managing the economy and had strong backing. Even though he lost each fight, he had the capital to rise up once again, thus he was able to fight even after losing.

Xiang Yu however, although he won his fights, he had no businesses, as time passed, and they fought even more, the difference between Liu Bang and him became smaller. Eventually, Liu Bang won one battle and that turned into complete victory.

As for the cultivation of Gu Immortals, it was the same logic.

Battles were just a part of cultivation.

The victory and loss of battles was not too important, the important thing was the benefits behind them.

One had to look forward for everything, they could not be shortsighted.

Even though Fang Yuan could cause Hei Cheng and Xue Song Zi to suffer greatly, he had invested too much green grape immortal essence, in contrast, Hei Cheng and Xue Song Zi spent much less immortal essence compared to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan also went bankrupt after this fight, but Hei Cheng and Xue Song Zi were in good condition. If Fang Yuan had to fight them again now, Fang Yuan's battle strength would definitely be lower compared to them. If they fought for several more times, the winner would be obvious.

Hei Cheng had the rank six Immortal Gu House Dark Prison, could he not go all out with it? Of course he could, but the situation did not call for it.

Those who could become Gu Immortals were not rash boors that were hot blooded, they would calculate their gains and losses after every battle.

Of course, if not for the Demon Venerable true meaning infusion, Fang Yuan would not have expended this much green grape immortal essence.

"If I use up my green grape immortal essence, I can still replace it with immortal essence stones. But the Demon Venerable true meaning is an extremely rare opportunity. If I cultivate slow and steadily, I would need at least decades to reach this stage." Fang Yuan was very aware in his heart.

After Fang Yuan completed another two Immortal Gu remnant recipes, Tai Bai Yun Sheng finally returned from Snowy Mountain.

"You did not see the environment of the super grade blessed land, sigh, I saw it with my own eyes. Having over 6700km2 of land, the blessed land's time flow is thirty-eight times that of the outside world! There is much vitality and great potential in it, I could not help but feel jealous towards it. In my opinion, the biggest winner after the battle of this tribulation is Hei Lou Lan!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng returned and started talking incessantly, while sighing endlessly.

After Hei Lou Lan's tribulation, she asked for Tai Bai Yun Sheng to repair the super grade blessed land. Thus, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was lucky enough to enter Lou Lan blessed land, it could be said to be a truly eye-opening experience.

"A super grade blessed land is precisely like that, after all one of the ten extreme physiques becoming an immortal is like skating on thin ice, it is a fight for survival in a deadly situation. Compared to this, I am more worried about how many Immortal Gu Hei Lou Lan managed to refine during the third step of this immortal ascension." Fang Yuan asked.

"Her immortal aperture was created using the flying bear strength Immortal Gu, this strength path Immortal Gu was given to her by Giant Sun's will. Flying bear strength Gu is now her vital Gu, but she also elevated her original core Gu, self strength Gu, to rank six. Other than these two, she also obtained a rank six strength qi Gu." Tai Bai Yun Sheng replied.

When Tai Bai Yun Sheng ascended to an immortal, the remaining heaven and earth qi created his two Immortal Gu, Man as Before and Landscape as Before.

Whether Hei Lou Lan's remaining heaven and earth qi had been more than Tai Bai Yun Sheng's, nobody knew. But what Fang Yuan did know was that she had quite a number of small family qi Gu, these Gu had stored up some amount of heaven and earth qi.

Fang Yuan analyzed what Hei Lou Lan had: "In this case, Hei Lou Lan is confirmed to have four Immortal Gu. They are flying bear strength Gu, self strength Gu, strength qi Gu, and slavery Immortal Gu. Divert disaster Gu had been destroyed during the tribulation. But don't forget, she had once destroyed the flying bear phantom and obtained flying bear phantom Gu after suppressing it. After that, I lost my connection with the flying bear phantom Immortal Gu. I am not sure if this Gu was taken away by the formless hands or if it is still with her now!"

Hei Lou Lan's strength grew extremely quickly, she had at least four Immortal Gu and was a Gu Immortal herself now, her future was immensely bright.

Furthermore, she had a close relationship with Fairy Li Shan, after getting her help, she skipped the initial stage of being a newly advanced Gu Immortal. Fairy Li Shan did not lack immortal essence stones, with a huge amount of investment, Lou Lan blessed land would develop quickly.

"Hei Lou Lan who has a super grade blessed land will undoubtedly greatly exceed me in cultivation speed. I have a high grade blessed land, compared to other Gu Immortals, it is also a great advantage, but Hei Lou Lan is like someone who has grown wings and is soaring. Even though we formed an alliance with her, the alliance will eventually end. After the time limit, we will need to be careful, Fairy Li Shan has a huge network while Hei Lou Lan is a formidable person." Tai Bai Yun Sheng's tone was worried.

The rapid growth of the genius, Hei Lou Lan, had brought great mental pressure to an elderly man like Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

But it was worse for Fang Yuan.

His cultivation was stagnant, as long as he was still an immortal zombie, his cultivation level would not progress.

"As long as Hei Cheng is not dead, and Ma Hong Yun's matter isn't resolved, we will have the basis to cooperate with Hei Lou Lan. You have to be very careful when you go to eastern sea this time. Shark Demon is not easy to deal with, if you need reinforcements, use the moving perspective cup Gu to contact me." Fang Yuan reminded Tai Bai Yun Sheng to be cautious.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng rested in Hu Immortal Blessed Land for two days before setting off to eastern sea.

He was afflicted by the death sentence awaits Immortal Gu, and had promised an immortal zombie of eastern sea, Shark Demon, to explore Yu Lu blessed land, he had no choice but to set off.

Fang Yuan stayed in Hu Immortal blessed land, he deduced Gu recipes to earn immortal essence stones, while also placing priority on settling the important matter of feeding Immortal Gu.

After he completed the sixth deal, he had more than sixty immortal essence stones.

His Woman's Heart and Connect Luck were showing signs of weakness, they were evidently famished. Together with cleanse soul Immortal Gu, he had a total of three Immortal Gu to feed.

Cleanse soul Immortal Gu needed ten thousand white lotus giant silkworm Gu as food. Connect luck Immortal Gu needed five thousand kilograms of sand from the ancient desolate beast, worldly sand gull's, resting area. Poison path Immortal Gu Woman's Heart needed the hearts of women as food.

He had no idea how to get the first two, Fang Yuan decided to settle the easiest one first.

Western Desert.

Sand dunes were continually connected together, forming a huge and wide area of land.

The sun was high in the sky, the air was dry and hot, it felt like a person could be cooked in this weather.

A large sized caravan was moving forward.

The camel bells ringed, and the sounds of the vehicles could be heard constantly.

The accompanying Gu Masters used all types of Gu worms, some to reduce the temperature, some to summon winds, some to create fresh water, and some to navigate.

"Who is this?" The caravan leader shouted. There was a gruesome monster in front of the caravan.

This monster was six meters tall, it had bulging muscles and a large body. It had eight arms, a green face and sharp fangs, with eyes red as blood. With one look, people felt their hearts tighten as they felt a formless pressure.

The caravan went into a commotion.

"Two rank five, seventeen rank four, forty over rank three... This is quite a number." A hoarse voice could be heard from the monster's mouth.

"Sir, who might you be? I am Mo clan's caravan leader, Mo Yan." One of the rank five Gu Masters in the caravan cupped his fists and asked nervously.

Fang Yuan laughed ruthlessly, his eight monstrous claws opened instantly, the name of the super influence, Mo clan, could not deter him.

He was like the incarnation of a demonic god, he rushed into the caravan and whipped up a storm of blood and flesh.

Howling, screaming, crying, begging, all these noises tangled together, after a while, they went silent.

Chapter 694: A gentle gaze

After around ten minutes, the slaughter finally ended.

One's nose would be assailed by the thick smell of blood, the yellow sand was filled with corpses.

Fang Yuan stood at the center of the corpses, he summoned woman's heart Immortal Gu.

The Immortal Gu slowly rose up, floating into the air and emitting a reddish purple light. The light filled the entire battlefield, in a few breaths of time, all the female corpses in the entire battlefield started to tremble.

The vibrations of the corpses became more intense, as finally, with a loud pop, hearts burst out of the bodies and rose up slightly, flying towards Woman's Heart which was in the air.

Before they even got close, these bloody hearts were swallowed by the reddish purple light in the air, turning into inky purple light lumps.

The light lumps were like young swallows returning to their nest, they entered Woman's Heart.

Poison path Immortal Gu Woman's Heart slightly trembled, it let out a sharp screech, as if it sounded overjoyed from being fed.

A moment later, all of the women's hearts in the battlefield had been fed to Woman's Heart as food.

Fang Yuan called back Woman's Heart.

This Immortal Gu's hunger had been alleviated by quite a bit, but it was not full yet.

Fang Yuan frowned slightly: "At this rate, to feed the woman's heart Immortal Gu until it is full, I will need four thousand more women's hearts. This caravan that I slaughtered already had significant strength, such a large sized caravan is uncommon in western desert."

Fang Yuan thought about it for a while before flying into the sky.

In the air, he stretched out his palm, pushing it towards the ground.

Immediately, thousands of fireballs appeared, slamming into the battlefield. Explosions occurred as rocks and sand were sent flying, corpses were burnt as the place turned into a sea of fire.

This was not a killer move, it was simply the power of quantity, he had used numerous similar fire path mortal Gu.

Fang Yuan threw several black oil dragons.

The oil dragons flew into the sea of fire, raising its intensity and razing the battlefield to the ground, all the traces left behind were gone.

After doing this, Fang Yuan flapped his light illusion bat wings and flew away at a rapid speed.

He traveled north-east, past several large sized oases, before finding his target — a small sized oasis.

Looking down from a high altitude, the oasis was like a jewel, encased in the golden desert.

There was a lake in the oasis, its water was clear and blue, with trees growing around it. There were many people living in this place, the marketplace were lively and it was a scene of prosperity and peace.

Fang Yuan did not conceal his movements, he appeared above the cloudless sky, it was very eye-catching.

A group of Gu Masters riding sand gulls flew up from the oasis.

"What monster is this?"

"It seems like a zombie!"

These Gu Masters were mostly young people, they looked at Fang Yuan's monstrous appearance and couldn't help but mutter apprehensively.

They were almost all rank two, only the leader was a rank three Gu Master.

This group of people flew towards Fang Yuan, they stopped about three hundred steps away from him.

The leader was very vigilant, he cupped his fists: "This is Zhou Xi oasis, controlled by us, Lan clan. The sky above the oasis is a no-fly zone, I hope sir can land on the ground! If you wish to enter the oasis, we have Gu Masters in charge of attending to visiting Gu Masters from outside. Sir just needs to follow the procedures, as long as you meet the requirements, you will be allowed to enter the oasis."

Fang Yuan continued to stare at the oasis, using his investigative Gu to check the area.

He was trying to find out if there were any Gu Immortals hiding in this oasis, because only Gu Immortals could pose a threat to him.

According to normal circumstances, such a small oasis would not be a strong force, there should not be Gu Immortals here. If there were, they would have expanded or modified this oasis already.

After the leader said that, he saw that Fang Yuan was unmoved, he frowned as he said coldly: "Did sir hear me? The sky above the oasis is a no-fly zone, this is general knowledge in western desert. Sir flying above Lan clan can be regarded as a provocation! I hope sir lands now, otherwise, don't blame us for..."

Bam.

Before the leader finished his words, Fang Yuan flicked a finger and sent a rank five level attack at him.

The rank three leader could not react, he was blown to bits, his corpse scattered everywhere.

"Huh?!"

"Lord elder!"

The other rank two Gu Masters screamed shrilly after a moment of shock.

At this moment, unparalleled fear filled their hearts. The high and mighty lord elder did not even have a chance to react before he was killed in one hit.

This attack was too sudden, the rank two Gu Masters could not even clearly see what actually killed their leader.

"Lord elder is dead, he was killed in an instant!"

"Quickly retreat, this person is not someone we can deal with!"

"Enemy attack! Enemy attack!"

The rank two Gu Masters screamed, they scattered in the air, flying towards the oasis.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, he waved his hands.

Bam bam bam...

With consecutive explosions, these rank two Gu Masters were turned into pieces of flesh without exception. Even the sand gulls that they were sitting on were not spared.

A loud siren rang in the oasis.

Everything that had happened in the air was seen by the patrolling Gu Masters.

Fang Yuan looked down from above imposingly, seeing the mortals panicking and running away, the flourishing market had gone into chaos. Large numbers of mortal Gu Masters came out from the buildings, they faced up towards the sky, looking at Fang Yuan with deep animosity.

"Mortals are truly like insects." Fang Yuan let out a deep breath, he then summoned the hair armor and flapped his light illusion bat wings, flying like a meteor towards the oasis.

"He's here! Attack him!"

"Be careful, the other party is very strong, he is at least a rank four Gu Master! He is very likely to be rank five!"

"So what if he is strong? He is just one person, attack him!"

The Lan clan Gu Masters in the oasis screamed furiously, they unleashed a flurry of colorful attacks.

But Fang Yuan's charge was not slowed, he easily broke through these obstructions and crashed into the clan head pavilion at the center of the oasis.

Bam!

The loud crash could deafen one's ears, the huge impact caused the ground to shake. The clan head pavilion had defensive Gu worms protecting it, but they were useless, the place collapsed in an instant. Rocks flew and tiles burst, air currents pushed out and carried the dust clouds with them.

As the dust and smoke settled, Fang Yuan's huge body and eight monstrous arms were displayed before the Lan clan Gu Masters.

"He, he did not die!"

"Damn it, the clan head pavilion was destroyed by him! The ancestors' tablets are all inside!"

"Kill, kill this demon!"

Everyone's emotions were stimulated, they surrounded Fang Yuan.

"All of you shut up!" Suddenly, an elderly man shouted, walking out from the crowd.

"Lord clan elder!" The surrounding people paid respects to this old man.

The old clan leader was very shocked, he deeply understood the defensive power of the clan head pavilion. It was the central and most important place in the clan, it had great defenses, even if ten people of the elderly clan leader's strength attacked it, they might not break through.

But simply one blow from Fang Yuan destroyed the entire clan head pavilion.

Just one hit!

What did this mean?!

The elderly clan leader controlled his fear, he bowed deeply towards Fang Yuan: "Our Lan clan has been neutral for many generations, we have not meddled with the outside world. I am not sure if we have offended sir, but we will definitely compensate you until you are satisfied."

The moment he said that, he immediately attracted the fierce rebuttal of the Gu Masters.

"Lord clan leader, what are you saying?"

"This monster who is neither a human nor a ghost destroyed our clan head pavilion, even elder Lan Duan died in his hands."

"Clan leader, our Lan clan has no cowards, the other party is already so overbearing, we have to slaughter him into pieces to quench the hatred in our hearts!"

"Hehehe..." Fang Yuan laughed coldly, his voice was hoarse, everyone frowned when they heard his voice: "There is actually someone who understands how to react to the situation here, hmm, that's right, this small oasis is squeezed between many large forces. If you did not know your place, you would not be able to stay as the clan leader. Then listen to me, I want you to collect six thousand hearts within the next ten minutes. Remember, these hearts have to be intact and they need to be women's hearts, the hearts of men and young girls have no use."

"What?!"

"He... he actually wants six thousand women's hearts?"

"This is a demon, he is a lawless demon! He actually wants our clan to be his lapdog, to collect hearts for him!"

The Gu Masters were in an uproar.

The elderly clan leader's expression was also uncertain. Six thousand women's hearts was a huge number, there were many mortal villages around this oasis, but the number of mortals was certainly not enough. That means, to reach six thousand, he would need to sacrifice the clansmen in Lan clan.

Thus, the old clan leader's position would certainly be taken away. Nobody would allow such a person to be their leader.

"Isn't sir's request too overbearing. Sigh, heaven cares for all living beings, in broad daylight, how can anyone commit such heinous acts? I'm afraid Lan clan cannot help you." The old clan leader sighed as he showed a merciful expression.

"Heh, then there's no other way. Even though this is more troublesome, it will do." Fang Yuan laughed ruthlessly, his killing intent surged.

Light illusion bat wings flickered on his back, and a moment later, he appeared in front of the old clan leader.

The zombie claws stretched out like lightning, grabbing the old clan leader's neck, lifting him up easily.

"So, so fast!" The old clan leader's expression was pale, there was no trace of blood on his face. He was completely shocked, how could he be captured by the other party in an instant?!

Could it be that, he is not a mortal, but a Gu Immortal?

A horrifying thought appeared in the old clan leader's heart, he shouted anxiously: "Ev... everything can be discussed... please have mercy... ple... argh."

Crack, the old clan leader's neck was smashed into powder by Fang Yuan.

The old clan leader's head hung to one side, he stared with his eyes wide opened, he died without solace.

It was not that he did not want to use his Gu worms to retaliate, but Fang Yuan had many mortal Gu in his immortal aperture that could seal and suppress Gu worms.

"He, he killed the clan leader!"

"No—! Lord clan leader! You cannot die!"

"Revenge for lord clan leader!"

The Gu Masters reacted and shouted angrily, like a rushing tide, they charged towards Fang Yuan, using all sorts of attacks, unleashing a beautiful display of fireworks.

Fang Yuan did not dodge, he stood on the spot, allowing the attacks to hit his body without moving at all.

Everyone's attacks lasted for a hundred breaths before stopping.

Gu Masters had limited primeval essence, with such an intense wave of attacks, they could not keep it up for very long.

"Is he dead?"

"He was definitely beaten to a pulp already."

"Sigh, our poor old clan leader, we did not even manage to retrieve his corpse..."

But when the smoke dispersed, the Gu Masters eyes were opened wide, they saw that Fang Yuan was still standing at the same spot arrogantly.

Even though the surroundings were a mess, his black armor was still extremely new looking, even the broken spikes were regenerating rapidly.

A few breaths of time later, Fang Yuan's hair armor regenerated completely, there were not even any marks on it.

Hair armor was a mortal killer move, it was made of several hundred Gu worms, and dozens of rank five Gu worms. It was also used on the foundation of the immortal zombie body, the defense was not something these Gu Masters could break.

Among the people attacking Fang Yuan, the one and only rank four Gu Master, the elderly clan leader, had died. There were less than ten rank three Gu Masters remaining, the rest were rank two and one.

Their attacks were very scattered, many of the attacks had canceled each other out, it simply could pose no threat to Fang Yuan.

"This is your attack? It can't even scratch me." Fang Yuan chuckled, his laughter was not loud, but it was very clear in everyone's ears.

An intense chill rose up in the hearts of the Gu Masters and spread rapidly.

Even though the weather was so hot, they felt like they were in an icy pit!

"You, what are you?" Everyone trembled, their hearts were filled with terror.

"Monster, this is a monster!" Someone screamed, he had lost his mind.

"Run, quickly run!!" Their morale had sank to rock bottom, one person running away initiated the collapse of the entire group.

Fang Yuan was not surprised, the clan leader was dead, they had nothing to rely on. At the same time, he purposely took the attacks head on, it was to destroy the morale of these mortals.

Swoosh.

Fang Yuan smiled sinisterly, he chased up to a female Gu Master.

The female Gu Master's body froze, she stared at the monstrous claw piercing through her back and out of her chest, as the monstrous claw pulled out, her heart was taken away.

"Elder Lan Xin is dead too, run!" The surrounding Gu Masters saw this and were shocked out of their minds, they ran away even more quickly.

Fang Yuan waved a hand and large numbers of fireballs spewed out, buildings collapsed and fires were blazing. With another wave of a hand, wind blades were dancing in the air, slaughtering everything in their path, leaving behind large numbers of minced corpses.

"No, please, I'm begging you, don't kill me." This was an ordinary mortal woman with a delicate face and a beautiful figure, she had preserved her own body well, she should be a wife or concubine of a Gu Master.

Bam.

Fang Yuan flicked his finger, and the mortal woman's head exploded like a watermelon, her headless corpse collapsed on the ground.

Fang Yuan walked past this corpse, as the palm of his downwards hanging hand opened, the woman's heart burst out of the body and flew out, grabbed by Fang Yuan.

Woman's Heart let out a joyful scream, it stopped on Fang Yuan's shoulder, glowing in a reddish purple light.

Be it the heart in Fang Yuan's hand or the surrounding corpses, as long as they met the conditions, the purple light would swallow them and they would be absorbed by Woman's Heart.

Fang Yuan walked briskly, wherever he went, a slaughter occurred. It was a path filled with anguished wails, rivers of blood flowed.

Cleanse soul Immortal Gu was famished, it was too risky to use myriad self, and too much of a waste of immortal essence.

Icy drill stardust could not be used, because the starlight lump exploded continuously, it would mince the mortal corpses completely, even the hearts would not be spared.

Fang Yuan was only using mortal Gu, he did not use any killer moves, it was simply a huge quantity of Gu worms.

But even so, the efficiency of killing was not low.

Western desert was different from the other four regions, Fang Yuan chose this place purposefully. This was a huge desert, and the oases were like islands, even if a mortal escapes out of the oasis, they would not get far. Western desert was a place with unhindered vision, the desert stretched to the horizon, it was easy for Fang Yuan to chase them down.

"This time, I will let you eat till you are full, little one." Fang Yuan walked in the pool of blood, looking at the woman's heart Immortal Gu on his shoulder, his gaze was extremely gentle.

Chapter 695: Dead Sand Gull Egg

The light of the setting sun shone on Zhou Xi oasis.

The lively atmosphere in normal times was replaced by thick smoke and fire today.

There was nothing left of the former serenity, buildings had collapsed, turning into piles of ruins. In these ruins, on the streets, at the side of the lake, under the trees, pools of blood were connected and corpses lined the ground.

Fang Yuan went back to the clan head pavilion, standing on a pile of broken concrete, he placed the poison path Immortal Gu Woman's Heart back into his immortal aperture.

After killing for a long time, he had finally fed Woman's Heart until it was full.

Woman's Heart combined refinement and nurturing, if he fed it any further, Woman's Heart would enter the refinement stage, the more women's hearts it ate, the stronger the poison.

But Fang Yuan had no intentions of refining the Gu at this point.

With his strength, slaying mortals was like slaughtering animals, but with so many mortals, he still spent half the day on this.

Furthermore, Woman's Heart was a consumable Immortal Gu. No matter how strong it was, it would be gone after one use. The prospects of investing in it were not great, unless Fang Yuan had the Immortal Gu recipe of Woman's Heart.

Standing on the rubble of the clan head pavilion, Fang Yuan activated several hundred Gu worms in his immortal aperture, undergoing a thorough search of the area.

After two breaths of time, Fang Yuan finally found an underground entrance.

He walked towards the entrance, his huge feet treaded and destroyed the ground under him, exposing the entrance.

This entrance could allow a normal person to enter, but it was too small for Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan used force to take apart this entrance, after several hundred steps, the space finally widened enough for Fang Yuan to walk while bending his waist.

A large stone door appeared in front of Fang Yuan.

On top of the door, there were words carved: "Important area of the clan treasury, people not specifically assigned are forbidden from entering."

Fang Yuan snorted, he destroyed the stone door and hundreds of golden light blades attacked Fang Yuan. A loud alarm rang, this was evidently the method of Lan clan in defending against thieves. But it was a pity that not even a single spike on Fang Yuan's hair armor was destroyed.

Fang Yuan entered the stone door, seeing a pile of primeval stones. Fang Yuan roughly estimated that there were at least a hundred thousand in total.

If Fang Yuan was still a mortal, these primeval stones would be a huge fortune. But now that he was an immortal with unlimited primeval essence, he had almost no need for primeval stones.

But he still kept these primeval stones in his immortal aperture, it was simply a move done in passing.

Soon, he broke through a second stone door, and entered.

He saw a huge amount of Gu refinement materials, they were classified and placed here, these were all ordinary materials. Although Fang Yuan also needed them, these materials were not in high quantity, when Fang Yuan truly wanted to refine something, he would need a vast amount of materials, he would still need to purchase in bulk from Gu Immortals.

But this was better than nothing, Fang Yuan would not leave empty handed, he sent it all into his immortal aperture.

Next, beyond the third, fourth, and fifth stone door, they all had Gu refinement materials, except that they were of different varieties and had different storage conditions. Fang Yuan took all of these as well.

At the sixth stone door, he found Gu worms.

Large numbers of mortal Gu were stored here. This was Lan clan's Gu worm treasury, the foundation of their entire clan.

Fang Yuan took them all away, with his abundant memories and great experience, he knew all of these Gu worms, they were not necessary for him.

But to mortal Gu Masters, these were all precious Gu worms, including rank four and five Gu worms among them. Getting one could change a person's life, their entire future might turn around.

Like the liquor worm that Fang Yuan obtained on Qing Mao mountain, the bone flesh unity Gu on Bai Gu mountain, and the all-out effort Gu in Shang clan city.

There were three Gu worm treasuries, and five primeval stone treasuries.

Other than that, there were treasuries hidden within treasuries, secret troves that did not escape Fang Yuan's detection.

Some troves were ravaged, there were Gu Master corpses here and traces of fighting. Evidently, when Fang Yuan was slaughtering the mortals, some greedy Gu Masters knew that the clan was finished and barged in here, trying to take whatever resources they could.

They fought here and took the treasures they could find, while a portion of people died from the Gu worms defending the troves.

Fang Yuan walked past these troves, along the main path deep underground.

Along the way, he saw more and more corpses of Gu Master, and there were also sand gull corpses.

These sand gulls were like a combination of seagulls and ostriches, they had large legs with huge muscles, but they also had huge wings and could fly in the sky.

Sand gulls could run rapidly in the desert, while also flying in the sky and carrying people, they only ate grass and drank clean water, they were easy to feed. With a mild temperament, they were the most common steed among western desert Gu Masters.

The only problem was, sand gulls had very low fertility. Three to four out of ten sand gull eggs would usually hatch and grow into healthy sand gulls.

However, this Lan clan raised many sand gulls, much more than other forces of the same level. When Fang Yuan slaughtered the clan, he killed many sand gulls. He estimated that Lan clan might have some secret technique to raise the fertility of the sand gulls.

If so, that would be the only thing in this entire Lan clan that could somewhat interest Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan walked for another few thousand steps, he saw more Gu Master corpses. Finally, at one point, he saw a large number of Gu Master corpses and sand gull corpses.

"It seems that the people who came in here met with the sand gulls' obstruction, they all perished here. They took a risk to enter here, quite evidently, there is a huge benefit attracting them." Fang Yuan analyzed.

Squawk squawk squawk...

After another few hundred steps, Fang Yuan was attacked by a wave of sand gulls.

There were a hundred sand gulls, among them, the sand gull hundred beast king was injured, likely due to the fight with Gu Masters earlier.

But how could this trifling beast group be Fang Yuan's match? In just a few breaths of time, Fang Yuan killed these sand gulls and continued moving forward.

The path was moving downwards, the depth was rather surprising to Fang Yuan.

After getting rid of ten waves of attacks from sand gulls, Fang Yuan walked out of the tunnel, his field of vision widened as he entered a huge underground cave.

This cave was quite big, it was like a square.

There was a huge stone table at the center of the cave. There was a huge egg on the table, it was the size of a house, it had a yellow luster but it was already quite dim.

There was a thick layer of yellow sand around the table.

The sand was extremely soft and slightly warm, it felt like cotton when one stepped on it.

Many eggs were placed on this sand, slightly buried into them. These eggs were of varying sizes, there were even some broken egg shells there.

"These eggs are all sand gull eggs. This is the breeding ground for Lan clan's sand gulls." Fang Yuan walked into the cave.

To protect their home and eggs, a large number of sand gulls rose up and charged towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was unmoved, he waved a hand and a large number of wind blades cut these sand gulls like harvesting crops, with another burst of frost, half of these sand gull were frozen.

There were very few sand gulls that survived, they no longer had their previous numbers, so their aura diminished and they started escaping in fear.

Fang Yuan had no interest in killing them all, the closer he got to the table, the more his gaze was attracted to the huge egg on the table, he showed some joy on his face.

"This egg, is it the egg of a worldly sand gull?"

Fang Yuan stopped atop the stone table and came in front of the huge egg. He touched the shell filled with cracks, there were several small holes on it, as transparent egg white flowed out of the cracks slowly.

The egg white fell onto the stone table, following the crevices on the table as it flowed down onto the yellow sand.

This was an egg of the ancient desolate beast worldly sand gull.

The life inside had perished in the egg. Even the egg white was leaking, this was obviously a dead egg.

Sand gulls had low fertility, worldly sand gulls which were of the same breed had even lower rates. But it was the life essence of an ancient desolate beast after all, even using the egg white so superficially could greatly raise the fertility of these sand gulls.

Fang Yuan did not obtain the fertility method he had been guessing, he actually obtained a dead egg of an ancient desolate bird instead.

This was an pleasant surprise.

"As expected, after using Connect Luck, I encountered something good? After slaughtering a small to mid sized clan, I actually obtained something useful to me." Fang Yuan sighed in his heart.

His connect luck Immortal Gu needed the sand of the resting area of the ancient desolate beast, worldly sand gull, as food.

This sand was known as sand gull soil, it was a special resource formed from ordinary soil due to the worldly sand gull's influence.

Originally, if Fang Yuan wanted to obtain the sand, he would need to buy it from others, or find a worldly sand gull nest and take a huge risk to sneak in and steal the sand gull soil.

But now that he had a dead egg of the worldly sand gull, he could use the life essence in this egg to turn ordinary sand into sand gull soil.

"I need five thousand kilograms of sand gull soil to feed the connect luck Immortal Gu. There is ample life essence in this egg, it should be enough. Even if it is not enough, it will tide me through this tough time. I do not need to feed the connect luck Immortal Gu until it is full, as long as it is not starving, that will do. After all, for the foreseeable future, there are no suitable targets, connect luck Immortal Gu is unusable anyway."

Feeling joyous, Fang Yuan took this dead egg.

After returning to Hu Immortal blessed land, he started his preparations. He was a blood path grandmaster in his previous life, now he had also become a strength path grandmaster, these two paths both involved life and vitality.

He quickly had an idea, using six hundred mortal Gu to create a Gu formation, extracting the life essence of this dead egg, forming a lot of vital energy.

Fang Yuan modified this method with the help of wisdom Gu, condensing the vital energy into a light yellow juice.

Ordinary sand had turned into sand gull soil after a day and a night in this juice.

Three days later, Fang Yuan obtained enough sand gull soil to feed connect luck Immortal Gu till it was full.

Therefore, the cleanse soul Immortal Gu in his hands was the only one he had an issue in feeding.

To feed cleanse soul Immortal Gu, he needed the flesh of ten thousand white lotus giant silkworm Gu, but the white lotus giant silkworm Gu was very rare. A hundred thousand years ago, during the Late Antiquity Era, soul path flourished, and this Gu worm had once been very popular.

Unfortunately, at this point, there were already very few white lotus giant silkworm Gu in treasure yellow heaven.

Fang Yuan used the name of the Eight Arm Immortal to request for this Gu worm and its recipe, but no one had answered him.

Chapter 696: Announcement of Betrayal

"Husband, Huang Er has been like this for three months. What should we do? I don't know how to live if anything happens to her." Fairy Bai Qing looked at Feng Jin Huang who was on the cushion, sobbing in a low voice.

She was a grand Gu Immortal of Spirit Affinity House, she had always been elegant and noble to the outside world. But now that this concerned her beloved daughter, she lost her bearings, she was no longer as calm as usual.

But in front of her, Feng Jin Huang sat on the cushion, in the posture of polishing her aperture.

She wore a phoenix coronet, she had slanted eyes and there was a small red birthmark between her eyebrows. Her appearance combined the gentle beauty of her mother, Fairy Bai Qing, with the valiance of her father, Feng Jiu Ge, she had a dignified disposition, yet also a matchless, fearless beauty.

She had incredible aptitude, her talent was overwhelming, she suppressed everyone of the same age in the ten great ancient sects. If not for Fang Yuan ruining her opportunity, Feng Jin Huang would have become the owner of Hu Immortal blessed land already.

Her skin was fair like snow, her eyes were shut, she breathed slowly like she was asleep.

About three months ago, Feng Jin Huang was meditating as usual, nurturing her aperture. But an accident occurred during this ordinary cultivation session, she fell unconscious ever since and nobody could awaken her using any method.

Ever since they found out about Feng Jin Huang's strange state, Feng Jiu Ge and Bai Qing had been thinking of ways to save their daughter, but there had been no progress.

They asked the supreme elders of Spirit Affinity House, they had tried all sorts of methods, but all of it was useless.

"Husband, do you think our Huang Er will stay asleep forever? Will she ever wake up and see us again?" Fairy Bai Qing thought about this terrible fate and couldn't refrain from welling up with sorrow.

Feng Jiu Ge sighed, he stretched out his arms to hug his beloved wife, consoling her: "Qing Er, don't worry. Didn't first supreme elder say it? Our daughter had discovered the true way to use dream wings Immortal Gu, thus she had reached a hidden region, her entire soul had entered a mystical realm unknown to us. She did not lose her life and is still alive and well. We should believe her, maybe this is a fortuitous encounter for her."

Although Feng Jiu Ge and Bai Qing did not awaken Feng Jin Huang, their attempts were not in vain, they had already found out the reason for Feng Jin Huang's coma was the dream wings Immortal Gu!

Fairy Bai Qing leaned on her husband as she relaxed on his broad and powerful chest, she felt slightly eased as she said: "When Huang Er was three years old, dream wings Immortal Gu came to her on its own, I had been feeling uneasy since then. We have never seen this Immortal Gu before, even after searching through all of Spirit Affinity House's records, there was no information about it. In our tests, the effect of this Gu expended the soul to create beautiful wings. But now it seems, dream wings Immortal Gu's true effect is not this."

Feng Jiu Ge nodded, agreeing: "Your analysis is very reasonable. When Gu Masters nurture, use, and refine Gu, if they are facing an unknown Gu worm, they would make new discoveries when using the Gu, eventually understanding everything about the Gu worm. Even for famous Gu worms, there are always new secrets hidden within them. When Gu Immortals and Gu Masters obtain valuable experience, they would treat it as an important secret to prevent others from learning about their information. When Huang Er awakens, I am sure she will have huge gains, she will learn the true way to use dream wings Immortal Gu. When I go to northern plains this time, our family will have to depend on you. Inform me immediately when Huang Er awakens."

The ten great ancient sects of central continent had plotted for countless years, they put in a lot of time and effort, expending manpower and resources, meticulously planning and making arrangements, before finally having some progress in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

But in the end, Fang Yuan used his previous life's memories and plucked the fruits of their labor, using these arrangements for himself.

In the end, Imperial Court blessed land was destroyed, and Eighty-Eight True Yang Building collapsed. This piece of information was a huge nightmare to the ten great ancient sects of central continent, who had planned this for a long time.

The leader of this plan — Spirit Affinity House, was pressured by all the different forces, not only from the other nine sects, but also internally within Spirit Affinity House.

"The plot against Eighty-Eight True Yang Building started from the information left behind by Fairy Mo Yao. All these years, our sect has been leading the way and holding the most crucial methods. Now that such a huge change has occurred, not only must we clear the suspicions, we also have to investigate the truth! As the person with the strongest battle strength in our sect, even though I want to stay by my daughter, all of the other elders have agreed that I will go to investigate this." Feng Jiu Ge sighed.

"Husband, you have to be careful during this northern plains journey. If anything goes wrong, make escaping your priority. After all, over there would not be like in central continent, there is no backup to assist you. Don't trust the people from the other nine sects, back then when you challenged the ten great sects in successive battles, you won many and faced zero losses, many people's reputations took a huge hit. All these years, you have been the publicly recognized strongest person in the ten sects, suppressing all of them. If Spirit Affinity House loses you, they might all sigh in relief instead."

"Don't worry, for you and our daughter, I will be careful." Feng Jiu Ge touched Fairy Bai Qing's cheeks as he kissed her lips gently.

When their lips separated, he took out a rank five letter sending green bird Gu.

"This is a letter from Hu Immortal blessed land, that rascal Fang Yuan accepted Huang Er's challenge." Feng Jiu Ge said.

"Him? Ever since Huang Er was born, she had only suffered a loss in this Fang Yuan's hands. After Huang Er returned, she was so indignant and wanted to take revenge, I got you to send him a challenge letter earlier, but he did not reply. To think that he has replied now, what is his motive?" Fairy Bai Qing had a deep impression of Fang Yuan.

Feng Jiu Ge's gaze concentrated: "Ever since Huang Er lost, we had investigated this lad thoroughly. He has quite the backing, there is a mysterious force behind him, he actually dared to snatch Hu Immortal blessed land under the eyes of all ten great ancient sects. But these smart alecks in Immortal Crane Sect acknowledged him as one of their own, leaving us no way to make a move."

"This way, Immortal Crane Sect can exclude the rest of us nine sects and claim Hu Immortal blessed land for themselves. If it had been me, I would have done the same." Fairy Bai Qing said.

"Over a year has passed according to central continent time, even northern plains' True Yang Building has collapsed in this period, the laughable thing is that Immortal Crane Sect has not even succeeded yet, Hu Immortal blessed land is still in that rascal's hands. What a joke." Feng Jiu Ge laughed in disdain.

"We can't say that. During this year, Immortal Crane Sect had first spent a lot of effort to capture the ancient desolate beast, spirit rhino, then many of the Gu Immortals in their sect were involved in the reincarnation battlefield, and now even Great Heavenly Sword Sect which is under their control is trying to gain independence, Immortal Crane Sect has too many things to deal with. Together with our nine sects exerting pressure on them covertly after we learned the truth, obstructing them from attacking Hu Immortal blessed land by force, all of these reasons resulted in Hu Immortal blessed land being yet to fall at this point." Fairy Bai Qing said.

Feng Jiu Ge shook his head: "The force behind Fang Yuan is shrouded in mystery, we do not know much about them yet. Yesterday, Immortal Crane Sect publicly declared that Fang Yuan had turned on them after obtaining Hu Immortal blessed land, he is now a traitor of the sect. It is evident that their soft tactics had no effect. Now it seems like Immortal Crane Sect is going to deal with Hu Immortal blessed land forcefully during this period of time. Hmph, I want to see what force it is, to be able to contest with our ten great sects."

Fairy Bai Qing's gaze flickered, she seemed to have comprehended something: "I understand this Fang Yuan's intention. He is not a member of Immortal Crane Sect, it seems he knew that Immortal Crane Sect was going to deal with him. Thus, he sent this letter, to interact with the outside world, so that he can resist Immortal Crane Sect using Spirit Affinity House."

"But now, Immortal Crane Sect has an upright reason to strike, because Fang Yuan is a traitor of Immortal Crane Sect. Immortal Crane Sect can attack Hu Immortal blessed land righteously, while we cannot interfere."

Fairy Bai Qing was unresigned: "Is there no way for us to interfere? If Immortal Crane Sect gets Dang Hun mountain, I'm afraid their sect's foundation will get much stronger."

"As righteous sects, we have rules to follow. After all, there are so many other sects in central continent observing us, if the ten great sects break established practices, will we still be able to command those on our sides? Even though Immortal Crane Sect initially deceived the other nine sects, they were indeed led into believing them for some time, because Immortal Crane Sect had Fang Zheng who could be used as a perfect excuse."

"Since Immortal Crane Sect's plan worked out, we had to acknowledge them. At least, we cannot interfere this time. But if Immortal Crane Sect fails in taking down Hu Immortal blessed land, our nine sects will have reason to strike. After all, everyone knows about this situation right now, but because of rules and reputation, we are all pretending to be ignorant. If Immortal Crane Sect fails, no one will allow them to take Hu Immortal blessed land for themselves anymore." Feng Jiu Ge continued.

He paused before continuing: "Before going to northern plains, I plan to give my one's own way Gu to Immortal Crane Sect for their use."

"Ah? What is your intention?" Fairy Bai Qing was slightly taken aback.

Feng Jiu Ge was very confident: "We do not know about the strength of Fang Yuan's force, whether he can protect Hu Immortal blessed land is an unknown factor. If he defeats Immortal Crane Sect, then the ten great sects will strike together to split up this blessed land. But if Immortal Crane Sect wins, we can use my one's own way Gu as a reason to gain some advantage from Dang Hun mountain as well."

Hu Immortal blessed land, Dang Hun palace.

"Declaring me as the sect's traitor, this means Immortal Crane Sect will attack Hu Immortal blessed land very soon." Fang Yuan looked at the report in his hands with a heavy feeling.

Cleanse soul Immortal Gu was not fed yet, under such circumstances, using the immortal killer move myriad self was extremely risky.

If he was unlucky, he might lose the cleanse soul Immortal Gu for good.

This way, without myriad self, Fang Yuan would lose his greatest trump card.

"Immortal Crane Sect announced that I was a traitor in advance, but they did not attack. They are evidently waiting now, trying to lure the force behind me to make a move, so that they can fight it out. This is truly the demeanor and confidence of one of the ten great sects."

Fang Yuan thought a little about it and knew that Immortal Crane Sect's attack would be very powerful this time!

To him, the most important thing now was to find the white lotus giant silkworm Gu, to feed cleanse soul Immortal Gu until it was full.

At the same time, he needed to accumulate funds, and prepare enough green grape immortal essence.

Most Immortal Gu required immortal essence to activate.

Without immortal essence, no matter how many Immortal Gu he had, he could not use their abilities.

What is the point of war? Money!

In this world, why do Gu Immortals fight? For immortal essence stones! It was about immortal essence stones!

"Sigh, this is quite the problem. My funds that have just recovered are going to take a huge hit again. Two consecutive battles would completely devastate my already weak finances."

Chapter 697: Immortal Crane Sect, Gu Immortal Meeting

Central Continent, Fei He mountain.

At the highest point of the mountain, in the hall of affairs.

Gu Immortals were seated in a circle, their immortal auras radiated as they discussed the important matters within Immortal Crane Sect.

"The spirit rhino's illness is getting worse, I need to purchase large amounts of materials, to refine the healing Gu that can treat it. But to completely heal the spirit rhino, I need a lot of healing Gu recipes and to carry out research on them. I estimate that I will need three hundred and sixty immortal essence stones." Gu Immortal Shu Zhi Ge spoke loudly.

Immediately afterwards, a Gu Immortal rebuked him: "The spirit rhino is an ancient desolate beast, it has a very strong body. But now, it has already been sick for half a year, why has it not recovered yet?"

"Shu Zhi Ge, are you trying to delay the treatment of the spirit rhino so that you can reap some gains from the process?" A Gu Immortal questioned.

Shu Zhi Ge heard this and his eyebrows rose up, he screamed: "Fan Xi Liu, don't bullshit me! Wasn't this all because you guys used a poison path Immortal Gu when you captured it? Back then, I urged you, don't use it, don't use it, but in the end, to save your efforts, you poisoned the spirit rhino. Now that there is trouble, you need me to clean up after you!"

"You are the one bullshitting! Do you know how hard it was to capture that spirit rhino alive? It is easy for you to speak like this!" Fan Xi Liu was just as fierce, shouting loudly.

Ding.

At this time, a bell rang, it was a crisp and clear sound.

The Gu Immortals' words were all swallowed by the sound of the bell, as this sound continued echoing, it became louder.

Shu Zhi Ge and Fan Xi Liu, no matter how much they spoke, their voices would only turn into bell sounds. They decided to keep quiet as everyone's gazes turned to the origin of the sound.

At the centermost seat, there was an old man, it was the person with the highest authority in Immortal Crane Sect, the rank eight first supreme elder that controlled the entire situation.

Immortal Crane Sect's first supreme elder's voice was low and slow: "Now, Shu Zhi Ge's suggestion requires three hundred and sixty immortal essence stones, to purchase Gu recipes and Gu worms to heal the spirit rhino, we will vote now."

"I object. Three hundred and sixty immortal essence stones is too many. My budget last time was merely two hundred immortal essence stones. Is healing a spirit rhino more important than healing Gu Immortals?" Fan Xi Liu was the first to object.

A Gu Immortal beside him said: "The spirit rhino is important, but it is not crucial. The most crucial matter now is the situation in the northwest, I object to this suggestion as well."

"We will talk about Great Heavenly Sword Sect in detail later, now we are only discussing the matter of healing the spirit rhino." First supreme elder interjected.

"I object." The third Gu Immortal said.

"Before expressing my decision, I would like to hear Lady Sang Xin's input. Our sect had expended much effort to capture the ancient desolate beast spirit rhino, it was to use the spirit rhino's blood to create an even more secretive information path Gu worm. I wonder what Lady Sang Xin's progress is?" The fourth Gu Immortal looked at Lady Sang Xin.

Lady Sang Xin was a rank six Gu Immortal, she smiled upon hearing this: "I am ashamed! Right now, we are making little progress, the spirit rhino's body is full of poisonous blood, the research of the information path Gu worm thus is progressing slowly."

The fourth Gu Immortal nodded: "That means this matter has few prospects. Then, I object."

Out of the eight Gu Immortals present, five objected. In the end, Shu Zhi Ge only got two hundred immortal essence stones.

This was evidently much less than the three hundred and sixty he requested for. Shu Zhi Ge snorted as he muttered something under his breath, expressing his unhappiness.

Ding.

With another sound of a bell, regardless of whether Shu Zhi Ge was satisfied, first supreme elder continued: "Then next, we will discuss the matter of the reincarnation battlefield."

Lei Tan stood up from his seat, he had a muscular body, his blue hair pointed towards the sky: "I have been in charge of the reincarnation battlefield's matters for over thirty years. I am sure everyone knows how important the reincarnation battlefield is. During the middle of this year, our sect had suffered a huge loss in the reincarnation battlefield. Even though reinforcements were swiftly provided and we regained our footing, the situation is still terrible. I need a rank six Gu Immortal's battle strength or three desolate beasts to reinforce us, and one of the desolate beast has to be a nine palace crane."

He Feng Yang immediately retorted: "A Gu Immortal's battle strength? Do you know Immortal Crane Sect's current situation? Mu Xiao Xiao is recuperating from a serious injury, Lin San Mei is in closed cultivation, we have a lack of manpower in terms of battle strength. You are making such a request at this time?"

Lei Tan snorted: "If Immortal Crane Sect is chased out of the reincarnation battlefield, can you, He Feng Yang, take responsibility?"

He Feng Yang snickered: "We have already invested a huge amount of resources into the Reincarnation Battlefield, two Gu Immortals were already involved in it, we can totally defend our side and maintain stability. Adding in forces will not solve anything, because our competitors in the reincarnation battlefield are the other nine sects. The more reinforcements we send in, the more reinforcements other sects would send, they might even send more than us!"

Shu Zhi Ge nodded: "Agreed, reincarnation battlefield's situation is stable now, the current objective should be to defend our territory."

Everyone looked around and started to vote.

Eventually, Lei Tan obtained the help of two desolate beasts, he looked at He Feng Yang in hatred, gritting his teeth.

Ding.

"Next, we will discuss the matter of Great Heavenly Sword Sect." First supreme elder said.

Gui Li heard this and firmed his gaze, sitting up straight.

Facing everyone's gazes, he spoke: "Great Heavenly Sword Sect has been under our Immortal Crane Sect for nearly a thousand years. Protected by us, after such a long time, they now have a third Gu Immortal. They want to get rid of this attachment and separate from our sect. If they succeed, our sect's control over the northwest would decrease significantly. Immortal Crane Sect's reputation will also take a huge hit. Even though there is not much evidence, I have gone through extensive calculations, I suspect that Myriad Dragon Dock is involved in this matter. If Great Heavenly Sword Sect detaches from us and joins Myriad Dragon Dock, the situation would be even worse. Our territory is connected to Myriad Dragon Dock's territory, the areas surrounding Great Heavenly Sword Sect would combine into Myriad Dragon Dock's sphere of influence if that happens."

"We all know how severe the matter is, you do not need to explain it. I'll ask you directly, who is the Gu Immortal that you want to recruit from Great Heavenly Sword Sect? How confident are you, is it the other party's scheme? And most importantly, how much of a price do we need to pay to recruit that Gu Immortal?" Second supreme elder asked.

Great Heavenly Sword Sect was a large sized force, it was unable to sustain the cultivation needs of three Gu Immortals.

Central continent's current situation was that the ten great ancient sects had control over the entirety of central continent, and eighty percent of its resources were split by the ten sects. Only the ten great ancient sects could sustain a large number of Gu Immortals.

For example, Great Heavenly Sword Sect, which was a subsidiary of Immortal Crane Sect, had to hand over a huge amount of resources every month. The Gu Immortals in Great Heavenly Sword Sect thus lack the resources they need. In this aspect, if there were enough benefits, it was possible to make a Gu Immortal betray them.

If Great Heavenly Sword Sect loses one of its three immortals, it will only have two left and its strength would fall, they could no longer stir up trouble.

Gui Li thought about his words as he said: "As the saying goes, nothing good is cheap, the one we are trying to recruit is not a mortal but a Gu Immortal. I promised them that they would be treated the same as us, after all, this is the standard for joining Immortal Crane Sect. Other than that, there are some resources as well, about seventy five immortal essence stones worth."

Pausing for a while, Gui Li continued: "In my humble opinion, we should not resort to force for Great Heavenly Sword Sect's matter, if we can. After all, the deadline of Great Heavenly Sword Sect's agreement to be our subsidiary sect is coming to an end. It is perfectly fair for them to want to end this relationship and detach from us. If we interfere forcefully, we would have no proper reason. Great Heavenly Sword Sect is also near a territorial border, Myriad Dragon Dock may find an excuse to intervene."

From start to finish, Gui Li did not mention which Gu Immortal he was thinking of recruiting.

Second supreme elder also did not pursue the matter.

All of the Gu Immortals present were supreme elders of Immortal Crane Sect, but they had internal factions and conflicts as well.

A place with people will have conflicts over benefits, and when there is conflict of interest, there are allegiances.

If Gui Li said it now, it might give rise to unnecessary conflict.

Great Heavenly Sword Sect's matter was extremely important to Immortal Crane Sect. After voting, Gui Li's suggestion was approved.

Ding.

With a loud sound from the bell, first supreme elder said: "Next, we will discuss the matter of taking back Hu Immortal blessed land. He Feng Yang, tell us about it."

Lei Tan snorted coldly, throwing a glance at He Feng Yang filled with ill intentions.

He Feng Yang stood up from his seat, showing a serious attitude: "Everyone, Hu Immortal blessed land is a rank six blessed land, even though Hu Immortal did not manage it well, Dang Hun mountain is in there. As we all know, Dang Hun mountain's guts Gu can greatly raise a sect's foundation, it is useful even to us Gu Immortals."

Before he finished speaking, Gu Immortal Lei Tan questioned: "He Feng Yang! It has already been more than a year, why is Hu Immortal blessed land not taken down yet? In fact, there is not even any progress. Do you know the other nine sects are looking at us like a joke now."

He Feng Yang was prepared for this, he spoke calmly: "Any person prepared to accomplish grand feats would face much mockery from the people around him, if we cannot endure this, how can we have any achievements?"

"I came here for a meeting, not to listen to your teachings. No matter what, it is undeniable that you have not retrieved Hu Immortal blessed land yet." Lei Tan said.

"During this last year, I have been extremely busy over this matter, I had not relaxed even a bit. A few days ago, I have already declared publicly that Fang Yuan is a traitor of the sect, and that we will take him down soon. During these recent days, I have sent informants to monitor the other nine great sects, we have not found any special reactions from any sect. The crucial person of this operation has been appropriately prepared, we just need Old Lord Can Yang and Fairy Cang Yu to assist in our move, and we will be able to take back Hu Immortal blessed land." He Feng Yang said.

"Old Lord Can Yang is rank seven, while Fairy Cang Yu has decent strength among rank six Gu Immortals, you have the nerve to request this? You are a grand Gu Immortal yourself, but you need three Gu Immortals to deal with a mortal? You are killing a chicken with an ox cleaver, this is what you have prepared after over a year?" Lei Tan mocked and laughed loudly.

He Feng Yang's eyes were twitching, he controlled the anger inside him as he looked around, calmly saying: "To ensure that nothing goes wrong, I have to make such a request. I'm sure everyone here knows the situation. I used Fang Zheng to lie to the nine sects, snatching Hu Immortal blessed land for ourselves in name. But ever since the nine sects found out the truth, they have been targeting Dang Hun mountain, obstructing us many times in secret. This time, we need to succeed, we cannot fail, otherwise they will intervene. By then, the situation is not something our sect can control anymore."

Hearing this, first supreme elder sighed lightly: "They have already obstructed us. He Feng Yang, I have bad news for you, as well as good news."

He Feng Yang's heart shuddered: "First elder, please tell me."

"Never mind, look at it yourself." First elder flicked his finger, as a rank five letter sending green bird Gu flew out.

He Feng Yang received it and his consciousness entered it, seeing the start, his expression turned ashen: "What? They are requesting Old Lord Can Yang to go to northern plains?"

In He Feng Yang's plan, Old Lord Can Yang was the greatest battle strength, he had an attacking type Immortal Gu, he was the powerhouse that could hold the fort.

But before He Feng Yang had even acted, he lost his strongest general!

Second supreme elder said: "We can't reject them. True Yang Building collapsed for no apparent reason, the cooperation of our ten sects to take down True Yang Building has failed. All the years of hard work have gone down the drain, all of our investments were wasted. This matter is too important, we have to organize a group to go investigate the truth in northern plains. At the same time, in northern plains, all sorts of Immortal Gu have appeared all over the place, thus this northern plains journey has another major objective, that is to capture some Immortal Gu. If the Gu Immortal we send has low battle strength, not only would we fail to gain anything, we might even be sidelined and reduced into being a shield, losing out in all aspects."

Chapter 698: Attacking Hu Immortal blessed land (1/3)

"But the decision of staying or going for Lord Can Yang would affect the ownership of Dang Hun mountain and guts Gu." He Feng Yang still wanted to fight for it.

"Feng Jiu Ge is the publicly recognized number one battle strength of the ten sects, he is also the leader of this northern plains expedition. We have no justifiable reason to reject his request. You know clearly that the sect's manpower in terms of battle strength is very tight recently. Even if we refuse him forcefully, the other nine sects will use excuses like not needing a burden to go with them, jointly pressuring us."

Hearing the first supreme elder say that, He Feng Yang's expression became utterly dark.

Lei Tan smiled silently, he did not conceal his schadenfreude at all.

He Feng Yang felt he was so angry that he was going to blow up, he continued reading the letter, but his expression suddenly froze, he said with mixed emotions: "This... Feng Jiu Ge is actually lending one's own way Immortal Gu to me? He has also raised one's own way Immortal Gu to rank seven! Rank six one's own way Immortal Gu is a consumable Gu that can only be used thrice. But the rank seven one's own way Gu has no such limits, it can be used as many times as possible, but the expended immortal essence is much higher."

"What? I remember that He Feng Yang's one's own way Gu only had one use left. To think that Feng Jiu Ge raised one's own way Gu to rank seven! No wonder he requested for one's own way Immortal Gu, he had an agenda all along."

"But his luck is really good, Immortal Gu are hard to refine, there is a very low chance of success, one's own way Gu was not his vital Gu, but he actually succeeded." Gui Li said.

Shu Zhi Ge said: "Spirit Affinity House has a lot of assets, and has close relations with Heavenly Court, their foundation is even deeper than Immortal Crane Sect. It is not a strange thing that they could refine a rank seven Immortal Gu."

"With one's own way Gu, we will not be suppressed by the blessed land, we can use mortal Gu freely." Lady Sang Xin looked at He Feng Yang.

"Feng Jiu Ge's scheme is great, on one hand he lent us one's own way Gu, if we succeed in obtaining Hu Immortal blessed land, he would be able to get a share. On the other hand, he took Old Lord Can Yang away, that was to lower our capability in the fight for Hu Immortal blessed land." Second supreme elder analyzed.

Third supreme elder Lord Tiger Demon drank the wine in his bowl before smashing it: "Damn! This is not the first time that the other nine great ancient sects have secretly obstructed our sect in dealing with Hu Immortal blessed land! He Feng Yang! Hu Immortal blessed land has been handled by you alone all along, I hope you can succeed this time, do not leave any opportunities for the other sects. Slap their faces hard. I want them to beg us to cooperate on selling the guts Gu!"

"I understand, third elder." He Feng Yang bowed.

The Gu Immortals discussed for a day and a night, they finally decided on what Immortal Crane Sect would do for the next few months.

Two days later, Fang Zheng opened the stone door, entering the blood pool.

"Fang Zheng, after so many hardships in training, we have finally reached this stage. Today, you will take revenge for your clansmen, you will make contributions to the sect, you will do a favor to all the people in this world. We must succeed!" In his aperture, the spirit incubating flea was vibrating, emitting Lord Sky Crane's voice.

"Yes, master! I will succeed!!" Fang Zheng clenched his fists, his expression was extremely firm.

He walked to the center of the blood pool, letting the boiling blood submerge half of his body.

Next, he breathed in deeply, using iron blood Gu. His blood became blacker and thicker, his skin turned darker.

Immediately afterwards, Fang Zheng activated blood blade Gu while maintaining iron blood Gu.

Sizzle...

From his body, hundreds of iron-blood blades flew out, shooting everywhere.

Hundreds of cuts appeared on his body, as blood like molten iron flowed out.

An intense pleasure hit him, Fang Zheng gritted his teeth as he entered the crucial step, using blood merge Gu...

At the same time, on Tian Ti mountain, two Gu Immortals arrived.

One of them looked young and mild like jade. He wore a green robe and had a jade pendant on his waist. What was most eye-catching were his dark green eyebrows, they were sharp and long, reaching down to his waist. It was the rank six Gu Immortal of Immortal Crane Sect, the one known as Winged Crane Flying Immortal, He Feng Yang.

The other was a young and beautiful looking woman, she had a good figure and her face was like a peach, her eyes were thin and delicate, she wore a pink-blue flowery dress, as it fluttered in the wind. She was another Gu Immortal of Immortal Crane Sect — Fairy Cang Yu.

The two stepped onto Tian Ti mountain, towards the location of Hu Immortal blessed land.

What they saw before them was a large green forest, it was plain and ordinary.

Hu Immortal blessed land was a separate small world, it was distinct from the world of central continent. As long as there were no loopholes in the blessed land, or the entrance of the blessed land was not opened, from outside, one could not see any signs of its existence. If one did not know of its existence, even if Gu Immortals passed by, they would not realize that there was a blessed land here.

Fairy Cang Yu looked around, the scenery was that of a jade green mountain with chirping birds, not one person was in sight.

But she smiled to He Feng Yang: "It seems that there are indeed many people today, and quite a few familiar faces too."

She and He Feng Yang did not conceal their traces, because their actions later would cause a commotion that could not be hidden. Thus, when He Feng Yang started to move, the other nine sects already knew about it.

Right now, Gu Immortals from the other nine ancient sects were already lurking close by, observing He Feng Yang and Cang Yu's actions, obtaining first hand information.

He Feng Yang scattered his Gu worms as he praised: "I've heard that fairy has an investigative killer move, known as micro sense, it can be sold for five immortal essence stones in treasure yellow heaven, it has great effect."

"Lord Flying Immortal is too kind, I merely obtained it from a fortuitous encounter in the reincarnation battlefield." Fairy Cang Yu delicately laughed.

"I will need fairy's help in this battle today." He Feng Yang's attitude was very gentle and kind.

"Lord Flying Immortal is too polite, my weak methods cannot compare to the grand Winged Crane Flying Immortal's myriad crane soaring flight. It would be a great honor if I can witness it today." Fairy Cang Yu sighed.

He Feng Yang laughed.

As he said this, he had already scattered about ten thousand mortal Gu, after five minutes, his preparations were complete.

"Next, we wait for the right time. Fairy, please." He Feng Yang waved his sleeves, as a lump of white cloud flew out.

The cloud was only three meters from the ground, turning into the shape of a cushion.

He Feng Yang leapt onto it and sat down cross-legged.

This was a white cloud cushion Gu, it was rank five and could assist a Gu Master in cultivating, increasing the effect of nurturing their aperture. Although the effect was not great, years of accumulation would still be a significant amount.

After He Feng Yang ascended to an immortal, white cloud cushion Gu lost its primary use, and could only be used as his seat.

The white cloud cushion was huge, He Feng Yang purposely left enough space for Fairy Cang Yu.

But Fairy Cang Yu took a look and did not step onto the white cloud cushion, she flicked her finger as a wood path Gu flew out.

The Gu worm drilled into the ground, several breaths later, peach trees started growing, the branches intertwined together, forming a comfortable bed made of peach blossoms.

Fairy Cang Yu lightly chuckled as she stepped onto the bed, half lying down and relaxing herself.

At the same time, in Fu Hu blessed land, Fang Zheng was at the last step.

He activated failed blood demon flower Gu, as all of the flesh and blood in his body became the soil and nutrients for the demon flower to grow. Countless vines grew out of his skin, coiling around his body.

The beautiful and demonic blue chrysanthemums blossomed and opened brightly.

An intense pain assaulted his entire body, even iron blood Gu was having no effect, Fang Zheng gritted his teeth as his expression contorted, he forced himself to endure it.

"Quickly use cold blood Gu!" Lord Sky Crane's soul was observing Fang Zheng's condition, at this moment, he reminded him.

Fang Zheng endured the inhuman pain as he mobilized his primeval essence, activating cold blood Gu.

His body shuddered for a few moments, as the temperature of his boiling blood fell, preventing him from suffering the terrible fate of being cooked alive.

"Use blood sense Gu." Lord Sky Crane gave instructions.

Fang Zheng gritted his teeth till blood was dripping out, he activated this rank five blood path investigative Gu forcefully.

This Gu could allow him to sense others with the same bloodline as him. The closer they were and the thicker their bloodline, the clearer the connection between them.

But this time, no matter how Fang Zheng tried to sense him, he could not see any images.

"How can this be? You and Fang Yuan are brothers by blood, your bloodlines are of the most close relations, meanwhile failed blood demon flower Gu can enhance the effect of blood path Gu worms, how could you not sense anything after such a long time?" Fang Zheng was in so much pain he could not talk, but Lord Sky Crane was monitoring him closely, seeing that there was no effect, he became nervous, shouting in panic.

"Fang Zheng, hang in there! You have trained for so long, enduring so much inhuman hardship, it was all for this. Our sect's two Gu Immortals have already set off, we are waiting for you to lead the way! Do not give up, do not relax your concentration for even a minute." Lord Sky Crane urged worriedly.

Fang Zheng's body was shivering intensely, he could not answer his master, he could only use actions to express his obedience.

"You still can't sense him? Strange! Too strange! Fang Zheng, you have to extend your sense towards the hole earth Gu in the blood pool. If Hu Immortal blessed land's hole earth Gu has not been destroyed yet, then this hole earth Gu would connect to Hu Immortal blessed land. It can help you greatly in sensing Fang Yuan!" Lord Sky Crane reminded.

But Fang Zheng had already sent his sense over to the hole earth Gu, there was little effect.

To him, he felt like he was in complete darkness, searching for his target was like looking for a speck of light in complete darkness.

Be it Fang Zheng or Lord Sky Crane, they did not know about the changes in Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had become an immortal zombie!

His body's blood had turned into a cold jade green zombie blood, from the original healthy red blood.

This, no doubt, raised the difficulty for Fang Zheng immensely.

No matter how hard Fang Zheng tried, he could not sense Fang Yuan's existence!

"Damn it! Damn it!" Lord Sky Crane was extremely anxious, according to the experience of their previous training, Fang Zheng's endurance had a time limit. Ninety percent of the time had passed already, he was near his limit.

"Don't tell me, we have to use that trump card?" Lord Sky Crane was having an internal struggle.

To ensure that this succeeded, He Feng Yang had secretly placed some blood path Gu worms in Fang Zheng's body. Together with the Gu worms in the blood pool, it formed a trump card that could prevent any accidents from happening.

But if they used this trump card, Fang Zheng would completely lose his mind, he would activate blood sense Gu without caring about his life. Fang Zheng's soul would be consumed intensely, and his blood and flesh would shrivel quickly, there was an extremely high chance of dying!

Chapter 699: Attacking Hu Immortal blessed land (2/3)

Lord Sky Crane hesitated.

On one hand, he had instructions from He Feng Yang and was responsible for the heavy task. Reason told him he needed to sacrifice Fang Zheng, this mortal child, for the benefits of Immortal Crane Sect, and it was also the most appropriate choice.

But on the other hand, his sentiments were obstructing him.

Humans were not made of stone, how could they be devoid of emotions?

'Being with Fang Zheng day and night, watching him grow step by step, looking at him unable to think properly sometimes, looking at him cultivate bitterly with all his effort for vengeance, he really resembles me back then...'

Lord Sky Crane could not bear to sacrifice!

"Fang Zheng, you brat, I taught you so many times, this is the most basic refinement method!"

"Sorry, master." Fang Zheng's hand was emitting smoke, the Gu worm in the palm of his hand had already turned into a pile of ash.

...

"Fang Zheng, practice, practice, and practice more. A disciple of mine, the grand Lord Sky Crane, can't even arrange the cranes in an arrow formation? Where would my face go if this was spread?!" Lord Sky Crane shouted in fury.

"Sorry, master, I will definitely try harder... ugh!" Fang Zheng made more mistakes the more nervous he became.

Two groups of cranes collided against each other in the air because of his last mistake.

The miserable cries of the cranes and the sounds of bone fractures resounded like dumplings dropped into a pot, as they fell down to the ground.

The spirit incubating flea was dazed for a moment at beholding this scene before erupting like thunder, "You fool!"

...

"Master, I was wrong, sorry." Fang Zheng faced the wall inside a room for confinement, as he apologized to Lord Sky Crane.

"Stupid kid, what are you saying sorry for? You fought well!"

"Ah? Master, doesn't the sect prohibit internal fights?"

"Hmph, Zhang Nan's master is Xuan Ji Zi, back then I didn't find him pleasing to my eyes and beat him till his head was swollen. I was also confined longer than you. I might have died already, but as my disciple, how could you be bullied by others!" Lord Sky Crane snickered.

"Master...." Fang Zheng choked with sobs, his eyes reddened and tears started forming in his eyes.

"Idiot, what are you crying for. A man does not easily shed tears!" Lord Sky Crane berated.

"Yes, master. Sorry, master!"

...

This crucial moment seemed to span endlessly.

The past scenes floated by one by one in Lord Sky Crane's mind. He seemed to hear being called master again and again.

Lord Sky Crane roared in a voice so loud that it could awaken the dead: "Fang Zheng, persevere! Have you forgotten the pain Fang Yuan inflicted upon you? Forgotten how your fellow disciples beat you black and blue when you first arrived at Immortal Crane Sect? Forgotten the grieving ghosts of your clan, forgotten how miserably your uncle and aunt had died at Fang Yuan's hands? Your hatred, your effort, all of it need to be shown at this moment! You can't fail, you can't give up!"

"I will definitely sense him, definitely!" Fang Zheng's spirit was stirred up when he heard Lord Sky Crane's roar.

However, he still only sensed endless darkness.

No matter how much effort he exerted, no matter how he used his energy, he still could not sense any indication.

"Why?! Why!" Fang Zheng's mind was shaken and was starting to turn chaotic when the memories of that unbearable past hidden deep within him started surfacing one after another.

The shadow which Fang Yuan had cast upon Fang Zheng since youth seemed to be the same as this darkness he was sensing, causing Fang Zheng to feel boundless pressure and not a trace of light.

Fang Zheng felt he was an extremely tiny speck in this vast darkness.

Hesitation, bewilderment, loneliness, helplessness, all sorts of feelings gushed in his heart.

"Sorry, master, I... failed." Tears fell down Fang Zheng's eyes as his body reached the limit and his mind was close to collapsing.

"No! You can't fail, I don't allow it!" Lord Sky Crane was also anxious, shouting repeatedly.

However, Fang Zheng was slowly unable to hear him, he was about to fall unconscious like in the previous drills.

"Damn it, damn it!" Lord Sky Crane shouted in his heart, he thought of his possession plan, and thought of the punishment He Feng Yang would give if he failed this task.

"Fang Zheng, you brat, all my efforts to cultivate you are in vain. In the end, you are still unable to get rid of that man's shadow! Since that is the case, then let me give you a hand!!"

Lord Sky Crane's thoughts flashed before he finally convinced himself. The situation also forced him into making this choice.

He used that trump card.

Instantly, the whole blood pool let out bright lights, sweeping away the previous darkness.

Gu worms concealed around the blood pool activated one after another on Fang Zheng's body.

"Ahhh——!" Fang Zheng's body spasmed intensely like he was electrocuted. He fiercely raised his head and spread his arms, clenching his fists so tightly that the nails pierced into the flesh.

An incomparable pain attacked his mind, causing his eyes to roll backwards and show the whites.

Almost in the next breath of time, Fang Zheng's roar stopped abruptly; he lost his consciousness, but under the effects of Gu worms, he still continued to activate failed blood demon flower Gu, and was still using blood sense Gu to sense Fang Yuan's existence.

The blood pool seethed and gurgled.

Squeak squeak... the failed blood demon flowers started growing rapidly, emitting bone-chilling sounds.

Fang Zheng maintained his position, with his head raised and arms spread, without budging in the slightest, like a statue.

The demonic vines had been small and thin like needles, but now these vines grew thicker, at least as thick as fingers. The largest vine grew from the depths of Fang Zheng's throat and extended out from his mouth like a python.

Besides this, there were vines growing out from his ears and nostrils.

Soon, vines grew out from every pore on his skin; Fang Zheng had thoroughly turned into nourishment for the demon flowers, his body was cut open everywhere, there was nothing remaining of his original appearance, just like a flower statue that had been tastefully trimmed.

"Brat...." Looking at Fang Zheng transforming into this miserable appearance, Lord Sky Crane's original anxiety and nervousness disappeared. He felt a bleak emptiness that spread to the depths of his heart, it was extremely unbearable.

This unbearable feeling soon turned into a heavy guilt that filled Lord Sky Crane's mind.

"Brat, master... has done you an injustice!" Lord Sky Crane's soul, which was stored in the spirit incubating flea, was unexpectedly letting out drops of soul tears!

"Hmm? He Feng Yang's arrangements have been activated." In the depths of Fu Hu blessed land, Immortal Crane Sect's third supreme elder slowly opened his eyes and mumbled.

He thought of the matter that He Feng Yang had specially requested of him before he left.

The third elder, Lord Tiger Demon, used his immortal essence to activate an Immortal Gu that gracefully flew out of the hall.

This Immortal Gu was not Lord Tiger Demon's, but had been borrowed by He Feng Yang from Lady Sang Xin. It was a rank six information path Immortal Gu - Mutual Sense.

In ten or so breaths of time, the Immortal Gu descended down to over the blood pool, above Fang Zheng.

"This is — Immortal Gu?!" Lord Sky Crane's eyes opened wide in shock.

Mutual sense Immortal Gu let out a grey light pillar, the smoke-like light pillar covered Fang Zheng. Several breaths later, the grey light pillar was dyed red with Fang Zheng's blood.

"Where... is this?" Fang Zheng's remaining consciousness surveyed his surroundings.

It was darkness around him, no matter where he walked and no matter how far, the surroundings were still covered in deep and boundless darkness.

However, right at this time, a blood-red light speck appeared ahead of Fang Zheng.

"Ah? That is...." Fang Zheng tried walking towards the light; when he reached closer, he sensed a familiar aura from the blood-red light speck, "This is older brother's, no, Fang Yuan's aura! Master, master, do you hear me, I have succeeded! I finally sensed him!"

Fang Zheng was extremely excited and tried to speak, but no words came out.

His mouth was opened so wide that it had almost deformed, it was being held in place by the thick demon flower vines. But a joyful teardrop fell down from the corner of his eye.

This tear fiercely shook Lord Sky Crane's soul, he sank down into deathly silence.

Fang Zheng approached the blood-red light speck, suddenly the light speck let out an extremely powerful suction force that completely caught Fang Zheng off-guard, absorbing his remaining consciousness.

At this moment, in Hu Immortal blessed land, Fang Yuan gave a sound of surprise and slowly opened his eyes.

He sensed a blood pool, sensed Fang Zheng's body, sensed the lush, enchanting failed blood demon flowers, sensed the spirit incubating flea, sensed the information path mutual sense Immortal Gu above....

"So it is like this." Fang Yuan sneered, "My cute little brother, you are finally going to die? No, in the words of the righteous path, you are sacrificing yourself for the group? Hahaha."

"What happened?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng, who was sitting to the side, saw Fang Yuan suddenly speaking and immediately questioned.

At the other side from him were Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan, who similarly casted inquiring gazes at Fang Yuan.

"Such a coincidence, I had invited you guys to talk about guts Gu business, but it seems Immortal Crane Sect is making an attack." Fang Yuan smiled. He then intentionally lowered his eyes and waved his hand, "The other side used my own little brother and used the Immortal Gu, Mutual Sense, to get my location. Everyone, first leave Dang Hun palace and lie in ambush. My senior brother will explain the details to you."

Immortal Gu Mutual Sense could allow two parties to sense each other's situation.

At this moment, Fang Zheng and Fang Yuan had sensed each other's situation through blood sense Gu and mutual sense Immortal Gu.

Naturally, because of the difference in strength between the two sides, Fang Yuan was able to sense everything about Fang Zheng while Fang Zheng could only see things through Fang Yuan's eyes. His perception was limited and he was not even able to sense the immortal aperture inside Fang Yuan.

Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan glanced at each other, and saw the heavy mood in the other's eyes.

They were hindered by the Snowy Mountain Alliance and could not easily avoid this, they could only brace themselves to fight alongside Fang Yuan.

On Tian Ti mountain, He Feng Yang, who was sitting on a white cloud cushion Gu, suddenly opened his eyes.

"The time is ripe!" A sharp light burst out of his eyes as he took out an Immortal Gu.

"Expand space Immortal Gu." Fairy Cang Yu softly breathed out when she saw the Immortal Gu.

This Immortal Gu belonged to Immortal Crane Sect's second supreme elder, its ability was to expand the space of a blessed land. He Feng Yang had borrowed it to use it as the core of an immortal killer move.

Immortal killer move — Force Intrusion!

Over ten beads of green grape immortal essence were spent in an instant. An enormous aura rose up and formed translucent ripples in the air.

Crack...

Like the sound of glass breaking, space broke apart in front of He Feng Yang and Fairy Cang Yu, revealing the terrain of Hu Immortal blessed land.

He Feng Yang leisurely stored expand space Immortal Gu before glancing at Fairy Cang Yu and inviting in a gentlemanly voice: "Fairy, please enter."

Fairy Cang Yu delicately laughed before stepping forward in the direction of Hu Immortal blessed land.

Suddenly, lightning struck towards her!

Chapter 700: Attacking Hu Immortal blessed land (3/3)

Fairy Cang Yu's mind was immediately alerted.

The flash of lightning came quickly, it tore through the air and emitting a crackling sound like that of sparks.

"Even though there are many Gu Immortals present, our sect had won in our scheme earlier, according to the rules, the other nine great ancient sects can merely observe this. If they are not from the nine sects, which demonic path Gu Immortal would dare to take a risk and mess with Immortal Crane Sect?"

In an instant, Fairy Cang Yu's mind was flashing with thoughts.

At the same time, her fingers did not slow down, her ten dainty fingers were fluttering around, about to activate a killer move to strike back.

But at the next moment, He Feng Yang stopped her: "Fairy, wait."

Saying this, he pulled Fairy Cang Yu to one side, while opening up the hole leading to Hu Immortal blessed land.

The flash of lightning ignored the two of them, it entered Hu Immortal blessed land through this hole.

Using this time, Fairy Cang Yu saw the lightning's true identity: "This is the earthly calamity — Blue Charm Lightning Shadow?"

He Feng Yang laughed plainly: "This is an earthly calamity targeting Hu Immortal blessed land, after Fang Yuan discarded a huge portion of Hu Immortal blessed land, he sent it out of the blessed land. To think that this blue charm lightning shadow did not vanish, instead it had been hiding on Tian Ti mountain."

"Great. Blue charm lightning shadow has good battle strength, about the mid-tier of rank six. With it leading from the front, we would have an easier time." Fairy Cang Yu's brows eased, she started smiling.

"Fang Yuan has decisiveness, he really is quite impressive, directly discarding close to a quarter of the blessed land. But his strength is simply too low, no matter how much he plots, it is useless."

He Feng Yang sighed, entering Hu Immortal blessed land along with Fairy Cang Yu.

Once they got in, a wave of heavenly power descended on them, sealing all of the mortal Gu in their hands.

But immediately after, He Feng Yang and Fairy Cang Yu's bodies shone with an orange and yellow light.

This was the effect of the rank seven one's own way Immortal Gu, it could prevent their mortal Gu from being suppressed, and let them be activated normally.

Fairy Cang Yu shut her eyes, after a few breaths, she opened them again: "We are at the west area of Hu Immortal blessed land, the blue charm lightning shadow has already gone to the center of the blessed land, towards Dang Hun mountain."

He Feng Yang nodded: "As I expected, within Hu Immortal blessed land, the safest place is Dang Hun mountain. The blue charm lightning shadow's first target is the blessed land's owner. Back then, Hu Immortal was caught off guard and killed by the blue charm lightning shadow. Since it is heading for Dang Hun mountain, that means Fang Yuan is hiding inside Dang Hun mountain, let's go there."

"Okay. I've always wanted to see what the legendary Dang Hun mountain looks like." Fairy Cang Yu laughed lightly.

"With the blue charm lightning shadow leading the way, we can also see what kind of ambush the enemy has prepared." He Feng Yang said, activating expand space Immortal Gu, using another immortal killer move as the hole behind him closed in the blessed land.

"That's the immortal killer move, force closure."

"Immortal Crane Sect is so petty, they are not letting us watch."

"In this battle, if Immortal Crane Sect fails, whether the door is closed or not, we will take over. If Immortal Crane Sect wins, whether the door opens or not, we will leave. Letting us watch would not affect anything."

"Hmph, they are projecting their own shortcomings onto others. Did they really think we would act out of greed?"

Outside, on Tian Ti mountain, the Gu Immortals from central continent's other nine great sects were conversing using their divine senses.

"Bi Weng, how high do you think Immortal Crane Sect's chance of succeeding is?" Gu Immortal Zhang Wen Jiu asked casually.

"Relatively high. Even though we have been obstructing them in secret, causing them to only send two Gu Immortals in the end to take back Hu Immortal blessed land, they still have the battle strength of two Gu Immortals and now the blue charm lightning shadow. Fang Yuan who controls Hu Immortal blessed land is a mere mortal, how can he block Immortal Crane Sect?" Bi Weng answered.

"That's not what I think. According to the investigation of us, Spirit Butterfly Valley, Fang Yuan had refined Fixed Immortal Travel in Three Kings blessed land, and came here alone. How is that possible? As a mortal, how could he refine an Immortal Gu, how could he have an image of Hu Immortal blessed land's scenery? Behind him, there is definitely a mastermind. Since the other party dared to snatch Hu Immortal blessed land from the ten ancient sects, I am sure they have the battle strength to protect it. Maybe, they might be able to resist Immortal Crane Sect's attack?" Rainbow Butterfly Immortal Concubine Han Cai Xin said.

"Immortal Concubine also does not speak without reason." Gu Immortal Du Teng laughed: "If Immortal Crane Sect fails, do we have a competition to decide the victor or choose to have an agreement among the ten sects first before striking?"

This was a crucial problem, the Gu Immortals from the nine sects fell into silence.

"Of course we'll discuss it in detail another day. We are the ten great ancient sects, not rabid dogs scavenging for food." Myriad Dragon Dock's Gu Immortal Guan Cao Ze immediately said.

Among the Gu Immortals present, Guan Cao Ze had the lowest battle strength. If they battled, he would be at the greatest disadvantage.

"This is inappropriate, this is inappropriate." Green Canary Boy shook his head.

"We should strike while the iron is hot, this is just a blessed land, we should decide on it today and not waste more time!" Great Lord Lie Yang pretended to be unaware.

"Strange, didn't Vicious Lightning Fiend of your Myriad Dragon Dock just end his closed cultivation? Why would you be sent here for this contest for Hu Immortal blessed land?" Poison Count Lu Xu laughed coldly as he pointed out Guan Cao Ze's weakness.

The Gu Immortals quickly formed a consensus, if Immortal Crane Sect failed, they would have a competition to decide who the blessed land belongs to. If Immortal Crane Sect won, they would also have a competition, the sect that places first would have priority in reaching an agreement with Immortal Crane Sect for the guts Gu.

Guts Gu could raise the foundation of a sect, it was even useful to Gu Immortals. Any sect would not be able to take it solely for themselves, when the other nine sects exert pressure, they would be forced to sell it.

"You guys..." Guan Cao Ze was fuming on the outside, but he was snickering on the inside.

At the same time as the discussion between the Gu Immortals of the nine sects, within Hu Immortal blessed land, He Feng Yang and Fairy Cang Yu were slowly flying towards Dang Hun mountain.

"This is a blood pool?" Halfway there, He Feng Yang gave a curious gaze.

He found that within Hu Immortal blessed land, there was a huge blood pool, it was so huge it could be called a blood lake.

"Hmph, another blood path scoundrel!" Fairy Cang Yu frowned, saying in a despising tone.

"Blood path cultivators harm all living beings in this world, as it can allow them to raise their battle strength. This is the reason why countless Gu Masters choose this path! Every ten years, Heavenly Court would issue the Demon Judgment Board, and many blood path Gu Masters would be on it. Blood Sea Ancestor, he truly caused much harm to the world!" He Feng Yang criticized, thrusting with his palm as a jade lightning ball flew towards it.

Boom boom boom.

After a series of explosions, the blood pool was destroyed, turning into ruins.

After destroying the blood pool, the two immortals continued to fly towards Dang Hun mountain.

On the way, Fairy Cang Yu shook her head: "This Hu Immortal blessed land is managed too poorly, it is almost completely desolate. I've heard that this place had large groups of foxes in the past, but now, after flying for so long, we have not seen a single myriad fox group."

"There are few fox groups, but there are surely a lot of rockmen. Fang Yuan is a mortal after all, he only knows how to use guts Gu to increase the production of rockmen. But he does not know that he is pursuing tiny gains while discarding the foundations. Hu Immortal was an enslavement path Gu Immortal, enslavement path was the main law in her blessed land, it is best for rearing fox groups." He Feng Yang laughed in disdain.

"Hu Immortal blessed land is truly wasted in his hands. Once it is in our sect, Hu Immortal blessed land will develop greatly, but I wonder who in the sect would be its owner." Fairy Cang Yu sighed.

Hearing that, He Feng Yang sighed: "According to the rules, after we recover it, Hu Immortal blessed land would be a public blessed land of Immortal Crane Sect, we would only have a limited time in operating it after getting it. But this managing right is also extremely lucrative. After all, the center of the blessed land is Dang Hun mountain, it is a gold mine!"

"The scariest part is that this gold mine will never run out." Fairy Cang Yu nodded in agreement.

The two of them talked along the way, not facing any obstruction. This raised their confidence that the blessed land was in terrible shape.

They started to fly faster, and when they were in front of Dang Hun mountain, they were already talking about 'what they would do when Dang Hun mountain belongs to them'.

In the air above Dang Hun mountain, the blue charm lightning shadow was shrieking and charging, attacking Dang Hun mountain.

But though it was formed from an earthly calamity, it had life as well, Dang Hun mountain's vibration could attack its soul, its weakness.

"Fang Yuan, come out. You should know that Dang Hun mountain can only block the blue charm lightning shadow because it has no Gu worms. Even if you raise Dang Hun mountain's power to its limits, you cannot block two Gu Immortals." He Feng Yang shouted, his voice could pierce through heaven and earth.

"Fang Yuan, a wise man submits to circumstances, I am sure the land spirit is beside you now. Then you should know that Hu Immortal blessed land cannot seal our mortal Gu. Furthermore, we've brought an Immortal Gu!" Fairy Cang Yu followed up, pressuring Fang Yuan.

Thus, Fang Yuan walked out, standing on Dang Hun mountain's peak.

He Feng Yang's heart tightened, but he quickly relaxed. This was a rank six immortal zombie, immortal zombies had great weaknesses, they could not produce immortal essence and their blessed land would shrivel and break apart at set intervals, thus their battle strength was usually below ordinary Gu Immortals.

"Immortal Crane Sect has finally lost their patience? You want my blessed land, aren't you afraid I will destroy Dang Hun mountain?" Fang Yuan said.

"You are... Fang Yuan?" He Feng Yang squinted, he found it unbelievable. Only a year had passed, how could Fang Yuan become an immortal zombie?!

While He Feng Yang was suspicious and confused, Fairy Cang Yu spoke beside him, smiling: "We came prepared, of course, how could we allow you to destroy Dang Hun mountain? If you think using Dang Hun mountain could threaten us, then you are very much mistaken. Oh, that's right, we can even reduce Dang Hun mountain's pressure until it is insignificant. By then, we would not need to strike, this blue charm lightning shadow alone can kill you."

Fang Yuan looked at the blue charm lightning shadow in the air, this human shaped lightning was growling non-stop, charging towards Dang Hun mountain but was forced back each time by the intense vibrations.

Fang Yuan heaved a long sigh.

Fairy Cang Yu thought that this was a chance, and continued: "As long as you give up the ownership of the blessed land, we can forget past matters, and even accept you as a disciple of our sect!"

"But I remember, Immortal Crane Sect promised to give me the position of an elder back then?" Fang Yuan retorted.

He Feng Yang laughed coldly: "Times have changed, Fang Yuan, you are a smart man, can't you see the circumstances now?"

Fang Yuan heard this and he smirked: "Oh? The circumstances now... oh, let me have a good look."

Just after he said this, the aura of Immortal Gu burst out in his body.

"This, this is?!" Fairy Cang Yu's beautiful face transformed.

"Immortal Gu, so many Immortal Gu!" He Feng Yang could not tell which Immortal Gu they were, but the aura would not lie to him, his eyes were burning with an intense light of greed.

But at the next moment, three figures appeared around Fang Yuan.

Hei Lou Lan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, Fairy Li Shan!

Two rank six, one rank seven!

Not only that, each of them gave off an intense Immortal Gu aura, not concealing it at all.

Fairy Cang Yu's complexion changed.

He Feng Yang's greedy gaze also turned into one of uncontrollable shock!

Fang Yuan's force was so powerful it was out of his imagination.

Next, one, two, three... six, seven, eight beast figures flew out from Dang Hun mountain and arrived in eight surrounding directions.

Ice spike divine ape, phoenix feather lava crocodile, golden sand dark stallion, azure dragon vine... eight desolate beasts formed an encirclement.

"This is a trap!" He Feng Yang growled, his body shuddering.

Fairy Cang Yu suddenly felt outnumbered, her face turned pale and she was speechless.

Even the blue charm lightning shadow in the air stopped its angry growl.

Fang Yuan's plain voice came from Dang Hun mountain once again: "Oh, I have seen the current circumstances very clearly now, but the question is, have you?"

Chapter 701: Rank Three Airsac Gu

Eight desolate beasts encircled closer to He Feng Yang and Fairy Cang Yu.

"They are all real." Fairy Cang Yu had extremely outstanding investigative methods to check the situation, but the result caused her pretty face to blanch further.

He Feng Yang looked around him and saw —

To the east was an ice spike divine ape whose bulk was only somewhat inferior to Dang Hun mountain; a tyrannical aura spread out from it and as it moved, it left behind a pure white icy trail. The fur on its whole body were like ice cones which brought a stifling pressure upon the two Immortals. The sclera of its eyes were jade green, while its pupils had a frost blue luster. This represented the dense bloodline in this ice spike divine ape. If the eyeballs were completely frost blue in color, that would be the ancient desolate beast, icefall divine ape, whose battle strength was comparable to a rank seven Gu Immortal.

To the west floated a phoenix feather lava crocodile. This crocodile was two to three times the size of ordinary crocodiles and could not compare to the enormously huge ice spike divine ape, yet its aura surged mightily. Its every breath brought a scalding hot heat wave. Its brownish-red scale armor was thick and robust, and its slender tail was over six meters long. It did not have any scales on its back but instead had colorful phoenix feathers that resembled blazing lava.

To the north stood a proud golden sand dark stallion. This horse was huge, its size reaching the chest of the ice spike divine ape. It had six legs that looked like they were cast from metal, its muscles were bulging, its posture was proud and aloof like a dragon, and its whole body shone with a golden luster. Only the six hooves were pitch black.

The south side was entrenched by an azure dragon vine. This vine was not a wild beast, strictly speaking, but a plant. The vines had condensed into a dragon shape and when its roots were pierced into the soil, its defensive and regenerative powers were extremely terrifying, thus it specialized in battles of attrition. If it pulled out the roots, it could soar in the sky like an azure dragon.

On the southeast side was a swamp crab. It was the king of swampy terrain. Its broad, mountain-like body could reach up to a quarter of Dang Hun mountain's height when standing. Its eyes had degenerated till they were nonexistent, and its shell was so thick that He Feng Yang felt a powerless sensation, like he was facing a tortoise shell. It had altogether nineteen pairs of legs and its front pair of pincers could easily crush boulders and cut dragons, even Fang Yuan with his immortal zombie body did not dare to test the might of this pair of pincers.

A peach wolf was crouching down on the northeast. This wolf had the smallest size, the same as that of a newborn puppy. It looked extremely good natured and cute with its round body, plump claws, pink tongue and round dark eyes. Judging from appearance, it seemed to be harmless to both man and beast, however, He Feng Yang's pupils shrunk and if he had to choose a direction to break through, he would avoid this one outright!

An iron crown eagle circled over the northwest side. This eagle gave off a valiant and imposing aura as it hovered in the air, its eyes locked onto He Feng Yang and Fairy Cang Yu. Its wings were broad and thick, and each of its feathers could be shot out like sharp arrows. Its claws were firm and savage, able to crush boulders and rip apart dragons and tigers.

Finally on the southwest side stood an earth chief desolate beast. It had a humanoid body with a snake tail, its face resembled a bat's and its nose was pointed up. It had large ears and was black all over, with armor made of flesh covering it. Around its chest were fifty to sixty fleshy whips, each over twenty meters in length. There were suction organs on the surface of the fleshy whips; it would be hard to free oneself if someone was entangled by them. At the front of each fleshy whip was a chrysanthemum-like orifice which could shoot out a white milky fluid at the crucial moment; the fluid had very high corrosiveness and contained extremely large numbers of parasitic worms, which could drill into the pores of people and wreak havoc from inside the body.

Fang Yuan had borrowed these eight desolate beasts from Lang Ya land spirit.

More accurately, it should be said that Fang Yuan borrowed Lang Ya land spirit's rank seven beast enslavement Gu. This Immortal Gu could subdue all kinds of wild beasts, including mutated beasts, myriad beast kings, beast emperors, even desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts.

Desolate beasts had the power of a rank six Gu Immortal and could be very difficult to deal with when the wild Gu residing on them were unknown.

Eight desolate beasts encircled He Feng Yang and Fairy Cang Yu, eying them with greed.

The two sank into silence with no signs of a leisurely attitude like before.

He Feng Yang turned his heavy gaze towards the peak of Dang Hun mountain. Compared to the eight desolate beasts, the true threat was still Fang Yuan and the other three immortals.

Almost no desolate beasts could use killer moves, but Gu Immortals had ample wisdom to use and research killer moves.

He Feng Yang's heart had sunken to rock bottom, he forcibly calmed down and shouted towards Fang Yuan: "Who are all of you?"

Except Fang Yuan, the other three immortals were wearing masks; Hei Lou Lan wore a black bear mask, Fairy Li Shan wore a blue bird mask, while Tai Bai Yun Sheng wore a deer mask. The three were also shrouded in a layer of light that concealed their true appearance, hiding it from the investigative methods of He Feng Yang and Fairy Cang Yu.

Fang Yuan chuckled: "Before asking us of our identities, shouldn't you two introduce yourselves first?"

He Feng Yang and Fairy Cang Yu silently glanced at each other, and saw the bitter look in each other's eyes.

They had thought this trip would be simple, and at worst, they thought the other side would possess a Gu Immortal's battle strength. However, they absolutely had not anticipated the enemy force would be this strong!

Thus, they had been arrogant and directly requested Fang Yuan to surrender without giving self-introductions.

"My name is He Feng Yang, a rank six enslavement path Gu Immortal of Immortal Crane Sect."

"I am Cang Yu, a rank six water path Gu Immortal of Immortal Crane Sect."

The two introduced themselves one after the other, their attitude was no longer as overbearing as earlier, they were behaving very humbly at the moment.

A wise man submits to circumstances, those who could become Gu Immortals were outstanding people. At present, Fang Yuan had an imposing force, He Feng Yang and Cang Yu decisively lowered their high heads.

It might be easy to defeat Gu Immortals but killing them was difficult. He Feng Yang could use expand space Immortal Gu to tear a hole in Hu Immortal blessed land's space and escape. However, they did not know Fang Yuan's abilities, if Fang Yuan had an Immortal Gu that could prevent their escape, the situation would become dangerous.

"So it is brother He and Fairy Cang Yu." Fang Yuan's tone was polite, "I am Fang Yuan and I welcome you two as guests in my blessed land."

These polite words felt grating when He Feng Yang and Cang Yu heard them, it was full of sarcasm.

He Feng Yang could not help but feel stifled.

What he had asked for was clearly these people's true identities, but Fang Yuan played dumb and gave an irrelevant answer by only replying with his name.

Right now, who in Central Continent's ten great sects would not know of his name?

Fang Yuan intentionally avoided this topic, and He Feng Yang, as the weaker side, did not dare to pursue it.

"I wonder what both of you are here for?" Fang Yuan asked.

He Feng Yang was silent, but inwardly he was screaming insults: 'What else could we come for? It is to take Hu Immortal blessed land and capture Dang Hun mountain. This brat, asking when he already knows!'

Fairy Cang Yu snorted: "Why is sir speaking in such a weird and sarcastic tone? Sir's power surpassed everyone's imagination, when did such a force appear in Central Continent? Today was our loss, sir's planning skills are indeed excellent and have fully controlled the situation. Now what should we do? If you want to battle, then let us begin, why waste time chit-chatting? We will battle to the end if you wish to, in the worst case, our blood will splatter all over and we will perish here."

Fang Yuan could not help but take another look at Fairy Cang Yu upon hearing these words, shortly afterwards he smiled: "Fairy, you are quite brave, I am filled with admiration. I can roughly guess your intentions in coming here, it should be for Dang Hun mountain's guts Gu, right?"

"You are right." He Feng Yang frankly admitted. Under the circumstances, he had no choice but to admit it, the scheme which he had painstakingly devised and prepared for over a year in order to capture Hu Immortal blessed land had already completely failed.

However, right at this time, he could not help but have some hope: 'If Fang Yuan wanted to battle, he should have started already. But he has been talking up to this point, it seems he is afraid of Immortal Crane Sect, as long as I use this correctly, maybe we can escape without any accidents.'

Fang Yuan suddenly clapped and smiled: "You two came in at just the right time, I had already been thinking of selling guts Gu. What do you think of this Gu?"

A rank three Gu worm flew out of his hand.

The Gu worm slowly flew under the gazes of six Gu Immortals, eight desolate beasts as well as the blue charm lightning shadow, and landed in He Feng Yang's hand.

He Feng Yang was uncertain and worried of Fang Yuan's scheme as he carefully accepted this mortal Gu.

This rank three Gu worm resembled a ladybug. It was the size of a large bowl, its head was extremely small while its stomach was so big that it occupied ninety-nine percent of its body.

Its stomach was round like a lamp bulb and was translucent. It did not have a carapace on its back and also did not have wings.

In its translucent stomach, there was a Gu.

"A Gu within a Gu?" Fairy Cang Yu softly mumbled.

This rank three mortal Gu was clearly a storage Gu worm, particularly with the purpose of storing Gu worms. These types of storage Gu worms were extremely common, it included examples like Earth Treasury Flower.

However, the Gu worm inside the belly made He Feng Yang's gaze fix on it as if it was glued. He then said with uncertain eyes: "This Gu inside... could it be guts Gu?"

Fang Yuan gave a bright smile: "That is exactly right!"

"What?" Fairy Cang Yu's beautiful eyes widened in astonishment.

She might know very little about guts Gu, but she knew guts Gu could not be taken out of Dang Hun mountain; if taken out, they would dissipate.

It was because of this that Fang Yuan was not willing to trade guts Gu before. Because if others wanted to use guts Gu, they would have to personally come to Dang Hun mountain. And letting so many outsiders enter Hu Immortal blessed land would no doubt be a huge threat to Fang Yuan's life.

This was the reason central continent's ten great ancient sects wanted to seize Dang Hun mountain. Guts Gu could not be taken out of Dang Hun mountain, thus taking control of Dang Hun mountain meant being in control of guts Gu.

However, the fact right in front on them showed that guts Gu could actually be stored and taken out of Dang Hun mountain.

Fairy Cang Yu soon recognized how much significance this unremarkable ladybug-like Gu worm carried; for a moment, her eyes were tightly affixed to it.

"This Gu worm, what is its name?" He Feng Yang looked up at Fang Yuan and asked with a slightly trembling tone.

Fang Yuan had in truth not thought of a name, and casually named it at this moment: "Airsac Gu."

He Feng Yang sank into silence.

In an instant, he thought of many things.

Immortal Crane Sect's higher ups had also made these attempts. Back then, many Gu Immortals had participated but it ended up in failure.

Now, success was in He Feng Yang's hand.

He Feng Yang's hands shivered slightly.

'If guts Gu could be taken out of Dang Hun mountain and exported to all places, treasure yellow heaven, Hai Shi blessed land, Central Continent, Southern Border, Northern Plains... how big of a profit would this be?'

'Something that even our Immortal Crane Sect could not research was successfully accomplished by the force behind Fang Yuan. What are their origins? Maybe they had planned for a long time and thought of every means to capture Hu Immortal blessed land, in order to engage in the business of guts Gu!'

'Fang Yuan did not attack, could it be that he wants to... with our Immortal Crane Sect...'

He Feng Yang was still considering when Fang Yuan spoke: "Since both guests are interested in my guts Gu, what do you think of doing this transaction?"

He Feng Yang's heart wavered!

Chapter 702: Accident, Assault of a Mysterious Gu Immortal

Fang Yuan's suggestion moved He Feng Yang's heart.

When Fang Yuan launched the ambush and encircled He Feng Yang, he had thought that this operation was going to end in failure. In the best case scenario, he would use expand space Immortal Gu and break out of the encirclement forcefully after sustaining huge injuries.

Even if he consumed a lot of immortal essence during the process of escaping, he could not care about it. After all, comparing immortal essence and his life, the latter was much more important.

After returning to Immortal Crane Sect, He Feng Yang's life would definitely go downhill.

Immortal Crane Sect placed such great expectations on him, and he had even prepared for over a year, but he ended up failing. His rival, Gu Immortal Lei Tan, would definitely seek him out to mock him personally when he hears the news!

Second supreme elder would be utterly disappointed with him, and He Feng Yang might not be able to lift his head for several years after that. This loss could be a lifelong blemish, solely with just this failure, he would be mocked by countless people in the dark forever.

If he could establish the deal with Fang Yuan for guts Gu, to He Feng Yang, that would be many times better than breaking through the encirclement.

He Feng Yang assessed in his heart: "Hu Immortal blessed land has four Gu Immortals and eight desolate beasts, together with the territorial advantage, they are as secure as a fortress! Even though any of the ten great ancient sects have the capability to take this on, that is only speaking of capability. They might not be able to gather so many Gu Immortals here. Even if they could send Gu Immortals to attack Hu Immortal blessed land, a battle between Gu Immortals will expend a great amount of immortal essence and other resources."

"Even if they could get enough manpower and invest a lot into this battle, the other party also has Gu Immortals and can easily destroy Dang Hun mountain. By then, even if Hu Immortal blessed land was obtained, it would all be for nothing."

In the outside world, Great Heavenly Sword Sect had three Gu Immortals, and could attempt to leave one of the ten great ancient sects, Immortal Crane Sect.

This was because to deal with three Gu Immortals, the resources and manpower needed were something Immortal Crane Sect needed to consider. If they failed, not only would they suffer a loss in their reputation, this huge loss might also cause unrest within the sect, and trigger other problems.

Gu Immortals were easy to defeat, but they were hard to kill. Why would anyone who could reach this stage not have any means or trump cards to escape?

If they failed to kill him, they would utterly offend a Gu Immortal. A Gu Immortal that is holding grudges may cause trouble to mortals, with Immortal Crane Sect's huge size and wide range of assets, they would have to salvage the situation everywhere.

Now that Fang Yuan has displayed such a force, Immortal Crane Sect alone could no longer attack forcefully, unless the other sects cooperated with them. But if they cooperated, there would be issues in many aspects, regarding the allocation of benefits.

If He Feng Yang agrees to cooperate with Fang Yuan, they would establish trade for guts Gu, this result was not an utter failure.

That was because Immortal Crane Sect's main objective in taking down Hu Immortal blessed land was for the guts Gu.

Using the smallest price to obtain the biggest benefits, this was the issue that all of the supreme elders in Immortal Crane Sect were concerned about.

Before this, Immortal Crane Sect had already requested for Fang Yuan to initiate the sales of guts Gu.

"If we could establish a trade with the other party, I would not need to force my way out and risk injury, I can save a lot of immortal essence and have a proper justification when I return to the sect." He Feng Yang considered this option.

Fang Yuan observed his expression, even though He Feng Yang was a shrewd man and did not show emotions on his face, he was clearly moved due to how long he was considering this for.

Thus, Fang Yuan continued: "A hundred of my guts Gu will sell for one immortal essence stone in treasure yellow heaven. I will sell a hundred and twenty guts Gu to Immortal Crane Sect for each immortal essence stone. However, in return, I want your Immortal Crane Sect to acknowledge my Hu Immortal blessed land as your sect's subsidiary force. Furthermore, this subsidiary can detach from you at any time."

As long as he had this identity, the other nine great ancient sects would not be able to deal with Fang Yuan without involving Immortal Crane Sect. These were the rules of the righteous path, it was like making Immortal Crane Sect the big boss, while Hu Immortal blessed land was the lackey, you would need to ask the boss before hitting his lackeys.

He Feng Yang smiled insincerely as he spoke: "Fang Yuan, are you thinking of using my sect as your protection? With your force, you can definitely establish your own sect, right?"

"Nobody can set up a sect on Tian Ti mountain. I have no intention to leave this valuable spot." Fang Yuan laughed.

Tian Ti mountain had directly connected to Heavenly Court, even Gu Immortals did not dare to fight on this mountain. If Immortal Crane Sect did not declare Fang Yuan as a sect traitor and hold perfect reason to take him down, they would not dare to attack Hu Immortal blessed land.

"Furthermore, Hu Immortal blessed land becoming Immortal Crane Sect's subsidiary will also account for your sect's reputation, right?" Fang Yuan continued.

He Feng Yang fell into silence again.

A long while later, he sighed out: "This matter is very important, I cannot be in charge of the decision, allow me to return and report to the sect."

Fang Yuan nodded: "It would be best if brother He goes and explains it. But Fairy Cang Yu would need to remain as a guest here for a while longer."

He Feng Yang and Cang Yu made eye contact.

Fairy Cang Yu said: "Lord Feng Yang, go ahead and return, I will wait here."

"I will return quickly." He Feng Yang nodded solemnly at her, before looking deeply at Fang Yuan and his gang.

He wanted to engrave these people into the depths of his heart.

"Land spirit, open the door and let brother He out." Fang Yuan said with a concerned tone.

"Yes, master." Little Hu Immortal quickly replied.

On Tian Ti mountain, a brilliant white gold light formed.

In the light, a bright red door appeared, it was over thirty meters tall, and there was a rainbow colored plaque. Pink clouds gathered as the aurora condensed into a flight of stairs of light.

He Feng Yang came out of the door, when he left, it was through the proper exit of the blessed land.

This action quickly attracted the attention of the Gu Immortals of the other nine great sects.

They started to converse.

"He's out!"

"So fast? Don't tell me there was no resistance at all?"

"When He Feng Yang entered, he used the expand space Immortal Gu, but when he came out, it was through the main entrance. This is proof that he succeeded."

"Something's wrong, look at his face, there is no joy of victory, he looks more calm and composed instead."

Even though they were suspicious, none of them asked him directly.

This was a hidden contest between the ten great sects, a direct confrontation was damaging to their reputations.

He Feng Yang could not care about their feelings, he only wanted to return to Fei He mountain, to report this matter.

He flew quickly, traveling far from Tian Ti mountain in a moment's time.

He Feng Yang's brows were locked, he was indignant and suspicious: "Where did Fang Yuan's force come from? Other than Fang Yuan, the other three immortals all covered their faces with masks, and used Gu worms to block investigative methods, they evidently do not want to expose their identities. Why is that?"

"Don't tell me they are Gu Immortals from the other nine sects? They did not want our sect to obtain Dang Hun mountain, thus they secretly colluded with Fang Yuan beforehand?"

The moment he thought of this, He Feng Yang rejected this possibility.

Paper could not cover up a fire, secrets were temporary and would be outed, the nine great sects would not do such a thing, it was against the demeanor of one of the great sects.

"Then, are they Gu Immortals gathered from Central Continent's smaller sects?" He Feng Yang thought.

Central Continent had countless sects, other than the ten great ancient sects, there were large sized sects, middle sized sects, small sized sects, and mini sects. There were untold numbers of sects, within them, there naturally were some Gu Immortals.

If it had been them, then these Gu Immortal would all have foundations in Central Continent, to prevent their home sect from being suppressed or troubled by the ancient sects, they would not want to reveal their identities, that made sense.

"That's right, Fang Yuan has the fixed immortal travel Immortal Gu! These people might not be Central Continent Gu Immortals, they might be from other regions. The stronger the Gu Immortal, the harder it is to get past the regional walls. Every once in a while, they have to let out their aperture in the region that they became an immortal to recollect and gather heaven and earth qi to stabilize the blessed land. But with Fixed Immortal Travel, the other party can settle these problems easily!"

He Feng Yang's thoughts moved swiftly, he quickly guessed Fang Yuan and the other Gu Immortals' identities. But he had too little evidence, he could not confirm it.

"All in all, Hu Immortal blessed land is very mysterious and dangerous, before we find out their secrets, we cannot strike easily. This time, I suffered a huge loss, the root of the problem was that the enemy was in the dark while I was out in the open, we suffered from a lack of intel!"

He Feng Yang concluded his experience from this incident, but he suddenly stopped in the air.

"Who is this? You dare to ambush me here!" He Feng Yang quickly became alert, shouting.

"Hmm, you are very vigilant." A voice came from somewhere, it was high and low pitched at times, with a hoarse male voice that turned into a crisp female voice. Someone had evidently modified their voice with Gu worms.

Two figures appeared, one in front and one behind, they blocked He Feng Yang's paths.

What changed next was the sky. The bright, shiny and clear sky with no clouds turned dark and eerie, fog became thick as vengeful souls flew all over the place.

This was a battlefield killer move!

This was a battlefield environment created to amplify the effects of certain Gu worms.

This was not something ordinary Gu Immortals could have.

"I am Immortal Crane Sect's He Feng Yang, both of you are concealing your appearances and acting so secretive, what is your intention?" He Feng Yang shouted.

The two Gu Immortals before him were masked in a layer of dark light, their appearances could not be seen.

"So what if you are from Immortal Crane Sect?" The mysterious Gu Immortal in front of him laughed coldly.

The Gu Immortal behind him said directly: "We will kill you regardless!"

Just as they said that, the Gu Immortal struck.

Five fingers spread open and thousands of grey white threads appeared from the palm.

The threads got close to He Feng Yang, as his heart jumped, this was obviously a mortal killer move designed to trap people. Once he was entangled by these threads, it would be difficult to escape.

He Feng Yang quickly summoned the crane group.

Within his immortal aperture, there were large numbers of flying cranes, he brought them with him everywhere and he never lacked any troops.

The crane groups were huge in numbers, there were iron beak flying cranes, fire pellet cranes, tailwind cranes, cloud mist cranes, stellar light cranes, and illusion lightning cranes all mixed together in perfect harmony, forming a tight formation.

A desolate beast nine palace crane flew out, crying out and causing the surrounding fog to disperse.

He Feng Yang stepped onto the nine palace crane's back, his hair was fluttering as his gaze was like lightning, the anger within him had awakened: "Do you really think I am an easy target? Today, you will taste the fury of the Winged Crane Flying Immortal!"

As the threads flew to him, the iron beak flying crane group flew out and blocked them with their bodies.

The other mysterious Gu Immortal puffed up his cheeks and blew out huge flames. These flames were pale green, and in this battlefield, their power was amplified, causing many cranes to fall from the sky after getting burnt.

He Feng Yang was not to be outdone, he activated his enslavement path killer move.

Immediately, a group of illusion lightning cranes flew out, shooting lightning bolts that gathered and formed into a pillar, piercing the battlefield. Another group of fire pellet cranes flew out, their bodies covered in flames, burning their enemies.

Two groups of flying cranes charged towards the two mysterious Gu Immortals like a pair of giant fists.

Boom boom boom...

With an intense explosion, the two sides engaged in intense battle!

Chapter 703: Plot within plot, a fatal killer move

On the battlefield, the intense battle continued.

A large group of iron beak flying cranes, each with bodies black as steel, they had increased defense and did not fear death, they charged towards the two mysterious Gu Immortals fiercely.

One of the two mysterious Gu Immortals opened their mouth, as a loud sound came out of it, echoing everywhere.

This was a sound path killer move!

The iron beak flying crane group's formation went into chaos under the effect of the sound, their tight formation became loose and there were many weaknesses exposed.

"Go!" The other mysterious Gu Immortal saw a chance and grabbed the other person's limb, the two of them turning into two lumps of grey white flames, piercing the iron beak flying cranes' formation and moving towards He Feng Yang.

Against an enslavement path Gu Immortal, one should not fight intensely with their beast group, taking down the enslavement Gu Immortal was the proper battle tactic.

He Feng Yang saw that the enemy was approaching, not only was he not anxious, he showed a cold smile: "You fell into my trap."

He took out a five hole jade flute Gu, placing it near his mouth and started playing the flute. He looked like a green clothed young man, but he was actually the lord of myriads of beasts. His sleeves fluttered in the air despite having no wind, his eyes burst out with a lively brilliance.

Enslavement path killer move — Eight Sided Ambush!

Tens of thousands of flying cranes moved with his music, groups of invisible cranes that had hidden their figures exposed themselves, encircling the two mysterious Gu Immortals tightly.

He Feng Yang purposely left behind an empty space in the formation around himself, that was a trap to lead his enemies right into it.

Now that the other party had fallen for it, he did not let them off, as his flute continued to play, three five string zither Gu flew out of his body.

Amidst the music of the flute, the zither played a crisp tune, turning into another enslavement path killer move — Formation Like Water!

Innumerable flying cranes flew outward, while countless flying cranes flew towards the center.

The entire battlefield was like a perfect harmony of churning gears, the scale was massive but orderly, the flying cranes moved fluidly, their formation was changing like the flow of water.

The two mysterious Gu Immortals were within this formation, they saw the array of flying cranes changing their formation smoothly, they felt like beans in a stone grinder, about to be turned into pulp!

He Feng Yang continued to blow the flute, safely at the center of the beast group, standing on the back of the desolate crane, he watched the crane group engage with the two mysterious experts.

He thought in his heart: "Ever since we started fighting, these two have used countless killer moves, ranging from sound path, space path, fire path, wind path, light path, dark path, rule path and more, they were doing this on purpose, they did not want to use their real abilities and expose their identities."

When Gu Masters become immortals, according to the foundation of their bodies, as well as the Gu worm used to create their immortal aperture, they would be classified into Gu Immortals of their respective paths. There were fire path Gu Immortals, wind path Gu Immortals, wisdom path Gu Immortals and many others, forming the immortal bodies of the respective paths.

The immortal body is obtained when a Gu Masters ascends, their body will be modified by the three qi, removing all impurities and elevating the essence of their life itself.

A wind path immortal body will have the dao marks and comprehension of wind, thus when they use wind path Gu worms, the effect would be greater. A fire path immortal body would be cleansed by the Great Dao in relation to fire, it would be closely connected to fire path, and would cause fire path killer moves to be much more powerful than normal.

For example, Fang Yuan, although he was an immortal zombie, he was still a strength path Gu Immortal, his body was the strength path immortal body, thus when he used Gu worms and killer moves of other paths, the effects were only ordinary.

The two mysterious Gu Immortals trying to kill He Feng Yang did not use their real fighting methods, therefore, they were suppressed by him despite outnumbering him two to one.

"Are you two still trying to conceal your identities? If you do not use your true abilities, you might die here." He Feng Yang snickered continuously, his voice filled the battlefield.

The two mysterious Gu Immortals were breathing roughly, the attack of the crane groups were unceasing and furious like a tide, the two of them were tired from dealing with them.

Like what He Feng Yang said, if the two did not start using their real methods, they would truly get killed soon.

The two made eye contact as they nodded, making up their minds.

One of them sighed: "As expected of a reputed righteous sect. The might of the Winged Crane Flying Immortal, I have truly seen it today."

The other said: "However, even if we do not use our real capabilities, we can still kill you. He Feng Yang, take a look around you."

"Oh?" He Feng Yang's gaze quickly swept the surroundings.

Originally, it was a foggy scene, the battlefield was full of crying and anguished screams, but now there was a change.

Within the lumps of thick fog, dark blue soul beasts were formed. In just a few breaths of time, the number of soul beasts increased greatly, they were equally numbered with He Feng Yang's crane group.

"Is this... soul taker battlefield?" He Feng Yang's heart jumped, he said it subconsciously.

"Hehehe, Winged Crane Flying Immortal, you are very knowledgeable." The mysterious Gu Immortals laughed, their voices changing constantly, sounding like male or female at times.

He Feng Yang's expression turned grim.

This soul taker battlefield killer move had a vile reputation, it was very hard to deal with. Living beings who died in this battlefield would have their souls taken and transformed into soul beasts, under the control of the killer move's user.

Most importantly, this battlefield killer move's origin was huge, it was created by one of the ten venerables in history when he was young, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable who had the most murderous nature.

Who were these two mysterious Gu Immortals, they actually had a battlefield killer move, soul taker, that was long lost in history?!

Once the soul beasts appeared, they started fighting with the crane groups.

The battle situation changed.

He Feng Yang quickly manipulated the crane groups, changing formations to defend against the soul beasts. The two mysterious Gu Immortals felt less pressure now, and were able to rush out of the crane groups' encirclement.

The size of the soul beasts was the same as the crane group, but they could not defeat the cranes, often, ten soul beasts were sacrificed to kill one crane.

But He Feng Yang became increasingly alert in his heart, after the soul beasts were shredded into fragments, these fragments could form into new soul beasts in this soul taker battlefield.

Meanwhile, when a flying crane dies, its soul would be taken by the battlefield, forming a soul beast, becoming part of the enemy's troops. No matter how high He Feng Yang's cultivation was, he could not battle with zero casualties. Once he suffered losses, over a long period, the soul beasts would have the upper hand.

As this dragged on, He Feng Yang's advantage would dwindle, the crane groups would slowly be taken down by the soul beasts.

"He Feng Yang, just so you know, we expressed weakness earlier on purpose, to delay for time. Now that the soul taker battlefield has grown to a sizable amount, your enslavement path advantage is gone."

"Winged Crane Flying Immortal, today, you will perish here."

The two mysterious Gu Immortal worked together.

Wind path killer move — Tornado Dragon Whip!

With a wind whip that was hundreds of meters long, one of the Gu Immortals swung, killing countless flying cranes.

Poison path killer move — Killer Bee Stab!

Thousands of needles rained down like a torrential storm, the poison on them were very potent, any flying crane that was hit directly died on the spot, their flesh disintegrating.

The two mysterious Gu Immortals had finally showed their true abilities, one was a wind path Gu Immortal, while the other was a poison path Gu Immortal.

Large numbers of cranes were exterminated, their souls were extracted by the battlefield, forming new batches of soul beasts.

"Oh no, the enemy came prepared, they planned for this long ago, I cannot stay here." He Feng Yang saw this and wanted to retreat.

Only a fool would want to stay in the soul taker battlefield and fight it out with the enemy.

"This soul taker battlefield is filled with fog, it is easy to lose one's direction, it is hard to escape from. But right now, I have expand space Immortal Gu with me, it should not be hard to escape from here."

He Feng Yang thought about this and used his divine sense to communicate with a will in his immortal aperture.

This will was in the form of a burly man, when He Feng Yang left Fei He mountain earlier, it had entered his immortal aperture and had been observing the outside situation using his Gu worms.

All of He Feng Yang's experience this time, since he left Fei He mountain, in Hu Immortal blessed land, when he was encircled by Fang Yuan and the others, and after he left Hu Immortal blessed land and was trapped in the soul taker battlefield, attacked by two mysterious Gu Immortals. The will saw it all clearly.

He Feng Yang requested: "Lord Tiger Demon, please use your immortal killer move once again to break out of the battlefield and escape this place."

This will belonged to Immortal Crane Sect's third supreme elder, Lord Tiger Demon's anger will.

He sat in the air, opening his eyes emotionlessly: "You need to know that every time I use force intrusion, my main body will need to expend two red date immortal essence beads."

He Feng Yang quickly said: "Junior understand, I will make the appropriate compensation when we return."

Tiger Demon's anger will nodded, not speaking any further. He grabbed with his hand, tossing two red date immortal essence to the expand space Immortal Gu, at the same time, many mortal Gu rose up as well.

After a while of preparing, He Feng Yang opened his palm, taking out expand space Immortal Gu from his immortal aperture.

The Immortal Gu was covered in a yellow light, He Feng Yang patted it lightly.

The yellow light left his hands, breaking apart the soul taker battlefield and creating a hole.

He Feng Yang was overjoyed, he put back expand space Immortal Gu and the nine palace crane below his feet cried out, flapping its wings and bringing him out of soul taker battlefield.

Outside the battlefield, it was clear skies with no clouds.

"Oh no! He actually had expand space Immortal Gu, he's escaping!"

"He Feng Yang, don't run if you have the guts, let us battle for three hundred rounds!"

The shouts of the two Gu Immortals behind him had a tone of anxiety and panic.

He Feng Yang laughed heartily, his heart was filled with pride: "Even soul taker battlefield cannot contain me. No matter who you are, ambushing and attempting to kill me, I will remember this. Don't think I will not find out just because you hid your identity, you used your own killer moves. When I return to the sect, I will investigate, I will definitely find out who you really are! Eh? Oh no!"

Suddenly, He Feng Yang sensed something amiss, his expression changed.

He had always been a vigilant person and had great self control, how could his emotions become so overjoyed the moment he left the soul taker battlefield, like he had just won a battle?

This time, he failed to take back Hu Immortal blessed land, he had let down Lord Tiger Demon's nurturing and expectations, he should feel downcast instead.

"Oh no!" An intense warning of danger rose in his heart, He Feng Yang turned around, only to see a Gu Immortal as tiny as a little boy, his body covered in a dark light. He was holding a dagger shaped Gu worm, he was right behind He Feng Yang, less than a foot away.

A third Gu Immortal!

There was a third Gu Immortal in ambush!

This was their true killer move, a plot within a plot! While He Feng Yang's mind relaxed the moment he left the soul taker battlefield, the fatal strike was launched at him!

He Feng Yang was furious and shocked, his eyes were blood red and he was extremely angry, he did not retreat, instead, he had the urge to fight to the death with the enemy.

"Quickly dodge! The enemy is an emotion path Gu Immortal, they can interfere with your judgment by influencing your emotions!" Within his immortal aperture, Tiger Demon's anger will was shouting.

"Hehehe, it is too late." The third Gu Immortal raised their dagger, stabbing at He Feng Yang.

The dagger shaped Gu worm burst out with an intense Immortal Gu aura.

He Feng Yang was horror stricken and full of grievances.

The enemy had an attack type Immortal Gu?!

He only had an expand space Immortal Gu, it could not help him. The defensive mortal killer moves he had could not block this attack type Immortal Gu!

Chapter 704: Little Nine

The dagger shaped Immortal Gu was about to pierce into him; He Feng Yang felt anger, fear, bewilderment, unresignedness, all kinds of feelings seethed in him like lava, greatly influencing his actions.

"Am I going to die here today?" He Feng Yang involuntarily had this thought.

However, right at this dangerous moment, the desolate beast nine palace crane under his feet suddenly let out a clear cry before fiercely turning its body around.

He Feng Yang's body was thrown down while the nine palace crane blocked the ambushing Gu Immortal.

Plop.

A soft sound echoed, the dagger shaped Immortal Gu ruthlessly pierced into the nine palace crane's chest.

"Eh?" The third Gu Immortal showed a shocked expression.

He had thought disturbing He Feng Yang could influence the nine palace crane. After all, He Feng Yang was an enslavement path Gu Immortal and the nine palace crane had been enslaved by him. If he was influenced, the nine palace crane should also be nothing to worry about.

He activated several emotion path killer moves to heavily disturb He Feng Yang, but he had never expected that at the last juncture, this nine palace crane would actually move to protect its master.

"Little nine!" He Feng Yang saw the nine palace crane taking the fatal strike, tears immediately streamed down his eyes as he gave a pained roar.

He had raised this nine palace crane with great care and had never used any enslavement methods on it.

Back when he was young, he had been brutally chased when out on a mission. His life was hanging in the balance when he accidentally bumped into the similarly heavily injured nine palace crane.

After this coincidental and accidental meeting, he and the nine palace crane helped each other to escape the plight.

The nine palace crane was on the verge of death, He Feng Yang brought it back to the sect and used all of his wealth, barely managing to stabilize its life.

In the dozens of years afterwards, He Feng Yang braved many dangers to earn money to treat the nine palace crane little by little, slowly pulling it out from the brink of death.

A profound sentiment more intimate than brothers was established like this between a man and a crane.

Later an accident occurred, the rank five Gu Master He Feng Yang had failed his mission and was in a heavily injured state. The resources on him could only save one person. If he treated the nine palace crane, he would die, but if he saved himself, the nine palace crane would not be able to maintain its lingering vitality.

At the juncture of this choice, He Feng Yang thought for three days and three nights, in the end, he decided to sacrifice himself to save the nine palace crane!

This action caused third supreme elder, Lord Tiger Demon, to be moved, and with his help, both He Feng Yang and the nine palace crane were saved.

He Feng Yang lived up to his expectations and after becoming a Gu Immortal, he joined Lord Tiger Demon's faction.

The nine palace crane let out a mournful cry. Its enormous and slender body was covered with a layer of grey light. In this grey light, its body was rapidly shrinking and becoming younger, from a mature age it continuously turned to its youth, then to its infancy.

This was the power of the Immortal Gu!

The dagger shaped Immortal Gu was actually a time path Immortal Gu that could reverse the target's body to a younger state.

"Retreat. Don't let down your friend's kind intention." In his immortal aperture, Tiger Demon's anger will heaved a long sigh.

"Little nine!" He Feng Yang shouted furiously and went back regardless of the advice of Tiger Demon's anger will.

The hems of his gown fluttered and moved, turning into a crane feather cloak. A blood red glint blossomed in his eyes and his slender green brows moved nimbly like a snake or dragon.

The mysterious Gu Immortal showed a surprised expression.

He had not thought He Feng Yang who could have clearly escaped in the moment just before would actually return with killing intent.

He Feng Yang was an enslavement path Gu Immortal!

He Feng Yang pushed forward his palms from which jade green lightning rays surged out.

The mysterious Gu Immortal snorted, he raised the dagger and confronted it head-on, simultaneously activating emotion path killer moves to influence He Feng Yang's emotions.

However, He Feng Yang's heart was filled completely with anger and was unexpectedly not influenced.

Bam!

A loud explosion erupted and the mysterious Gu Immortal was thrown back. He Feng Yang's body trembled intensely and blood spurted out of his mouth, but he forcibly pulled himself together and pulled the infant nine palace crane into his hands.

"Little nine!" He Feng Yang held the nine palace crane in his embrace and turned around, escaping immediately with no intent to stay.

The nine palace crane had already become the size of a white goose and was softly twittering as He Feng Yang held it in his embrace.

The emotion path Gu Immortal had been sent some distance away, that gap was enough for him to be unable to chase He Feng Yang in this moment.

The other two mysterious Gu Immortals hurried over after canceling the soul taker battlefield.

"Sigh, he escaped in the end!" The wind path Gu Immortal heaved a long sigh in pity.

"This guy is clearly an enslavement path Gu Immortal but he is actually not weak in close combat. That green lightning killer move isn't what it appears to be, it makes me think of..." The emotion path Gu Immortal said.

"Hmph, if not for lacking time to gather more people, would we be afraid of not being able to put him down? How about we chase, maybe we can...." The poison path Gu Immortal was not resigned.

"He has expand space Immortal Gu, soul taker battlefield cannot trap him. Let's leave quickly, it is not convenient to stay here." The wind path Gu Immortal was calm.

"Right, this ambush was nothing more than a hastily considered course of action. We absolutely cannot lose sight of the main goal for small gains and risk exposing our identities, which would affect master's grand plan. We will retreat!" The emotion path Gu Immortal ceased his absent-mindedness, and said softly.

His position seemed to be higher than the other two Gu Immortals and his words had a tone of decisiveness.

"I shall take my leave." The wind path Gu Immortal rapidly flew in the air and soon was no more than a small black dot in the horizon.

"Hmph!" The poison path Gu Immortal dropped into the ground and escaped.

The emotion path Gu Immortal paused for a while until the other two had completely left, his body then disappeared in the air as if he had never been there.

He Feng Yang flew at top speed to Fei He mountain, and without stopping, he directly entered Fu Hu blessed land.

Lord Tiger Demon was standing beside an enormous stone pit, looking at the tens of thousands of rockmen working inside the pit.

"Junior was incompetent and let down Lord's expectations." He Feng Yang bowed in greeting to Lord Tiger Demon, his body filled with injuries and his expression one of shame.

"You got injured? First go take a rest and heal yourself." Lord Tiger Demon did not ask anything to He Feng Yang and only waved his hand, that anger will in He Feng Yang's immortal aperture flew out and entered his mind.

In just an instant, he understood all the things He Feng Yang had experienced in this trip.

His gaze flickered, shortly afterwards, he activated anger will Gu to produce anger will.

The anger will flew through the sky, out of Fu Hu blessed land and towards the peak of Fei He mountain. When it reached the conference hall at the mountain peak, three wills that were left here came after sensing it.

These three wills were respectively from first supreme elder, second supreme elder and the third supreme elder, Lord Tiger Demon, they were in charge of monitoring the sect and also handling some small matters.

The major matters were also arranged and at every set period of time, they would gather a group of Gu Immortals to hold a joint discussion on them.

Tiger Demon's anger will landed in the hall and fused with its previous will, then narrated the events that occurred to He Feng Yang.

The first and second supreme elders' wills sank into silence when they heard the narration. They started to rapidly think which caused their bodies to shrink at a visible speed.

When they had shrunken to almost half the previous size, second supreme elder's will said: "Let's allow Lord Tiger Demon to have the final decision on the matters of Hu Immortal blessed land."

First supreme elder's will spoke: "He Feng Yang was ambushed and almost killed, this is much more serious than Hu Immortal blessed land. Where was he ambushed?"

A Gu worm flew out from the hall and turned into a map made of light and shadow.

"Here." Lord Tiger Demon's anger will pointed at the location.

First supreme elder's will nodded and spoke heavily: "This location is a very good place to lay an ambush. There is no force situated both in front and behind, and this makes it a very good place of concealment. It seems the ambushers are very familiar with Central Continent's terrain."

"Investigate! When has there been anyone that had the guts to try to kill our ten great ancient sects' Gu Immortals?" Second supreme elder's will shouted in rage.

"My concern is this. Elders, where do you think these Gu Immortals came from?" Lord Tiger Demon's anger will asked.

First supreme elder's and second supreme elder's wills glanced at each other, both revealing heavy expressions.

"Third elder is worried these Gu Immortals are Central Continent Gu Immortals?" First supreme elder said quietly.

Tiger Demon's anger will spoke frankly with confidence: "Right. How long have our ten great ancient sects been in control of Central Continent? The situation has been getting increasingly harder over these recent years, why is that? Our Central Continent is different from the other four regions. Led by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, Central Continent had already been reformed during the Remote Antiquity Era, establishing the sect system. During the Remote Antiquity Era, sects had been rare. In Olden Antiquity Era, clan forces surpassed sect forces. In Medieval Antiquity Era, sects and clans clashed against each other, and advanced at an equal pace. In Late Antiquity Era, clans weakened while sects flourished. And now, sects stand in great numbers in Central Continent while there are almost no clans."

"The clan system only selects the clan's children as Gu Masters. The sect system, however, allows ordinary mortals to step on the path of Gu cultivation. Our Central Continent's history is filled with the conflicts between the two great systems. After going through over three million years of struggles, evolution and accumulation, the sect system has prevailed; the number of Central Continent Gu Immortals far surpass the other four regions and they continue to increase, and soon will leave the control of our ten great sects."

"How many Gu Immortals can our ten great sects recruit? The number of other Gu Immortals in Central Continent are several times our own! As these Gu Immortals of other sects, demonic path Gu Immortals and lone cultivator Gu Immortals continue to cultivate, they would require more cultivation resources. Conflicts are unavoidable because our ten great sects control eighty percent of cultivation resources in Central Continent."

"Have there not been cases like Great Heavenly Sword Sect before? It is just that they were secretly suppressed by our ten great ancient sects. But in these recent years, new sects are still emerging unendingly, new innovations and new schools of thought are common occurrences, uncommon geniuses and monstrous talents are constantly sprouting among the mortals while there are limited spots in our ten great ancient sects. Despite recruiting exceptional talents every year, Central Continent is truly too big."

Lord Tiger Demon's anger will sighed as he said this.

The two supreme elders were silent all along.

The ten great ancient sects held control of eighty percent of Central Continent's resources, but after the resources were split amongst everyone, how much would be left behind for individual Gu Immortals?

As a Gu Immortal's cultivation got higher, their blessed land would require more resources to manage. In particular, the heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities would also continue to become stronger, and after every tribulation, the losses would be very severe, and the price to repair it would continue to become higher.

It was impossible for the ten great ancient sects' Gu Immortals to share their resources to others.

In the past, although there were many sects outside of the ten great sects, there were not many Gu Immortals. Immortal and mortal were different concepts, there was a wide gap in the strength between mortals and immortals, thus mortals could be suppressed.

But at present, the Gu Immortals outside of the ten great sects were increasing constantly in numbers. Although these Gu Immortals usually had inferior battle strength, their vast numbers were enough to bring about an impact to the ten great ancient sects.

Great Heavenly Sword Sect was a good example. This large sized sect had two Gu Immortals originally and was a vassal of Immortal Crane Sect. Now, that they had a third Gu Immortal, they immediately planned to leave Immortal Crane Sect and be independent.

Chapter 705: Immortal Slaughtering Plan, Fang Yuan distributes benefits

Lord Tiger Demon's anger will continued: "These years, our ten great ancient sects have been in difficult circumstances, we could be said to be treading on thin ice. It is as if we are blocking the top of a volcano, the magma underneath will eventually burst out one day, causing a major impact to our ten great sects!"

"Third supreme elder is talking about the general situation in Central Continent right now. But this is the situation of the whole region, how can we change it?" Second supreme elder's will sighed.

Lord Tiger Demon's will continued: "Great Heavenly Sword Sect's example is in front of us. The Gu Immortals in Hu Immortal blessed land could be from other regions, but they are most likely to be an alliance of lone cultivators in our region. The ones who ambushed He Feng Yang today might also be Gu Immortals of our own region's forces. But if that is the case, it would be terrifying."

Second supreme elder nodded: "It is indeed like that. The force that attacked He Feng Yang obviously does not want Hu Immortal blessed land to continue being in the hands of Fang Yuan. If He Feng Yang dies, Immortal Crane Sect will have to attack Hu Immortal blessed land forcefully to defend our reputation. Even though it is obvious that they are framed, Immortal Crane Sect has no choice but to go along with it."

The ten great ancient sects' pride and reputation that had been defended for innumerable years cannot be tarnished. If they could not take revenge for the death of their own Gu Immortals, then their reputation would be ruined, the hearts of the people would waver, and everyone would be emboldened to offend Immortal Crane Sect. If Immortal Crane Sect is under such problems, they would not be able to manage their resources and land within Central Continent. By then, Immortal Crane Sect would be worn out physically and mentally, their exhaustion would attract even more greedy jackals and wolves.

This would be a vicious cycle, once they fall into it, it would be hard to recover.

Immortal Crane Sect's top three supreme elders were all experienced people, they were old monsters with bountiful life experience, they had considered this terrifying future prospect already.

Not just them, among the other nine great ancient sects of Central Continent, there were sure to be people who understood this.

Right now, Central Continent was becoming saturated with experts, but there were limited resources, it was like a powder keg that was expanding endlessly. The ten great ancient sects were sitting on top of the keg, if they were careless and ignited it, they might be blown to pieces.

"Tiger Demon, you used this topic today to start a long discussion, I'm sure you have some insights to share with us. Why not just tell us straight away." First supreme elder said.

Tiger Demon's anger will laughed, saying startling things: "My current idea is to agree with Fang Yuan's conditions and acknowledge that Hu Immortal blessed land is a subsidiary of our sect. At the same time, we will find out the true identities of the culprits who attacked He Feng Yang. Once we know which lone cultivators are ganging up, we will collaborate with the other nine sects and engage in a wide scale immortal slaughtering plan!"

"Immortal slaughtering?!" Second supreme elder heard this and excitement shined in his eyes.

First supreme elder's will shut his eyes, he slowly said: "Tiger Demon, I will not hide it from you. This suggestion of yours had been brought up by Combat Immortal Sect's Gu Immortal Shi Lei many years ago, he had even sent a proposal to Heavenly Court, requesting for Heavenly Court to come out and organize the ten great ancient sects, in order to execute this plan."

"Oh, that Immortal Monkey King? Even though our ten great ancient sects have had changes throughout history, the root of all these changes were righteous reasons, like the interchanging of main and side branches, these all have much to do with Heavenly Court. If the ten ancient sects engage in a slaughter of immortals, it would have huge implications and involve innumerable benefits. Only Heavenly Court can step in to convince and assemble everyone, leading us towards victory!" Tiger Demon's anger will agreed.

"But Heavenly Court rejected this proposal. They even warned us ten great ancient sects not to specially target the respective smaller sects and lone cultivator Gu Immortals, we are not to consciously massacre them, violators would be heavily punished." First supreme elder's will said.

"What?" Tiger Demon's anger will shouted in shock.

"This matter, how did I not know about it?" Second supreme elder muttered to himself.

First supreme elder sighed loudly, looking at the sky: "The will of Heavenly Court is heaven's will. Heaven's will cannot be defied, heaven's will cannot be anticipated."

...

He Feng Yang returned to Hu Immortal blessed land once again.

Fairy Cang Yu and Fang Yuan were walking on Dang Hun mountain, observing the growth of the guts Gu.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng looked from afar, staring at Fairy Cang Yu.

Meanwhile, that blue charm lightning shadow was encircled by the eight desolate beasts, once in a while, a different desolate beast would go up and fight it, they were taking turns to wear it down.

"Brother He was a bit slow." Fang Yuan saw He Feng Yang and smiled while saying plainly.

He Feng Yang and Fairy Cang Yu first looked at each other, seeing her nod and hint that she was unharmed, he turned to Fang Yuan: "My sect has already agreed to acknowledge your side as our sect's subsidiary. The relationship would have no time limit, and you can leave at any time. At the same time, we will engage in the trading of guts Gu, the price will be one immortal essence stone for a hundred and twenty guts Gu. This is the rank six Immortal Gu, Promise."

Immortal Gu Promise was an information path Gu worm, its use was similar to mountain pledge Gu and sea oath Gu.

Immediately, He Feng Yang activated the Immortal Gu to make a promise.

When it was Fang Yuan's turn, he received the Immortal Gu and checked that there were no issues, he consumed his green grape immortal essence and made a promise as well.

Their promises created material forms that resembled lumps of gold, the two sides exchanged with each other to keep a copy each.

Fairy Cang Yu finally breathed out a sigh of relief, now that the transaction had been established, she was finally safe.

Fang Yuan breathed out in relief too, the situation that he had been trying to resolve had finally reached this stage. Fighting to the death with Immortal Crane Sect was definitely impossible. Immortal Crane Sect was a huge organization, if he angered them, Hu Immortal blessed land would certainly be lost. With Fang Yuan's finances, he could not sustain a huge battle against Gu Immortal level opponents.

But He Feng Yang's words quickly earned his attention: "On the way back, I was ambushed by three Gu Immortals and my life was almost lost. The other party evidently wants to frame you, our sect is investigating it now, I wonder if your force had offended anyone?"

"What? In Central Continent, there were actually Gu Immortals who dared to kill a Gu Immortal from the ten great sects?" Fang Yuan did not conceal his shock.

He remembered clearly that such situations would only happen a while after the five regions chaotic war started.

By then, the five regions would be in chaos, mortals would face difficulties living and battles would be unceasing.

Even the authority of Heavenly Court was useless, the ten great sects' Gu Immortals all faced assassinations, there were those who were taking revenge from the other four regions, but also Central Continent's own lone cultivator Gu Immortals who were trying to fish for benefits.

As the situation became more and more chaotic, Fang Yuan could even bring a band of demonic path Gu Immortals to attack Hu Immortal blessed land on Tian Ti mountain, killing Feng Jin Huang eventually.

Unknowingly, Fang Yuan thought about the mysterious force that plotted against him secretly in treasure yellow heaven over a year ago.

But he did not even know what this force was called, even if he knew, he would not expose such information to He Feng Yang.

Thus, he shook his head: "I have been in Hu Immortal blessed land for this period of time, how could I offend other forces? I have no intentions to offend brother He, but thinking about it, Immortal Crane Sect probably attracts more enemies than me, was it a force trying to plot against your sect, but wanting to use me as a diversion instead?"

He Feng Yang did not get the information he wanted, he was a little disappointed but he could not force Fang Yuan.

Immortal Crane Sect had their own worries, even though Fang Yuan was only an immortal zombie, the force behind him allowed the two sides to speak on equal terms.

He Feng Yang and Fairy Cang Yu did not stay any longer, Fang Yuan opened Hu Immortal blessed land's door and sent them out.

Fang Yuan stood at the door, saying goodbye to them.

The other nine sects who saw this immediately realized that something had occurred in Hu Immortal blessed land.

"What is going on? Why is there an immortal zombie?"

"He Feng Yang and Fairy Cang Yu came with great confidence, but now their expression are not quite right, it seems a problem occurred!"

"Did they fail to take it down? That's impossible, right."

The Gu Immortals were confused, they were guessing randomly.

The ten great ancient sects were in cahoots, they were the overlords of Central Continent, over these last years there was unavoidably no lack of hidden competition among themselves. The contest of Hu Immortal blessed land was at first an open competition, using disciples from each sect to decide the eventual owner, but the result was that Fang Yuan actually took advantage. Now, it was a hidden contest, they could not question Immortal Crane Sect in public, that would break the unspoken rules.

The Gu Immortals did not know what happened to Hu Immortal blessed land, they were hesitant to return.

Fang Yuan closed the door, as Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan came to congratulate him with smiles on their faces.

"Fang Yuan, you have caused me to look at you in a different light. This time, the collaboration between you and Immortal Crane Sect succeeded without any battle, it was truly a great victory." Fairy Li Shan was full of praise.

This was the type of victory that Gu Immortals loved the most.

Without any battles, without any huge investments, but the rewards were simply incredible.

"Senior is not entirely correct." Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "It is not me who is collaborating with Immortal Crane Sect, it is us. After all, to refine the airsac Gu, we will need Hei Lou Lan's strength qi Gu to muster the strength qi. As for the profits of the guts Gu, your side will take forty percent, my side will take sixty."

Fairy Li Shan heard this and the smile on her face intensified. As long as one was not a fool, they could see the prospects of the transaction of guts Gu.

She understood clearly that Fang Yuan's action was to stabilize their alliance completely, to bind them to Dang Hun mountain itself. In the future, when Hu Immortal blessed land is attacked, they would need to come and defend it too.

But with such great benefits, Fairy Li Shan could not help but be moved.

Hei Lou Lan looked at Fang Yuan deeply: "To think that you had this method, Fang Yuan, conceptualizing the airsac Gu. To refine the rank three airsac Gu, you need to use the rank six strength qi Gu. This Gu is truly very special."

A part of this was definitely due to wisdom Gu's credit.

After obtaining wisdom Gu, Fang Yuan had been conceptualizing, to see if there was a way to extract guts Gu under the help of unlimited inspiration.

The success this time was also because he had unexpectedly heard from Tai Bai Yun Sheng that Hei Lou Lan had the strength qi Immortal Gu.

Only an immortal class strength could envelop the guts Gu, allowing it to leave Dang Hun mountain unscathed.

Fang Yuan changed the topic: "To produce guts Gu, we will need huge amounts of souls, I will have to trouble the two of you."

"Northern Plains is a land of battles, chaotic wars happen all the time, and beast groups and tribes relocate constantly. There are surely many souls that can be collected there. We will go and settle this now." Hei Lou Lan wanted to act immediately.

After she ascended to an immortal, her need for resources had become much greater, especially in terms of immortal essence stones, she could not always rely on Fairy Li Shan.

Relying on others was not Hei Lou Lan's style.

Fairy Li Shan agreed: "That's right, Dang Hun mountain does not have any requirements for the type of soul. We can even buy them from Northern Plains Zombie Alliance, it will be more expensive than collecting the souls ourselves, but the price would be acceptable and we can save lots of trouble."

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan waved a hand: "Please hold on for a moment, don't be too anxious now. Now, come with me to suppress a Gu Immortal. This Gu Immortal is inside Hu Immortal blessed land right now."

"Oh? Who?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng questioned.

"There are other Gu Immortals hiding in the blessed land now? Is it an ambush by Immortal Crane Sect, having ulterior motives?" Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan looked at each other with confused and shocked expressions.

Chapter 706: Extorting an Immortal Gu Remnant Recipe

Fang Yuan smiled mysteriously: "This immortal is right under our noses, please follow me."

Under Fang Yuan's lead, everyone came before the blue charm lightning shadow.

The blue charm lightning shadow right now was fighting in the air with the iron crown eagle, its small blue figure was colliding with the desolate beast iron crown eagle's huge body, fighting evenly back and forth.

Hei Lou Lan was even more uncertain now: "The Gu Immortal you are talking about is the blue charm lightning shadow?"

Fang Yuan smiled and did not respond.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's eyes shone with brilliance: "Now that you've mentioned it, this blue charm lightning shadow is acting really strangely."

"That's right." Fairy Li Shan showed a wary and vigilant expression: "Logically speaking, the blue charm lightning shadow was formed from an earthly calamity, its main target would be the owner of Hu Immortal blessed land, which is you, Fang Yuan. But it has been engaging with these desolate beasts all this time, it had no intentions to attack you."

Hei Lou Lan continued: "No wonder I felt that it was strange, when the desolate beast appeared, this blue charm lightning shadow seemed to have been shocked, it stopped growling and started to conceal its presence. This blue charm lightning shadow is weird, I'm sure it is not normal!"

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan laughed heartily, saying: "The blue charm lightning shadow in the past had no issues, but after it was sent out of the blessed land by me, it was captured by a lightning path Gu Immortal, and was refined into some sort of puppet killer move. When Immortal Crane Sect came to attack my blessed land, this Gu Immortal manipulated the blue charm lightning shadow into barging in, his objective was to fish for benefits. If Immortal Crane Sect failed, he could show up as a representative of his sect, and strike first. I wonder if my analysis is correct, Myriad Dragon Dock's Vicious Lightning Fiend?"

"How did you know that I am Vicious Lightning Fiend?!" The blue charm lightning shadow could not put up a facade any longer, he ignored the iron crown eagle and flew to Fang Yuan.

The iron crown eagle chased it, but Fang Yuan waved a hand, the eagle screeched and flew away.

"Myriad Dragon Dock's Vicious Lightning Fiend?" Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan looked at each other, they knew about Myriad Dragon Dock, it was one of the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent, just like Immortal Crane Sect. But who Vicious Lightning Fiend was, they did not have much of an idea.

Only Tai Bai Yun Sheng's eyes shone brightly, after coming to Hu Immortal blessed land, he had collected a lot of information upon Fang Yuan's advice, he knew a lot of intelligence about Central Continent's Gu Immortals.

"Vicious Lightning Fiend is a rank six Gu Immortal, he has passed two heavenly tribulations and had an amazing history of ending in a draw after fighting with a rank seven Gu Immortal. But many years ago, he had entered closed cultivation. There had been no traces of him these last few years in Central Continent." Tai Bai Yun Sheng introduced.

"A draw with a rank seven Gu Immortal?" Fairy Li Shan's gaze shone.

Hei Lou Lan had a proud and arrogant demeanor as she snorted coldly.

The blue charm lightning shadow looked at everyone, but eventually his gaze locked onto Fang Yuan: "Who are you guys? My immortal killer move was the fruit of my many years of closed cultivation, after thinking of how to raise my battle strength. A year ago, I learned that there was a blue charm lightning shadow on Tian Ti mountain, it was lurking around there and did not want to leave, thus I struck secretly and captured the blue charm lightning shadow. A few months ago, I perfected my immortal killer move, making this blue charm lightning shadow my puppet. I have only told this secret to a few people. You guys actually know about this in detail! Tell me, who in the world are you?"

Fang Yuan snorted, he said very unkindly: "Vicious Lightning Fiend, you might have a fierce reputation, but we are not afraid of you. You made the blue charm lightning shadow into your puppet, I'm sure you paid a heavy price for that. I am in a bad mood, you should be careful, otherwise if I get angry, I will kill this blue charm lightning shadow right here, can you stop me?"

The blue charm lightning shadow shouted out angrily, he showed his irascible nature: "You dare! I am a Gu Immortal of Myriad Dragon Dock! Don't think you can continue to be arrogant, it is only temporarily that you are occupying Hu Immortal blessed land, once your identities are exposed, we, the ten great ancient sects, will make sure all of you lone cultivators and demonic cultivators are done for."

"Oh? Is that so..." Fang Yuan's eyes shone with brilliance: "You saw our earlier transaction clearly, we are already a subsidiary of Immortal Crane Sect, we have both made a promise, even if Myriad Dragon Dock wants to deal with us, you will need to get past Immortal Crane Sect first. That's right, that's right, earlier, Immortal Crane Sect's He Feng Yang was attacked, the mastermind was you, or rather, Myriad Dragon Dock. right?"

"Bullshit! We of the ten great ancient sects are on the same side, even if we compete with each other both openly and secretly, how could we do things without limits like you lone cultivators with demonic natures?" The blue charm lightning shadow was furious.

Fang Yuan did not speak, he glanced over at Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan was a formidable character just like him, they cooperated flawlessly, she pretended to jump to a realization, saying: "Fang Yuan, you are absolutely right. Hu Immortal blessed land, Dang Hun mountain, and guts Gu are extremely huge benefits. After assassinating He Feng Yang, Immortal Crane Sect will come to attack us. By then, when we both suffer great losses, Myriad Dragon Dock will be able to take advantage of the situation."

"You're bullshitting! Bullshit! How can I be such a petty person!!" The blue charm lightning shadow's anger was through the roof, he shouted unceasingly.

Hei Lou Lan laughed sinisterly: "But the timing in which you appeared was simply too coincidental. When He Feng Yang attacked Hu Immortal blessed land, all the events that happened in here, how could the outside world know? Why did He Feng Yang encounter an assassination the moment he left Hu Immortal blessed land? Obviously, you were an insider and used some special method to inform your main body, who then organized the ambush."

Hei Lou Lan fully expressed her twisted logic, her words shocked the blue charm lightning shadow.

But immediately after, he reacted, turning angry from shame, rebuking: "Hu Immortal blessed land is a separate piece of heaven and earth, unless I have an immortal killer move, how could I communicate with my main body? But if I use an immortal killer move, such intense immortal aura would be detected by you guys, isn't that right?"

"But there was a moment when Hu Immortal blessed land opened its doors, that way, we were connected to the outside world. You communicated with your main body at that very point in time." Hei Lou Lan immediately retorted.

"Scumbag! Bullshit! I am honorable and righteous, how can I be like that? No, no, I was almost tricked by you. How can He Feng Yang's ambush have anything to do with my blue charm lightning shadow sending out information? Even if the other party did not know what happened in Hu Immortal blessed land, they can still ambush He Feng Yang. There is no relationship between the two issues!" The blue charm lightning shadow screamed.

Hei Lou Lan said eerily: "Whether a relationship exists, we do not care about that. We will tell this to Immortal Crane Sect, you can explain things to them yourself."

"Go ahead and tell them. I have not done any of the things you've said, why would I be afraid of slander?" The blue charm lightning shadow tried to put up a front.

At this time, Tai Bai Yun Sheng said: "Oh! I remember now, recently in Immortal Crane Sect's region of control, wasn't there the matter of Great Heavenly Sword Sect trying to gain independence? There had been rumors that the matter of Great Heavenly Sword Sect was instigated by Myriad Dragon Dock. Hehe, I get it. After killing He Feng Yang, Immortal Crane Sect's main forces will come and attack our blessed land. In that case, it will be even easier for Great Heavenly Sword Sect to detach from Immortal Crane Sect. After Great Heavenly Sword Sect joins Myriad Dragon Dock, and become your subsidiary, Immortal Crane Sect's territory at the northwest area will be devoured by Myriad Dragon Dock. By then, even if they taken down Hu Immortal blessed land, they will suffer a huge loss in battle strength, if they return and want to settle the matter with Myriad Dragon Dock, it would be too late, and they would not have the strength to do so."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's words not only shocked the blue charm lightning shadow, even Fang Yuan was looking at him in surprise.

Although Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a good person and had been kind in his life, he was old and experienced, his words were like a dagger stabbing into the heart of the matter, he directly pointed out Vicious Lightning Fiend's weakness.

The blue charm lightning shadow finally became quiet.

After a dozen breaths of time, he said: "Damn, you bunch of scheming scoundrels, you are simply twisting logic as you like, you're making things up! Say it, what is the condition for letting go of my lightning shadow puppet?"

Hei Lou Lan and Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not speak, they looked at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan laughed lightly, saying a ridiculous condition: "Vicious Lightning Fiend, I am very interested in this immortal killer move that can turn the blue charm lightning shadow into a puppet. Why don't you teach me."

"Screw you! This is a trump card that I finally came up with after four years of closed cultivation! With just a few words from you, you want to take the fruits of my labor, it will only happen in your dreams! Even if this puppet is destroyed, I will not give it to you!!" The blue charm lightning shadow shouted in anger, categorically rejecting this.

But Fang Yuan had his previous life's memories, he was carrying out a plan based on them and knew about Vicious Lightning Fiend's bottom line.

He chuckled as he said slowly: "Vicious Lightning Fiend, your immortal killer move was only created in a rush, the success rate is definitely not high. The blue charm lightning shadow has rank six battle strength, isn't it such a waste to discard it here? How about this, I will take a step back, I do not want your immortal killer move, I want the Blood Deity remnant recipe that you have."

The blue charm lightning shadow's expression was grim: "How did you know that I have Blood Deity's remnant recipe? There are only a small number of Gu Immortals in Myriad Dragon Dock that know about this secret!"

"Hmph, frog in the well, there are no impenetrable walls in this world, even if very few people know, can't I have Gu worms to deduce it?" Fang Yuan showed a disposition of unfathomable depth.

"Good, very good. I am even more curious about your true identities now. Hmph, I will admit a loss this time!" The blue charm lightning shadow agreed as he gritted his teeth.

"Let's trade using treasure yellow heaven." Fang Yuan said.

"No way, treasure yellow heaven will expose the blue charm lightning shadow puppet, it will expose my immortal killer move in advance!" The blue charm lightning shadow rejected immediately.

Fang Yuan laughed coldly: "Vicious Lightning Fiend, don't think I am unaware, after coming out of closed cultivation, you plan to imitate Sword Immortal Bo Qing, to challenge experts from all over the region, and use your power to contest for the title of the strongest. Your first target must be Bee Immortal Liao Mao."

"You sure know a lot!" The blue charm lightning shadow's tone was cold, but his heart was jumping.

The other party's grasp on information was far too detailed, he was in a very passive spot.

Fang Yuan ordered Little Hu Immortal to act, using connecting heaven Gu to connect to treasure yellow heaven, before finding Vicious Lightning Fiend's main body.

After the two negotiated, Fang Yuan sent the blue charm lightning shadow as merchandise and sent it over.

Immediately, the treasure light burst into the sky, attracting countless divine senses.

Vicious Lightning Fiend quickly took out Blood Deity's Immortal Gu remnant recipe, who knew how many Gu Immortals cried out in alarm at this.

"Scoundrel, quickly settle the deal!" Vicious Lightning Fiend's divine sense screamed.

"Vicious Lightning Fiend, you are not being genuine. The Blood Deity remnant recipe you have is seventy percent complete, you are trying to scam my ignorance, only taking out a forty percent remnant recipe?" Fang Yuan said slowly.

Vicious Lightning Fiend was shocked: "How can I have a seventy percent Blood Deity remnant recipe!"

"I am in no rush, the longer the blue charm lightning shadow is exposed, the more people will know." Fang Yuan said casually.

Vicious Lightning Fiend almost spat blood from anger: "Lad, don't think that with a wisdom path Gu Immortal behind you deducing things, you can act so arrogantly!! I will remember you, just you wait!!"

Saying this, he finally tossed out a seventy percent Blood Deity remnant recipe.

"An Immortal Gu remnant recipe with such a high completion rate appeared!"

"Since when did blue charm lightning shadow become a commodity?"

Some Gu Immortals fortunate enough to witness the transaction went into deep shock.

Fang Yuan did not make things difficult for Vicious Lightning Fiend this time, they swiftly ended the deal.

Under the gazes of Hei Lou Lan and the others, Fang Yuan took the Immortal Gu remnant recipe, exclaiming in his heart: "I obtained this so easily, something that I had been unable to get my hands on in my previous life no matter what. A seventy percent blood deity Immortal Gu remnant recipe, together with my previous life's accumulations, and with wisdom Gu's power, I should be able to complete the blood deity Immortal Gu recipe."

Next, he thought about Vicious Lightning Fiend.

This person had an fierce, ruthless, and fiery personality, in his previous life, he attained rank seven and had incredible battle strength. During the five regions chaotic war, he used the immortal killer move Lightning Deity, to accumulate eight rank six battle strength beings that were similar to the blue charm lightning shadow. After Feng Jiu Ge died, he contested for the prized status of being the number one in battle strength among rank seven, he fought with Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei for three days and three nights but unfortunately lost.

In his previous life, Fang Yuan had most wanted to refine the Immortal Gu Blood Deity. He had once targeted the Immortal Gu remnant recipe in Vicious Lightning Fiend's possession, but his plot failed and he escaped after being heavily injured.

To think that in this life, he could obtain what he had always wanted in his previous life in such a manner.

Chapter 707: Overwhelming Profits!

In central continent time, three days after extorting Vicious Lightning Fiend, Immortal Crane Sect announced to the world: They recognized Fang Yuan as the owner of Hu Immortal blessed land, Hu Immortal blessed land was now a subsidiary force of Immortal Crane Sect, and could leave at any time.

This shocking news was like a large rock being thrown into a lake, causing many surging waves and splashes.

At once, the world of Central Continent's Gu Immortals was in a commotion!

Earlier, Immortal Crane Sect had declared publicly that Fang Yuan was a traitor of the sect, and would receive judgment soon. Such matters were common in Central Continent. Many Gu Masters, after obtaining benefits, would not want to share it with their sect, or they might be recruited by other sects, and so on, such reasons caused them to betray their original sect.

The cohesion of members under the sect system was weaker compared to the clan and tribe system that united people from the same bloodline together.

Among sects, the ten great ancient sects had the highest cohesion. But there were still traitors that appeared in these ancient sects.

In the past, First Gen Gu Yue obtained a blood path true inheritance and betrayed Immortal Crane Sect, going to Southern Border and hiding his name and identity.

These recent years, Myriad Dragon Dock's former disciple Song Zi Xing had also betrayed his sect. After growing from battles, he was now a rank seven Gu Immortal, known as the Blood Dragon, he was a famous demonic path expert in Central Continent.

Thus, when Fang Yuan as a rank five Gu Master had betrayed Immortal Crane Sect, it was only news of mild magnitude.

But now, Immortal Crane Sect had gathered up its forces and gone to pass judgment on Fang Yuan, the result was nothing anyone could have expected.

In this time, who knew how many people thought that Fang Yuan was courting death, their eyes were popping out of their sockets when they learned about the news.

After that, even more inside information was released, from Immortal Crane Sect, Vicious Lightning Fiend, and Fang Yuan.

There were many rumors, like the strength of Dang Hun mountain and Hu Immortal blessed land, the rise of a mysterious force, Vicious Lightning Fiend's immortal killer move, all these attracted people's attentions. Among them, the biggest highlight was the transaction of guts Gu.

Guts Gu could leave Dang Hun mountain and be stored, thus they could be traded! There were such great profits implied by this information, all the different forces were moved.

The Gu Immortals finally understood why Immortal Crane Sect made such a declaration, it was the motivation of profits!

For guts Gu, forsaking some hollow reputation was nothing. Furthermore, Fang Yuan acknowledged that his force was a subsidiary of Immortal Crane Sect, this was giving face to the ancient sects.

The other nine great ancient sects called Immortal Crane Sect shameless on one hand, while interacting with Hu Immortal blessed land on the other.

Fang Yuan's guts Gu had yet to begin being traded, but he had already received a large number of letter Gu, and they were still coming.

Regardless of whether it was a large or small force, Fang Yuan replied to them all. This was to establish the first contact between them.

Using this as an opportunity, Fang Yuan finally entered the limelight of Central Continent, with the status of an immortal zombie and the owner of Hu Immortal blessed land, he entered the eyes of all the Gu Immortals and the different forces.

A few days later, Hei Lou Lan brought in the first batch of souls, there were hundreds of thousands of them.

Of course, most of them were souls of wild beasts.

Fang Yuan placed them all into Dang Hun mountain, and Hu Immortal land spirit started to release Dang Hun mountain's power, vibrating and turning these souls into fragments, as these soul fragments were scattered on the surface of Dang Hun mountain, they gradually formed into guts Gu.

As the guts Gu grew here, Fang Yuan started to make his preparations elsewhere.

He ordered all of his hairy men to start creating the foundational Gu worms.

After seven days and seven nights, working in three shifts, they had finally produced a large number of Gu worms.

He next ordered the rockmen to start building a stone nest.

Half a month later, the first batch of souls were all used up, as a large number of guts Gu were formed on Dang Hun mountain.

Hei Lou Lan brought the second batch of souls into Hu Immortal blessed land.

Fang Yuan brought her to the stone nest near Dang Hun mountain.

Hei Lou Lan stood at the edge of the stone nest, seeing the huge structure below her, she was very shocked at Fang Yuan's huge investment.

This stone nest was tens of acres in area, and it was hundreds of meters deep into the ground.

At the outer ring of the stone nest, it was a huge sinkhole, dug manually, vertically up and down. The circular sinkhole was one li in radius, at least three li deep, like the frame of a tall piece of glassware.

At the center of the sinkhole, there was a huge stone pillar.

The stone pillar was over three hundred meters in radius, this length was slightly more than half of one li, thus, the stone pillar and the circular sinkhole did not touch, they were at least a hundred and fifty meters apart, and there was an empty space left purposely.

The stone pillar was like an ant hill, it was complex inside but could reach anywhere as long as one knew the directions.

Be it the outer wall of the stone pillar, or the inner area of the circular sinkhole, there were countless rooms dug out. In each room, there was an elderly hairy man, and they had the basic Gu refinement materials and tools they needed.

"Fairy Lou Lan, please." Fang Yuan brought Hei Lou Lan to the top of the stone pillar, at the center-most spot.

Hei Lou Lan used her investigative Gu non-stop, realizing that this stone pillar and the sinkhole around the stone pillar had countless Gu worms around them at set intervals.

These arrangements had many complicated smaller details, Hei Lou Lan was going dizzy from seeing them, but what she knew was that these arrangements were not randomly set up, they were linked to each other and formed a great influence as a whole, it was set up with deep intentions.

"Don't tell me..." Hei Lou Lan was guessing in her heart, when Fang Yuan said: "Fairy, I am already done preparing, you can use the strength qi Immortal Gu now."

"Oh? Please teach me."

"Fairy only needs to activate strength qi Immortal Gu, and let the strength qi spread out naturally." Fang Yuan explained.

Hei Lou Lan followed his instructions, a powerful strength qi formed air currents and spread out everywhere. As the strength qi got thicker, they formed into a fog-like state, as they slowly spread and covered the entire stone nest.

In the stone nest, countless mortal Gu were activated, shining with all sorts of dazzling lights, like the stars in the night sky.

Under the combined force of these Gu worms, the vast strength qi was slowly extracted strand by strand, in a few breaths of time, all of the strength qi was in between the stone pillar and the sinkhole.

After a dozen breaths of time, these strength qi continued to move about, forming into the shape of a tornado, spinning around the stone pillar.

"Start the Gu refinement." Fang Yuan instructed, as the hairy men in the rooms prepared themselves, they opened their eyes and started to refine Gu.

Whenever they needed strength qi as a Gu refinement material, the turbulent strength qi outside the room would enter it automatically.

Such a scene was praised by Hei Lou Lan in amazement: "Fang Yuan, your stone nest is so grand and huge, it can accommodate thousands of hairy men refining Gu at the same time, this is truly an innovative and incredible idea."

Fang Yuan laughed: "Didn't I tell you I am also a refinement master?"

In truth, this stone nest was invented during the five regions chaotic war in his previous life.

Because of the unceasing battles that occurred at both large and small scale, Gu Masters would expend a lot of their Gu worms, all of the forces needed to replenish their Gu worms. Thus, they gradually researched and came up with such a stone nest that could accommodate so many Gu Masters, a structure that can allow mass refinement of Gu.

"I will name this the Fang Yuan stone nest, it is a place specially used to mass produce mortal Gu. I split the refinement process of the airsac Gu into over a dozen steps. When the hairy men at the highest level finish the first step, they will pass the partly-done product to the next floor's rooms. After the next floor finishes their refinement, they will send the partly-done product to the next floor. This way, each of the hairy men would be specialized in one step, not only would this prevent my Gu recipe from leaking, they can also get more familiar with their own steps and increase the success rate."

Fang Yuan shamelessly took the invention of someone in his previous life for his own.

Hei Lou Lan could not help but praise again: "This is indeed the right method to mass produce mortal Gu, in a certain aspect, it can even reduce the required proficiency of the Gu refiners themselves, because they only need to finish one step of the entire refinement process. But you, Fang Yuan, would be able to free yourself from the complication of dealing with all the many small steps, only having to control the materials."

"There are some Gu recipes that need the Gu refiner to refine it non-stop. Thankfully, airsac Gu is not like that." Fang Yuan said.

Hei Lou Lan nodded: "I was worried that the number of airsac Gu would be too little, and that would affect the sale of guts Gu. After all, each airsac Gu can only hold one guts Gu. But now that I've seen this stone nest for myself, I can feel assured. How are you intending to sell these guts Gu?"

Fang Yuan had a plan already: "Most of the sales will be towards the ten great ancient sects of Central Continent. I have already established a connection via hole earth Gu with the ten great sects. From now on, we will trade using these hole earth Gu, the remaining guts Gu will be sold in treasure yellow heaven."

"Aren't you going to sell some to the other sects in central continent specifically?"

"No. Right now, the ten great sects are the leaders of Central Continent, our identities and statuses are already very sensitive, we do not need to test the limits of the ancient sects. Our current peace was not obtained easily, we should quietly wait and reap our profits."

Hei Lou Lan heard this and nodded, she was completely at ease now.

Time passed by quickly, another half a month passed in Hu Immortal blessed land.

The first batch of guts Gu had already been sold, after accounting for the costs, as well as Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan's forty percent cut, Fang Yuan earned forty-three immortal essence stones.

A month later in Hu Immortal blessed land's time, the second batch of guts Gu was sold, and Fang Yuan's immortal essence stone stockpile increased by another forty-six pieces.

The third batch of guts Gu earned him forty-seven pieces.

The market reception was great, the ten great ancient sects' demand was increasing, and sales in treasure yellow heaven were extremely heated, usually in just one to two days, they would all be sold.

Guts Gu was after all a treasure that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable recommended, the efficiency of strengthening the soul was very high, at least ten times as efficient as ordinary methods.

In truth, not only did soul path Gu Masters need it, enslavement path, refinement path and other related paths also needed a foundation in their soul.

When a Gu Master ascends to Gu Immortal, the soul was also an important element for the thickness of the human qi, nobody would resent their soul for being strong.

Fang Yuan started to feel the benefits of having a monopolized market.

He could control the market, and control the situation. He could sell to anyone he wanted to, and he could sell at any quantity he set.

But he did not raise prices randomly, because guts Gu were not the only way to strengthen souls, if the price was too high, people would just use their original methods instead. That would instead, cause Fang Yuan's profits to fall.

After three batches of guts Gu were sold, Fang Yuan had over a hundred immortal essence stones. He started to purchase hairy men in bulk, creating more rooms in the stone nest and expanding his scale of production.

The more hairy men he had, the higher the efficiency of refining Gu, this caused the profits that Fang Yuan gained from each batch of guts Gu sold to be higher as well.

After five months in Hu Immortal blessed land's time, his earnings finally stabilized, each batch of guts Gu would earn him forty-eight immortal essence stones in total profit.

This was genuinely an overwhelming profit!

The scariest thing was, guts Gu were consumable Gu, they were gone after one use. The market demand for them would never dwindle.

Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan started to feel that they were a burden.

Because their job was to collect souls.

But now, the quantity of the souls gathered to use for Dang Hun mountain gradually became the biggest restriction in the sale of guts Gu.

Chapter 708: Returning the Eight Desolate Beasts

Northern Plains, Lang Ya blessed land.

Boom boom boom...

The huge ice spike divine ape caused tremors with every step it took.

Walking towards the cloud building, it stopped and raised its head to growl, the sound waves traveled far,causing the clouds to shake.

Fang Yuan was standing far away with Lang Ya land spirit, they were conversing but they turned around to look after hearing the noise.

"This little monkey!" Lang Ya land spirit stretched out his left arm, stroking his mustache as he laughed.

He was sealed by a qi path killer move, the fifteen layers had been reduced to six layers, all thanks to the help of the Inkman King.

Thus, Lang Ya land spirit's left arm was free to move now, only his right arm was left immobile.

Fang Yuan smiled, as he saw the cloud building rise up slowly, exposing a cave made of cloud soil underneath. The cloud fog was misty, covering the ice spike divine ape completely. The ice spike divine ape stepped into the hole and its tall figure gradually vanished from Fang Yuan's vision.

Finally, the cloud building gradually descended, and resealed the cave. The Gu worms in the cave were activated, causing the ice spike divine ape to go into hibernation.

Not far away, the same sight was happening with other cloud buildings.

Except that the ones entering the caves were not the ice spike divine ape, but the phoenix feather lava crocodile, golden sand dark stallion and the other desolate beasts.

"Ice spike divine ape, phoenix feather lava crocodile, golden sand dark stallion, azure dragon vine, swamp crab, peach wolf, iron crown eagle and earth chief desolate beast, I have returned to you the eight desolate beasts that you lent me without a single scratch. Actually, letting them out to roam once in a while is a good thing. Letting them sleep all the time, although it saves food, it will affect their battle strength." Fang Yuan said.

Lang Ya land spirit rolled his eyes: "Rascal, do you think I cannot understand what you are trying to imply? You want to borrow my desolate beasts again to fight for you, right? Hmph, these desolate beasts were captured with much difficulty, they are an important line of defense for Lang Ya blessed land. If you want to borrow them again, you cannot bring all eight at once!"

Fang Yuan laughed nonchalantly, stretching out his arm: "Alright, I returned to you your desolate beasts, according to our agreement, you should return the two great Immortal Gu, Man as Before and Landscape as Before, to me now."

Lang Ya land spirit heard this and his aura diminished, he smiled sheepishly: "Well... Little Fang, no, brother Fang, Man as Before and Landscape as Before are two incredible Immortal Gu, I have not finished researching them yet, can you give me a few more days?"

Fang Yuan's expression turned stiff: "Don't even think about it, hand them over!"

"Little brother Fang, no, big brother fang, you cannot be so ruthless. You know that I am current sealed by the qi path move, I cannot display my true strength as an expert, there's no way my research can have progress. This deal was very disadvantageous to me!" Lang Ya land spirit shouted.

"This transaction was willingly done by the two of us, I did not force you. It is your problem that you made a loss, you want to regret it now? Too late! Quickly hand it over, don't forget that we used mountain pledge Gu to make the vow, this also involves your friend Mo Tan Sang, whoever breaks the vow would have to pay with his life." Fang Yuan snickered continuously.

"Oh land spirit, return him the Immortal Gu." Mo Tan Sang quickly hurried over, staring at Lang Ya land spirit worriedly.

Lang Ya land spirit looked at Mo Tan Sang, he could not stand his gaze and stomped his foot, handing over Man as Before and Landscape as Before, these two Immortal Gu, over to Fang Yuan with much reluctance.

"Damn brat, you always take advantage of me in the end. Take it, take it, you scheming fellow!" Lang Ya land spirit continued to grumble.

Fang Yuan snorted disgruntedly: "I took advantage? What advantage did I take? I fed all eight of your desolate beasts till they were full, while no battles actually took place, it was like taking a walk with them. I saved some costs for you, nor am I even asking you to settle the score."

"Score, what score? Didn't I feed your rising azure cloud Immortal Gu as well, in order to buy the food, I spent a lot of immortal essence stones too, if you want to calculate all of this, let's count properly and see who paid a higher price!" Lang Ya land spirit was stomping his foot in agitation, he rebuked immediately.

The feeding of desolate beasts was naturally much simpler and cheaper than feeding Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan could not argue with Lang Ya land spirit over this, but he had control of Lang Ya land spirit's weakness, thus he could speak in a confident tone, he laughed coldly: "Lang Ya land spirit, do you still want to research Man as Before and Landscape as Before? Do you?"

Lang Ya land spirit's expression changed, he smiled amicably: "Yes, I want to even in my dreams."

"Then good." Fang Yuan patted Lang Ya land spirit's head: "Is there a point in being calculative, it was your fault for keeping my rising azure cloud Immortal Gu as collateral, right?"

"Get lost!" Lang Ya land spirit was so angry that he shrugged off Fang Yuan's hand: "You brat, you have no manners, I am your senior's senior's senior's senior's senior's senior!"

"Oh?" Fang Yuan stared, while showing a flash of the two Immortal Gu in his hand.

Lang Ya land spirit's expression changed, he laughed as he patted Fang Yuan's leg: "Fang Yuan, there's nothing I can do, you really suit my taste, we are old friends with much in common after all!"

Mo Tan Sang, who was at the side, witnessed this entire scene speechlessly.

Fang Yuan placed the two Immortal Gu into his own immortal aperture and took out three Immortal Gu recipes.

After five months in Hu Immortal blessed land, Fang Yuan had made six deals with Lang Ya land spirit.

The lower the completion rate of the Immortal Gu recipe, the more green grape immortal essence would be consumed during the deduction, and it would take more time as well. The three Immortal Gu recipes that Fang Yuan took out now had only sixty percent completion rate originally, he spent half a month before he completed them with difficulty.

Lang Ya land spirit received the Immortal Gu recipes and looked, sighing while shaking his head: "Lad, I have to admit, you are an unparalleled genius in deducing Gu recipes. It is such a pity that you have become an immortal zombie."

Fang Yuan followed up and asked: "I also want to find a way to remove my immortal zombie status, do you know of any methods?"

"There are a bunch of methods, of course, but they are all old and cannot keep up with the times. Some have high risks, some have low probabilities of success, while some have extinct materials, for some, I don't even believe the methods." Lang Ya land spirit shook his head: "After all, I am a land spirit, I would not usually think about an immortal zombie's problems."

"Brother Fang might be able to get into Northern Plains' Zombie Alliance branch. The higher ups of Zombie Alliance are mostly immortal zombies, they have been researching on how to get rid of the immortal zombie body, and regain their lives. Furthermore, several years ago, I've heard some rumors that Northern Plains Zombie Alliance had made some progress on this matter." Mo Tan Sang suggested at this time.

Fang Yuan nodded: "I have such intentions, but I cannot expose myself. I destroyed Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and ruined Imperial Court blessed land, it is inconvenient to appear in public. If deductions were made against me, that would be horrible."

"Now that Dong Fang Chang Fan is dead, there might not be any Gu Immortals who can deduce brother Fang's identity." Mo Tan Sang said.

"It is hard to say, some thousand year old monsters or some wisdom path Gu Immortals might exist." Fang Yuan shook his head, sighing.

"Oh? Lad, aren't you a wisdom path Gu Immortal? If you can deduce so many Immortal Gu recipes, your wisdom path attainment must be very high, you should use your own wisdom path methods to prevent others from deducing you. I remember that many wisdom path Gu Immortals have done that before." Lang Ya land spirit asked.

Fang Yuan laughed bitterly in his heart.

How could he be a wisdom path Gu Immortal? He was only using the might of the rank nine wisdom Gu to impersonate as one, shamelessly claiming credit for it.

Thus, he said: "My wisdom path methods are very heavily skewed towards deducing Gu recipes, they are very poor in other aspects. Furthermore, Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun are both living eyewitnesses, they had experienced the situation in Imperial Court blessed land. I am afraid my current appearance has been found out by Qin Bai Sheng already."

Speaking of Qin Bai Sheng, Mo Tan Sang's eyes shone, he praised: "This person is quite impressive. I had thought that he was only strong in battle strength, but to think he was very wise as well. He captured Ma and Zhao, obtaining the core of the luck path true inheritance. Originally, Northern Plains' Gu Immortals were going to attack and exterminate him together. But during this month's time in Northern Plains, he recruited allies, giving up some benefits and persuading Fairy Li Shan to come out and use mountain pledge Gu, to forcefully gather and unite a bunch of lone cultivators, even Ye Lui tribe was convinced by him."

"Originally, there was a huge battle ahead, but because of his actions, the battle flopped. He even is going to hold a huge auction in his blessed land, purposely selling the core Immortal Gu of the luck path true inheritance, he even will be placing Ma and Zhao as commodities for sale."

After saying that, Mo Tan Sang looked at Fang Yuan deeply in the eye.

He knew that Fairy Li Shan and Fang Yuan had a deep relationship.

Back then, when Fang Yuan borrowed the desolate beasts from Lang Ya land spirit, he was present. Lang Ya land spirit rejected him outright, having a firm attitude, after all, the desolate beasts were an important defense of Lang Ya blessed land. If Fang Yuan had ill intentions, and was in cahoots with the group that attacked the blessed land, Lang Ya land spirit would be in danger.

But out of his expectations, Fang Yuan took out mountain pledge Gu.

Using this Gu to make a vow, Lang Ya land spirit's worries were dispelled.

Later, he used Man as Before and Landscape as Before, these two Immortal Gu, to attract Lang Ya land spirit and strike at his weakness. After all, Lang Ya land spirit had offered Tai Bai Yun Sheng five immortal essence stones just to research Landscape as Before in the past.

Lang Ya land spirit was moved by the two Immortal Gu, and after being provoked by Fang Yuan's words, he lent eight desolate beasts to him.

"Qin Bai Sheng knows how to give in at the right time, he can adapt to circumstances and has amazing methods, he is truly skilled in both brains and brawn, one can't help but admire him." Fang Yuan said lightly, before changing the subjecting and asking the land spirit: "Do you have any leads on the white lotus giant silkworm Gu?"

Fang Yuan's cleanse soul Immortal Gu has not been fed, after this period of time, it became even weaker.

But to feed cleanse soul Immortal Gu, he needed the flesh of the white lotus giant silkworm Gu.

Earlier, Fang Yuan had asked Lang Ya land spirit, but Lang Ya land spirit did not have the recipe of the white lotus giant silkworm Gu, or even any remnant recipes of it.

Thus, he could only ask for a lead, not raising any talk of the Gu recipe.

Lang Ya land spirit shook his head: "Lad, this white lotus giant silkworm Gu was created by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable. My main body had lived through the eras of Thieving Heaven and Giant Sun before dying. Spectral Soul Demon Venerable only rose up after Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, by that time, I was already confined inside this blessed land, how could I have any leads?"

"But, I do have an incredible transformation path killer move here. This killer move originated from Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable. When he was young, he used this set of Gu worms to hide his appearance and evade his enemies when they chased him, the effect was great. With this killer move, you will be able to change your appearance and aura, to conceal your identity. Even if Gu Immortals manage to deduce your identity, you might be able to deny it in person and claim that their deduction was wrong, successfully hoodwinking them!"

Chapter 709: Familiar Face

"Oh?" As it involved Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, Fang Yuan's interest was roused: "Is it the legendary 'familiar face'?"

In Gu Master history, there were many interesting records about the immortal killer move 'familiar face'.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had once relied on familiar face to transform into all sorts of appearances, he had once scammed a rank eight Gu Immortal, Deng Zuo Yan, while he himself had rank six cultivation, causing Deng Zuo Yan to think that he was his best friend, Wan Che Zhen. In the end, Deng Zuo Yan allowed the thief into his house, and Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable used the opportunity to steal a lot of treasures in his blessed land.

After the incident, Deng Zuo Yan was angered to the point of spitting out blood, he found Wan Che Zhen and engaged in a fierce battle, it was an extremely heated match.

Wan Che Zhen was very puzzled, he tried to explain himself but it was not working. In the end, he took a risk and stopped defending him, letting Deng Zuo Yan deal three blows to him.

After three blows, Wan Che Zhen was on the verge of death, he finally managed to convince Deng Zuo Yan of their friendship.

Deng Zuo Yan felt deep regret, he tried to heal Wan Che Zhen regardless of the consequences. After he found out the truth, he saw Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable as his most hated enemy and one that he must kill.

Wan Che Zhen's deep injuries could not heal, and seeing that Deng Zuo Yan was about to face a tribulation, he did not want to be a burden to his friend and left secretly.

But to think that Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had perfect timing, he disguised as Wan Che Zhen and lied to Deng Zuo Yan, lying in bed and pretending to be ill, extorting countless cultivation resources from him.

After that, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable escaped scot-free.

Deng Zuo Yan lost a huge amount of his foundation, he died during his heavenly tribulation and earthly calamity not long after. Wan Che Zhen heard that his friend had died and vomited blood from anger. His weak body that was heavily injured finally gave in and he died several days later.

This was the most illustrious achievement of the immortal killer move 'familiar face'.

It was not an offensive killer move, but it indirectly took the lives of two rank eight Gu Immortals.

In history, other than this incredible account, there were also countless incidents where Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable used this move to pretend to be a weakling to catch people off guard, or scammed people by pretending to be an expert. He also transformed into a snowman and caused trouble in an inkman city, resulting in a huge battle between the snowmen and the inkmen.

Lang Ya land spirit stared at Fang Yuan, shaking his head: "Familiar face? You are really daring! That is an immortal killer move, the core Gu is the legendary attitude Gu. Even if I give it to you, you will not be able to use it. But this killer move of mine has a huge relationship with familiar face, it can be said to be the former version of it, this is a mortal killer move and is suitable for you to use."

"Oh?" Bright light shined in Fang Yuan's eyes.

Seeing that he had drawn out Fang Yuan's interest, Lang Ya land spirit chuckled as he continued: "This killer move is called 'unfamiliar face'. But if you want it, you will need to do me a favor."

Fang Yuan knew that there was no free lunch in this world, he nodded: "Say it."

Lang Ya land spirit said his plan immediately: "My twelve cloud buildings all had one desolate beast inside each in the past. But because of the attacks of the Gu Immortals from the mysterious force, two of them died and one died after succumbing to injuries. Now, I only have nine left. If you can enslave a desolate beast with outstanding battle strength for me, not only will I pay you immortal essence stones based on market rates, I will also give you this mortal killer move 'unfamiliar face'."

Fang Yuan was overjoyed deep inside: After making many transactions with Lang Ya land spirit over the Immortal Gu remnant recipes, and using the mountain pledge Gu to dispel any suspicions, along with returning the desolate beasts, he had finally improved his relationship with Lang Ya land spirit.

In the past, Lang Ya land spirit would not ask Fang Yuan for such a matter.

Fang Yuan thought about it and agreed.

Next, he obtained three new Immortal Gu remnant recipes from Lang Ya land spirit, after saying goodbye, he went back to Hu Immortal blessed land.

"Junior brother, you are back, was this trip successful?" Tai Bai Yun Sheng was inside Hu Immortal blessed land.

Now, with the eight desolate beasts already returned, it was impossible for Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan to stay in Hu Immortal blessed land, when Fang Yuan went to Lang Ya blessed land, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was the only Gu Immortal left to defend it.

"Mm, it was rather fruitful." Fang Yuan said, returning landscape as before Gu and man as before Gu to Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

"Shark Demon is calling me urgently, I have to go to Eastern Sea now." Tai Bai Yun Sheng took the two Gu and rushed over without examining them.

Fang Yuan did not obstruct him, he only told him to be careful.

Now that he was finally alone, it was time to plan what to do for the future.

"After resolving the huge crisis of Immortal Crane Sect attacking Hu Immortal blessed land, I have finally stabilized the situation, I have entered the righteous path faction using the status of a subsidiary force, now that I can sell guts Gu, I can intervene slightly in Central Continent's matters now."

In the past, Fang Yuan was a mortal, he did not even have the qualifications to speak to Gu Immortals as equals. Although he had Hu Immortal blessed land, he was like a child walking into a bandit's den holding primeval stones. Once the bandits saw Fang Yuan, they would only think of how to take Hu Immortal blessed land for themselves.

Now that Fang Yuan was an immortal zombie, he finally was qualified. After gathering his strength and showing the mysterious force behind him, he had finally intimidated Immortal Crane Sect and the other forces. Using the guts Gu transaction to form an economic connection between them, the child had now grown into a young man, seeing a bandit, he scattered some primeval stones to them. The bandits want to rob him, but they are afraid of a counterattack from the young man that would cause them to suffer greater losses, thus, they took the primeval stones to temporarily satisfy themselves.

Furthermore, these bandits themselves are wary of each other and restrict themselves, their attention is placed on many other things. The young man is temporarily safe in this den.

But Fang Yuan was aware, that when the guts Gu transactions become bigger, and the benefits become larger, there would be even greater pressure on him, as more people would want to snatch it from him.

Especially during the five regions chaotic war, all of the forces would not let go of something that could raise their strength.

Although the young man gave out some primeval stones and satisfied the bandits temporarily, as his wealth grows, these bandits were bound to engage in another attempt of robbery soon.

Thus, Fang Yuan lowered his head and became a subsidiary of Immortal Crane Sect in name. This way, the young man was now a young bandit, these bandits could not rob each other, they had to follow the rules.

But rules were just formless restrictions, as time passed, as the profits grew, they would have less effect.

After all, this young bandit was not as powerful as he had displayed himself to be.

"Four Gu Immortals, eight desolate beasts, this is just a facade that I put up by borrowing the strength of others. The Snowy Mountain Alliance I have with Hei Lou Lan has a time limit. Lang Ya blessed land is facing strong enemies, it can hardly protect itself, I cannot bring out the eight desolate beasts anytime I wish. Even though we made Immortal Crane Sect retreat and have set up transactions with the ten great ancient sects, since I have now appeared in the open, they will definitely use all sorts of methods to investigate me. They have not struck yet because they are not sure of my background at this point. One they know, they will strike again." Fang Yuan considered.

Using an analogy, when Fang Yuan first obtained Hu Immortal blessed land, the situation was like a torrential rainstorm with thunder and lightning, it was vicious weather and only by taking a fatal risk could he have a chance of survival.

After Fang Yuan's trip to Northern Plains, he became an immortal zombie, when he returned to Hu Immortal blessed land, the situation was like a sky with dark clouds covering him, and strong winds blowing. The future was grim, only by plotting carefully, taking every step vigilantly, and grabbing onto every opportunity, could he climb out of the swamp slowly and with much difficulty.

After Fang Yuan repelled Immortal Crane Sect and started selling guts Gu, the fierce winds had disappeared, and the dark clouds had thinned, a hole was exposed and the blue sky could be seen. The future was now bright and hopeful, but the dark clouds were still looming, if he was careless, they would cover the sky again, with lightning and rain pouring. It was like a person had just escaped from a swamp, he was standing at the edge of the swamp, finally safe for the time being.

If he took a step back, Fang Yuan would fall into the swamp again, if he wanted to get out, he would need to struggle intensely, and his luck would matter greatly.

If he moved forward, Fang Yuan would become more stable, and he would finally get back onto a wide and large track. Even if there were thorns along the way, it would not be like before, when he was struggling between life and death, and every step could lead to a fatal disaster.

"The following period of time is a time of peace that I have obtained with much difficulty, I need to advance forward, accumulating my foundation and raising my cultivation, I have to become stronger, until none of the forces around me dare to have any ill intentions against me."

Fang Yuan thought about it carefully, there were several huge problems in front of him.

The first question facing him now was the feeding of Immortal Gu.

Cleanse soul Immortal Gu was the most urgent one.

Lang Ya land spirit and Fairy Li Shan did not have any leads to the white lotus giant silkworm Gu, even though he could buy some in treasure yellow heaven for a high price, it could only sustain cleanse soul Immortal Gu's life and not let it die of hunger.

To feed it till it was full, he needed ten thousand white lotus giant silkworm Gu, this Gu was in small quantity even for Gu Immortals who collected them.

Unless Fang Yuan got the Gu recipe and refined it in bulk, he could not solve the issue completely.

Looking at his other Immortal Gu, feeding them was still a huge problem.

Although he got through it this time, the next round of feeding would be a problem again.

The six headed snake's bones had turned into black blood and were fed to calamity beckoning Immortal Gu. Delight in water and mountain Immortal Gu's feeding problem had never been resolved. It was just that Mo Yao's will had fed it earlier, thus there were no issues yet.

Worldly wave trace Gu needed tens of thousands of underworld jellyfish and thousands of deepsea lightning eels. Although the former was in huge quantity, it could be bought easily using immortal essence stones. But the latter was rare in the market, if not for Tai Bai Yun Sheng encountering Shark Demon and putting his own life at risk, he would not have gotten the required amount.

Rising Azure Cloud was in Lang Ya land spirit's hands, it need not be considered for now. Connect luck Immortal Gu needs five thousand kilograms of sand gull soil, looking at the condition of the worldly sand gull's dead egg, it could produce another fifteen thousand kilograms, which was three feeding sessions. The feeding of Woman's Heart was troublesome, after all, mass killing of mortals would attract the attack of righteous path Gu Immortals.

After all, now was not the five regions chaotic war yet.

Within the five regions, the righteous path suppressed the demonic path, order was abundant in society.

Although Fang Yuan had many immortal essence stones now, the feeding of Immortal Gu could not be resolved simply by having immortal essence stones.

Generally in most cases, the feeding of Immortal Gu was usually connected to the cultivation path of the Gu Immortal themselves, and their blessed land.

Chapter 710: Crossing the Regional Wall

For instance, a water path Gu Immortal's blessed land would be in the form of a sea. After obtaining worldly wave trace Gu, the Gu Immortal would raise underworld jellyfish, deepsea lightning eels and so on inside their blessed land. Thus, the Gu Immortal could be self-sufficient, by drawing materials from their own blessed land to feed the Immortal Gu Worldly Wave Trace.

Another example was Tai Bai Yun Sheng's two Immortal Gu, he could obtain food for them by managing his own blessed land.

Hei Lou Lan's blessed land contained large numbers of heavy metal ores. These heavy metals were strength qi Immortal Gu's food.

However, Fang Yuan's situation was different from theirs.

Their Immortal Gu were mostly obtained by refining vital Gu and core Gu when advancing to Gu Immortal, and were integrated with their path.

Fang Yuan's Immortal Gu were mostly obtained from scheming. His vital Gu was Spring Autumn Cicada but he had no time path inheritance, and what he currently practiced was strength path.

Moreover, Fang Yuan's Immortal Gu were extremely disordered, involving time path, space path, water path, wisdom path and other paths. The most crucial point was that Fang Yuan's blessed land was dead.

His immortal aperture had turned into a dead aperture and whatever he placed in there would die, it could neither be managed nor developed like a normal blessed land, nor could it provide convenience in feeding Immortal Gu, and most importantly it could not produce immortal essence. Thus, there was a much heavier burden on immortal essence stones.

Fang Yuan not only had to use his immortal essence stones for transactions, but also turn a part of them into green grape immortal essence, and furthermore bear the costs for feeding Immortal Gu. The main reason for Fang Yuan almost becoming bankrupt after the battle with Hei Cheng was this.

Thus the second problem in front of Fang Yuan was his immortal aperture.

The immortal aperture was already dead, his cultivation had stagnated.

The blessed land was involved in many aspects of the Gu Immortal's cultivation, therefore this was a great burden to Fang Yuan. The day Fang Yuan truly got rid of his immortal zombie body would be the day he can formally start his Gu Immortal cultivation.

However, getting rid of the immortal zombie body and returning to his human body meant Fang Yuan would not be able to step into the wisdom light halo, this was also a problem.

As for the final important problem, it was battle strength.

Currently, cleanse soul Immortal Gu was weak from hunger and was too risky to use. Fang Yuan's trump card — the immortal killer move myriad self, also could not be used.

Fang Yuan's battle strength had fallen as a result.

Whether it was confronting Central Continent's ten great ancient sects in the days to come, dealing with the pursuit of Northern Plains' Gu Immortals, seizing Dong Fang Chang Fan's wisdom path inheritance, helping Lang Ya land spirit to capture a desolate beast, seeking the Thieving Heaven inheritance pertaining to Luo Po Valley, taking Immortal Gu Dark Limit from Fairy Jiang Yu, all of these required powerful battle strength.

"There are mainly four aspects that influence a Gu Immortal's battle strength. The Gu Immortal's own battle attainment, Immortal Gu, killer moves and immortal essence. With the guts Gu business now, I don't lack immortal essence for the moment. A Gu Immortal's battle attainment is formed from constant accumulation of their foundation over time and cannot be raised in a short period. In the Immortal Gu aspect, the Blood Deity remnant recipe is enough to deduce the complete blood deity Immortal Gu recipe, but my wealth right now is still quite far from reaching the standard of refining Immortal Gu."

Fang Yuan thought it over, even if he could refine Blood Deity, he did not want to do so.

Blood path had been affiliated with the demonic path since long ago, even the ten great ancient sects had to research blood path in secret and did not dare to publicly announce it. Heavenly Court even had the Demon Judgment Board and Fang Yuan did not want to put his name there this early.

Moreover, almost all the Immortal Gu in Fang Yuan's hands were in a bad state from hunger. The burden of feeding was too heavy and Fang Yuan lacked confidence in managing it if a new Immortal Gu was added on top of that.

Therefore, the only method Fang Yuan could use to raise his battle strength quickly was through killer moves.

The killer move aspect involved both immortal killer moves and mortal killer moves.

"I have sufficient immortal essence stones, my disposable income is much higher than in the past, not only can I purchase a lot of good mortal killer moves, but I also can continuously experiment, deduce and reproduce some powerful killer moves from my past life."

Having thought things through, Fang Yuan immediately started with the task.

Central Continent.

With Feng Jiu Ge as the leader, a group of Gu Immortals were standing in front of an enormous light wall.

The light wall was incomparably tall, connecting the sky and ground. The white light had condensed into a solid and formed a wall. Within it flickered golden light which was full of vigor and majesty.

This was Central Continent's membrane, known as the saint regional wall.

The world of Gu Masters had five large regions: Central Continent, Southern Border, Eastern Sea, Western Desert and Northern Plains, each was covered with a layer of membrane forming the boundaries of heaven and earth, mutually isolating each other.

"Old Oracle, what is the result of your calculation this time?" Old Lord Can Yang asked a young looking Gu Immortal in the group.

The young looking Gu Immortal slowly opened his eyes, they were filled with clouds and mist and constantly transforming.

A long while later, the clouds and mist dispersed and he returned to having ordinary white eyes with black pupils.

The young looking Gu Immortal spoke with a slightly happy tone: "It can be done. This part of the regional wall is rather weak, it is the third weak spot we have found over these last days. But compared to the first and the second, this is more stable. I suggest we use this to cut open an entrance and cross the regional wall to Northern Plains!"

"Hahaha, good, we have searched close to a thousand areas and finally found an ideal weak spot." Old Man Tian Long laughed loudly.

Fairy Ling Mei let out a breath of cloudy air and said with a sigh: "We have searched for so many days before finally getting a good result, it was really not easy."

"We have already wasted a lot of time, let's begin." Feng Jiu Ge said briefly, "Who goes first?"

Fairy Ao Xue and Fairy Ling Mei glanced at each other, then stood up together, speaking in unison: "This time, let our Heaven's Envy Manor take the lead."

With that statement, the two exerted strength and activated an immortal killer move together, called peerless crescent moon slash.

This killer move's core was the rank seven crescent moon Immortal Gu, with two rank six Immortal Gu as support. The immortal essence required to activate this immortal killer move was extremely high and it also burdened the mind significantly; just one Gu Immortal could not display its might, two Gu Immortals must activate it together.

The immortal killer move was activated, instantly forming a blue crescent moon.

The crescent moon was not large and was only the size of a water jar, but it had condensed into solid form and was sparkling like a magnificent piece of artwork. Only the terrifying aura it leaked out occasionally would let one know that it was not harmless like its appearance showed.

The surrounding Gu Immortals distanced themselves far away from Ao Xue and Ling Mei.

After accumulating enough power, the two fairies gave soft cries and released the blue crescent moon.

The crescent moon flew extremely quick and silently, shining with gentle moonlight.

The blue crescent moon slashed the saint regional wall and immediately cut open a path about seventy-six steps in length.

"Worthy of being a well-known killer move of Heaven's Envy Manor, it directly cut open a distance of seventy-six steps, remarkable." Gu Immortal Chen Zhen Chi exclaimed in admiration.

Feng Jiu Ge led the way with the other Gu Immortals behind him and entered the saint regional wall.

The moment they stepped into the saint regional wall, many Gu Immortals' expressions changed slightly. Their bodies became heavier, their thoughts moved more slowly and even the immortal aperture inside them gradually started to tremor.

"Quick, we need to move faster." Feng Jiu Ge hastened. They had walked seventy-four steps before they could not walk any further.

In this short period of time, the saint regional wall had already started to rapidly heal; the path of seventy-six steps in depth had already shortened by two steps.

Old Lord Can Yang stood up: "Next, let this old man give it a try."

He took out an Immortal Gu, this Immortal Gu resembled a mostly burnt out candle with a small amount of candlelight burning at the top.

Old Lord Can Yang softly blew at the candlelight.

The candlelight shook and following the direction of Old Lord Can Yang's breath, it let out countless glittering light spots.

The light spots struck the white-gold saint regional wall, the regional wall melted like snow as it rapidly dissolved and formed a sixty-three steps passage.

Everyone quickly moved ahead. At the end of the passage, Old Man Tian Long stood up and activated an Immortal Gu, opening a sixty-seven steps passage.

All the Gu Immortals took turns in using their Immortal Gu or immortal killer moves to open the passage deeper into the saint regional wall.

The deeper they went, the greater the pressure on them was, even turning into a giant force that dragged them backwards, seemingly as if this world did not want them to leave Central Continent.

The thoughts in their minds also kept on moving increasingly slowly, which caused the Gu Immortals to have extreme difficulty in activating their immortal killer moves. As a wisdom path Gu Immortal, Old Oracle had no choice but to use all sorts of methods and even immortal killer moves to reinforce the other Gu Immortals' minds. But in spite of this, Ao Xue and Ling Mei, these two fairies could not activate peerless crescent moon slash anymore.

The most crucial point was the immortal apertures in their bodies.

The deeper they went, the greater the intensity of the tremors in their immortal apertures. The earth within their blessed lands cracked, boulders started falling down and countless life forms within died pitifully.

These Gu Immortals came from the ten great ancient sects, they were famous experts with outstanding battle strength. However, several hundred steps later, most turned pale, some with weaker cultivation even started trembling slightly.

A thousand steps later, most of the Gu Immortals were covered with sweat, some were deathly pale. Ao Xue and Ling Mei were walking while supporting each other.

Only Feng Jiu Ge alone was still walking ahead upright, his expression was normal. Every time he made a move, they were all immortal killer moves, cutting open passages longer than a hundred steps.

After walking for over three thousand steps, there was much thinner white-gold light in front, instead a trace of green was vaguely revealed.

"Old Oracle, your deduction was correct, this is indeed a weak area of saint regional wall, we reached here after only walking over three thousand steps." Someone immediately praised.

"Beyond saint regional wall is Northern Plains' licorice regional wall. Let's speed up and break through it in one move!" Old Lord Can Yang attempted to raise the morale while gasping for breath.

The young looking Gu Immortal Old Oracle, however, was somewhat worried: "My ability is limited, I could only deduce saint regional wall. Hopefully this area of licorice regional wall is not too thick."

After around eight minutes, the Gu Immortals were out of saint regional wall and entered into licorice regional wall.

This regional wall was quite different from saint regional wall. The Gu Immortals felt an enormous formless force pushing at them and constantly repelling them.

The intensity of the tremors of their immortal apertures increased further, the losses causing great heartache to many Gu Immortals.

"I hope we can subdue one or two Immortal Gu in this trip to Northern Plains, otherwise the losses would be too huge." Old Man Tian Long said.

"Sigh, I had passed the regional wall to Northern Plains when I was younger, but back then the whole process only took about five minutes of time and was very easy." Gu Immortal Hong Chi Ming sighed deeply.

When he had crossed the regional wall back then, he had only been a rank four Gu Master. As one's cultivation became higher, the difficulty in traversing regional walls would become increasingly difficult.

After a long time, this group of Gu Immortals had no choice but to stop.

They were in licorice regional wall and everywhere around them was filled with green fog. Grass was growing wildly in the fog and was constantly twining and twisting like a sea of snakes or hair, blocking their paths.

Feng Jiu Ge's body was dripping with sweat and his lips were pale: "This won't do, this part of licorice regional wall is extremely firm, we need to change to another direction even if we have to walk more."

Everyone nodded, approving of Feng Jiu Ge's resoluteness.

Old Oracle began to deduce, and in this period of time, the regional wall was constantly recovering, making the Gu Immortals retreat further.

"This way." Finally, Old Oracle calculated a direction.

The Gu Immortals changed their direction and after suffering bitterly for a day and a night, they passed the licorice regional wall and entered Northern Plains.

"Rest and reorganize for three days, we will talk after that." Feng Jiu Ge exhaustedly said.

Among the whole group, only he was able to barely stand while the others fell down unsteadily to the ground like piles of mud, not wanting to even budge anymore.

Chapter 711: Giving Up on Possession

Cranes cried out, flying beautifully in the sky, displaying their elegant appearances.

As the wind blew gently, the trees on Fei He mountain were swaying lightly.

The sun was high in the sky, but the sunlight could not penetrate into this dark gloomy underground secret room.

The underground secret room was plain and simple, the surroundings were stone walls and other than the stone bed at the center, there was nothing.

Moist water vapor slipped into the cracks of the walls, as moss grew on them.

On the stone bed, there was a rotten and ruined body of a young rank five Gu Master, it was Gu Yue Fang Zheng.

In order to detect Fang Yuan's location, coordinating with He Feng Yang to attack Hu Immortal blessed land, Fang Zheng was plotted against by Lord Sky Crane and lost control of the failed blood demon flower Gu, causing him to lose too much blood and his soul went on the verge of collapse, as he entered a deep state of unconsciousness.

"You want to revive Fang Zheng?" He Feng Yang was right beside the stone bed, looking at the spirit incubating flea which was floating in front of him.

Fang Zheng's master was inside the spirit incubating flea — Lord Sky Crane's soul.

At this moment, a firm voice came from within the flea: "Yes lord, I am willing to give up this possession opportunity, please save Fang Zheng instead."

He Feng Yang turned his gaze towards Fang Zheng who had fainted, saying softly: "The injuries to his body might seem terrifying, but it is not a big concern, even without my help, the sect has many ways to heal him. The problem is his soul. He did the blood sense forcefully this time, it caused a huge burden on his soul, his soul was only a step away from collapsing."

"Actually, the current situation is most suitable for you to possess his body. This body has A grade aptitude and a rank five aperture, his soul is extremely weak so if you undergo possession now, you would win the contest between souls without doubt. Wasn't possession your goal all along?"

Lord Sky Crane laughed bitterly.

Ever since he used the method to harm Fang Zheng, Lord Sky Crane had been recalling Fang Zheng's appearance and all the memories of their experiences had been flashing through his mind.

Fang Zheng's purity, his pursuit of justice, it reminded him of his younger self. Fang Zheng's desire for revenge was so similar to his own experiences.

"Subordinate's original plan was to possess Fang Zheng. But... now in my heart, I feel guilt and reluctance. According to logic, he has the bloodline of First Gen Gu Yue, yet he has been calling me master and trusts me, he had never thought I would harm him. He believes in justice, just like I did in the past. If I kill him and succeed in the possession, I would have to live within his shell in the future, how would I face myself?"

Lord Sky Crane sighed.

He Feng Yang was silent for a while, before he raised his hand and placed it on Fang Zheng's forehead.

A green light that was gentle as water dripped down from He Feng Yang's palm, spreading all over Fang Zheng's body.

Everywhere the green light reached, his swollen flesh and scars healed rapidly at a visible rate.

After several breaths of time, Fang Zheng's body fully recovered, his breathing relaxed, but he was still unconscious.

"I have already healed his physical body, and stabilized his soul. As a reward for being my subordinate, I will give you another opportunity, Sky Crane. You do not need to give up on the possession chance, I will give you some time to consider it, think it through properly." He Feng Yang said.

"Lord..."

He Feng Yang retracted his hand: "The possession technique we have is not complete, it originated from Northern Plains. Right now, our sect's Old Lord Can Yang has followed Feng Jiu Ge into Northern Plains, he had been assigned several missions from the sect him. One of them is to collect more information and improve the possession technique. When he returns to the sect, Sky Crane, you will have a higher chance of succeeding in the possession. By that point, you would have already reflected thoroughly on it, give me the answer then."

"Lord..."

Without waiting for Lord Sky Crane to finish speaking, He Feng Yang waved his sleeves and his figure vanished.

Hu Immortal blessed land, in an underground cave.

The wisdom light halo that was shining in many colors shone on Fang Yuan's face.

Fang Yuan's brows were tightly locked, his expression was grim and uncertain.

Guh.

Suddenly, he opened his mouth, spitting a mouthful of green zombie blood. At the same time, countless joyful wills in his mind collapsed and disintegrated.

This was the first time Fang Yuan had gotten injured from using the light of wisdom.

Fang Yuan stepped out of the light of wisdom, finding a mushroom nearby and sitting on it like a bench.

He stretched out one arm to wipe the zombie blood around his mouth, as he inspected his mind while enduring the huge pain in his head.

His mind was experiencing tremors, thoughts disintegrated on their own the moment they were created. The surrounding boundaries of his mind had mild cracks on them, this was the backlash due to Fang Yuan's forceful thinking.

At this moment, as long as Fang Yuan had a thought, intense pain would assault his mind.

He shut his eyes and stopped all his thinking, he was like a rock statue without any movement.

A while later, he slowly opened his eyes, inspecting his mind again.

The tremors had stopped in his mind, but the boundaries still had remaining cracks on them. The speed of his thought generation was slower than before, but they would not collapse upon creation.

That was to say, Fang Yuan could think again.

This injury was no doubt a valuable experience, Fang Yuan learned many things from it.

"Wisdom path deductions have a risk as well, one can get injured. Just like strength path, overexerting oneself would cause them to pull their muscles, and their tendons might even break."

"This time, I was trying to deduce a difficult question of the star path, I used a large amount of joyful wills and the unlimited inspiration from the light of wisdom to deduce countless possibilities. It surpassed the limits and endurance level of my mind, thus I got injured."

"I thought I could use the power of wisdom Gu to deduce the recipe of star shoot Gu. But now it seems that my star path foundation is too low, the unlimited inspiration can give me countless possibilities and directions, but I will need to deduce every single possibility. At the same time, during the process of deduction, more choices would be generated."

Star shoot Gu was Star Lord Wan Xiang's self-created Gu worm. Using large numbers of star rain Gu, small numbers of spring wind Gu, as well as many other Gu worms, one could assemble the killer move — Spring Star Rain.

The effect of spring star rain was to increase the growth rate of plants. Fang Yuan used it many times to nourish his star fragment grass.

But star shoot Gu was a consumable Gu, right now, he could only purchase it from Star Lord Wan Xiang, and Star Lord Wan Xiang was making a huge profit out of this Gu.

Fang Yuan had wanted to use the light of wisdom to reverse engineer the star shoot Gu's recipe, but he did not succeed, and even got himself injured.

"Although star shoot Gu is a mortal Gu, it had been tampered with by Star Lord Wan Xiang, the recipe is very hard to reverse refine. Unless my star path realm reaches master level, if not, it will be hard to succeed." Fang Yuan had a realization.

Star path master level realm, it represented a foundation in star path, and could greatly reduce the possibilities when undergoing deductions. It could help Fang Yuan reach the correct answer much quicker.

Fang Yuan made an estimate based on the difficulty: "If reverse refining star shoot Gu's recipe requires star path master level attainment, then researching an entirely new Gu recipe to create the starlight firefly Gu would be even harder, most likely, star path grandmaster realm is needed. As for modifying Dou Min Jun's star path inheritance and creating an entire new star path Gu worm, to amplify the effects of attacking, defending, movement, and healing in star path Gu worms, that would be even harder. At least quasi-great grandmaster realm attainment is required."

Starlight firefly Gu was a necessity in activating stargate Gu, it would not hurt to have more of it.

But in Dou Min Jun's inheritance, a bit of star Gu, brilliance of two stars Gu, three stars in the sky Gu, four stars cube Gu, five stars aligned Gu, these could amplify the offense of star path Gu worms. If this was circulated, star path Gu would definitely become much more popular, it would even have a mild effect on the current status of the different paths.

Fang Yuan's original plan was to reverse refine the Gu recipe of star shoot Gu and starlight firefly Gu, one was to escape from his reliance on Star Lord Wan Xiang, but also to have a method to obtain even more starlight firefly Gu for his use of stargates.

In addition, raising the effects of a bit of star Gu, brilliance of two stars Gu, three stars in the sky Gu... this series of Gu worms would help in developing a whole new star path killer move that would suit Fang Yuan's needs, and raise his battle strength.

But after making an attempt, Fang Yuan knew that this was not feasible yet.

Even if he had the light of wisdom and had unlimited inspiration, his refinement path realm was master level, his star path realm was merely ordinary, it was hard for his plans to work.

"It seems that to raise my battle strength, I have to focus on my strengths and make use of my advantages." Fang Yuan assessed himself, he was a blood path grandmaster, strength path grandmaster, flying quasi-grandmaster, refinement path master, enslavement path master, as well as transformation path master.

He first eliminated blood path.

Blood path Gu Immortals were heavily targeted by everyone, because blood path cultivation focused on harming others to raise one's own battle strength. The righteous and demonic paths were both unwilling to face such a huge threat like blood path Gu Immortals.

Only during the five regions chaotic war, when the law and order of the regions go into chaos, would blood path emerge again.

Although Fang Yuan had Blood Deity's remnant recipe, he did not want to deduce the completed recipe yet, he did not have the financial capability to refine blood deity Immortal Gu now.

Furthermore, the blood path inheritance in his previous life had yet to mature, he could not retrieve it yet.

Next, Fang Yuan eliminated strength path.

Strength path had once flourished in the past, at present, it had already heavily declined. Even though there were incredible geniuses like Chu Du, it was unlikely for the past glory of strength path to reappear.

The might and prosperity of a path not only relied on genius Gu Masters and Gu Immortals, they also relied on resources.

In the present era, the resources for strength path had mostly gone extinct, or were extremely rare.

Strength path had little prospects, many Gu recipes were lost, and the future was grim. Even though Fang Yuan was a strength path immortal zombie, he did not want to walk on this path.

The reason he chose strength path was because the conditions back then were very convenient, he would use it as a springboard, to change to another path in the future. He later became a strength path immortal zombie because he was left with no choice in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Unless Fang Yuan was like Hei Lou Lan with multiple strength path Immortal Gu, who can raise her battle strength using these Immortal Gu. But such a situation was not feasible for Fang Yuan.

Blood path and strength path were dead ends, flying quasi-grandmaster was merely part of his battle proficiency, refinement path did not excel in fighting, Fang Yuan's only options were enslavement path and transformation path.

But enslavement path needed beast groups.

At the level of Gu Immortals, ordinary beasts were of little use. Their core beast groups would be elevated from mutated beast kings and beast emperors to desolate beasts.

Fang Yuan used the light of wisdom and thought about it for a long time.

Three days later, he finally made a breakthrough in transformation path.

Chapter 712: Lion Fur Armor, Transplanting Bat Wings

Time flew by quickly and in a blink of an eye, ten days had passed in Hu Immortal blessed land.

Fang Yuan was flying in the air.

"Hair armor." His thoughts shifted, his hair grew wildly and instantly condensed into a malevolent looking pitch black armor full of spikes.

"Icy drill stardust." Fang Yuan pinched at the air with his five fingers, a ball of starlight formed on his hand.

The starlight constantly let out crackling sounds, looking closely inside, one could discover there were countless small specks of icy drills colliding and exploding non-stop.

Fang Yuan slowly pressed this ball of starlight into the hair armor on his chest.

The hair armor lasted for a few breaths before it began to be damaged. A dozen or so breaths later, the surroundings of the damaged area were dyed azure blue, and the blue frost was spreading everywhere.

Twenty breaths later, the hair armor completely shattered, and there was a small hole on Fang Yuan's chest.

This was completely within Fang Yuan's expectations.

He had merged Du Min Jun's inheritance into icy drill stardust, this would sell for four immortal essence stones in treasure yellow heaven. And the defensive killer move hair armor would only be worth around two and a half immortal essence stones.

The starlight on his palm dissipated, Fang Yuan willed and activated hair armor again.

However, the hair armor this time was different, it was a new and improved version, having gone through many days of experimentation.

The hair armor transformed quickly. The useless malevolent spikes were removed. The black iron-like luster before also turned into bronze.

The primary cause for this was Fang Yuan perfectly merging large numbers of golden lion fur Gu into the original foundation of hair armor.

Golden lion fur Gu was a rank five mortal Gu that could let Gu Masters grow golden lion fur, increasing their defense and having an even higher increase in resistance to metal path attacks.

Several breaths later, the original black iron spiked hair armor was gone, and replacing it was a smooth bronze armor which was twice the thickness of the black armor. The helmet had turned into the shape of a lion roaring with an open mouth, revealing Fang Yuan's face inside. The defensive ability had also increased by one hundred and fifty percent. If it was defending against metal path attacks, the defensive power would increase by a whole two hundred percent.

Fang Yuan made a lump of starlight again and pressed it towards his chest area like before.

The stardust drilled endlessly into the hair armor, but after a whole dozen or so breaths had gone by, the starlight was completely used up and merely a crack appear on the hair armor.

"Let's call it lion fur armor." Fang Yuan mumbled to himself before raising his eight arms and letting out eight lumps of starlight.

The starlight flew to the sky and gathered into a large lump.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily, charging into the large lump of stardust with his lion fur armor.

The icy drill stardust constantly produced tiny explosions which impacted against Fang Yuan's lion fur armor from all directions.

Fang Yuan constantly maintained the lion fur armor killer move, rapidly restoring any cracks that appeared. He maintained it till the starlight lump dissipated, and then flew down. There was not even a trace of a crack on the lion fur armor.

"Such recovery ability is about twice that of before. If placed in treasure yellow heaven, this could sell for four and a half immortal essence stones."

Lion fur armor was one of the accomplishments Fang Yuan had made these days.

He returned to Dang Hun palace where Hu Immortal land spirit was maintaining connecting heaven Gu, paying attention to treasure yellow heaven.

"How is the situation?" Fang Yuan asked.

"Master, the other party is still insisting on four immortal essence stones and shows no signs of lowering it." Little Hu Immortal land spirit replied.

Fang Yuan wanted to buy a pair of bat desolate beast wings.

The other party had killed this bat desolate beast and was putting its corpse on sale in treasure yellow heaven. Fang Yuan had asked for price before, but the other party had asked for four immortal essence stones just for this pair of bat wings, and their attitude was firm, not willing to lower it.

Four immortal essence stones was no doubt an expensive price. Back then, when Fang Yuan bought a six headed snake's skeleton, he had only had to pay three immortal essence stones.

According to the normal price, it should be two and a half at most.

Fang Yuan personally activated divine sense Gu and used the identity of Eight Arm Immortal to get in touch with the seller: "I am willing to pay three immortal essence stones to buy this pair of bat wings."

The seller's will, however, refused: "I'm not selling, not selling, the lowest is at least four immortal essence stones."

Fang Yuan snorted: "Sir is too greedy, look at how damaged these desolate beast wings are, they would normally only sell for two and a half immortal essence stones. If not for me wanting to research some new Gu and coincidentally happening to need this material, I would not have even asked."

The seller's will's tone softened and it sighed: "I am also helpless, my losses were too severe when hunting this desolate beast. This desolate beast's blood had already flowed out and my main body also suffered heavy injuries, if I don't sell it for this price, my finances will collapse and it might even lead to a delay in healing my injuries."

"Whether you live or die, is that my problem? Also, why would I believe your one-sided words? Three immortal essence stones, are you selling or not?" Fang Yuan said coldly.

"Not selling."

Fang Yuan immediately withdrew his divine sense.

After a while, he commanded Little Hu Immortal land spirit to inquire about the price and show a stance of being impatient: "How about this, I will take out three immortal essence stones to buy your bat wings. Say it, are you selling or not?"

The seller's will hesitated this time, but still refused in the end: "This pair of wings is the most valuable part of the whole desolate beast corpse. If sir only wants to buy the wings, it won't be easy for me to sell the remaining parts. If you are sincerely thinking of buying, how about you take out five immortal essence stones to buy this whole desolate beast corpse?"

Little Hu Immortal talked with Fang Yuan, and replied: "I only need the wings, what will I do with the other parts? I have wasted enough time already. Three immortal essence stones are already a lot, alright I shall give you three and a half immortal essence stones, this is my final bottom line. If you are still not selling, then forget it."

The seller's will was clearly shaken and it replied with hesitation: "This... let me consider it."

The land spirit hastened him: "My patience has limits, I will give you five breaths of time. Any longer and I might just take back my offer."

Four breaths passed before the seller's will heaved a long sigh. He also knew that although there was a high demand for desolate beast corpses but his price was indeed high. Gu Immortals were shrewd people, there were few that would spend money casually.

"Alright, I will sell..." The seller's will was just replying when a divine sense interrupted him, "Slow down, I want this bat desolate beast's corpse, I will give you five immortal essence stones."

"Eh? Sir is Immortal Monkey King!" This change naturally made the seller very happy.

If he sold the bat wings to Fang Yuan for three and a half immortal essence stones, then trying to sell the remaining parts of the corpse which were extremely damaged for one immortal essence stone would be demanding a very high price.

Now, Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei cut in and was willing to pay five immortal essence stones, the seller was naturally willing to accept this transaction.

"Wait a second, we have already made the deal. Immortal Monkey King, what do you think you are doing by suddenly butting in?" Hu Immortal land spirit refused to accept this.

"What deal?" Shi Lei scoffed, "Who are you kidding? Does business in treasure yellow heaven pay attention to first come, first serve? The item will naturally go to whoever pays the higher price. Since the transaction has not been carried out, there is no deal."

After saying that, Shi Lei then said to the seller: "Hey, this deal will earn you a great profit, why are you not quickly finishing the transaction?"

The seller's will was just about to nod when Hu Immortal land spirit obtained Fang Yuan's instructions and immediately prevented it: "Slow down, I will pay five and a half immortal essence stones."

"Hmph, only adding half an immortal essence stone, aren't you too petty? I will pay seven immortal essence stones." Shi Lei said with a rich and overbearing attitude.

Hu Immortal land spirit's tone immediately became gloomy: "Since it is so, I will pay eight immortal essence stones."

"Eight?" Shi Lei laughed, "Then I will pay nine!"

"Nine and a half." Hu Immortal land spirit immediately quoted.

That seller's will had never expected such a change and was already overjoyed.

Shi Lei was dazed before laughing loudly: "Alright, Hu Immortal, as expected of someone doing the business of guts Gu, you have so much money. I don't want to contend with a junior. Just a mere damaged desolate beast corpse, I hope you can be happy when you take it."

The divine sense left directly after laughing heartily.

"Hu... Lord Hu Immortal... you meant what you said, right?" The seller's will wore a fawning smile as he said while stammering. From the looks of it, he had not lied before, he was indeed a poor rank six Gu Immortal.

"Hmph, business needs to be done with sincerity, would my words be a lie?" Hu Immortal land spirit coldly snorted.

The two finished the transaction.

The seller received nine and a half immortal essence stones while Fang Yuan obtained a bat desolate beast's corpse.

After this transaction, Fang Yuan checked his wealth again; he had one hundred and seventy-two immortal essence stones and seventy-seven beads of green grape immortal essence.

So far, Fang Yuan had already sold the sixth batch of guts Gu. It was an average of one batch per month and every batch gave him forty-eight immortal essence stones in profit.

Over these six months, Fang Yuan had completed one transaction of an Immortal Gu recipe with Lang Ya land spirit, earning over twenty immortal essence stones.

But he had fed the eight desolate beasts earlier and converted large numbers of immortal essence stones into green grape immortal essence. He also consumed green grape immortal essence to reverse refine star path Gu recipes, which ended in failure, and finally, to make a breakthrough using transformation path, he improved on his killer moves.

He had not only improved his defensive killer move hair armor to lion fur armor, but also upgraded light illusion bat wings by a great degree.

But to complete the new light illusion bat wings, he needed to transplant a pair of real bat wings onto his immortal zombie body.

Because of this, Fang Yuan did not hesitate on spending a large amount to buy this bat desolate beast's corpse.

"Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei, making me spend three times the price to buy this bat corpse. I will remember this."

Shi Lei was a higher up of Combat Immortal Sect, which was one of the ten great ancient sects. During his previous life's five regions chaotic war, after Feng Jiu Ge died, he replaced Feng Jiu Ge as the most powerful rank seven in Central Continent. He was an earth path expert but cultivated transformation path as well, having secretly obtained several inheritances of Reckless Savage Demon Venerable.

Fang Yuan thought of raising the price of guts Gu to Combat Immortal Sect, but he dispelled this thought after pondering about it.

For the next half a month, he concentrated on handling the bat desolate beast's corpse.

He carefully cut apart the bat wings and did more than a dozen sessions of meticulous treatment and maintenance.

He then used fire path and strength path Gu worms to constantly temper the bat wings; as a result, the extremely wide bat wings gradually became more condensed and small.

Finally, after Fang Yuan endured intense pain, he finally succeeded in transplanting the bat wings onto his back.

Chapter 713: True Solid Bat Wings

A wind wolf had its head lowered, its four limbs were stealthily moving as it traveled in the lush grassland.

The prey that it was targeting was a pink flower rabbit.

The rabbit's two ears were standing on end, listening to every movement nearby. The rabbit's head was buried in the flowers, eating pollen as food.

As a cool breeze blew on this mountain, flowers blossomed in this lush greenery, giving off waves of fragrant smells.

The wind wolf slowly got closer, but the pink flower rabbit had no idea.

Suddenly, a black shadow flew past the ground rapidly.

The pink flower rabbit was shocked, it raised its head. Even though Hu Immortal blessed land had no eagle groups, it sprinted away in fear, managing to survive this trial, causing the wind wolf to fail in its hunt.

Fang Yuan, who was flying in the air, observed all of this.

He could not help but start to think: "Right now, I have ample funds, and my own blessed land has turned into a dead aperture, I might as well manage this Hu Immortal blessed land first. After the journey in Northern Plains, the beast groups in Hu Immortal blessed land had fallen in numbers, becoming very sparse. Right now, I am already selling guts Gu, the rockmen transaction is simply unnecessary."

"Hu Immortal was an enslavement path Gu Immortal, Hu Immortal blessed land has a grassland landscape, it is most suited for raising fox groups. If I raise the vitality of Hu Immortal blessed land and make it flourish with life, when I revive, I would gain much greater benefits if I fuse this Hu Immortal blessed land."

Thinking so, Fang Yuan inspected the bat wings on his back.

This was the third time he had tested out flying with these newly transplanted bat wings on his back.

The processed bat wings, if spread fully, were not even half of Fang Yuan's arm length. They were yellow-brown in color, and were quite petite, they seemed much less impressive than the prior light illusion bat wings.

But Fang Yuan did not care about appearance, he only looked at its value and usefulness.

The new light illusion bat wings gave Fang Yuan almost double the speed boost, at the same time, the duration of his flight had greatly increased. After all, the bat wings back then were only a phantom, the bat wings now were real physical wings.

The flesh, skin, fur, bones, and blood were all condensed and refined. There were also many Gu worms inside these wings.

The Gu worms residing in the bat wings were used to activate the newly modified movement killer move, light illusion bat wings.

"No, right now, using the name light illusion bat wings for this killer move is no longer appropriate. I should call it true solid bat wings." Fang Yuan created a new name for this newly modified killer move.

He was more pleased with this movement killer move true solid bat wings than the lion fur armor.

If this movement killer move was sold in treasure yellow heaven, it could be sold for six immortal essence stones or more!

That was because true solid bat wings had much potential left, one pair of bat wings was not its limit. It could transplant three pairs of bat wings at most. The origin of these wings should be at least desolate beasts. Of course, ancient desolate beasts and immemorial desolate beasts would be even better.

If Fang Yuan could transplant three pairs of desolate beast bat wings on his back, his speed would be at least three times faster.

Light illusion bat wings was the most widely spread movement killer move during the five regions chaotic war due to its price to value ratio. On that basis, raising one's speed by three times as much would be even more impressive.

Even though it could not compare to movement Immortal Gu like Worldly Wave Trace, or Rising Azure Cloud, if Fang Yuan met Plump Lady again, her light sand escape would not allow her to run from Fang Yuan's assault.

As the winds blew intensely behind him, Fang Yuan flapped with his wings and flew up into the sky.

After flying to a high altitude in midair, Fang Yuan closed his eyes and felt the sensation of the air currents blowing on the bat wings silently.

His immortal zombie body could not feel any pain, his sense of touch was nearly non-existent. This was a strength and also a weakness.

When Fang Yuan transplanted the bat wings, he spent a lot of effort in order to retain the sense of pain and touch that the bat wings had. Only by doing this could he have a clearer and realistic feeling of the air when he flaps his wings, to feel the strength of the air currents, and to sense the state of the wings.

Losing the sense of pain numbed him and made Fang Yuan fight more fiercely.

But flying was another matter.

Flying required meticulous control, especially when Fang Yuan's flying attainment had reached quasi-grandmaster level. Only by regaining his sense of pain and touch could he truly display his actual flying attainment.

If it was a pair of zombified wings, the feeling would be very vague, especially in intense battles, when he needed to rely on the wings, sensitive nerves would allow him to react and adapt more easily, instead of being rough and careless.

"With a boost in movement strength, I will be able to advance or retreat at will. After I get three pairs of wings, true solid bat wings will be an exceptional mortal killer move, it would only lose out to worldly wave trace Immortal Gu."

Fang Yuan was a strength path Gu Immortal, he obtained a strength path immortal body. Worldly wave trace Immortal Gu had the law of water path, when Fang Yuan uses this Immortal Gu, water path and strength path do not work together perfectly, there was a problem of them restricting each other.

If a fire path Gu Immortal uses worldly wave trace Immortal Gu, his speed would be even slower than Fang Yuan.

The most suitable would be water path Gu Immortals, when they use this same Gu, by expending the same amount of immortal essence, they would achieve greater speed.

Most importantly, true solid bat wings was a mortal killer move, compared to using worldly wave trace Immortal Gu, it had a much greater value to cost ratio.

This was the intelligence of humans.

Using the combination of many mortal Gu, they could achieve an effect that was only somewhat below Immortal Gu.

Using Gu, nurturing Gu, and refining Gu, they were extremely profound and deep.

"The corpse of a desolate beast is rarely seen, even if Gu Immortals sell new beast corpses in treasure yellow heaven, they might not be bats. To collect two more pairs of bat wings, I would need to actively seek them. It seems that now, I should take some risks and go to Starry Sky grotto-heaven."

The immortal aperture of a rank eight or nine was known as a grotto-heaven.

The owner of Starry Sky grotto-heaven was a rank eight Gu Immortal from one thousand and seven hundred years ago, Seven Star Child.

Seven Star Child had died long ago, during Fang Yuan's previous life, one day, Starry Sky grotto-heaven fell from high up in Central Continent, it broke up into tens of immortal aperture fragments, and was scattered all over Central Continent.

Fang Yuan had already become a Gu Immortal, he could not enter these grotto-heaven fragments.

These fragment worlds of the grotto-heaven were already very fragile, Fang Yuan's cultivation level was too high and if he tried entering one, it would destroy the extremely unstable grotto-heaven fragment.

Thankfully, Fang Yuan had a bunch of elite subordinates in Blood Wing Demon Sect.

After competing with several Gu Immortals, they split a relatively large grotto-heaven fragment world between themselves.

Fang Yuan and the other immortals sent their respective Gu Master disciples or subordinates towards the grotto-heaven fragment world to explore and find resources.

Fang Yuan left a will in each of his capable subordinates' minds to direct and supervise them.

Thus, he was rather familiar with the scenery inside Starry Sky grotto-heaven.

"In this life, currently, Starry Sky grotto-heaven is still high up in the sky, it had not fallen or broken into pieces. The scenery of Starry Sky grotto-heaven in my mind will allow me to use Fixed Immortal Travel to enter the grotto-heaven in advance, to take the resources inside. I remember that there were a number of desolate beasts inside the grotto-heaven, there were even ancient desolate beasts and among them, there was a star demon bat desolate beast. My goal this time is to go and kill the star demon bat, and obtain the wings. At the same time, I can check the situation and see if I can capture a desolate beast and bring it to Lang Ya land spirit." Fang Yuan planned in his mind.

There were still many places in Fang Yuan's memories that were similar to this Starry Sky grotto-heaven.

But for some, now was not the time yet, and others were simply too dangerous.

Starry Sky grotto-heaven was the immortal aperture of a rank eight Gu Immortal, it had not reached the point of breaking down like in Fang Yuan's previous life, it was still very strong now.

"In my previous life, I only sent people to indirectly explore the grotto-heaven fragment world. By that time, the heavenly spirit was no longer around. But in this life, if I go now, the heavenly spirit is sure to be alive, it can summon the entire defensive power of Starry Sky grotto-heaven. If I had not become an immortal zombie, I would not have the qualifications to explore it."

Fang Yuan did not know too much about the current Starry Sky grotto-heaven, he could only deduce it based on his previous life's experiences.

In his previous life, he was not the person who benefited the most from this opportunity. It was a rank eight immortal zombie who rose up as a result of this. The ten great ancient sects which had been extremely forceful all along suffered a loss under the hands of this immortal zombie.

Next, this immortal zombie entered the Central Continent Zombie Alliance branch, and easily defeated the branch leader, becoming the one in charge and calling himself Star Constellation immortal zombie.

He had been the cause of many incidents, during the five regions chaotic war, he was an overlord that could hold his own in his territory.

As for the real Starry Sky heavenly spirit, Fang Yuan did not see it, and did not know the conditions for the grotto-heaven to belong to a new owner.

A few days later, Hei Lou Lan brought strength qi Immortal Gu and entered Hu Immortal blessed land using a stargate. Next, in Fang Yuan's stone nest, she and Fang Yuan, together with the thousands of hairy men, refined the eighth batch of airsac Gu.

After this, Hei Lou Lan did not leave immediately, instead she stayed in Hu Immortal blessed land and listened to Fang Yuan's information on Starry Sky grotto-heaven.

With Fang Yuan's current strength, it was rather dangerous to enter Starry Sky grotto-heaven.

Thus, Fang Yuan invited his allies.

But Fairy Li Shan was cooperating with Qin Bai Sheng right now, her mountain pledge Gu was having great use at this time, it allowed Qin Bai Sheng to gather his forces and eliminate the enmity of his foes, he was preparing for a Northern Plains auction that was of unprecedented scale.

Qin Bai Sheng's compensation to Fairy Li Shan was an Immortal Gu.

With such great benefits, Fairy Li Shan obviously chose Qin Bai Sheng and gave up on working with Fang Yuan this time.

As for Tai Bai Yun Sheng, he was with Shark Demon now, entering the sea and exploring Yu Lu blessed land.

Even thought Tai Bai Yun Sheng wanted to help his 'junior brother' Fang Yuan, he was afflicted with death sentence awaits Immortal Gu, and could not split himself into two, there was nothing he could do to help.

Only Hei Lou Lan was free now, she agreed with Fang Yuan to explore Starry Sky grotto-heaven together.

According to the Snowy Mountain Alliance, since the two were exploring and taking the risk together, any losses to Hei Lou Lan would not require Fang Yuan to compensate her twice the amount. At the same time, their gains would be split into Fang Yuan getting sixty percent, and Hei Lou Lan getting forty percent.

After resting for a few days in Hu Immortal blessed land, Hei Lou Lan entered Fang Yuan's immortal aperture.

Fang Yuan tried to activate Fixed Immortal Travel with the image in his mind.

He tried for three or four times, but he did not succeed.

Fang Yuan was not surprised.

The image in his memories, although it was a portion of Starry Sky grotto-heaven, it had already fallen at that time, and the scenery had changed drastically.

Thankfully, Fang Yuan had many images in his memories.

After trying for a dozen times, after he spent more than ten beads of green grape immortal essence, he finally succeeded.

With a flash of jade green light, at the next moment, he appeared inside Starry Sky grotto-heaven.

Chapter 714: Fighting Star Desolate Hound

They appeared before a thick forest which was verdant and lush, the foot of the mountain was serene and fog filled the place.

Fang Yuan had already activated lion fur armor to protect him tightly. He used all his concentration to quickly scan his surroundings and discovered that he had appeared on the waist of a mountain.

Surrounding him were tall ancient trees, and even his six meter tall immortal zombie body could not reach one-third of these giant trees.

Raising his head, he gazed at the sky through the opening between the lush leaves.

The sky was a tranquil green color. There were six giant shadows of stars in the green sky, they appeared to be six round moons in the color of red, brown, yellow, blue, purple and white.

Fang Yuan opened his immortal aperture, and Hei Lou Lan shortly appeared outside, stepping on the mountain stones.

Her eyes flashed with bright light as she looked around: "This is inside Starry Sky grotto-heaven?"

"It is indeed, let's go. The desolate beast that I want to kill, star demon bat, should be nearby."

The two did not know the exact location of the star demon bat, thus they casually chose a direction and moved along it.

While moving forward, the two used investigative methods to scan around them all the time. After advancing to a Gu Immortal, they had unlimited primeval essence and could use mortal Gu freely.

The two had also made ample preparations before they had come here.

Although they did not have investigative killer moves, they had prepared large numbers of investigative Gu worms of all paths to not only enhance their vision and hearing, but also to sense the slight tremors when they walked, and to smell any odd odors when they breathed. At the same time, they spread out their divine senses to cover their surroundings, attaining completion in all aspects of scouting.

Time flowed little by little, but this forest did not seem to have any end.

"Five minutes have already gone by, there seems to be something wrong!" Hei Lou Lan stopped and solemnly asked Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan nodded, saying in a deep voice: "Indeed, we have already been in Starry Sky grotto-heaven for some time now but haven't actually encountered a single wild beast. There are only trees or fog. Whether we go up the mountain or down, or move in any direction, things all look the same."

Hei Lou Lan looked up: "Let's fly."

The two carefully flew up.

The green sky was completely empty; if the two flew high up, they would be very conspicuous and it would be extremely easy for them to be discovered by beast groups and get surrounded.

Thus for safety purposes, Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan had chosen to move along the ground.

Right now, the two took the risk to attempt flying, but the result was disappointing.

The higher they flew up, the thicker the fog became. Finally, the fog became so thick that they could not even see their own fingers.

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan's investigative methods were greatly restricted in this fog.

The two discussed and chose to be cautious, not willing to continue taking this risk, they descended to the ground.

"Has the Starry Sky heavenly spirit already begun to target us?" Hei Lou Lan guessed.

"The situation here, if it is not a unique law of the grotto-heaven, then it is an illusion, quietly disturbing our sense of direction and obstructing our true senses. Unfortunately, I don't have any investigative killer moves." Fang Yuan replied.

"Don't you have wisdom path methods?" Wisdom path is also specialized in resolving these kinds of circumstances." Hei Lou Lan asked while frowning.

Fang Yuan shook his head: "I indeed have some wisdom path methods, but they are rather special, they cannot deduce directions. How about you, do you have any investigative killer moves?"

Hei Lou Lan snorted lightly and raised her two delicate fists: "I don't have any investigative killer moves, but I do have offensive killer moves! Self Strength!"

She suddenly punched out with her two fists, sending out majestic fist qi.

The fist qi surged all around and rapidly condensed into strength path phantoms.

These strength path phantoms had fat bodies like bears with triangular eyes and jagged teeth. It was the male shape Hei Lou Lan had disguised as before.

Fang Yuan took a few steps back to give Hei Lou Lan sufficient space.

These strength path phantoms pounced at Hei Lou Lan's main body. The phantoms merged together and soon covered Hei Lou Lan, forming a giant strength path phantom.

This killer move had astonishing might, Hei Lou Lan had used it before in Northern Plains to destroy the flying bear phantom.

She again raised a fist.

The giant fist ruthlessly smashed at an ancient tree on the side.

The thick and sturdy ancient tree immediately broke into two; the lower half remained at the ground but was shaking intensely, the soil around it splattered to reveal the tree roots. The upper half was directly sent flying, cutting through the wind as it collided with another ancient tree, smashing two to three branches.

Boom boom boom...

Hei Lou Lan punched and kicked, the heavy punches and kicks shook the earth, stones flew, trees toppled down and the fog dispersed.

Fang Yuan flew into the sky, his sight was now much more clear.

He saw this forest only had the range of a hundred li, he and Hei Lou Lan had been moving in a circle.

Outside of this forest, he saw a scene abundant in nature and life; the wild beasts roaming around, the cries of birds and insects, the gurgling of streams and wild flowers swaying with the wind.

"It seems this forest itself was special, it should be an extinct tree species. Your information source is somewhat dubious, our entry was actually in this forest." The giant strength path phantom transmitted its divine sense to communicate with Fang Yuan.

Even Fang Yuan, with his plentiful experiences from his previous life and broad vision, did not recognize the origin of this kind of tree.

He gave a bitter laugh and changed the topic: "After the trees became sparse, this forest no longer has the bewilderment effect. We should take some and plant it in our own blessed lands, maybe we can make some profits."

There was absolutely no issue with the information source.

Because he himself was the information supplier.

In his previous life, Starry Sky grotto-heaven had shattered into many parts which then fell towards Central Continent. When Fang Yuan had sent people to explore the grotto-heaven's fragment world, this forest was already in a different shape, much of it had been damaged and thus it did not show any special effects.

This was an warning to Fang Yuan — although he had previous life's memories, however he had come early to Starry Sky grotto-heaven in this life, the situation was different, and he could not blindly rely on these memories.

The giant strength path phantom gazed at these ancient trees: "Even if you had not said it, I intended to do it."

When the two had just taken four to five trees, a dog shaped desolate beast charged down from the top of the mountain.

The dog shaped desolate beast growled, not concealing the fierce glare of its eyes as it looked directly at Hei Lou Lan. Hei Lou Lan's strength path phantom giant was not concealed by the trees and was exceptionally conspicuous.

Fang Yuan looked at the source of the growl and saw the desolate beast. Its body was as large as a small hill, and glossy azure fur covered it. Whether it was its head, stomach, back, tail or its limbs, they were all covered with star shaped stripes. These stripes were emitting faint blue radiance.

Fang Yuan recognized this beast with just one glance, immediately reminding Hei Lou Lan: "This is a star desolate hound, it should be this mountain's overlord. Let's check how powerful the desolate beasts in Starry Sky grotto-heaven are. If it is weak, don't kill it, it is best if we capture it alive, I have other uses for it!"

Hei Lou Lan frowned.

She had an extreme physique strength path immortal body and possessed several great strength path Immortal Gu; it was not difficult for her to kill a desolate beast, but she still had some difference between the level of capturing a desolate beast alive.

However, Fang Yuan continued: "You take the lead, I will support. Decide it according to the situation, if we can really capture it alive, I will use immortal essence stones to pay you."

"Alright, then let's do it like that." Hei Lou Lan was not an irresolute person, with a loud shout, the giant strength path phantom took large and loud steps as it charged towards the star desolate hound.

The star desolate hound fiercely charged down from above and pounced at the giant strength path phantom.

Hei Lou Lan was not to be outdone and immediately punched and kicked, clashing with the star desolate hound. The two huge figures rolled down from partway up the mountain towards the foot, like a rolling gourd.

It was like a giant compactor had steamrolled through a path, as the trees were toppled, protruding boulders were smashed and beast and birds who had not time to escape were crushed into paste.

Fang Yuan flapped his bat wings and flew down.

Eight lumps of starlight condensed separately on his eight monstrous claws, but they did not crash down yet.

Hei Lou Lan's giant strength path phantom was rolling and turning around at times as it clashed with the star desolate hound, like a rolling wheel. The fight was fierce but the situation was still not decided, the attacks moved so quickly that even an old demon like Fang Yuan was not able to find an opportunity to interfere.

Rumble...

Dust flew up, the giant phantom and the desolate beast rolled down to the foot of the mountain before finally stopping.

The star desolate hound fiercely pounced on the giant phantom. It raised its head and opened its mouth, revealing the snow-white canines that were as sharp as swords and long as halberds, and bit down.

Fang Yuan saw the chance, his eight arms moved and the eight lumps of starlight that had accumulated enough energy slammed down.

Bam bam bam...

A series of explosions resounded, the star desolate hound furiously barked, its attack was interrupted.

The giant hound head shook in every direction, flinging off the starlight lumps.

However, Hei Lou Lan obtained the critical opportunity due to this, letting out a fierce attack.

The giant strength path phantom bent its knee and fiercely struck a crucial part between the star desolate hound's rear legs.

Howl——!

The star desolate hound immediately let out an extremely painful cry, its giant body fiercely jumped like it had been electrocuted and bounced around in the lush forest.

Fang Yuan immediately fluttered over, not giving the star desolate hound any time to recover.

He flapped his wings in the sky, moving nimbly like a fly as he threw down lumps of starlight right at the star desolate hound's vital areas like eyes, mouth and anus.

The star desolate hound bounced around everywhere but it was gradually not able to hide from Fang Yuan's crafty attacks and started to whine in pain.

The star desolate hound had defensive wild Gu on it.

But facing a killer move like icy drill stardust, a defense from ordinary wild Gu would not work, instead the defensive Gu would rapidly die when facing icy drill stardust.

Hei Lou Lan controlled her giant strength path phantom and stood up.

"As expected of a desolate beast." Hei Lou Lan sighed in her heart.

The strength path killer move that had never failed her before was actually not able to resist the tyrannical strength of the star desolate hound. Especially this giant strength path phantom, which was the pinnacle transformation of her killer move, and yet was actually not a match against the star desolate hound in terms of strength.

"Since that is the case, then let me use self strength Immortal Gu." Hei Lou Lan gave a sinister smile and was about to attack.

Suddenly, familiar barks came down from the nearby two mountain peaks.

Shortly afterwards, two female star desolate hounds charged into Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan's sight.

Fang Yuan's movement slowed down, Hei Lou Lan's pupils shrunk, and as if they had identical thoughts in mind, they transmitted the same message to each other: "Run!"

Chapter 715: Diamond Soil

Three star desolate hounds chased, as Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan retreated along the way.

It was not that they could not defeat the three desolate beasts, but they would have to engage in fierce combat and expend a lot of effort to defeat them.

As Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan were inside an unfamiliar environment like Starry Sky grotto-heaven, they would not want to fight with their full strength randomly, especially not against these desolate beasts which they had met by chance, only a fool would do such a thing.

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan were experienced schemers, this trip of exploring Starry Sky grotto-heaven needed to be handled with caution, they had to preserve their battle strength to deal with unexpected situations.

Especially when the heavenly spirit of Starry Sky grotto-heaven had not shown itself yet.

The heavenly spirit controlled all aspects of the grotto-heaven, when Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan entered, they would have been detected already.

Fang Yuan led the way, flapping his wings continuously, he was extremely fast. He did not dare to fly at high altitude, he only flew near the ground.

Hei Lou Lan was much slower than Fang Yuan, she was behind him as she deeply looked at his wings, thinking and comparing in her heart: "Fang Yuan's current speed is not outstanding, I can reach it. But he can move and maneuver so agilely and precisely, he can swerve around the branches of the trees so freely."

After nearly ten li of flying, the three star desolate hounds behind them stopped and gave up on Hei Lou Lan and Fang Yuan, no longer chasing them.

The two stopped at a tall tree and took a small rest to recover.

Fang Yuan stood on the crown of the tree, trying to decipher their direction, the surrounding mountains were not far from each other, yet they were independent and distinct.

Some mountain peaks had green pines growing on them. Some had only shrubs. Some had no trees and only had weeds and wild flowers — all these were man made arrangements, nature would not have made things so organized.

Fang Yuan could tell.

The owner of Starry Sky grotto-heaven, Seven Star Child, had categorized these mountain peaks into independent areas to nurture different vegetation. This way, he could raise the productivity of specialized products.

"It seems that the owner of this grotto-heaven had spent quite some effort on managing it." Hei Lou Lan walked over, standing beside Fang Yuan and observing the area.

Fang Yuan instead frowned.

This landscape was simply too different from the one in his memories. Did that mean that hundreds of years later, there would be a huge change to Starry Sky grotto-heaven's terrain, causing it to be completely different after it broke apart and collapsed?

This way, Fang Yuan's previous life's memories could not give him any precious help.

Hei Lou Lan directed her gaze towards the small bat wings on Fang Yuan's back, asking with great interest: "Your killer move is not bad, where did you buy it?"

According to the Snowy Mountain Alliance, Fang Yuan could not lie to Hei Lou Lan, but he could choose to not talk about it.

However, true solid bat wings was an ordinary technique of Fang Yuan's, he did not need to hide it.

He answered plainly: "This killer move is based on an improvement of my previous killer move, suited for my immortal zombie body. If you want to use it, you will need to transplant a pair of bat wings onto your back."

Hei Lou Lan heard this and frowned, though not because she was concerned over destroying her image, she pursued strength: "The body of a desolate beast is also an immortal body. Just like the bodies of us Gu Immortals, their bodies contain dao marks and are closer to certain laws. Your pair of bat wings should not have the dao marks of strength path, they are closer to wind path. Transplanting them casually like this, are you not afraid that there would be a conflict between strength path and wind path, resulting in your strength path killer moves weakening?"

Fang Yuan chuckled: "You know about how Reckless Savage Demon Venerable can transform into all sorts of fierce beasts, right?"

"Of course. Reckless Savage Demon Venerable created transformation path, he was the progenitor of transformation path." Hei Lou Lan answered.

"The essence of transformation path is to transform one's own body into a fierce beast or plant, and obtain their strength and abilities at the same time. A transformation path Gu Master can become a wind path bird, fire path tiger, or water path fish, using just one path to project countless paths. Why do their dao marks not interfere with one another?" Fang Yuan asked.

Transformation path Gu Masters who solely transform their bodies had not truly ventured into transformation path.

A truly successful transformation was not only changing one's appearance, but also gaining the beast's respective dao marks.

Gu Immortals who become desolate beasts not only have the strength, defense, and speed of the desolate beast itself, they can even amplify the effect of Gu worms in their respective paths.

"That is because, every time they transform, they will turn into a single fierce beast, they would only have one type of dao mark on their bodies, it is unlike you who has two types of dao marks mixing together, like a Gu Master trying to cultivate two paths. Furthermore, after they transform, they will use their relevant Gu worms to cleanse their bodies, removing all of their current dao marks, before they can transform into a fierce beast which has another dao mark." Hei Lou Lan said.

Fang Yuan laughed arrogantly: "No, that is because they are not good enough yet, their methods are lacking. Reckless Savage Demon Venerable was not like this, he ate immemorial desolate beasts and formed desolate beast totems on his body, encompassing countless dao marks in his body, allowing him to transform at will. When you were undergoing your tribulation, I obtained the true meaning infusions of the Demon Venerable, I have already become a transformation path master."

Hei Lou Lan was truly shocked: "That is to say, you obtained pointers from Reckless Savage Demon Venerable, you have a method to balance different dao marks?"

Fang Yuan nodded, but shook his head soon after: "I am only at master realm, I can only balance three different dao marks. I am also limited by physical transplantation and other restrictions, true solid bat wings can only have up to three pairs of wings, that is the greatest display of my current transformation path master realm attainment."

Hei Lou Lan heard Fang Yuan's words and gained much interest in true solid bat wings: "Sell this movement killer move to me, I will purchase it at a high price!"

Fang Yuan shook his head, rejecting her.

He had modified this killer move after much effort, it was his unique method, how could he give it to someone else?

Unless he no longer needed it in the future, then he would consider selling the simplified version.

Hei Lou Lan was slightly disappointed that Fang Yuan rejected her, but she was not surprised. If their roles were swapped, she would have rejected him as well.

Fang Yuan did not lack immortal essence stones currently.

"I finally understand why you want to kill star demon bats now. What does your information say? A star demon bat is nearby?" Hei Lou Lan asked.

Fang Yuan nodded: "From my information, it is close by. But the terrain here is slightly different, let's look around first."

He had surveyed for a long time, but he could not confirm the location.

The place in his memory was a rotten swamp with poisonous air. But here, there were mountains independent of each other, how could there be a rotten swamp?

Two hours later.

Two figures were attacking a desolate beast.

This desolate beast's body was transparent, like it was made of diamond, its figure resembled a bear, but it was as large as a mammoth, it was a diamond bear that was rarely seen in the five regions.

It was Hei Lou Lan and Fang Yuan fighting the diamond bear.

"Take this." Fang Yuan flew in the air, his eight arms were moving around as they sent out lumps of starlight specks.

The diamond bear stood up, waving its paws and smashing the starlight completely.

Hei Lou Lan transformed into the strength path phantom giant again, she raised her leg and kicked at the diamond bear's belly.

The diamond bear growled, as its diamond-like body shined, Hei Lou Lan's giant strength path phantom's right leg broke.

"This diamond bear's body contains wild Gu worms that counter my strength path giant!" Hei Lou Lan was shocked, retreating immediately.

Killer moves were not invincible, they had weaknesses and could be countered.

But the diamond bear did not want to let Hei Lou Lan go, it pounced in her direction.

Fang Yuan saw this and immediately rushed over, the starlight lumps in his hands were shot out more quickly, like the pelting of raindrops.

At once, the diamond bear was unable to raise its head from the attacks.

"Here's a big one, enjoy it." Fang Yuan raised four of his arms up, summoning a huge icy drill stardust lump that he threw it down.

With a loud explosion, the entire diamond bear was covered by the icy drill stardust.

The diamond bear was assaulted by the stardust, it growled in pain, it had become greatly angered.

Boom!

At the next moment, it charged out of the starlight lump, flying into the sky.

"This bear could fly?" Fang Yuan was the closest to it, caught off guard, he was hit by the diamond bear's raised paws.

Bam.

At the next moment, Fang Yuan was like a cannonball, he flew out, crashing into dozens of large trees before stopping.

His zombie blood was pouring out, with two of the arms used to block the bear paw having been cut off, and three were fractured.

Fang Yuan's mouth twitched, accidents were bound to happen when fighting desolate beasts.

Desolate beasts were not like Gu Immortals, they did not have much intelligence, but as for which wild Gu they had in their bodies, one could not tell upon first contact.

Like earlier, the diamond bear actually dispelled Hei Lou Lan's strength path phantom and flew into the air, causing heavy injuries to Fang Yuan.

Only after suffering some injuries did Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan learn that the diamond bear had very powerful Gu worms on it, not only were there Gu worms that countered the strength path phantom, it even had flying Gu that could raise such a heavy body into the air.

"Retreat!" Fang Yuan shouted to Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan had the intention to retreat already, she stopped her killer move and escaped with Fang Yuan.

The diamond bear did not chase after them, it picked up Fang Yuan's two arms and placed them into its mouth, chewing.

Crack, crack...

The diamond bear's teeth were sharp, they easily broke Fang Yuan's immortal zombie arms. It continued to chew, turning the arms into minced meat.

The green zombie blood flowed out from the space between the diamond bear's teeth, and an intense stench spread out.

The diamond bear swallowed the zombie meat with a weird expression, but it immediately opened its mouth and vomited the food that it had just eaten.

What a terrible taste!

The diamond bear had a constipated expression as it looked at Fang Yuan's remaining arm with disgust, slamming it into a mountain rock before moving back to its cave that was at the mountain peak grumpily.

A moment later, Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan sneakily returned.

Fang Yuan picked up the amputated arm, after verifying it, he placed it at a wound on his body.

He used healing Gu worms, and with the recovery ability of the immortal zombie, the amputated arm quickly connected to his wound.

As for the remaining arm, it was chewed up by the diamond bear, Fang Yuan could not use it, he sighed and had to regenerate it himself.

The immortal zombie body was not a mortal body, to regrow limbs, six to eight hours were needed. This was not simply a regrowth of body parts, the relevant strength path dao marks had to be replenished.

Hei Lou Lan looked at the cave entrance at the highest point of the mountain: "In that cave, there are at least fifteen kilograms of diamond soil left."

Diamond soil was formed from the feces of the diamond bear, it was filled with rich nutrients, and was one of the soils that could be sold for a high price in treasure yellow heaven.

Not long ago, Fang Yuan had come to this mountain peak with Hei Lou Lan. While Fang Yuan attracted the bear out of the cave, Hei Lou Lan sneaked in and took hundreds of kilograms of diamond soil, they were worth at least thirty immortal essence stones.

Fang Yuan shook his head: "Fifteen kilograms of diamond soil is not worth the risk. The first time was fine, but if we try a second time, with even more animosity, the diamond bear might not let us off. The diamond bear is sturdy and tough, we will need to pay a huge price to kill it. My goal is the star demon bat, since it is not in this direction, let's try another direction."

Chapter 716: Star Hall

Half a day later, Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan had almost searched through this area and seen many desolate beasts, but did not come across the star demon bat.

"Your information seems to be somewhat unreliable." Hei Lou Lan casually sat down on the ground and said while healing her wounds.

There was a long, bloody wound on her left arm which stretched from the back of her palm to her elbow.

This was the mark left behind from the encounter of Hei Lou Lan and Fang Yuan with a desolate beast flying sword rat.

The flying sword rat was small and extremely fast, a bit of carelessness resulted in it slashing its claws at them.

Even if Hei Lou Lan had the Great Strength True Martial Physique, having a strength path extreme immortal body, she had to struggle to heal this wound.

This was because the wound the flying sword rat caused was filled with dao marks of metal path, which were repelling the strength path dao marks of Hei Lou Lan's immortal body, and resisting the extreme immortal body's recovery ability.

A long while later, Hei Lou Lan was able to heal the wound and a thin layer of scab had formed on top of it.

She went up to Fang Yuan; Fang Yuan was sitting on the ground, using his iron-sharp fingernails to draw the outline of the terrain they had explored on a flat rock.

There were dozens of green mountain peaks. Most of the green peaks were the territory of a desolate beast, like the star desolate hound, flying sword rat, diamond bear and so on.

The mountain peaks with no desolate beasts had large numbers of beast groups as well as a sea of Gu worms living together.

Seven Star Child had clearly invested a great amount of effort to manage Starry Sky grotto-heaven, only then could such dense numbers of desolate beasts survive in this piece of territory.

However, the strange thing was there were no ancient desolate beasts.

Ancient desolate beasts were comparable in battle strength to a rank seven, according to common sense, there should be ancient desolate beasts in this outstandingly managed Starry Sky grotto-heaven.

This was only one of the strange aspects.

The second strange aspect was that the heavenly spirit had still not shown itself.

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan had explored all around and encountered many fights, but were able to smoothly free themselves.

Strictly speaking, they were invaders, but this Starry Sky grotto-heaven was behaving as if it had no heavenly spirit to manage it, and the suppression Fang Yuan had expected did not appear.

The third strange thing was that Fang Yuan could not find the poisonous swamp no matter where he searched.

According to his previous life's memories, the area he was in right now was the same as the small fragment world of the original grotto-heaven, which he had sent his subordinates to explore in his previous life.

Originally, the poisonous swamp should have been near that ancient tree forest, but Fang Yuan was not able to find it.

"Could it be that the poisonous swamp is part of the terrain that only appears after several hundred years? I came here this early, thus I am not able to find it? If that is the case, my plan to hunt star demon bat will end in failure."

Fang Yuan stared at the diagram of the terrain on the rock, and was pondering everything when suddenly a bright light shot out.

He and Hei Lou Lan raised their heads at the same time and looked at the green sky; unknowingly, the sky was filled with countless star specks.

The amount of this starlight grew rapidly and continued to grow. In a blink of an eye, the starlight filled the whole world, drifting in disorderly fashion like snow.

"This is an astronomical change that occurs only in grotto-heavens." Fang Yuan stood up with an alert gaze, activating lion fur armor.

Hei Lou Lan also activated her defensive killer move with a vigilant mind.

The bright starlight shone on all living beings; beast roars resounded from each mountain peak, some clear, some crisp, some long and some hoarse.

Wind surged, the endless specks of starlight suddenly converged on top of a mountain.

After a dazzling blue radiance was sent out, the star specks dispersed and a resplendent giant hall, exquisite and gorgeous, appeared on the mountain peak.

"This hall...." Fang Yuan's pupils enlarged, as he felt a great sense of familiarity with the structure of the hall. It clearly resembled the ruins that had been left behind in the shattered worlds of the grotto-heaven, which had spread everywhere during his previous life.

It was only that the former ruins now showed no trace of damage.

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan glanced at each other, Hei Lou Lan guessed: "Did the astronomical change occur due to some specific timing and result in the appearance of the hall?"

"Or did the heavenly spirit intentionally set up a trap to lure us in?" Fang Yuan eyes flashed with bright light.

The two only hesitated for a moment before deciding to go in the star hall.

At the same time, in another area of Starry Sky grotto-heaven.

An intense battle was nearing its climax.

"Foul beast, take this king's fist!" A rockman that was as tall as a hill shouted as it smashed down its fist, wind surged and even the air burst.

The desolate beast flying bear could not dodge in time, its head was struck by the giant stone fist and with a loud sound, it crashed down on the ground, smashing a large crater. Stones and soil flew all around, dust surged up and the earth shook for a while.

The rocky giant did not stop, it spread open its two fists then smashed down from high up.

Bam. The two palms heavily smashed at the flying bear's thick, snow-white body.

The flying bear tried to budge but it was not able to let out even a cry. It was already filled with injuries, the punch just before had cracked its skull and caused it to be on the brink of losing consciousness.

Immortal killer move — Earth's Root!

From the center of his two palms, earth qi bubbled, and countless thick and sharp earth spikes protruded out from the ground like spears.

Plop...

The desolate beast flying bear was pierced through instantly by hundreds of earth spikes.

In its last burst of energy, it raised its head, opened its eyes and let out a mournful cry before its energy was completely spent, its body stiffened and its head fell back down to the ground.

Dong. A sound like that of a drum being struck resounded, with dust rising and falling.

An intense scent of hot blood erupted, as it flowed down the stone pillar and quickly dyed the ground red.

The flying bear was dead.

The rocky giant snorted, it suddenly emitted a piercing light. After the light dispersed, a Gu Immortal proudly stood in the air while crossing his arms.

He had short white hair, a pair of golden pupils, broad shoulders and a thin waist. He wore a tight fitting combat uniform and a valiant aura was emitted from him.

A ray of starlight shot over, transforming into a middle-aged man. He was wearing a long robe with wide sleeves and a high hat on his head. He clapped his hands and praised: "As expected of Lord Immortal Monkey King, killing the desolate beast flying bear in just three minutes."

The white haired man with golden pupils was a rank seven Gu Immortal of Combat Immortal Sect, Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei.

Shi Lei looked at the middle-aged man with an indifferent gaze: "Seven star halls have already appeared, Star Lord Wan Xiang, the eighth star hall you spoke of, why has it still not opened?"

This middle-aged man was Star Lord Wan Xiang, who had traded with Fang Yuan several times.

Star Lord Wan Xiang gave a bright smile: "Immortal Monkey King, there's no need to worry. We can only make the eighth star hall appear when we have killed enough desolate beasts and let their blood seep into the ground. We have already killed six desolate beasts but the amount of blood is still not enough."

"How much more desolate beasts should we kill exactly?" Shi Lei asked impatiently.

Star Lord Wan Xiang revealed a thoughtful expression and said after a pause: "According to my annual explorations over the past twenty years and my own speculations, we probably only need to kill one more desolate beast."

"Hmph! You better not deceive me." Shi Lei replied in an overbearing manner.

Star Lord Wan Xiang lowered his head: "I am just a lone cultivator, even if I had ten times the guts, I would not dare to deceive Lord Immortal Monkey King. Based on Central Continent's time, I can only forcibly break into this star path Grotto-Heaven during this point of the year. Moreover, the duration we can stay is only two days, after these two days, the small opening leading to the grotto-heaven will close up and we won't be able to exit. Why would I deceive you when time is so limited? I also want to plunder more resources, but several years ago, I accidentally saw the eighth star hall, that hall was covered in a foreboding atmosphere. The guards of the star hall were all ancient desolate beasts, it definitely is the central control point of this grotto-heaven and it is very likely for the heavenly spirit to be there."

Shi Lei nodded, he believed Star Lord Wan Xiang's words.

He has known Star Lord Wan Xiang for some time and was familiar with the latter's nature.

"Sigh, if not because I had a huge battle with Song Zi Xing and spent large numbers of immortal essence, and that I urgently require large amounts of immortal essence stones to covert into immortal essence due to my blessed land's approaching tribulation, I would not have told such a huge secret to you." Star Lord Wan Xiang sighed.

Shi Lei's tone softened: "Don't worry, I will abide by the agreement, eighty percent of this exploration's battle spoils will go to you while I take twenty percent. Also, I will not tell anyone else about this secret. Later, we will come to explore this grotto-heaven every year."

Right now, only Star Lord Wan Xiang had the special method to enter Starry Sky grotto-heaven, Shi Lei still had not grasped the method.

"Lord Shi Lei has an outstanding reputation, I can be at ease. According to my past explorations, there is a star demon bat not far away and it is rather easy to kill."

"Alright, let's go there. Old rules; when fighting, you stand to the side, don't interfere." Shi Lei was very decisive and immediately started flying rapidly towards the destination.

Star Lord Wan Xiang laughed bitterly while hurriedly following behind.

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan cautiously entered the star hall.

This star hall had no defenses, there was no one inside, only six large wells in the center of the main hall.

Water was surging inside these six large wells.

The water in the wells were of different colors; red, brown, yellow, blue, purple and white. The well water was glittering and translucent, and emitted slight radiance.

Hei Lou Lan and Fang Yuan used investigative Gu worms to completely check them.

Their discovery was that the well water, the star hall, everything was as normal as they could be. This was naturally impossible. How could an ordinary hall appear out of thin air? How could ordinary well water be of different colors and emit light?

The only explanation was that the six well waters in this star hall were related to the grotto-heaven's astronomical transformations. If so, the mortal investigative Gu of Hei Lou Lan and Fang Yuan were not of high enough level to investigate anything.

The two were unable to distinguish the mysteries of the six wells, and fell into a predicament for a while.

"This color..." Hei Lou Lan observed again and could not help mumbling.

Fang Yuan knew what she was thinking. He remembered when they had just arrived in Starry Sky grotto-heaven, he had looked at the sky. He saw the shadows of six stars in the sky, they were as large as the full moon and were easy to notice.

These six star shadows were the colors of red, brown, yellow, blue, purple and white, the same as these six waters in the wells.

"What connection do they have?" Fang Yuan mumbled and sent a mortal storage Gu inside a well to take out some of the water to study.

However, when the mortal Gu entered the well water, the tranquil and calm well water suddenly moved and formed a whirlpool, swallowing the mortal Gu.

Chapter 717: Killing Star Demon Bat

The well water quickly settled down, there were no ripples, it was shining brightly.

But the mortal Gu that Fang Yuan tossed in had completely vanished into the water.

Fang Yuan knew that his mortal Gu had not been destroyed yet, because he could still sense its existence.

But this connection was very weak now.

The connection between a Gu Master and Gu worm had much to do with distance. The further the Gu worm is from the Gu Master, the weaker their connection. In that case, when a Gu Master uses the Gu, their mind would send orders, if they gave ten orders, nine might be missed and the Gu worm would only execute one.

Of course, this was in ordinary cases.

A small portion of Gu worms could maintain a strong connection over a huge distance, they could be easily activated even if they were far away. Some Gu worms were even more peculiar, the closer they were to the Gu Master, the weaker their connection, creating distance between them could improve their connection instead.

Fang Yuan originally had a close connection to the mortal Gu, but now the feeling was much weaker, it was like the two were very far apart.

Fang Yuan followed the connection in his mind, slowly deducing the direction and raising his head.

All he saw was the top of the walls in the star hall.

Fang Yuan activated his investigative Gu, in his field of vision, the roof of the star hall became translucent. Fang Yuan's gaze pierced through the roof of the star hall, seeing the six huge circular star shadows in the green sky.

He felt a sensation in his mind, his gaze remained on one of the star shadows. According to the remaining connection he had, he knew that the mortal Gu was on top of that star shadow!

...

Swoosh swoosh swoosh!

The star demon bat's huge wings whipped up fierce winds as countless arrows shot out at the same time.

These arrows were all made of starlight, they flew very quickly, piercing the air. Their numbers were high, flying towards Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei like a storm.

Seeing the large scale attack, Shi Lei scoffed in disdain: "Merely rank two star arrow Gu, except the numbers are a bit high."

Mortal killer move — Fallen Grey Cloak.

Shi Lei's body shook, as a thin layer of yellow-white smoke and dust covered him.

He did not dodge, he allowed the arrows to land on his body.

No matter how many star arrows came, they dissipated after coming into contact with the mortal killer move fallen grey cloak, vanishing in an instant.

The star demon bat lacked intelligence, it could not use killer moves. Although the scale of the wild Gu on its body was large, it could not use Gu in great quantity.

How could such an attack compare to a killer move that a human cultivator came up with painstakingly?

"This time, look at my eagle transformation!" Shi Lei shouted, his body shining in a bright golden light.

As the light dissipated, Shi Lei had vanished, in his place was a desolate beast iron crown eagle.

The iron crown eagle spread its wings, flying in the air, its sharp claws that resembled steel gave off an imposing aura. The size of its body was not any smaller than the star demon bat.

Far away, Star Lord Wan Xiang quietly observed the battle, seeing this, he sighed helplessly.

Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei was a battle maniac, he refused to fight together in each of these battles. Up to this point, Shi Lei had already killed eleven desolate beasts. Every time he fought a desolate beast, he would use a different type of transformation path killer move, to fight using the body of different desolate beasts.

Star Lord Wan Xiang was anxious about the time, he had urged Shi Lei to use his strongest methods. But Shi Lei rejected him, saying that he wanted to use this opportunity to accumulate transformation path battle experience, he did not want to waste any chance he had. By accumulating his foundations, he would eventually trigger a qualitative change, elevating his transformation path realm.

The iron crown eagle flew for a while, before screeching and pouncing towards the star demon bat.

The star demon bat was also screeching, its ruthless nature was awakened as it did not evade, it flapped its wings and collided with the iron crown eagle.

Two huge winged figures were clashing in the sky violently. The star demon bat bit with its mouth, while the iron crown eagle attacked with its beak. The star demon bat scratched with its claws, but the iron crown eagle's talons were just as sharp, they were evenly matched.

The two had exchanged many blows within a moment, they left many injures on each other's body. After a while, they pulled some distance between them.

The star demon bat shrieked loudly in a self-satisfied manner.

The iron crown eagle that Shi Lei had transformed into had lost most of its feathers, it flapped its wings and after much effort, it stabilized its body.

In the battle earlier, the iron crown eagle had suffered a loss, while the star demon bat had the upper hand.

Not only were most of its feathers gone, there was an injury on its stomach, filled with star path dao marks, it bled continuously and prevented the iron crown eagle's body from healing naturally.

Desolate beasts were different from Gu Immortals.

Gu Immortals had weak bodies, their strength rested in Gu worms. Even if strength path Gu Immortals made their bodies extremely strong, it was still from the effects of Gu worms.

Meanwhile, the strength of desolate beasts was in their own bodies. Desolate beasts have strength, defense, and other attributes from birth, this was something humans could only dream of. Especially when a desolate beast gets closer to nature during their growth, and develops more dao marks on their bodies. When they fight in battle, the injuries that desolate beasts cause will have dao marks lingering. Injuries involving dao marks were very hard to get rid of, not only did they resist the body's self healing, they also hindered the use and effect of healing Gu.

Of course, if the desolate beast had an Immortal Gu, the situation would be completely different.

The iron crown eagle shrieked, ignoring its injures and pouncing towards the star demon bat.

The two met in the sky again, after several attacks, the star demon bat found an opening and flapped its wings quickly, slamming on the iron crown eagle's head.

The iron crown eagle went into a daze, falling towards the ground.

The star demon bat flew in the air, flapping its wings thrice at the iron crown eagle.

The first one caused an intense wind to blow, as thousands of wind blades shot out.

The second caused a burst of starlight, over ten thousand star arrows flew out.

The third caused darkness to gather, forming a giant specter that charged towards the iron crown eagle.

The iron crown eagle first crashed onto the ground, causing rocks to fly and a crater to form. Next, after it raised its head, it was cut by the wind blades.

The iron crown eagle shrieked, it endured the attacks and did not retreat, after enduring the wind blade attacks, it had hundreds of light wounds on its body.

It wanted to flap its wings, but the star arrows flew over. These arrows had extraordinary strength, they pierced into the iron crown eagle's body and caused many wounds, but those were not deep.

Next, that specter which had no solid body drilled into the iron crown eagle's mind.

If it was any ordinary desolate beast, they would have been in trouble, but this iron crown eagle was Shi Lei's transformation.

Shi Lei snorted coldly, thoughts and wills moved in his head, destroying the specter in the blink of an eye.

Although he was an earth path Gu Immortal who also cultivated transformation path, he was an established expert, he was a veteran Gu Immortal, he learned a lot about many other paths and had a set of complete defensive measures against Gu worms of other paths.

"Lord Immortal Monkey King..." At the side, Star Lord Wan Xiang shouted in concern.

The iron crown eagle spoke human words, laughing loudly: "Don't interfere, stay at the side, this is my battle!"

Intense fire seemed to be burning in the eagle's eyes, with much determination, Shi Lei flapped his wings and flew up, towards the star demon bat, but was sent flying.

Bang, with a loud sound, the eagle crashed on the ground again.

"Good, interesting!" Shi Lei shouted, he got more excited as he fought, ignoring his injuries, he rushed up again.

He was fighting with something he was not familiar with, in terms of close combat, how could he be the star demon bat's match. In their fight, he quickly fell into a disadvantage.

But every time Shi Lei lost, he would battle again, the eagle's head would rise up highly, and the eagle eyes would always stare at its opponent.

"This maniac..." Star Lord Wan Xiang watched with a grimacing expression.

Shi Lei obviously had defensive moves like fallen grey cloak, but after transforming into the iron crown eagle, he did not use any of them in battle.

This had happened many times in his previous battles as well.

Star Lord Wan Xiang had asked earlier, but Shi Lei's answer was that he was purposely not using them, it was to experience the joy of battle with his own body, this would be the most effective way to raise his battle foundation.

Shi Lei was a battle-addict, he was a fierce man who derived pleasure from fighting.

"Again!" Shi Lei shouted, flapping his wings towards the star demon bat.

The two sides got closer rapidly, seeing that they were about to collide, the star demon bat suddenly flapped its wings, displaying an incredible flying ability, passing the iron crown eagle narrowly.

Whoosh!

The star demon bat suddenly breathed out a shooting star, hitting the iron crown eagle's back.

The iron crown eagle spat out some blood, its body shook as it had to flap its wings to stabilize itself. Next, Star Lord Wan Xiang heard Shi Lei laughing: "Interesting, bullying my flying attainment which is only master level?"

Saying so, he flapped his wings and rushed up.

The star demon bat did not take the attack directly, it retreated while using star path, wind path, or dark path Gu worms to attack its enemy from far away.

The two had fought for a long time, unknowingly, the star demon bat's body was filled with injuries. These injuries all had metal path dao marks, they could not heal any time soon.

Of course, the injuries on the iron crown eagle were at least twice as severe as the star demon bat.

But Shi Lei fought crazily, it struck fear in the star demon bat, this dominating desolate beast that ruled over a mountain felt some apprehension and did not dare to fight directly.

The star demon bat's intelligence was low, what it was doing was giving on its advantage and fighting with its weakness.

It had mortal Gu on it, although they could disturb Shi Lei, they were not as dangerous to him as fighting at close range.

The iron crown eagle did not use any defensive methods as usual, but its aura was surging as it dodged left and right, finally getting close to the star demon bat.

After shrieking loudly, the eagle claw grasped downwards at it.

The star demon bat dodged agilely, but Shi Lei found an opening.

In terms of flying attainment, the star demon bat which had been flying its entire life was at least a flying grandmaster.

The star demon bat pulled some distance, using Gu worms to attack at a range, while the iron crown eagle tried to get close to engage in close combat with it. In this fashion, the two fought for a while, the star demon bat was bound to mess up at some point, finally, the iron crown eagle found a flaw and used its eagle claws to tear the bat wings.

With a hole in the bat wings, the star demon bat's flying ability fell drastically. Before it could adapt to the injury, the iron crown eagle found even more flaws.

Shi Lei pursued it during this prime opportunity, after enduring the star demon bat's final struggle, he killed it.

The star demon bat landed on the ground, its blood was pouring like a river.

The ground absorbed the blood, just like what Star Lord Wan Xiang said, a formless energy had been activated.

In the sky, starlight appeared again.

Chapter 718: Starshine Fake Eye Gu

The specks of starlight coiled around and fluttered for a while before gathering high up in the air and forming a completely new star hall.

Different from the previous star halls, this star hall was floating in the air, its design was exquisite, giving off a majestic beauty that was far above those star halls on the mountains.

"The eighth star hall has finally appeared. My speculation was indeed correct!" Star Lord Wan Xiang spoke with excitement.

Shi Lei canceled the iron crown eagle transformation and returned to his human form. The injuries on his body were still recovering, the blood flow had yet to stop. He indifferently glanced at the sky with his golden pupils: "No wonder you guessed that this was the grotto-heaven's central control point, looking at its appearance, it is very likely to be that."

He grimaced in pain and sat down, healing the wounds.

His healing was in no way simple, he first used large numbers of Gu worms to eliminate the dao marks of star path, wind path, dark path and other paths that had filled the wounds, only then did he use healing Gu worms which showed visible effects.

Star Lord Wan Xiang waited for a little while and when he saw Shi Lei's injuries were roughly treated, he finally could not endure and urged him: "Your healing is almost done right? Time is limited, Lord Immortal Monkey King. The prerequisite for the eighth star hall to appear is that the other seven star halls should be formed first. Every time the seven star halls appear, they will only exist for fifteen minutes. When the seven star halls disappear, the eighth star hall will also disappear."

"Why are you in a hurry? If you are in such a rush, you can enter it first." Shi Lei opened his eyes and coldly glanced at Star Lord Wan Xiang.

"Lord Shi Lei is jesting, my battle strength has fallen to the depths, I still need to rely on lord to break through the ancient desolate beasts' defenses." Star Lord Wan Xiang chuckled and did not speak any further.

However, his fists that were hidden inside his sleeves were tightly clenched, if not for his strength plummeting and the tribulation coming soon, why would he reveal this treasury on his own initiative? And why would he have to be forced to bottle up his frustration?

He knew Shi Lei's scheme and intentions.

Shi Lei was a battle-addict, unreasonable and unruly, but he was in no way stupid.

Everyone who reached a high position had their own outstanding points. The outstanding and famous Shi Lei did not lack shrewdness.

Shi Lei accepted Star Lord Wan Xiang's invitation to come to Starry Sky grotto-heaven to plunder resources. But he did not put in his full effort, he was interested in breaking through the eighth star hall, but he was not willing to see Star Lord Wan Xiang obtain large numbers of resources to pull through the difficulties and escape his grasp.

If Star Lord Wan Xiang does not obtain a fortune in this trip, he would have to request help from others when undergoing the tribulation. Shi Lei could help him then and also obtain a greater grasp on him.

When that happens, in their future visits to Starry Sky grotto-heaven, Shi Lei could obtain larger benefits which would absolutely not be in an eighty to twenty ratio like in this trip.

Every year, Starry Sky grotto-heaven would reveal a tiny gap which allowed Gu Immortals to enter it. Every time, the Gu Immortals could only stay inside for two days of Central Continent's time.

There were abundant desolate beasts and resources in Starry Sky grotto-heaven, it was clearly a small but steady source of resources. Star Lord Wan Xiang was a prime example of this, he was obviously a lone cultivator, but with each of his visits to Starry Sky grotto-heaven, he was able to strengthen himself to the extent that his peak battle strength did not lose out to the majority of Gu Immortals of the ten great ancient sects. Even when fighting Song Zi Xing, he had even been able to make a good record of himself.

After a while, Shi Lei's injuries healed completely with no traces of injuries anywhere on him.

Because of the previous oath, Shi Lei could not push it too far; he examined his body once then stood up: "Sorry to keep you waiting, we can now go in."

Star Lord Wan Xiang put on a smiling expression and shook his head: "It was me who was overly anxious, I have to ask Immortal Monkey King to not blame me. More preparations quicken the speed of the work, I will still have to rely on your strength a lot more."

Shi Lei bluntly nodded: "Naturally."

He stamped his foot and charged straight into the sky.

Star Lord Wan Xiang followed closely behind.

The two immortals moved towards the eighth star hall in the sky together.

At the same time, Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan also jumped out of a well.

"This is another star hall." Fang Yuan said as he scanned his surroundings.

Hei Lou Lan nodded: "We used many methods to test and we were not wrong, these six wells are passages."

The two gazed behind them.

The center of this star hall also had six wells.

But the colors were slightly different from the previous star hall.

In the previous star hall, the six well waters were of red, brown, yellow, blue, purple and white color. However, the six well waters here emitted the colors of red, brown, yellow, blue, green and white.

Purple was gone and green was added.

Hei Lou Lan and Fang Yuan looked at each other. Both were clever and shrewd, and they both obtained an understanding.

"What do you think of it?" Hei Lou Lan asked.

Fang Yuan grinned, showing his sharp, jagged canines as he replied with his hoarse voice: "If I am not wrong, this Starry Sky grotto-heaven has a special terrain, there are a total of seven spaces. These seven spaces are isolated and independent of each other, outsiders can only enter or exit them through the six wells in the star halls."

Hei Lou Lan nodded and picked up a Gu worm from the ground: "This is the mortal Gu you tossed earlier into the purple well water, it is the best proof. If my speculation is right, there is also another form of proof, that is the sky. When we go out of this star hall, this space's sky should also have six round shadows of stars. The difference should be that there instead of a purple star shadow, there should be a green star shadow."

Fang Yuan agreed with Hei Lou Lan's speculation.

Normal grotto-heavens and blessed lands would have integrated spaces. But Starry Sky grotto-heaven was special, it was actually divided into seven spaces, and every space had an independent sky, earth and ecology.

In his previous life, what Fang Yuan explored was only the fragment world of Starry Sky grotto-heaven and he did not know of this layer of mystery.

He and Hei Lou Lan finished discussing and they walked out of the door of the hall, gazing at the sky.

They saw six round star shadows like six full moons floating in the air, Hei Lou Lan clapped her hands and gave a bright smile: "Just like I guessed."

"Wait, someone is here!" Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk as he looked at the moving objects in the distance and happened to see Shi Lei and Star Lord Wan Xiang rapidly flying. Following the direction they were flying towards, Fang Yuan discovered the eighth star hall.

"This star hall seems to be of a higher standard, it is hovering in the air and is being coveted by others, it is very likely that it is the central control point of Starry Sky grotto-heaven." Hei Lou Lan guessed, her gaze stuck on the eighth star hall.

"There are actually others who are one step ahead of us!" Fang Yuan mumbled. He was shocked internally, according to his previous estimation, Starry Sky grotto-heaven was a place with no one but the heavenly spirit existing in it.

If not for this, Starry Sky grotto-heaven should not have fallen in his previous life.

However, the current situation was that he saw no signs of the heavenly spirit and instead saw two Gu Immortals.

As for the Gu Immortals' appearances and identities, the distance between them was very far so Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan were not able to see clearly.

However, the two felt that these neither of these two Gu Immortals were the owners of this grotto-heaven. If one of them was the owner of this grotto-heaven, they would have already sensed Hei Lou Lan and Fang Yuan, and would have acted by now.

"What's strange about it? You could obtain the secret intelligence about Starry Sky grotto-heaven from some source, does that mean other Gu Immortals cannot?" Hei Lou Lan was able to accept this fact much more easily than Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan laughed bitterly in his heart.

He had concealed from Hei Lou Lan that the so-called information source was, in fact, his own self.

However, it seemed that the truth and his preconceptions were vastly different.

The first possible cause for this situation would be Fang Yuan's rebirth constantly influencing the various events in the world, causing a butterfly effect. The second possible reason was there was a lot of details behind the scenes regarding the fall of Starry Sky grotto-heaven in his previous life, it was just that he did not know about them and now in this life, he ran across one of the inside stories.

Fang Yuan's thoughts ebbed and flowed, inclining towards the second cause.

At this moment, sounds of fighting came from the eighth star hall.

"Looks like these two Gu Immortals are of similar status to us, they are also outsiders. But, they are a step ahead of us." Hei Lou Lan's gaze flickered.

Fang Yuan did not reply, he just snickered, his laughter was cold.

Hei Lou Lan also silently grinned.

These two were formidable characters and were also schemers. Right now, the enemy was in the open while they were in the dark and both felt they had a had huge advantage, they could even be said to be the oriole in the saying 'the mantis stalks the cicada, unaware of the oriole behind'.

Immediately, Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan activated large numbers of mortal Gu to hide their bodies and restrain their auras, as well as using many kinds of investigative methods to scout.

The two quietly closed the star hall's door, got rid of all their traces and slowly moved outside.

After a while, Fang Yuan who was walking in front suddenly stopped and warned Hei Lou Lan: "Slow down, there is a rank five investigative Gu ahead."

Hei Lou Lan carefully probed, and saw an eye-like small Gu worm quietly hovering in the air. Its eyes were slowly moving around, constantly scanning its surroundings.

The two were not surprised.

With just one look, one could see this Gu worm was not a wild Gu and was clearly left behind by the two Gu Immortals from before.

This was expected.

Previously, when Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan had explored the space relating to the green star shadow, they had also left behind similar investigative Gu to keep watch on their paths.

After becoming a Gu Immortal, one no longer lacked mortal Gu.

These mortal Gu could let the Gu Immortal constantly scan their surroundings, mark the area, warn them and many other uses.

Hei Lou Lan was young, she had just advanced into a Gu Immortal, thus was not able to recognize this Gu's details, giving a suggestion of caution: "Let's detour."

Fang Yuan smiled: "No need. This Gu is starshine fake eye Gu, it has a long range sensing ability, Gu Immortals can observe the situation of the surroundings through it. Its scope is five li, it cannot detect stealth, and not only does using this Gu constantly consume primeval essence, it also burdens the soul. We can use methods to be invisible and boldly go past it."

At the same time, Fang Yuan added in his mind: 'This Gu worm is often used together with true sight Gu which can then detect stealth and invisibility. But that is the situation during the five regions chaotic war, the true sight Gu is still being held by some small sect right now and has not been wantonly spread."

Hei Lou Lan glanced at Fang Yuan, still not feeling relieved: "Are you sure you are not wrong? Gu Immortals research new Gu all the time, maybe this Gu worm is a newly researched Gu that can see through invisibility?"

Fang Yuan snickered: "You think I only looked at it with my eyes and did not use other Gu worms to check it? Don't worry, eight or nine out of ten Gu Immortals are flying masters, but having even two to three refinement path masters out of ten would be pretty good. Refinement path is considerably harder to advance compared to other paths."

Chapter 719: Small methods have profound meaning, the more one understands the more shocking it is

Fang Yuan spoke with such certainty that Hei Lou Lan chose to believe him.

The two hid their bodies and swaggered into starshine fake eye Gu's range, and they indeed did not attract any Gu Immortal's attention.

Along the way, the two found similar types of investigative Gu like starshine fake eye Gu.

Some of these Gu worms were buried in the ground, some were disguised as tree leaves, and some were hidden in brooks, drifting with the water.

Fang Yuan used his methods one by one, sometimes invisibility, sometimes Gu worms directed at countering them, or tunneling under the ground or swimming through water, all kinds of methods to slip past these investigative Gu worms.

The two had wanted to move until they were below the eighth star hall, and the shortest way would be a straight line to the eighth star hall. If they got a chance, they could also quickly react and use the shortest amount of time to charge to the eighth star hall, and fish benefits from the messy situation.

However, as they walked through this straight line, a bloody odor assailed their noses from ahead.

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan glanced at each other, the latter revealed a doubtful look as she used her divine sense to transmit: "Strange, both the amount of investigative Gu in this path and their types are increasing more and more."

"Let's take a look." Fang Yuan replied.

The two cautiously evaded or deceived the investigative Gu worms, and discovered further traces of battle.

After a while, they finally reached the area where there was the most intense odor of blood.

They saw a black leopard's corpse lying on the shattered and disordered pile of rocks.

The black leopard was as large as an elephant. Its fur was glossy and shiny, full of wild charm. The remaining aura showed the black leopard's identity, a genuine desolate beast.

"This desolate beast is a vanishing shadow leopard." Fang Yuan said in a low voice.

"It is that someone killed this vanishing shadow leopard and yet left behind its corpse here?" Hei Lou Lan revealed a trace of doubt.

Fang Yuan squatted down near the ground, and used his hand to feel the gully beside his legs.

He then took out a time path Gu worm and carefully activated it.

This Gu worm had the appearance of a crystal sphere, and was an extremely rare rank five Gu. Its name was backtrack Gu, an investigative Gu under time path, which could backtrack to the past events within a specific range.

Backtrack Gu was activated; it displayed a blurry and mute battle scene.

In the scene, two giant figures were in an intense battle while a small figure was standing far away to the side.

Backtrack Gu was only a rank five mortal Gu, and whether it was Shi Lei, the vanishing shadow leopard or Star Lord Wan Xiang, they were all rank six or above, immortal bodies and desolate beast bodies had dao marks, thus backtrack Gu's investigative ability was restrained greatly.

Hei Lou Lan came closer and watched the battle.

The mute battle scene was extremely blurry. But they could roughly guess that one of them was the vanishing shadow leopard from the approximate build.

And the one battling with the vanishing shadow leopard did not seem to be a human but a tiger desolate beast.

The one standing far away had a human shape and could be a Gu Immortal. But their appearance was blurry and they could not be sure.

Not only this, the battle scene broken off intermittently and was not coherent.

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan observed the battle with all their attention, for a moment, other than the slight breeze in the mountains, there was no other sound.

After a dozen breaths of time, scorching smoke started to curl up from the backtrack Gu and the battle scene suddenly disappeared.

The backtrack Gu had died as a result of forcibly recreating the image of the Gu Immortal level battle.

Fang Yuan felt slight heartache, and put the scorched corpse of backtrack Gu back inside his immortal aperture to get rid of any traces.

He had been gathering this backtrack Gu from treasure yellow heaven recently but even then, he only had a total of fifty to sixty. This was still the case when the five regions were in peaceful times, during the chaotic war of the regions, backtrack Gu would be widely used and very hard to get, it would be a case where one would have to produce them for their own use, treasure yellow heaven would simply have none for sale.

Hei Lou Lan was very interested: "This Gu worm is quite ingenious, what is its name, did you buy it in treasure yellow heaven?"

The varieties of Gu worms in existence were as vast as the ocean. Moreover, Hei Lou Lan cultivated strength path, not time path, and her understanding of other paths was only at the basics, limited to the typically used Gu worms.

Gu worms like backtrack Gu were classified as rare Gu of another path, it was normal for her to not know of it.

Fang Yuan did not reply, instead he took out another Gu.

He had refined this Gu himself based to his memories. According to the course of history, this Gu should have only appeared three hundred years later, its name was thread trace Gu.

Its appearance was quite special, resembling a small horsewhip which children from Northern Plains played with as toys. Fang Yuan used his enormous, monstrous zombie claws to grab it, making its small size even more apparent.

Fang Yuan grabbed the handle of the horsewhip and softly whipped at the air in front of him.

Crack. The empty air suddenly showed traces of marks.

"What is this?" Hei Lou Lan gazed at the marks without blinking.

Crack crack crack.

Fang Yuan whipped the horsewhip like thread trace Gu repeatedly, the marks in the air continued to increase.

Hei Lou Lan watched the whole process and soon was able to sense that the space Fang Yuan was whipping at was the area where the fight in the battle scene had occurred, and also the area where that blurry Gu Immortal had been standing.

As various thoughts flashed past, Hei Lou Lan's pupils slightly enlarged, blurting: "Could these marks be dao marks?"

Fang Yuan gave a contented smile at this moment: "Right, they are dao marks. Whether it be Gu Immortals or desolate beasts, they are filled with dao marks, and any area they stop at will leave behind dao marks for a short period of time. It is just that these dao marks are extremely weak, that even Gu Immortals paying close attention won't be able to sense them, that is, unless they use this thread trace Gu that I researched. From observing these dao marks, I can infer some information on them."

Fang Yuan once again brazenly took on someone else's creation from his previous life as his own.

"Thread trace Gu...." Hei Lou Lan mumbled, her gaze towards Fang Yuan had changed a little.

Fang Yuan pointed towards the area where Star Lord Wan Xiang had stood previously: "Look, the dao marks have manifested and formed a human shape. The color is azure blue which means a star path Gu Immortal had been observing the battle. The greater portion of the dao marks had stayed there and although there are some dao marks in the surroundings, they are mostly tightly enclosed around the greater portion, this means that star path Gu Immortal had only been observing from the side during the whole battle. And looking at the concentration of the dao marks, it seems to be a rank six Gu Immortal."

Hei Lou Lan looked at the direction Fang Yuan pointed towards and listened to him, paying full attention.

Fang Yuan then pointed at the area where the vanishing shadow leopard died, there were remaining dao marks of black color for dark path and red color for fire path.

He continued: "The dark path dao marks clearly belong to the vanishing shadow leopard while the red colored dao marks belong to the existence that killed the vanishing shadow leopard. As for their identity, whether they are man or beast, that is still not certain. Look at how concentrated these dao marks are and how they are intertwined with each other, this shows that the battle was very intense. The dark path dao marks are sparse while the red colored dao marks are rather dense, we can deduce that the existence that killed the vanishing shadow leopard is also at least of rank six realm."

Hei Lou Lan's mouth widened slightly as she listened to Fang Yuan.

Her gaze towards the thread trace Gu in Fang Yuan's hand became slightly burning.

This thread trace Gu was only a rank five mortal Gu, but it was very useful. With just this Gu, one could infer so much useful information.

The key thing was the thoughts involved in refining it were very special, and it could even be said to have blazed an unexpected new trail that bypasses common logic.

Hei Lou Lan might have just recently advanced into a Gu Immortal, but she understood the importance of information and started to give more significance to Fang Yuan 'invention', thread trace Gu.

Had Shi Lei and Star Lord Wan Xiang been here, they would probably be soaked in cold sweat.

They had used mainstream investigative methods and counter-investigative methods, but thread trace Gu just happened to pierce through the gap in them. Fang Yuan's methods were from the time of the chaotic war of the five regions after all, the materialization of the intelligence of the whole five regions, it was like they were over half an era ahead of current Gu Immortals, naturally they had huge superiority!

Crack crack crack.

Fang Yuan lashed the horsewhip several times, many more dao marks appeared but also many more disappeared.

These dao marks were very weak and were gathered together by thread trace Gu, thus greatly shortening their already limited lifespan.

Dao marks entangled mutually, getting more disorderly. Fang Yuan finally stopped lashing the horsewhip and sighed: "This is more or less the ability of this thread trace Gu, the manifestation of dao marks lasts only for a period of time and requires the observer to have plenty of experience. Moreover, activating Immortal Gu also leaves behind responding dao marks. In an intense battle, many abilities and methods are used, causing the dao marks to entangle and become extremely chaotic with no way to infer anything. However, fortunately, few methods were used in this battle, so we are able to roughly understand the situation."

Hei Lou Lan's eyelids twitched.

Inferring so much useful information with a mere rank five mortal Gu and still not satisfied?

Her gaze firmly locked upon the thread trace Gu until Fang Yuan stored it back in his immortal aperture. She keenly discovered that the formerly intact thread trace Gu's whip-like body was full of cracks now. Clearly, there was a price to pay for manifesting the dao marks.

Hei Lou Lan inwardly estimated, this thread trace Gu could be used for two more times at the minimum. Immediately, her evaluation of thread trace Gu increased by another level.

It could be used for a total of three times!

A mere rank five Gu worm could be used three times to investigate into existences of rank six level and obtain so much information.

Just as Hei Lou Lan was unable to endure and was about to ask if Fang Yuan was selling thread trace Gu, Fang Yuan took out another investigative Gu worm.

This was only a qi path Gu worm which Fang Yuan used to draw in the surrounding scents.

Next, Fang Yuan stored this qi path Gu worm and took out another Gu worm.

He moved everywhere around the battlefield and activated Gu worms from time to time. Hei Lou Lan was only able to recognize a small portion of these Gu worms, but it was also not to the extent where she was certain. The remaining greater portion, Hei Lou Lan simply had no idea, unable to recognize any of them.

She subconsciously pursed her lips, as she for the first time felt that Fang Yuan had unfathomable depths.

During the journey in Northern Plains, she only felt that Fang Yuan was experienced and astute, and a major enemy. When cooperating with Fang Yuan, she had no choice but to do so, and was very aware that it was asking for favors from a tiger.

She got Fang Yuan's help to pass through her tribulation and become a Gu Immortal, she had thought she could suppress Fang Yuan a notch. But soon, Fang Yuan used her and Fairy Li Shan to scare even Immortal Crane Sect's Gu Immortals away. The whole thing was won before engaging in battle, which gave no chance for Hei Lou Lan to make a move. Since there was no loss in battle, Fang Yuan did not have to pay twice the compensation, it was akin to him obtaining his objective without losing anything.

In contrast, to coax Fang Yuan to make an effort, Hei Lou Lan had to give the precious true meaning infusion of Reckless Savage Demon Venerable to him. Fang Yuan was also truly ruthless, he swallowed it whole without leaving behind anything to Hei Lou Lan.

Later, Fang Yuan started the guts Gu business and took the initiative to share profits with Hei Lou Lan and Fairy Li Shan. Although he needed Hei Lou Lan's strength qi Immortal Gu in the process, Hei Lou Lan did not feel comfortable the whole time, it seemed as if she was being controlled.

Now, Hei Lou Lan felt a shiver in her heart as she looked at Fang Yuan using these methods.

These small methods all used mortal Gu and were seemingly unremarkable, but Hei Lou Lan was a discerning person, how could she not understand the profound significance represented by these small methods!

Chapter 720: Picking them up one by one, a windfall of a great fortune

After Hei Lou Lan ascended to an immortal, she was taught by Fairy Li Shan, guided step by step, she was instructed in almost all aspects.

Thus, in terms of investigative methods, Hei Lou Lan was not inferior to ordinary Gu Immortals.

"But Fang Yuan's foundation is so deep, he is evidently miles ahead of most Gu Immortals now. Although I have several Immortal Gu, can I be like Fang Yuan and create new Gu independently, to modify and perfect my own killer moves?"

Hei Lou Lan shook her head internally.

Her strength path killer move was given to her by her mother.

To refine new Gu, one had to create new Gu recipes. This process not only required resources and ample foundation in that path, one also needed inspiration and luck!

Hei Lou Lan was indeed a Gu Immortal, but she was too young, she was not a refinement path master, and not even skilled in refinement path. Foundation could only be attained after a long period of trial and error, of exploring and accumulating experiences slowly.

At this point, Fang Yuan walked back, he hummed: "Summing up all of the clues, I mostly know the other party's identities already."

"Oh?"

"One is a rank six star path Gu Immortal, he has not made a move yet and is more mysterious. The other is an earth path Gu Immortal who cultivates transformation path as well, he has a powerful aura and using Gu worms, I caught a trace of his voice, this is likely Shi Lei from Combat Immortal Sect in Central Continent." Fang Yuan said.

"That Immortal Monkey King?" Hei Lou Lan and Fang Yuan had shared most of their information, she naturally knew who Shi Lei was.

She started to frown, finding it a little troublesome.

Shi Lei was a rank seven Gu Immortal, he had outstanding battle strength. Even though Hei Lou Lan had several strength path Immortal Gu, Shi Lei had earth path Immortal Gu and had even created his own unique immortal killer moves long ago. In addition, he even cultivated transformation path, his battle talent was exceedingly rare.

Hei Lou Lan had Immortal Gu Self Strength, using it to activate her former mortal killer move, forming a giant strength path phantom, that could barely be considered an immortal killer move.

Up to this point, Hei Lou Lan had been attempting to improve and modify it, but her progress was slow.

"Fang Yuan, if you use the myriad self killer move, and cooperate with me, we might be able to resist the Immortal Monkey King. But in that case, we will not be able to deal with the mysterious star path Gu Immortal." Hei Lou Lan muttered.

Fang Yuan laughed bitterly: "I have not told you yet, but because the core Immortal Gu is starving, myriad self cannot be used anymore. All I can use are mortal killer moves."

Hei Lou Lan looked at Fang Yuan deeply, squinting: "In other words, we should avoid fighting with the other party directly."

Roar roar roar—!

High in the air, there was loud growling noises.

Fang Yuan raised his head and looked: "There are bound to be injuries when two sides fight, we should just go with the flow and observe the situation now. Although our battle strength is lower than them, if we find the chance, it is not necessarily the case that we can't have them killed. In the worst case, I still have Fixed Immortal Travel, we can definitely resist them while we find the time to activate Fixed Immortal Travel."

Hei Lou Lan nodded in agreement, Fang Yuan's words were very similar to her own thoughts.

The two decided to devour the loot in front of them first.

The vanishing shadow leopard corpse was quite a fortune. Even though there were large numbers of investigative Gu around, they could not stop the old demon Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had methods that were ahead by half of an era, he made his moves, sealing or deceiving the investigative Gu. A moment later, they obtained the vanishing shadow leopard's corpse without alerting Star Lord Wan Xiang.

"This vanishing shadow leopard's fur can be used to make many defensive Gu. The bones can be made into shadow attachment Gu, shadow tracing Gu and others, the eyes are top tier materials for making dark vision Gu and dark fog Gu. It is a pity its blood had already been lost completely. Otherwise, it would be even more valuable." Hei Lou Lan placed the vanishing shadow leopard corpse into her immortal aperture, her eyes shining with a joyful light.

"The other party seems to be letting it bleed on purpose, it seems that the star hall in the air is truly an important place. They even ignored the desolate beast corpse for now." Fang Yuan showed an interested expression as he pondered.

His immortal aperture was filled with death energy, it was not good for keeping corpses fresh, thus he placed the vanishing shadow leopard in Hei Lou Lan's hands.

The two were fearless and unscrupulous people.

Even if the other party was strong, they dared to continue plotting against them.

Next, they followed their original plan and secretly advanced, trying to get close to the eighth star hall in the air.

But along the way, they quickly made a new discovery.

"The number of investigative Gu ahead have increased, does that mean..." Hei Lou Lan's gaze shone with anticipation.

After a while, the two avoided all of the investigative Gu, passing a mountain ridge and into a valley.

In the valley, there was a desolate beast corpse, resembling a small hill.

It was like a colt, it had a huge, bright red body with thick legs, dark as steel, its body was strong, muscular and bulky.

Its mane and tail were vibrant and golden in color.

Blood was dripping from the holes all over its body. The blood was scalding hot, and the heat spread to the surrounding trees and plants, causing them to wilt.

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan gradually got closer, feeling a heat that was like a blisteringly hot summer day.

"This is the desolate beast blazing divine stallion, it has many fire path wild Gu on it and can walk on fire. Its blood is extremely hot and is a top tier material in refining fire path Gu worms, it is very rare even in treasure yellow heaven."

Hei Lou Lan's heart bled as she looked at the horse blood flowing out.

The two worked for a while, getting their hands on the blazing divine stallion, while Star Lord Wan Xiang still had absolutely no idea.

After leaving this valley, the two moved stealthily, but Fang Yuan slowed his footsteps.

"Our destination is up ahead. But towards the left, there are large numbers of investigative Gu, should we go take a look?" Fang Yuan looked at Hei Lou Lan, transmitting.

"Of course." Hei Lou Lan's reply was very curt.

The two came to the area that was filled with investigative Gu, they found a desolate beast corpse as expected.

This was a yellow jade lion.

Its body was like an elephant, lying on the ground with its eyes mostly closed, only opened by a slit. Large amounts of yellow blood flowed along the wound on its stomach, pouring out.

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan stealthily moved closer, but this yellow jade lion's body shook, it tried to open its eyes as its bloody mouth opened slightly, emitting a barely discernible growl, as if it wanted to continue battling.

"This yellow jade lion truly has a courageous nature. To be able to hurt the yellow jade lion to this extent, this Shi Lei's transformation path battle strength is greater than I thought." Hei Lou Lan praised.

Fang Yuan was overjoyed.

He quickly made his move, after deceiving many of the surrounding investigative methods, he stole the yellow jade lion.

He patted with his hand, as large numbers of healing Gu flew out of his aperture, landing on the yellow jade lion, rapidly stabilizing its injuries and keeping it alive.

"You intend to save it?" Hei Lou Lan was slightly surprised.

Fang Yuan nodded: "Saving it is a hundred times easier than capturing another desolate beast alive, why shouldn't we? You can keep this desolate beast in your immortal aperture for now, be careful and keep it safe, this will be part of my share."

This way, as long as things progressed well, the mission that Fang Yuan agreed upon with Lang Ya land spirit would be completed.

Hei Lou Lan placed the yellow jade lion into her immortal aperture, her gaze was shining as she seemed to have made up her mind, saying: "The three desolate beasts we had encountered had their blood drained for some reason. Very likely, Shi Lei's group is trying to complete some procedure. Maybe this was the reason why the star hall in the sky appeared. After all, when we first appeared in this place, the sky was still empty. How many desolate beast corpses do you think are around here now?"

Fang Yuan laughed upon hearing this: "Even if you did not mention this, I was going to talk about it. Indeed, looking at this situation, there are definitely many desolate beast corpses around. One desolate beast corpse can be sold for around forty immortal essence stones optimally. It is truly an effortless profit for us to pick up these desolate beast corpses. The benefits are huge, yet we are paying zero costs. A bird in the hand is worth two in the bush, moreover, we might not have the opportunity again. We should secure these profits first, that is the safest measure."

The two had the same plot in mind, they changed their tactics and started scouring for desolate beast corpses.

They could not use investigative Gu openly, but the clues were very obvious.

Star Lord Wan Xiang's original plan was to keep these desolate beast corpses around first, and deal with them after taking down the eighth star hall.

The aura of these desolate beasts was still around, with that to induce fear, he was not afraid of wild beasts devouring them.

Shi Lei was in charge of fighting, while Star Lord Wan Xiang was in charge of setting up investigative Gu worms. Naturally, he would place more investigative Gu around the corpses of the desolate beasts.

But he would never have guessed that putting all of these investigative Gu together was the biggest clue in itself, they were guides for Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan to find the corpses.

"This is the chestnut yak, its meat tastes like chestnut, it can be eaten raw. It has a mild nature and is a somewhat unusual desolate beast. Mm, let's keep it, keep it." Hei Lou Lan was laughing happily.

"Oh, there is a golden pangolin. It is a pity its armor is tattered, otherwise, it could be sold for a higher price." Fang Yuan said with some disappointment.

"Flying bear, there is a flying bear corpse. Great, excellent, I want this corpse!" Hei Lou Lan was overjoyed.

"Hmm? Star demon bat! I knew this rotten poisonous swamp was very familiar. It is a pity that the bat wings are in bad shape, it would greatly affect my movement speed if I transplant it like this. I wonder if I can fix it first." Fang Yuan also stole the corpse of the star demon bat.

He felt some regret, but he quickly got over it.

After all, he did not battle the bat himself, why would Shi Lei care about his plans. Obtaining the corpse without any cost, this was already a huge gain.

He had not felt such good luck in a long time.

The two obtained nearly ten desolate beast corpses, it was a windfall. After the two searched around and ensured that there was no lingering desolate beast corpses, they hurried towards the bottom of the eighth star hall.

But when they arrived, a figure like a small hill crashed onto the ground.

With a loud bang, it landed and caused the mountain rocks to shatter, dust and smoke was rising.

"This is the ancient desolate beast, astral wind flying heavenly boar!"

"It is dead! This is the corpse of an ancient desolate beast."

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan made eye contact, after communicating through transmission, they were evidently moved!

Chapter 721: Walking Meat Tree

The corpse of the ancient desolate beast, astral wind flying heavenly boar, was right in front of them.

Although Hei Lou Lan and Fang Yuan were moved, they did not close in on it.

The two looked up towards the sky at the same time.

They saw that high in the air, the eighth star hall was shaking slightly. Loud explosions and the growls of fierce beasts could be heard from within the hall.

With a loud bang, the star hall shook intensely, a pillar of fire burst up from the roof of the star hall, creating a huge hole on it.

The star hall was not made of ordinary material, it was formed from the phenomenon in the grotto-heaven. At the area of the roof that was broken, starlight was emitting from it, as the hole continued to spread outwards.

A pillar of smoke flew up outwards into the sky.

"What an intense battle." Hei Lou Lan sighed.

"Fight, fight, the more intense the better it is." Fang Yuan muttered.

In the eighth star hall, it was a mess, the two sides were fiercely engaged in combat.

A heavily injured desolate beast flame tiger growled loudly, shooting out a fireball from its mouth.

The fireball shot a huge tree, while it was in the air, the flame tiger moved its claws and followed behind the fireball, attacking towards the huge tree.

The huge tree moved its huge branches.

Its branches were very peculiar, they were like soft and thick octopus tentacles.

With a loud thud, a tentacle-like branch destroyed a fireball.

With another whipping noise, a branch swung over, causing the flame tiger who was behind the fireball to be sent flying.

The flame tiger cried out in pain, it flew for up to a hundred steps and crashed onto the ground. With a burst of bright light, it returned to a human form — it was Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei.

Shi Lei spat out three teeth, his expression was excited and crazed: "What a great walking meat tree, as expected of something of legend, this ancient desolate plant is truly incredible."

Star Lord Wan Xiang who was beside him continued to unleash starlight attacks while transmitting helplessly when he heard Shi Lei's words: "Lord Immortal Monkey King, the enemy is very powerful, stop playing with it and use your earth path main battle strength."

Shi Lei was not an ignorant person, he did not hesitate as he said: "Alright, I have already used my transformation path battle strength to kill an astral wind flying heavenly boar, I am satisfied. Next, I will use my true earth path cultivation and destroy this energetic walking meat tree."

Star Lord Wan Xiang was overjoyed when he heard this, Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei was finally going to use his true strength.

But at the next moment, Shi Lei sat down on a rock in the hall, healing himself: "Star Lord Wan Xiang, hold on for now, when I remove the fire path dao marks on my body, I will use my earth path methods."

Star Lord Wan Xiang heard this and almost scolded him in anger.

But he did not do so, Shi Lei's request was reasonable, with fire path dao marks on him, it would interfere with and weaken the effects of his earth path Gu worms.

Star Lord Wan Xiang could only hold in his anger and agree, flying forward and facing off against the walking meat tree.

Although Star Lord Wan Xiang was heavily injured by Song Zi Xing and his foundation was damaged, he still had ingenious methods left.

Beams of starlight shot out like grand pillars, towards the walking meat tree.

The walking meat tree moved three branches to retaliate.

Star Lord Wan Xiang's body suddenly shuddered, as five starlight clones split from his main body and together, they took up six positions, unleashing different star path killer moves and attacking the walking meat tree.

The walking meat tree was hit several times, it flew into a rage and moved more than ten branches to fight back.

Crack crack crack.

Star Lord Wan Xiang's starlight clones were all smashed, Star Lord Wan Xiang evaded the branches coming from left and right, he quickly got into a disadvantage.

Facing off against the walking meat tree directly, he finally felt immense pressure.

Bang!

With a loud noise, Star Lord Wan Xiang could not defend himself and was sent flying. Along the way, he crashed through a thick pillar, but his momentum was not lost, as he directly flew out of the star hall.

Seeing that Star Lord Wan Xiang was gone, the walking meat tree moved its branches and assaulted Shi Lei who was sitting down.

"Useless!" Shi Lei opened his eyes, the battle intent in his golden pupils were surging, he shouted in anger as he stood up, attacking the walking meat tree.

Star Lord Wan Xiang flew a long way out of the star hall before stabilizing his body.

He wiped the blood on his lips, looking at the eighth star hall, he showed a cold smile as his scheme worked.

He sent himself flying on purpose, this way, he could force Shi Lei to fight.

"I exposed the secret of this Starry Sky grotto-heaven to you, regardless of the consequences, yet you do not even want to fight? Guh." Suddenly, Star Lord Wan Xiang spit out a mouthful of blood.

An intense pain assaulted him.

He sucked in a breath of cold air, shock shining in his eyes: "When this walking meat tree hits me, it directly etches the dao marks of strength path into my body, causing my internal organs to suffer a huge blow!"

After realizing this, Star Lord Wan Xiang did not want to rush up foolishly to fight the walking meat tree.

"I'll let Shi Lei fight, he is a battle maniac anyway. Under the pressure of the walking meat tree, he would need to use his full strength. I have already paid such a huge price, I should heal the injuries on my body first."

Immediately after, Star Lord Wan Xiang summoned his Gu worms, which formed a star cloud bed. He sat on the bed as he floated in the air, healing his injuries.

After a while, he opened his eyes, the injuries on him had healed.

He first took a look at the eighth star hall, before looking down at the huge corpse of the ancient desolate beast, astral wind flying heavenly boar. He then looked at the other areas of the battlefield, seeing the other desolate beast corpses.

He hesitated, although he wanted to take all of the corpses first, considering Shi Lei's feelings, he had to dispel this thought.

"Forget it, I do not need to give Shi Lei an excuse later to make things difficult. In any case, there is no one else in this grotto-heaven, I should battle now and deal with the current situation."

Thinking of this, Star Lord Wan Xiang retrieved the star cloud bed Gu and flew away, entering the eighth star hall after traveling a short distance.

In the thick lush forest, Hei Lou Lan and Fang Yuan, who had concealed their auras, sighed in relief.

"Fang Yuan, the Gu worms that you left behind successfully deceived the enemy!" Hei Lou Lan said excitedly.

"My method can only create a hologram, it cannot deceive a proper investigation. Quick, let's not talk about this anymore, we should make this part of our earnings first!" Fang Yuan did not want to indulge in self praise, he moved ahead and sneaked towards the corpse of the astral wind flying heavenly boar.

The two quickly got to the side of the astral wind flying heavenly boar corpse.

The astral wind flying heavenly boar corpse was tall like a small hill, it cast a huge shadow on the ground.

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan purposely detoured, hiding under the shadow, waiting for the appropriate moment to strike.

They first inspected the wild Gu on the astral wind flying heavenly boar's body.

There were many wild Gu originally, but after the battle with Shi Lei, more than half were destroyed. After the flying boar died, much of the remaining half escaped, very few were left.

After Fang Yuan completed his search, he started to collect the astral wind flying heavenly boar's soul.

The desolate beast corpses they encountered earlier had no souls. Maybe because they had died for a long time, their souls had flown away from their bodies, but the more likely reason was that Shi Lei or Star Lord Wan Xiang had taken them.

This astral wind flying heavenly boar had not been looted yet because the battle had just ended, thus Fang Yuan had a chance.

But the result was very disappointing.

This astral wind flying heavenly boar's soul was heavily injured, only a little bit was left. Evidently, during the earlier battle, it was attacked by methods directed at the soul.

"No wonder the star path Gu Immortal earlier did not fly here to collect the soul of this boar." Fang Yuan sighed, he willed and mobilized several hundred Gu worms.

These Gu were from light path and dark path, while a small number were from strength path, blood path, bone path, and qi path.

Under Fang Yuan's control, these Gu worms flew around the surface of the astral wind flying heavenly boar's body, going round and round as Fang Yuan nodded to Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan was prepared since long ago, once Fang Yuan gave the signal, she used the tens of Gu worms prepared earlier.

Using these Gu worms, the astral wind flying heavenly boar corpse was quickly pushed into Hei Lou Lan's immortal aperture in a short time.

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan activated the several hundred Gu worms, remaining at the same spot as they continued to fly in the same manner as earlier.

They gave out bursts of light and shadow, forming into one figure, it was the image of the astral wind flying heavenly boar, it was very realistic! Simply looking at it, one would think this was really the astral wind flying heavenly boar in front of them.

"Your method is really good." Hei Lou Lan praised again.

Earlier, Star Lord Wan Xiang felt nothing wrong, he was deceived by this method.

Fang Yuan shook his head: "This simple method cannot deceive proper investigation. If I can elevate it to a killer move, the effect would be better."

"Oh no." Hei Lou Lan suddenly froze, she pointed at one area and noted to Fang Yuan: "You have a flaw here!"

Fang Yuan looked over and indeed, on the image of the astral wind flying heavenly boar, the anus was missing.

How could the flying heavenly boar not have an anus?

This was indeed a huge flaw.

Fang Yuan quickly manipulated his Gu worms, adjusting the image and forming the anus.

But Hei Lou Lan said: "Not good, not good, now that the anus is here, the penis is gone."

Fang Yuan looked and was embarrassed: "The astral wind flying heavenly boar is too high level of an existence and has a gigantic body, my methods cannot replicate it fully, this is the limit. To create something, it will have to lose something."

Hei Lou Lan nodded, her tone was grand and fearless: "Then stop changing it, keep the penis and discard the anus, that is more realistic."

Fang Yuan followed what she said and changed the image back.

"Hey, Fang Yuan, aren't you proficient in researching killer moves? When we go back, you should raise this to the level of a killer move, that would make it easier to use." Hei Lou Lan said in amusement.

"Do you think we will still encounter such good things later? This method is sufficient, we do not need to make it a killer move." Fang Yuan shook his head, before raising it and looking at the sky.

The roof of the star hall only had a small hole earlier, but now holes were all around the star hall.

All of the explosion sounds were even louder than before.

As he was looking, a broken tree flew out of the star hall.

With a loud bang, the giant tree's branches crashed onto the ground, causing the ground below Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan's feet to tremble violently.

Next, the other half of the giant tree, the crown, also collapsed.

"This is a walking meat tree!" Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan opened their eyes which were shining brightly.

Chapter 722: Zombie Dragon

Walking meat tree was a legendary plant that was recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> Chapter Three, Section Sixteen states:

Ren Zu's third son — Northern Dark Ice Soul was revived by unexpected Gu and was wandering outside. After encountering his sister, Desolate Ancient Moon, he gave her a new meaning in life.

Next, under the guidance of wisdom Gu, the brother and sister came to the blue sea to search for the life gem that could revive their father, Ren Zu.

In the end, Desolate Ancient Moon sensed the mysteries behind life and sacrificed herself, being turned into a damaged life gem.

Northern Dark Ice Soul carried the life gem as he attempted to return to his father, to revive Ren Zu.

But it was extremely difficult for him to enter the door of life and death.

The door of life and death had two routes, one was the road of life, the other was the road of death. No matter which path it was, there would be a lot of suffering Gu.

To overcome the interference of the suffering Gu, to enter deep into the door of life and death, he would need the help of courage Gu.

But because courage Gu had already been taken by Ren Zu and was currently with him, Northern Dark Ice Soul did not have courage and could not enter the door of life and death. He had no methods left and could only wander around and search for a method to resolve this.

He walked past tall mountains, travelled through streams, ran for his life under the assault of wild beasts, and had gone hungry during the intense cold, he had suffered a lot.

Northern Dark Ice Soul was filled with guilt and anxiety.

He was guilty because he was the one who gave Desolate Ancient Moon her meaning in life, but that caused her to sacrifice herself and become the life gem. Northern Dark Ice Soul was the murderer who indirectly caused his sister's death.

He was anxious because even though he had the life gem, he was unable to return to his father's side. He was afraid that if a long time passed, his father's soul might collapse in Luo Po valley, causing Desolate Ancient Moon's sacrifice to be in vain.

He walked and walked, until the purple sky above him faded and became black.

Originally, the immemorial nine heavens, white, red, orange, yellow, green, azure, blue, purple, black, would take turns to loom over the five regions at set intervals.

The sky of the Immemorial Antiquity Era was connected to the ground.

Heaven and earth were connected and whole, people could walk towards the sky from the ground, or walk towards the ground from the sky.

Northern Dark Ice Soul was walking aimlessly, unknowingly, he left the ground and walked towards an area deep within black heaven.

It was complete darkness inside black heaven, but it was not desolate, there were large numbers of life forms there.

Northern Dark Ice Soul was inside the darkness and could not find a way back, he was flustered, scared, and lost.

He could not tell what direction to walk, he tripped many times and fell. Suddenly, he saw a lump of fire ahead of him.

This was the only source of light in the entirety of black heaven.

Northern Dark Ice Soul was overjoyed, he quickly walked towards the fire.

When he got close to the lump of fire, he realized it was a Gu.

Northern Dark Ice Soul was very curious, he asked: "What Gu are you, you can actually give out light in black heaven. Help me, I want to leave black heaven, heading back to the ground, I have very important things to do."

The Gu's voice was very weak, it said to Northern Dark Ice Soul: "My name is fire, who are you?"

Northern Dark Ice Soul said: "I am a human, my name is Northern Dark Ice Soul. Can you help me? With your light, I will be able to see the way, and return to the ground."

The Gu sighed: "So you are a human. I've heard of a famous human before, he is called Verdant Great Sun."

Because Verdant Great Sun had reputation Gu, his name was spread in the entire world, there was almost nobody that did not know him.

Northern Dark Ice Soul was overjoyed: "That's right, Verdant Great Sun is my big brother."

Fire Gu said: "I can help you. But before I help you, you have to help me. I am too hungry, I am going to die of starvation. Go find me some food first."

Northern Dark Ice Soul asked: "Oh, fire Gu, what do you eat? This place is completely dark, how can I find what you need to eat?"

Fire Gu said: "I am the least picky Gu worm in the entire world, I can eat almost anything. I will eat whatever you feed me."

Northern Dark Ice Soul searched around, finding some tree branches and throwing them towards fire Gu.

After fire Gu ate, it started to shine more brightly, it was giving off a warmer light and it also grew from the size of a fist to around the size of a basin.

It was very happy: "Can you bring me more food?"

Northern Dark Ice Soul nodded and looked around, finding a pile of rocks and throwing them at fire Gu.

After eating for some time, fire Gu sighed: "Sigh, I was way too hungry, my teeth are not working well now. The things I could chew before, I can't chew them now. Bring me some stuff that are easy to digest."

Northern Dark Ice Soul thought about it: "How about this, fire Gu, follow me and light the way. Along the way, whatever you feel like eating, I will feed to you, is that alright?"

Fire Gu agreed and condensed into a small lump, letting Northern Dark Ice Soul hold it.

Like this, Northern Dark Ice Soul left on his return journey, along the way, he fed many things to fire Gu.

After a while, fire Gu grew larger.

On this day, Northern Dark Ice Soul was resting, fire Gu was eating branches in front of him while swaying with the wind.

Suddenly, countless footsteps could be heard, Northern Dark Ice Soul looked and saw a huge group of trees shining under the light of the fire, they were running towards him in huge numbers.

Not just trees, there were also countless wild beasts and insect groups.

Northern Dark Ice Soul was extremely scared, he quickly picked up fire Gu and ran.

Behind him, the trees, wild beasts, and insect groups were chasing. Wherever Northern Dark Ice Soul went, they followed.

The pursuers shouted: "Whoever is in front, stop running."

"We do not want to harm you, we just want to escape into the light."

"Dream realms are about to reach us, please help us and let us live under the light of the fire."

Northern Dark Ice Soul was breathing roughly, he could not run any further, seeing that he was about to be caught, fire Gu said: "Oh human, don't be afraid, these pursuers are my food, let me help you. Just toss me there."

Northern Dark Ice Soul was forced by the circumstances, he could only listen to fire Gu and toss it towards them.

What fire Gu first encountered were a huge group of trees.

These trees were walking meat trees. The branches were made of meat, they resembled the tentacles of octopuses.

Fire Gu burned all of these trees, turning the trunks into ashes, and branches into cooked meat. The smell of fragrant meat attracted Northern Dark Ice Soul and he picked up one to eat, exclaiming that it was delicious.

...

Hei Lou Lan stared with eyes wide open, looking at the broken tree trunk as well the tentacle-like branches, speaking in disbelief: "This is a walking meat tree?"

"Absolutely." Fang Yuan nodded, his gaze was heated as well: "Right now, only black heaven and white heaven are left from the immemorial nine heavens, walking meat tree is a life form from black heaven, it is much easier to obtain than other immemorial life forms in the other heavens, after all, black heaven is still around. Seven Star Child is a rank eight Gu Immortal, he has the ability to explore black heaven, this walking meat tree was most likely something he obtained from his explorations."

"This walking meat tree has an amazing aura, it has rank seven battle strength at least! Even more amazingly, it is a rare strength path plant." Hei Lou Lan licked her lips, saying excitedly.

Fang Yuan was also overjoyed.

Walking meat tree was a strength path plant, the branches, trunks and leaves were all excellent materials to refine strength path Gu worms. Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan were strength path Gu Immortals, they had great use for it.

But when the two were going to sneak over and take the walking meat tree, there was a huge, thunderous explosion in the sky.

This was an unprecedentedly large explosion, it shook the sky as a formless sound wave spread out intensely.

The eighth star hall shook harshly, it also broke apart as large amounts of starlight dispersed, it was in a half ruined state.

Roar—!

The roar of a dragon could be heard, not any softer than the explosion earlier.

Next, Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan saw Shi Lei and Star Lord Wan Xiang fly out of the star hall.

A huge dragon flew out of the star hall.

This dragon was hundreds of meters long, it was eerie and ominous, the dragon horn on its head was like silver, the dragon's eyes were half open, and the scales were like grey rocks. There were eight dragon claws that were fearsome and powerful, pale white zombie energy was coiling around its body like a mist.

"Is this... a zombie dragon?" Hei Lou Lan exposed the identity of this dragon.

Zombie dragon was not an immemorial life form.

After fate Gu was broken by Red Lotus Demon Venerable, souls in the world were no longer sucked directly into the door of life and death, thus zombies were born.

A zombie dragon was formed after a giant dragon died, if its soul did not leave the body, it would undergo a transformation and become a zombie dragon.

"This zombie dragon has eight claws, it should have been an immemorial desolate beast when it was alive, having rank eight battle strength. Now that it is dead, becoming a zombie dragon, it has battle strength at the peak of rank seven, no wonder Shi Lei was forced out of the star hall." Fang Yuan analyzed.

In the air, the zombie dragon was growling as its body twisted, flying towards Shi Lei.

The dragon opened its mouth and shot out a stream of pale white zombie fire.

Dragon fire was a primary form of attack of the giant dragon, that was a natural ability for them, like the horns of a bull, the paws of a bear, or the stinger of a bee.

Wariness shone in Shi Lei's eyes, he did not dare to receive the attack head on. He continued to fly to the left, after dodging the zombie fire, a huge dragon tail entered his vision.

Shi Lei opened his eyes wide as he placed both arms in front of him, defending his chest.

He could not dodge it!

In Fang Yuan, Star Lord Wan Xiang and Hei Lou Lan's vision, they saw that the zombie dragon had elegantly moved in the air, turning its huge body and swinging its tail, directly crashing it into Shi Lei who had dodged the zombie fire.

With a loud bang, Shi Lei was sent fly harshly like a cannonball.

He crashed onto a point partway up a mountain, entering deep into the mountain rocks. The entire mountain was shaking as rocks fell from above, they quickly covered him up completely.

Star Lord Wan Xiang sucked in a breath of cold air, he retreated hurriedly. The zombie dragon was so powerful, this was the first time he had seen Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei in such a pathetic state.

But soon, he heard Shi Lei shouting under the pile of rocks: "Worm, you have truly angered me, have a taste of my immortal killer move. Shocking rock break!"

The sky burst open as a small hill was aimed towards the zombie dragon.

Hei Lou Lan's eyelids were twitching: "This immortal killer move's activation is so fast?"

Normally, the stronger the immortal killer move, the more time is needed to activate it. But Shi Lei's shocking rock break defied common logic, not only was it strong, it could be used very quickly.

Even the zombie dragon could not dodge it.

But the zombie dragon did not want to dodge it, seeing the small hill that was approaching it, a hint of disdain flashed across the dragon's eyes.

With a loud bang, the zombie dragon raised its head and rammed into the small hill.

Shi Lei's immortal killer move had no effect.

"Good, such an opponent is what I like!" Shi Lei was shocked and excited, he shot up into the sky and crashed into the zombie dragon.

The human and dragon engaged in the sky, winds were blowing and clouds were in turbulence, heaven and earth were changing colors.

Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk: "This zombie dragon is not simple, it seems that defensive immortal Gu worms had been used on its body before."

"Then what do we do now?" Hei Lou Lan was very troubled: "Under their watchful eyes, there is no way we can get the walking meat tree."

Chapter 723: Shocking Appearance of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable

In the sky, the human and dragon were engaging in battle, with loud explosions, the battle was entering its climax.

Star Lord Wan Xiang was at the side, he could not interfere at all.

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan were hiding in the forest on the ground, they were observing the fighting and awaiting their chance.

The huge dragon roared, zombie energy was bursting from it as the famous expert of Central Continent, Shi Lei, was in a disadvantage.

"This zombie dragon is incredible, when it was alive, it was a wind path azure dragon, after becoming a zombie dragon, not only does it have wind path and dark path dao marks, its speed is even amplified by Immortal Gu." After observing the battle, Hei Lou Lan gradually understood the situation.

"Starry Sky grotto-heaven's owner, Seven Star Child, originally had a wind path Immortal Gu, called wind sprint Immortal Gu. But using this Gu required immortal essence. According to rumors, Seven Star Child had once developed a killer move that could apply the effects of the Immortal Gu on another target for a long period of time. Looking at this now, it seems the rumors were right." Fang Yuan added.

The zombie dragon's defense and movement were boosted by Immortal Gu, it was experienced in battle and its giant dragon body could strike with huge force. Manipulating its tail while flying, it gave off an unrestrained aura.

Most importantly, the zombie energy dragon flames were very powerful, they were on par with the highest tier of mortal killer moves.

Shi Lei continued to shout as he used near ten different battle tactics, but he could not change the situation. Often, when he took back some of the initiative, the zombie dragon would suppress him again.

The zombie dragon had no weakness in attack, defense, or movement, it had an all-around advantage.

Hei Lou Lan's expression turned heavy as she watched, she said solemnly: "Shi Lei's battle strength far surpasses my estimation! If it had been me, facing the attacks of the zombie dragon, I would only last for a moment before getting killed by it. If it was you, Fang Yuan, unless you could use myriad self, you would only hold on for a while longer than me, there is no way of winning."

Fang Yuan did not rebuke her, Hei Lou Lan's assessment was very reasonable.

Although she was a strength path extreme immortal, because of her life experiences, she was not arrogant at all, she was humble and vigilant, she understood her own strength clearly.

The reason why Fang Yuan could last longer than her was because of his flying attainment, as well the movement killer move true solid bat wings.

But even if Fang Yuan's speed surpassed Hei Lou Lan, without the killer move myriad self, he could not pose a threat to the zombie dragon. He could only run away, as icy drill stardust could not cause damage to the zombie dragon, he had no way to win.

Although Hei Lou Lan had strength path Immortal Gu, and half an offensive immortal killer move, her offense surpassed Fang Yuan but her movement speed and defense were her weaknesses. Although she could cause damage to the zombie dragon, it would not take a beating without fighting back, once they fought, Hei Lou Lan would not last as long as Fang Yuan.

Those who were called experts not only had battle strength, they also needed great insight.

Looking at information and knowing if they could do it or not, whether they could win or not. That was the ability to assess a situation and know one's own limits.

Without these abilities, even if one had great strength, they would not go far.

Knowing whom they could offend, know whom they could not afford to offend, knowing when to battle or retreat... retreating was not cowardly, it was treasuring one's own life, awaiting the time where they could soar towards success!

"In this situation, we have no way of succeeding. We should leave the walking meat tree there, I suggest we retreat." Fang Yuan said.

Hei Lou Lan nodded: "That was my intention as well, nobody can predict any accidents in battle. Even if we stay here and take a risk of getting discovered, we cannot do anything anyway, we should withdraw towards a safer location."

The two came to an agreement and retreated stealthily.

Their advantage was that they were in the dark while their enemies were out in the open, they could afford to watch on the sidelines. Right now, the enemies were stronger than them, they had to hold onto this advantage.

After they retreated to a safe distance, Hei Lou Lan suddenly said: "Actually, I have a question — how did they get in?"

Fang Yuan's gaze shone: "I was thinking about this question too. The area near the star hall that we came in from did not have any investigative Gu worms around, that is not the usual behavior of Gu Immortals."

"In this case, we can deduce that they did not come from a star hall. This area is the place where they first arrived in. To enter someone else's blessed land or grotto-heaven, the most usual method is to follow cracks and loopholes, or Gu worms like connecting heaven Gu and hole earth Gu." Hei Lou Lan continued.

"It is unlikely for them to use hole earth Gu or connecting heaven Gu, after all, both sides need to agree for that to work. This Starry Sky grotto-heaven is quite strange, the heavenly spirit has not shown up yet, after being here for so long, we have not faced any obstacles as well. And if Shi Lei's group was able to gain access normally, they would not be fighting so intensely." Fang Yuan said.

"Thus, it is most likely that they used a loophole or crack." Hei Lou Lan laughed.

A dark light shined in Fang Yuan's eyes, he spoke what Hei Lou Lan was thinking but did not say out loud: "They are not like us who have Fixed Immortal Travel, so be it if they have other space path Gu worms. But if they really came in from a loophole, we can use this to ambush them or plot against them, we might have a huge profit from it!"

If Star Lord Wan Xiang and Shi Lei heard this, they would definitely be breaking out in cold sweat.

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan were demons full of evil ideas, most importantly, they could keenly analyze and would not give up on any minute clues, they even managed to guess Shi Lei's and Star Lord Wan Xiang's method of entering the grotto-heaven.

But just as Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan were about to search for the loophole, the battle in the sky changed.

Shi Lei had been fighting for a long time, suppressed by the zombie dragon the whole time, he was growling in anger.

He quickly moved back as he pulled some distance, his body started shaking.

Immortal battlefield killer move — Rolling Rock Battlefield!

The sky was changing, turning into a grey rock battlefield. The battlefield rapidly expanded, covering the zombie dragon and Shi Lei.

From outside, it looked like a huge grey rock cloud was hanging in the sky, it completely blocked any vision from outside.

Hei Lou Lan's and Fang Yuan's hearts shuddered.

Hei Lou Lan thought: "An amazing method, it actually is an immortal level battlefield killer move, to form such a killer move, he needs to use at least three Immortal Gu, and these Immortal Gu need to be connected in some way."

Fang Yuan was thinking: "Rolling rock battlefield! In my previous life, Vicious Lightning Fiend lost to this move. To think that Shi Lei has already obtained this method at this time."

At the same time, Star Lord Wan Xiang was thinking: "Shi Lei is going to fight the zombie dragon to the end! What should I do? There are no longer any ancient desolate beast guards inside the eighth star hall, the battlefield killer move also isolates the inside and outside of the domain... I, should I explore the eighth star hall first?"

The more Star Lord Wan Xiang thought about it, the more he was moved.

After a dozen breaths of time, he could not control it anymore, he turned into a shooting star and flew into the eighth star hall.

"Huh?"

"Eh?"

Seeing Star Lord Wan Xiang move so swiftly, Hei Lou Lan and Fang Yuan stopped their current plans.

The two were familiar with people's thought processes, they had keen perception, they immediately guessed the possibility that the star hall's defenses were no longer a threat!

"Let's bet on it."

"Do you dare to bet on it and charge in?"

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan transmitted at the same time, they flew up and towards the eighth star hall.

The two came to the eighth star hall and found the ravaged battlefield. There were three defenses in the eighth star hall, the first was the astral wind flying heavenly boar, the second was the walking meat tree, and the third was the zombie dragon.

After the three defenses were gone, one could enter the deepest area of the star hall.

The two used their defensive killer moves at the same time, moving together deep into the star hall.

Soon, they found the inner hall.

The inner hall's doors were opened, as Star Lord Wan Xiang was already inside.

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan did not dare to waste their precious time, they hid their figures and stepped into the inner hall.

At the next moment, they saw Star Lord Wan Xiang.

Star Lord Wan Xiang was in a strange condition, his back was facing Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan as he stood on the spot, shivering as if he was filled with extreme fright.

"Immortal Venerable, please spare me!!" Suddenly, he shouted with a tone filled with fear, he directly knelt on the ground, he was begging for mercy!

Before him was deep darkness.

The lights in the inner hall were not lit, there was no light source, Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan could only see the figure of a huge throne.

"Immortal Venerable?!" Hei Lou Lan and Fang Yuan looked at each other.

"Hmph, acting mysterious." Soon after, Fang Yuan snorted coldly as he walked forward.

Hei Lou Lan followed behind.

At the next moment, their pupils shrunk to pin size as their bodies froze like a rock.

A woman's figure appeared before them.

She was wearing a dark blue robe, her hair was dazzling like the milky way, drooping down. She looked down from above as she pointed at Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan: "You two juniors are simply too daring, you dare to offend Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, quickly kneel down!"

The aura of rank nine was overwhelming, she was the real deal!

...

Central Continent, Spirit Affinity House, Bai Qing blessed land.

The sunlight pierced the window as it shone on a small building on a mountain.

In the small building, there was a warm and comfortable bed, on it was a woman sitting in a meditating position.

This woman had inborn beauty like that of a flower, she had white skin and a straightly pointed nose with red lips, she wore a phoenix coronet as she appeared elegant and grand, incapable of being profaned. She was Feng Jin Huang.

Because of dream wings Immortal Gu, she had gotten into a strange state where she had not woken up for a very long time, all of the Gu Immortals in Spirit Affinity House could do nothing to help her.

A small sparrow was chirping as it flew onto the window from a tree branch outside.

As if she had heard this, Feng Jin Huang's eyelashes suddenly moved.

Soon after, she opened her eyes, she had woken up.

"Huang Er, my Huang Er, you have finally woken up!!" Almost at the same time, Feng Jin Huang's mother, Fairy Bai Qing, appeared in the building. Looking at Feng Jin Huang who had woken up, she was overjoyed and in tears, she hugged Feng Jin Huang tightly.

"Mother, Huang Er was unfilial, I have worried you." Feng Jin Huang hugged Bai Qing as she consoled her maturely.

"All is fine as long as you are alright, Huang Er, are you injured, do you feel anything wrong?" Fairy Bai Qing was worried, she touched Feng Jin Huang's face and shoulders, checking everywhere.

"It is not a problem mother! This time, I have found the true use of dream wings Immortal Gu. It can bring me into dream realms!" Feng Jin Huang said.

"Dream realms?" Fairy Bai Qing was shocked.

At the next moment, she reacted, her pupils expanded as she showed some uncertain joy, she grabbed Feng Jin Huang's shoulders: "Daughter, are you sure? It really is about dream realms?!"

Chapter 724: Pitiful Dreamer, Precarious Situation in Dream

"That's right." Feng Jin Huang nodded with certainty: "Using dream wings Immortal Gu, I traveled in a dream realm, I encountered many life forms. I met many people, there were Gu Masters and ordinary people. I saw many wild beasts, tigers, wolves, rabbits, rats, I even found a desolate beast iron crown eagle, I watched it grow up from birth. In the end, I came across an old man, he had a strange temperament, constantly muttering to himself, saying that he is called Kong Jue, he often killed people and dissected their corpses, it was terrifying. He even tried to block my way, I could only dodge left and right and had to escape for a long time. Otherwise, I would have woken up long ago."

When Feng Jin Huang first spoke, she had an excited and agitated tone, but when she mentioned Kong Jue, her tone became grim and she felt some lingering fear.

Fairy Bai Qing heard this and stared straight at her daughter.

"Mother, what's wrong?"

Only when Feng Jin Huang was starting to get worried and asked did Fairy Bai Qing breathe in deeply, her eyes showing extreme happiness: "Huang Er, your opportunity has come! It seems you truly entered a dream realm!! The Kong Jue that you mentioned is likely to be Old Immortal Kong Jue, in history, he was one of the Three Olds, along with Old Eccentric Tian Nan and Long Hair Ancestor. The so called Three Olds were the three refinement path supreme grandmasters over the long course of history!"

"No wonder I felt that Kong Jue was so familiar when I heard the name." Feng Jin Huang realized at once, but then her beautiful face showed some confusion: "But why did I encounter Old Immortal Kong Jue? Why did he want to capture me? Why is it that after I woke up, I felt that there are a lot of refinement path methods in my mind, my recognition of certain Gu worms became clearer, and when I see a Gu worm, I would think of its refinement recipe, the materials needed, the funds necessary for the refinement and so on?"

"Great fortune! This is your great fortune..." Fairy Bai Qing raised her head and sighed, tears were almost about to fall from her eyes.

"Mother, what is this dream realm, why is it so magical?" Feng Jin Huang asked again.

Fairy Bai Qing let out a breath of cloudy air, she calmed her emotions and said gently: "Regarding dream realms, mother does not know much either, but the earliest record of a dream realm is written in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>."

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, Chapter Three, Section Sixteen states: Ren Zu's third son, Northern Dark Ice Soul had entered a deep part of black heaven, obtaining fire Gu.

He was chased by many life forms inside black heaven, left without a choice, he tossed fire Gu towards them to protect himself.

Fire Gu lit up many of the walking meat trees, and the fire spread out to ignite many of the wild beasts' bodies.

At once, life forms were crying out as the light of the flames burst out brightly.

"So many delicious things, so many delicious things!" Fire Gu shouted in excitement, it was no longer weak like before, it was tall and imposing, there was even a hint of ruthlessness and madness in its tone.

Northern Dark Ice Soul was shocked: "Fire, oh fire, how did you become so huge?"

"I said, I am the least picky when it comes to food, I can eat almost anything. Fire can draw out more fire, a spark can create a forest fire." Fire Gu shouted proudly as it answered.

Suddenly, the flame rose up like a wall, moving towards Northern Dark Ice Soul.

Northern Dark Ice Soul quickly took a step back.

Fire Gu laughed loudly: "Oh human, do not be scared! You saved me, you are my benefactor, you are my friend. They are afraid of me, but they need me to deal with those dream realms, thus they imprisoned me and starved me. Only you helped me, thus you are my true friend, from now on, if you have any difficulties, you can count on me!"

Northern Dark Ice Soul's heart was eased, he said happily: "That would be great, my friend."

"Friend!" Fire Gu laughed loudly, it turned into a form of a human as it opened its arms, wanting to give Northern Dark Ice Soul a hug.

Northern Dark Ice Soul jumped back in fear: "Oh fire, excessive fervor is the fire of self-immolation, let's keep a distance between us."

Fire Gu had no choice but to stop its actions, it spun around Northern Dark Ice Soul as he said: "Oh human, you are so weak, you are not fun."

Northern Dark Ice Soul was surrounded in flames, he quickly waved his hand: "Don't get too close, don't get too close. It is so hot, way too hot, leave a path open for me to walk out."

Fire Gu had to open a path for Northern Dark Ice Soul to walk out of, after he walked for several hundred steps, he looked back at the blazing sea of fire with a sigh of relief.

But at this time, a wild beast came out from the shadows behind him, swallowing Northern Dark Ice Soul in one mouthful.

"That is a dream realm! There are so many dream realms, they are catching up!" Many life forms shouted as they escaped.

"Quickly release my friend!" Fire Gu shouted in anger, pouncing towards the beast group of dream realms.

The dream realm beast group shrunk when shone by the light of the fire, they rapidly melted like a candle. They growled and scattered all over the place.

Fire Gu continued to eat along the way, it spread towards the dream realm that consumed Northern Dark Ice Soul.

The dream realms were escaping, but fire Gu was chasing behind them.

Among the escaping dream realms, the larger their bodies, the stronger they were, and the faster they ran away, soon, they pulled some distance from fire Gu.

As it turned out, the dream realms used the emotions and desires of their prey to strengthen themselves.

Northern Dark Ice Soul, who was swallowed by a dream realm, had a huge desire to survive, at the same time, his greatest goal was to revive his father.

In addition, he was filled with anxiety and was afraid he would not make it. He was also filled with guilt and regret, because Desolate Ancient Moon died due to him giving her a meaning in life.

One could say that Northern Dark Ice Soul was the best prey for the dream realms.

The dream realm who swallowed him grew rapidly, fire Gu growled loudly in anger, but it was getting closer to the dream realm.

Northern Dark Ice Soul was deep inside the dream realm, he had fallen asleep, in his dream, he saw Desolate Ancient Moon reviving and smiling to him, calling him a good brother and saying she forgave him, and that she knew he did not do it intentionally.

He saw that he was at the door of life and death, successfully saving his father, Ren Zu. Ren Zu praised him: You are indeed my good son, if not for you, father would not have revived.

Northern Dark Ice Soul's face was filled with a blissful smile.

And like that, many days passed.

The sea of fire was still burning intensely, it spread all over black heaven as it finally blocked all of the dream realms which were escaping.

Under the burning of the flames, the dream realm quickly melted as Northern Dark Ice Soul fell onto the ground, waking up from his dream.

He suddenly understood that everything in his dream was fake, his happiness was not real, what he faced was a burning hot fire Gu. But his face was filled with tears, he felt an extreme cold that was piercing into his bones.

He cried out loud, questioning fire Gu: "Why, why did you wake me up? I still want to dream, I want to be eaten by the dream realm!"

Fire Gu reminded him helplessly: "Oh human, you must know, dreams are often the opposite of reality, they are fake."

"I don't want to listen, I don't care." Northern Dark Ice Soul cried out as he covered his ears and shook his head.

Fire Gu was anxious: "I am your friend, I do not want..."

Northern Dark Ice Soul interrupted it before it finished: "Since you are my friend, you should not restrict me or obstruct me!"

"Sigh..." Fire Gu let out a long sigh, it fell into silence, giving Northern Dark Ice Soul a path leading out without a better choice.

Northern Dark Ice Soul quickly ran out, wanting to find another dream realm within the darkness to have him eaten once again.

...

Central Continent, Starry Sky grotto-heaven.

"Star Constellation Immortal Venerable!!!" Facing this person, Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan were tongue-tied, they were shocked and dazed.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, one of the ten venerables in the history of Gu Masters.

Legends regarding her had been passed down even until this day.

She was a rarely seen female rank nine Gu Immortal, the founder of wisdom path, and the creator of star path. She was the second generation reigning immortal of Heavenly Court, even after death she plotted against three Demon Venerables, protecting Heavenly Court from danger.

Now that she was standing in front of Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan, she looked down arrogantly as her grand aura of rank nine burst out towards them.

"What is going on? Star Constellation Immortal Venerable? She is still alive?!" Hei Lou Lan gritted her teeth, feeling an immense pressure. Even if she had great confidence, and was a formidable person plotting to kill her own father, at this moment her body was shaking as she faced an intense trial of her will.

After all, the other party was at the peak of Gu Masters, a rank nine Gu Immortal, the legendary Star Constellation Immortal Venerable that she had heard about since a young age.

Hei Lou Lan could not help but feel her legs go soft, while Star Lord Wan Xiang in front of her was already kneeling on the ground, kowtowing as he begged for mercy.

The aura of rank nine was undeniable. But Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, his eyes shining with ruthlessness: "This feeling? This feeling! This is actually... this is actually a piece of a dream realm?!"

He could only growl in his mind, he could not produce any sound.

He could not move at all, under the pressure of the rank nine aura, he felt like an ant that was sealed inside amber.

Under the intense threat of life and death, Fang Yuan felt a strong sense of danger in his heart.

"I have to get out of this dream realm, otherwise, all of my plans after rebirth would come to a halt. My plan for eternal life would end here! True solid bat wings, detonate now!!"

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, at the crucial moment, he decided to make a sacrifice.

The bat wings that he had transplanted after much effort detonated under Fang Yuan's resolute decision.

An intense sense of pain assaulted him, turning into a formless energy that protected Fang Yuan's entire body.

Star Constellation Immortal Venerable gasped lightly, looking at Fang Yuan deeply: "An immortal zombie, yet so fascinating."

Just as she said that, under Fang Yuan's perception, the entire scene changed, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable vanished, and the eighth star hall disappeared. What he could see was a blue robed Gu Immortal with his face facing Fang Yuan, looking up at the clear moon in the sky above the clouds.

He muttered: "Heaven has taken pity on me. I, Seven Star Child, have finally combined the seven star spaces into one, forming the unified Starry Sky grotto-heaven. I have passed another huge obstacle in my cultivation journey, I am one step closer to rank nine realm, one step closer! Hahaha, hahaha..."

Seven Star Child seemed to be unable to sense Fang Yuan's existence, he continued to face Fang Yuan as he had no inclination to turn around.

He continued to laugh loudly, his laughter was filled with joy, even Fang Yuan was affected by it and started to feel happy.

Fang Yuan started to feel some joy in him, but his body was turning cold, like he was in an icy domain.

"Oh no! This is a dream within a dream! I had just left the dream of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, but now I am inside Seven Star Child's dream."

But this time, Fang Yuan had no bat wings left to detonate.

Chapter 725: Seven Star Child Awakens

"Not good! A person's dream realm is filled with their desires and emotions. I am currently experiencing joy after hearing Seven Star Child's laughter, it is a signal that I am starting to be infected by the dream's emotions!" Being inside Seven Star Child's dream realm, Fang Yuan knew the situation was terrible.

He had his previous life's experiences, he knew about the dangers of a dream realm, if one was careless, a grand Gu Immortal could lose himself inside a dream realm, dying in the end.

At this moment, Fang Yuan had not fallen too deeply into it, to leave the dream realm, the most effective way was to stimulate himself with severe pain.

But as an immortal zombie, he had no sense of pain. If not for the fact that he had retained the sense of pain in his true solid bat wings earlier, he would have been stuck in Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm.

The encounter earlier was extremely precarious. Thankfully, Fang Yuan had his previous life's memories and recognized that it was a dream realm, thus he could leave before he sunk further into it.

Fortunately, he had true solid bat wings, and the pain produced from the self-detonation exceeded the power of Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream, thus Fang Yuan was pushed out of the rank nine venerable's dream.

But just when Fang Yuan escaped from the tiger's den, he entered the wolf's cave.

Seven Star Child was a rank eight Gu Immortal, he did not have a prominent reputation but his battle strength would have been exemplary. Be it Fang Yuan during his previous life or Fang Yuan currently, he was not Seven Star Child's match.

Fang Yuan had no more pain that he could inflict, he felt helpless at this moment, like he was quietly awaiting death!

"No, there has to be a way, there is another way..." Fang Yuan lips were dry, he was nervously clenching his fists.

"Huh?"

Sensing his clenched fists, a brilliant light shined in Fang Yuan's red eyes, he was overjoyed: "There is a chance! Although Seven Star Child is rank eight, he is far inferior to Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. In Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream, I could not move at all. But in Seven Star Child's dream, I have not lost all of my movement ability yet."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan raised one arm with much difficulty.

It felt like a huge mountain was pressing on his hand, such a simple act of raising his arm became extremely difficult.

"Rise, rise up!" Fang Yuan's veins were popping, he stared at this arm as he exerted all of his strength.

After fifteen minutes, he finally raised his hand to an appropriate degree.

With much difficulty, he slowly opened his five fingers, conjuring a lump of starlight in his palm.

There were countless icy shards in the starlight, a continuously soft explosion could be heard from them. The blue starlight shined the entire area blue.

Seeing this starlight lump, Fang Yuan had an intense feeling of joy and satisfaction.

"Oh no, I'm starting to feel the same joyful emotions as him, the deeper I am in this dream realm, the more mobility I lose." Fang Yuan reacted, suppressing his emotions.

As he expected, his mobility had fallen greatly, he could raise his arm earlier, but now he could only move his fingers.

His hand spent a lot of effort to create a lump of starlight, this was his final hope.

"Hidden dream realms cannot be attacked using normal methods. But this piece of dream realm is different, it has already surfaced, since it can interfere with outside forces now, it can also be disrupted and destroyed by those outside forces."

Although this piece of dream realm had Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and Seven Star Child's dreams, it had immense value, it was a huge waste to destroy it, but if Fang Yuan did not do this, he would lose his life.

He had no choice but to do this!

Fang Yuan exerted all of his strength, his five fingers trembled as the icy drill stardust flew out of his palm slowly.

Carrying Fang Yuan's hope, the icy drill stardust slowly hit Seven Star Child's back.

"Hahaha, I succeeded, I fused the seven stars into one. Hahahaha... guh!" Seven Star Child's laughter came to a stop, he turned around but his body was shattering rapidly like a mirror.

Fang Yuan could only see his face clearly, his entire body had collapsed.

"A good chance!" Fang Yuan's entire body relaxed, like the formless mountain pressing on his body had been lifted.

Fang Yuan regained his mobility and immediately retreated. If he did not move, when the dream realm recovers, he would not be able to any longer.

But Seven Star Child's dream was much more fragile that what Fang Yuan had expected.

Not only did Seven Star Child's body shatter, the surrounding clouds and the moon in the sky shattered. In the blink of an eye, this dream realm of Seven Star Child vanished completely.

"How could that be? My icy drill stardust is not strong, all it could do was shatter Seven Star Child's image, he should recover very quickly. Wait, this situation... could it be?!"

A flash of inspiration appeared in Fang Yuan's mind, he thought of a possibility.

As if responding to his thoughts, a sharp growl could be heard from within the eighth star hall, the voice creating strong sound waves: "Who? Who disrupted my sleep!"

At the deep, dark spot of the eighth star area, high up on the throne, there were two blue eyes shining brightly.

Soon after, a body of an immortal zombie resembling a mortal person stood up and stepped out, furiously looking around, fixing his gaze on Star Lord Wan Xiang, Hei Lou Lan and Fang Yuan.

At once, Fang Yuan felt extremely alert!

He moved his entire body and retreated quickly, he did not even have time to turn around, he directly charged out of the star hall.

"It turns out that Seven Star Child had not died, but transformed into an immortal zombie! No wonder the heavenly spirit did not appear. Hei Lou Lan, I can only help you to this extent." Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, before leaving, he fired icy drill stardust towards Hei Lou Lan.

"Worms, you court death!" Seven Star Child first went to Star Lord Wan Xiang.

He raised his leg and harshly stepped on Star Lord Wan Xiang's back.

Bam!

With a loud boom, he created a hole in the eighth star hall, Star Lord Wan Xiang's chest was almost entirely smashed. His injured body was like a shooting star, flying down and crashing into the forest.

Seven Star Child immortal zombie took large strides towards Hei Lou Lan.

But Hei Lou Lan was attacked by the icy drill stardust, under the intense feeling of pain and cold, she narrowly woke up from Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm.

Seven Star Child immortal zombie snickered sinisterly, when he got to around fifty to sixty steps from Hei Lou Lan, he pushed with his left arm.

Hei Lou Lan had yet to react before her entire body moved back subconsciously, at the same time she raised her arms to block.

At the next moment, a huge starlight pillar shot out of Seven Star Child immortal zombie's hand silently.

Immortal killer move — Star Billow Pillar!

The defense Hei Lou Lan created was thoroughly destroyed in the blink of an eye by the starlight pillar.

Luckily, Hei Lou Lan had obtained a crucial moment to rest, she quickly changed her direction.

Star billow pillar was a straight line attack, Hei Lou Lan narrowly escaped death and avoided the range of the pillar, retreating quickly.

Seven Star Child immortal zombie halted for a moment, before twisting his left arm and adjusting the direction of the pillar.

Hei Lou Lan dodged left and right, she narrowly avoided star billow pillar many times. Even if she was hit by the light pillar, it was not for more than three breaths of time.

After dozens of breaths, the huge starlight pillar in Seven Star Child's hand vanished, and Hei Lou Lan successfully escaped from the eighth star hall, rapidly descending towards the forest.

When Hei Lou Lan got to Fang Yuan's side, she could not believe that she actually escaped successfully, keeping her life!

She did not have strong defensive methods, even with the recovery speed of being a strength path extreme immortal, she could not stay in the light pillar for four breaths of time. During the process of her retreat, she was dancing on the edge of death, if there was an accident and she stayed in it for four breaths, she would have died.

Fang Yuan grabbed her arm and ran towards the deeper parts of the forest: "Quickly go! Seven Star Child immortal zombie had been trapped in that dream realm for too long, his condition is abnormal and there are few thoughts in his mind, his cognition is slow and he cannot think normally now."

Hei Lou Lan was dragged by Fang Yuan, they concealed their figures and stealthily moved past trees after trees, running frantically in the forest.

She was still confused even now, she asked rapidly: "Dream realm! The Star Constellation Immortal Venerable that I saw earlier was also part of a dream realm? What is a dream realm?"

Suddenly, Hei Lou Lan's voice came to a stop, seeing the icy drill stardust marks on her body, she shouted in anger: "Fang Yuan! You actually attacked me?"

"Shut up! I was saving you, without this icy drill stardust, would you be able to escape from Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream realm? If you could not react in time, you would have been killed by Seven Star Child immortal zombie's immortal killer move already!" Fang Yuan did not turn around, he replied in an displeased tone.

Hei Lou Lan was stunned, but she accepted his explanation.

Fierce and ambitious people were usually easily suspicious, Hei Lou Lan did not believe Fang Yuan, what she believed was the Snowy Mountain Alliance that they had.

The alliance stated that allies were not to harm or attack each other. When one side was in danger, the other party must attempt to save them to the best of their ability.

If Fang Yuan's icy drill stardust was an attack trying to harm Hei Lou Lan, he would have died from the oath already.

Seeing that he was rapidly running, and causing pain to her arm, Hei Lou Lan understood and broke free from Fang Yuan's grasp: "I can move myself!"

Pausing for a while, Hei Lou Lan followed behind Fang Yuan as she asked: "I will remember this favor of saving my life. The compensation that I give you should certainly satisfy you! However, what is that dream realm? As a strength path extreme immortal, I actually sunk into that dream realm with no way of resisting? Dream realm, dream realm... is it that dream realm in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>? Is it connected to Great Dream Immortal Venerable? Also, why are you running so rapidly? We have Fixed Immortal Travel."

"Shut up!" Fang Yuan shouted, running at his full speed.

His true solid bat wings were already gone, his speed was much slower now.

"Worms that invade my territory deserve death!" At this point, Seven Star Child immortal zombie's furious voice could be heard.

Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan ran as they looked up, seeing that Seven Star Child immortal zombie had already flown out of the eighth star hall, his attention was on the rolling rock battlefield that was in the air.

This was unavoidable, after all, the rolling rock battlefield was high in the air, it was massive and was like a huge poisonous tumor attached to the Starry Sky grotto-heaven, it attracted too much hostility.

Seven Star Child immortal zombie thought about it for a while, he stretched out his left arm and burst out with another star billow pillar.

An immortal level star path killer move, it crashed onto the rolling rock battlefield. The rolling rock battlefield shook intensely, but it did not break.

The star billow pillar was certainly an immortal killer move, but rolling rock battlefield was also an immortal killer move. In fact, it was a killer move formed by using three Immortal Gu that were related to each other!

Chapter 726: Retreat

Seeing that his attack did not destroy this despicable poisonous tumor, Seven Star Child immortal zombie was stunned, he opened his mouth and roared with even more anger, as his right arm pressed towards the rolling rock battlefield.

Following his action, a huge hand made of grand starlight formed and slapped the rolling rock battlefield with great force.

It was another immortal killer move!

After the attack of two immortal killer moves, the rolling rock battlefield cracked opened as a huge opening revealed the scene inside the battlefield, it had not broken apart yet.

Fang Yuan saw this and retracted his gaze, running without rest.

Hei Lou Lan let out a breath of foggy air, her worry was mostly lifted: "Alright, Seven Star Child immortal zombie is fighting Shi Lei now, this is the best situation. Fang Yuan, why are you running?!"

"Saving a person." Fang Yuan's reply was extremely brief and to the point.

Hei Lou Lan was curious: "Save who?"

At this time, Fang Yuan turned around a mountain wall and stepped onto a cliff, he pointed: "Him."

Hei Lou Lan looked and saw that there was a Gu Immortal lying on a cracked rock after a trail of broken trees: "It is that star path Gu Immortal!"

The two came to Star Lord Wan Xiang, and saw that there was a huge hole on his chest. Not only was it completely pierced through, he had lost almost all of his chest, only some flesh by the two sides were holding him together.

Such heavy injuries made even Hei Lou Lan breathe in sharply.

"This is the power of Seven Star Child immortal zombie's stomp." Fang Yuan lowered his body and his eight arms searched Star Lord Wan Xiang's body in turns.

After a while, Fang Yuan sighed in disappointment, thinking: "Although his body's injuries are severe, it can be healed by paying a huge cost. But his soul was sucked into the dream realm, unless Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's dream was broken, this Gu Immortal's soul can only wander inside that dream realm, or transform himself into another dream realm."

Hei Lou Lan was standing at the side, using her investigative Gu to check, she said with some lingering fear: "There is no way to save him, even his soul is entirely missing now, don't tell me it was because of that dream realm? If you did not save me, would I end up in that state as well?"

"What a pity." Fang Yuan muttered, his movements did not stop: "If he was still alive, we could still gain important information from him. In fact, we could use your slavery Immortal Gu to make him become one of us, doing our bidding. We could even plot against Shi Lei, and might have a chance of killing Shi Lei without taking any risks, while also leaving us free from suspicion, obtaining the greatest benefits!"

"Hey, are you listening to my words!" Hei Lou Lan was stomping her feet in anger.

"If you have the time for that, why don't you come and help me seal the immortal aperture in his body." Fang Yuan's words attracted all of Hei Lou Lan's attention.

This was a complete rank six blessed land!

Hei Lou Lan quickly moved ahead and sent out her divine sense, but it could only move around the area outside the immortal aperture, unable to enter.

"He is dead, but he left behind his obsession, the blessed land now has a land spirit." Fang Yuan's eight arms were continuing to move, planting all sorts of Gu worms on Star Lord Wan Xiang's corpse.

Star Lord Wan Xiang's injuries continued to heal.

"I, what can I do to help?" Hei Lou Lan was stunned by the incredible techniques that Fang Yuan was using endlessly right now.

Fang Yuan's brows were tightly locked, he was concentrating: "Sealing the blessed land is a troublesome matter, thankfully the land spirit has just been formed. I did not expect such a situation, I am lacking Gu worms now. You have to observe the battle situation up there, while communicating with treasure yellow heaven to buy these Gu worms. Remember, we cannot have a single one missing!"

Saying so, Fang Yuan transmitted his divine sense.

"I know." Hei Lou Lan obtained a list and her face was serious.

She stood beside Fang Yuan, acting as a guard while using her own immortal aperture to communicate with treasure yellow heaven. Not just that, she even used the moving perspective cup Gu that Fang Yuan lent her to ask for help from Fairy Li Shan.

Boom boom boom...

High in the sky, Seven Star Child immortal zombie continued to attack endlessly, his immortal killer moves were unleashed as if they did not cost any immortal essence at all, he used them one after another.

The rolling rock battlefield could not take the pressure and was finally broken.

The battlefield broke apart, and the zombie dragon fell from the sky helplessly, like a dead snake with lots of injuries.

Shi Lei, who caused its injuries, was not in a good state either, he was covered in wounds, especially the one on his chest, it extended from his shoulder to his waist, the wound was so deep his bones could be seen.

Shi Lei was panting heavily, his face was pale. There was still a trace of grey white zombie fire burning on his body. In order to defeat the zombie dragon, he had paid a huge price and suffered heavy injuries.

But the more injured he was, the greater his fighting intent.

Seeing Seven Star Child immortal zombie, who was stronger than the zombie dragon, this Gu Immortal from Combat Immortal Sect laughed loudly, he did not have any fear, instead, his fighting intent was blazing like a forest fire.

"Intruder, die." Seven Star Child immortal zombie shouted, expressionlessly pointing a finger at Shi Lei.

Immortal killer move — One Star Finger!

At the same time, Shi Lei snickered, flipping his palm.

Immortal killer move — Shocking Rock Break!

The two killer moves were attacking methods that had short activation time but great offensive power. Seven Star Child immortal zombie's fingertip burst out with starlight, in the blink of an eye, it tore through space and pierced Shi Lei's chest.

Meanwhile, a huge mountain rock pressed down on Seven Star Child immortal zombie, with a loud bang, Seven Star Child immortal zombie was sent crashing to the ground, buried under a small hill.

Shi Lei's blood was spewing out in a line, from the front and back of his chest. His body shook in the air for a while, he almost fell but he managed to continue floating.

Shi Lei was stunned, the attack earlier was too fast, if he did not move his body in time, his heart would have been destroyed.

At the area of his wound, there were countless star path dao marks, as they were near his heart, blood was flowing out unceasingly. Ordinary mortal Gu could not help, even mortal healing killer moves could not do anything, but Shi Lei had his own healing Immortal Gu.

After the treatment of the Immortal Gu, Shi Lei's injuries healed rapidly, the blood stopped spewing out, it flowed down his chest like a stream.

Right after he finished treating his injuries, the rock that was suppressing Seven Star Child immortal zombie broke apart, a huge starlight hand pressed hard and broke the rock into pieces, sending the shards flying.

Roar!

Seven Star Child immortal zombie shouted loudly, his body was covered in a multi-colored star cloak.

With a loud bang, he flew up, only leaving behind an illusory figure on the spot. The intense force caused the ground below the immortal zombie to crack, caving in to form a crater.

Shi Lei's pupils shrunk, he was shocked by Seven Star Child's burst of speed.

Shi Lei had just summoned his defensive Immortal Gu when Seven Star Child immortal zombie crashed towards him with a loud bang.

The Immortal Gu's defense was nearly broken, Shi Lei spat out a mouthful of blood with his vision spinning, he was sent flying into the sky from the impact.

"Oh no, this is a movement immortal killer move!" Shi Lei could feel the wind brushing against his ears, he tried hard to open his eyes.

Whoosh!

Hearing something with his ears, Shi Lei turned around with much difficulty, only to see Seven Star Child immortal zombie covered in a robe of starlight, piercing the clouds and appearing before him.

Seven Star Child immortal zombie flew alongside Shi Lei, towards the sky.

At that moment, the immortal zombie opened his left palm, aiming it at Shi Lei's head.

Immortal killer move — Star Billow Pillar!

Boom—!

The huge light pillar pierced the cloud layer from a high altitude, penetrating a mountain peak and causing a large area to collapse and fall apart, resulting in much dust and smoke.

A body descended from the sky like a broken sack.

It was Shi Lei.

He had endured the attack of the star billow pillar for fifteen breaths, but he was still alive and had some battle strength left. His entire head was charred black, his facial features were all blurry, like the melted wax of a candle.

Roar—!

Shi Lei opened his eyes, his golden pupils bursting out with an unprecedented ruthless light.

His heart was filled with rage, he finally used his greatest trump card.

Earth path, transformation path — dual immortal killer move — Rock Mountain Immortal Monkey King Transformation!

Seven Star Child immortal zombie charged over, but was repelled by a burst of golden light. When the giant pillar of golden light vanished, a sixteen meter tall giant monkey appeared.

The monkey had golden fur, like it was clad in golden armor. The muscles on its body were bulging like huge rocks. Its golden pupils were emitting an emotionless dominance, as the reflection of Seven Star Child immortal zombie could be seen in its eyes.

There were a pair of huge hands with red fingernails that were sharp as swords, when his fingers were extended, his hands looked like two fearsome claws.

Opening its mouth, fangs grew, in a moment, fangs were protruding out of its mouth, it was as if a demonic god had descended into the mortal world.

On one end, it was the huge Immortal Monkey King, on the other end there was the awakened immortal zombie clad in a starry cloak, the two were at a standstill, neither of them attacked yet.

Hei Lou Lan watched with her heart shaking, she knew that the moment the two of them attacked, it would be an overwhelming battle, she could not help but urge Fang Yuan: "Quick, the situation is becoming more troublesome."

"Okay, okay. But without Immortal Gu, we can only last for seven minutes. Once the time is up, the immortal aperture will have to land on the ground and take root." Fang Yuan was extremely busy, he felt dizzy as his eight arms stopped moving in that complex manner.

He heaved a deep sigh, looking at the sky, seeing the fearsome Immortal Monkey King, as well as the Seven Star Child immortal zombie who was surrounded by shiny starlight.

Immortal Monkey King moved his golden pupils, using his peripheral vision to look at Fang Yuan and Hei Lou Lan.

Fang Yuan's concealment method could not deceive Shi Lei in his current state.

Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk: "He found us. Quick, hide the corpse!"

Hei Lou Lan's expression was solemn, she quickly dragged Star Lord Wan Xiang's leg and tossed him into her immortal aperture.

At this time, Seven Star Child immortal zombie howled towards the sky.

His voice pierced heaven and earth, beams of starlight pillars shot down from the sky.

From the pillars, desolate beasts came out, diamond bear, flying sword rat, star desolate hound, golden pangolin...

After Seven Star Child immortal zombie started thinking again, he finally used the advantage of the grotto-heaven, he released the desolate beasts inside the seven spaces and displayed an overpowering position!

Seeing this, Fang Yuan said nothing more, activating Fixed Immortal Travel.

Immortal Monkey King's expression changed.

Hei Lou Lan entered Fang Yuan's immortal aperture, in just a few breaths of time, the two of them vanished.

"Fixed Immortal Travel, immortal zombie... Fang Yuan!" Three phrases appeared in Immortal Monkey King's mind, but Seven Star Child immortal zombie charged over again. Shi Lei was bold but he was not stupid enough to continue fighting.

He flew down, towards the walking meat tree, and placed the two segments of the tree into his immortal aperture.

Boom!

A trace of starlight tore through the sky, piercing Immortal Monkey King's huge body. It was Seven Star Child's immortal killer move, one star finger!

After Shi Lei was hit, his body merely shook slightly, he continued to fly towards the flying heavenly boar corpse.

He had the intention to retreat already, he wanted to get his loot before leaving.

He endured Seven Star Child immortal zombie's attacks as he flew towards the astral wind flying heavenly boar corpse, stretching out his arm to grab it, but he got nothing instead!

"What?!" Shi Lei was shocked, seeing the broken mortal Gu on his arm, he understood at once and flew into a rage, it had to be that Fang Yuan!

Bam!

At the next moment, a star billow pillar hit Immortal Monkey King directly on the back, causing him to fall onto the ground.

Chapter 727: Escape

Immortal Monkey King was hit directly by the star billow pillar, with a loud thud, he crashed on the ground, with his head facing the floor.

He growled angrily, spitting out the soil in his mouth, getting up quickly.

Shi Lei did not care about the Seven Star Child immortal zombie, he only wanted to get to the star demon bat corpse, towards the location in his memories.

He took huge steps as he ran, uprooting all of the trees in his way. He looked at the star demon bat corpse from afar, joyful to see that it was still intact.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh!

Right at this moment, three golden lights flew over from the sky.

The golden lights were extremely fast and agile, they were three flying sword rat desolate beasts.

Shi Lei snorted coldly, he did not want to engage with them, he raised his arms and covered his face.

Clank clank clank...

The flying sword rats' nails were as sharp as swords, they scratched Immortal Monkey King's huge body, but no blood was seen as the soft golden monkey fur blocked the nails, emitting a loud metallic noise.

Shi Lei's current form had outstanding defense.

The three flying sword rats did not let go of Shi Lei yet, they were small and agile, they followed him and continued to scratch and hack away at his body.

Bunches of monkey fur fell from Shi Lei's body.

Wherever Shi Lei went, monkey fur would scatter on the ground.

"Damn rats!" Shi Lei shouted, whipping his tail and using it like a golden whip.

The flying sword rats were hit by the tail, but after they were sent flying, they returned and continued to disturb him.

Just as he was about to reach the star demon bat corpse, a diamond bear appeared.

"Scram!" Shi Lei was furious, he clenched his fists and swept with his arms, his fists were slamming horizontally as his brute force pushed the heavy diamond bear away.

The diamond bear flew in the air for a short distance, before crashing partway up the mountain. With a loud thud, its body which resembled diamonds had cracks on it, but it stood up like it was uninjured.

Desolate beasts generally had strong vitality, they were durable and sturdy existences.

Shi Lei did not want to tangle with the diamond bear, he only wanted to get back his loot.

He ignored the disturbance of the flying sword rats as he reached the star demon bat corpse and grabbed it with his hand.

The star demon bat corpse shattered, he had been deceived once again.

Shi Lei reacted quickly, shouting in anger: "Damn, what method is this? How can it look so real! Flying bear, right, there is still a flying bear here."

Still having some hope in his heart, the golden fur giant monkey changed directions and continued to run.

Along the way, he was met with obstruction from desolate beasts, but with his brute strength, he forcefully carved out a path.

During this period, Seven Star Child immortal zombie who was in the air attacked non-stop, sending blows towards the golden fur giant monkey, even with the great defense of the Immortal Monkey King form, his skin was torn and flesh was exposed.

Shi Lei finally got close to the flying bear corpse, but he saw that there were five flying bears surrounding the corpse, some made mournful cries while others were licking the blood on the ground.

There was one which used its head to nudge the flying bear corpse, but the image flickered.

Shi Lei saw this and lost all hope, it was completely dashed as rage overwhelmed him: "It seems that all of the desolate beasts that I killed were stolen by that despicable thief Fang Yuan!! All of these are my loot, the fruits of my victory. He dared to steal my possessions, the Immortal Monkey King's, how long has it been since such a thing has happened?"

Shi Lei's huge body attracted the attention of the flying bears.

Grrr!

The five flying bears had bloodshot eyes as they charged towards the golden fur giant monkey.

Shi Lei did not have the mood to fight with them, at this point, he knew there was nothing to gain here, he wanted to escape.

Even though Star Lord Wan Xiang was killed and Shi Lei lost the method to leave Starry Sky grotto-heaven, he knew the location of that grotto-heaven loophole, as long as he can find that place, he could exert force and create a bigger hole, connecting to the outside world of Central Continent.

Shi Lei immediately changed directions, but he realized that while the five flying bears were still charging towards him from the front, on the left, there were three blazing divine stallions getting closer. On the right, there was a huge ghost face tortoise, and behind him were seven star desolate hounds.

In just a short while, he was surrounded by desolate beasts on all sides.

Shi Lei wanted to fly into the sky, but he looked up to see an iron crown eagle, a nine palace crane, and a qi grand lion, these three desolate beasts above him. Other than that, Seven Star Child immortal zombie was also ready to attack.

"Three desolate beasts are nothing much, but this immortal zombie..." The golden fur giant monkey's golden pupils shined with wariness.

He lowered his head, looking around and deciding to break through from the right side.

On his right, there was a ghost face tortoise, it was like the size of three mountains, floating in the sky silently. It was the largest in build and had the most difficulty in turning around. If Seven Star Child immortal zombie continued to attack, he could use the ghost face tortoise's huge body to act as a shield!

Shi Lei made up his mind and took a huge step forward, charging towards the ghost face tortoise.

He had transformed into the golden fur giant monkey, he was more than twice as large as Fang Yuan's eight armed immortal zombie form. But in front of the ghost face tortoise, he was like a pearl in front of a wolf.

The ghost face tortoise growled, as countless soul beasts emerged from the holes on its shell.

The dark blue colored soul beasts formed into an army, huge in numbers, filling the sky and charging towards the golden monkey like a torrential wave.

Shi Lei fought against the flow and moved up, his fists sending all of the soul beasts in his way flying. His golden fur had great defense, although the soul beasts were huge in numbers, they were slaughtered mercilessly.

Shi Lei managed to use this soul beast army to avoid the entrapment of the desolate beasts. Only those three flying sword rats were still near him, causing small wounds from time to time.

"This immortal zombie seems to be unable to think, even though he has strength, his beasts are hindering each other, and cannot display their true power. If it was me, I would've attacked long ago. Who cares about the lives of the soul beasts." Shi Lei had rich battle experience, after evading the ghost face tortoise, he had an idea and purposely slowed down.

Under the encirclement of the soul beast army, he continued to move forward. The other beasts could only stand far away, even Seven Star Child immortal zombie was staring blankly, as if he did not want to harm the soul beast army.

Finally, Shi Lei came to the opening of the loophole of the grotto-heaven.

He let out a breath of turbid air, he was just about to relax before he winced, as blood poured out from his back.

"These three accursed rats!" Shi Lei growled in anger, he turned around and raised his fist, sending the flying sword rats flying.

The flying sword rats earlier could not cause much damage, but when damage accumulated, a small injury would grow into a large one, his back's injury was already filled with metal path dao marks.

The flying sword rats crashed onto the ground, but they quickly flew towards Shi Lei again.

Shi Lei's eyes shone with a ruthless light, he activated an immortal killer move — Filthy Mud Robe.

The three flying sword rats landed on the filthy mud robe and could not free themselves, like they were stuck in a swamp.

Shi Lei used another move, earth's root!

From the thick filthy mud robe, countless spikes shot out, stabbing and piercing the flying sword rats.

The flying sword rats held on for over a dozen breaths of time before their tiny bodies were pierced through by hundreds of spikes, they died at the scene.

At this time, Seven Star Child immortal zombie finally reacted, he mobilized the soul beast army and ordered the desolate beasts to charge forward fearlessly.

"It is too late, fool." Shi Lei breathed in deeply, the sticky filthy mud robe on his body moved rapidly, detaching from his body and covering the grotto-heaven opening.

Shi Lei placed both his palms on the filthy mud robe, pouring a large amount of immortal essence into it.

Immortal killer move — Earth Disintegration!

The filthy mud robe scattered and flowed out, the grotto-heaven crack became a huge hole after this attack. Shi Lei could see another sky out of this huge hole.

He laughed heartily, taking a huge step and forcing his way out.

Because it was a forceful breakthrough and was not as meticulous as Star Lord Wan Xiang's methods, during the process of leaving, a huge invisible force squeezed at Shi Lei's body from all directions.

Thankfully, Shi Lei had become the golden fur giant monkey, his defenses rose by more than ten times. He resisted the pressure and went through the hole, his body was covered in blood, especially the wound caused by the flying sword rats, his flesh was mushy and large amounts of blood was oozing out.

Shi Lei sucked in a breath of cold air from the pain, he shouted in his heart: "Who dares to block my way, I am out of here! That accursed immortal zombie, I will definitely take you down. And for that Fang Yuan, the thief that stole my loot. A mere tiny rank six immortal zombie that doesn't know what is good for him, he dared to offend me! When I return, I will deal with you properly, and let you know the terrible fate for offending me!"

Thoughts flashed in Shi Lei's mind, but at this time, he heard the growls of flying bears near him.

Shi Lei quickly looked around, seeing that five flying bears had gotten extremely close to him from five different directions.

"What is going on?" He raised his head and looked, only to see six huge star shadows in the sky.

"Why am I still here? I had undoubtedly..." Shi Lei was extremely shocked, his mouth was wide open.

Seven Star Child immortal zombie looked at him as he laughed coldly: "Little monkey, did you think that my seven star space is so simple? I do have to thank you, if you did not awaken me, I might still be stuck in that dream realm. As thanks, I will bury your corpse below my most beloved mountain peak."

By now, Seven Star Child had actually regained his senses, he could think normally again!

"This is bad." Shi Lei's heart sank.

Five flying bears raised their paws, attacking the golden fur giant monkey.

"Scram!" Shi Lei was just about to erupt, when starlight flickered around him, his body became heavier and his movement became slower — Seven Star Child immortal zombie had attacked.

This was only a mortal killer move, but its effect was amazing, it was even more effective than the offensive immortal killer move earlier.

At once, bear paws slammed down from all directions.

Shi Lei shielded himself on his left and right, but he was unable to protect himself thoroughly, when he finally got rid of his restraint, he rolled and escaped from the five bears. But at this time, he was already dizzy from the beating, his muscles were swollen, becoming green and purple, although he had no bone fractures, his body was aching intensely.

After Seven Star Child regained his senses, his danger level escalated intensely!

"I have no choice, I will have to seek help from the sect! Hmph, to think that I, the grand Immortal Monkey King, was forced to use seek help Gu at this moment! Where will my reputation go after this? Fang Yuan, this is all your fault, after I am saved, I will make sure you pay!!" Shi Lei shouted in his heart, he was going to puke blood from anger.

Fang Yuan not only stole his loot, causing his trip to be an overall loss, he even took away Star Lord Wan Xiang and trapped Shi Lei in this Starry Sky grotto-heaven.

Woof woof woof!

Two star desolate hounds traveled over, and the ghost face tortoise also floated ahead of him soundlessly.

Immortal Monkey King raised his head, shouting at Seven Star Child immortal zombie: "Fight me for three hundred more rounds if you have the guts!"

Seven Star Child immortal zombie laughed arrogantly: "Sure, come here."

The golden fur giant monkey growled as sharp golden light burst out, forcing Seven Star Child immortal zombie to squint in response.

After the golden light faded, Shi Lei regained his human form, he charged into the forest and sped away rapidly.

The result was — he ran away!

He ran away!

The Immortal Monkey King Shi Lei famous for his bravery and ruthlessness in Central Continent had chosen to escape. If this was known to the outside world, who knows how many of Central Continent's Gu Immortals would gasp in shock.

Seven Star Child immortal zombie was shocked for a while before reacting, responding angrily: "You dare to trick me? I thought you were a heroic champion who would rather battle to the death and would never give up! Escape, go ahead and run, I want to see where you can escape to in this grotto-heaven of mine?!"

Shi Lei did not say a word, he ran even faster.